<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order>
<subOrder>
    <orderId>1239-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[3/23/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Brid Devlin]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[572 Winston Way]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Berwyn]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19312]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia>NotAvailable</shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 75th Birthday!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Ann Devlin]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Brid Devlin]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happiest of birthdays to you, Mom.  All our (ABSOLUTE, ENDLESS, UNDYING, EVERLASTING and PERFECT) love]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Patrick, Conor and Tara ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are an AMAZING woman, mother, grandmother and friend who deserves a celebration with all those that love you so dearly. Wishing you the very best birthday and we will be dancing with you in spirit! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tamara, Andrew, Presley and Aaron ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Have a wonderful birthday day and celebrate it all year long.  You deserve it.  Love, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill and Kara Mohan ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Baseball, Concert Hall, Outback and our Paddy over Ice – great times ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tim ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Mazer, I definitely did something right to have landed you or you did something really wrong!! I love you more than words can grasp – Looking forward to our next adventure with a splash of Margaritas ... Happy Happy Birthday My super amazing friend. All my love, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sinead ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Someone ask me if I knew you. I laughed and said Ha! That's funny!! I adore that woman!! She's blessed, caring, loving, sweet, beautiful and a woman of spirit. She's the kind of woman that when her feet hit the floor each morning the devil says: Oh shit, she up!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Jane ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Misses D, Happy 75th Birthday.  What a woman! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rory Quirke ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday, Ann, so blessed that Michael came to live with the Devlin's so we Donohues got to know and love you all.  Have a wonderful day. Love to all, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lennie Donohue ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Late at night or early in the morning.. she will always be there for you. A true inspiration for any parent. One in a million! Love you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrew ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Behind every great band is an even greater mother. Happy birthday! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike McAloon ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Can't think of a nicer, more spirited and fun person to wish a Happy Birthday. Enjoy your special day. Love, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[June and Bill ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are such a wonderful woman to spend time with, full of such great stories and warmth and wisdom. I treasure my time with you and always come away inspired. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gillian Walsh/Plockelman ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What a fabulous lady you are. I thoroughly enjoy our get togethers (though we need to up the anti and definitely try and get a Christmas lunch in this year!).  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gillian Walsh/Plockelman ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Enjoy all the love and attention.  You are truly worthy of it.  Happy Birthday! Love, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your sister Mary ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I was remembering all the fun we had with your family in Midland, especially the player piano! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dorothy Huber ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is the only person I know who could get me to an airplane museum.  She has a wonderful curiosity. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sherri Moran ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Ann we'll make the 100  yet !! You set the example we'll follow!! Love  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ann Smyth ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Ann keep going we're right behind you taking our cue from you! God Bless ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ann Eoin ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the BEST OLDEST sister anyone could have. I am glad you are mine!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rita ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Ann Devlin because she is in one word, fabulous!  How does she do it? I will never know, but she always remembers everything about you, even what the last conversation was about! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rebeca Salazar ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The great sages say that you have to bring at least six people to God in each lifetime.  Looks like you have done it 13 times.  You have always done more than your share, always given 100%, always tried your best and gave us the best life ever.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mari ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I want you to know that your great and sweet influence is always with me.  I think of your Godly example each day and follow your good ways.  You have been a wonderful example of mother and womanhood to me.   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mari ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wishing you a very happy 75th birthday!  We were so touched to get your card and gift for little Evie, you have always been so thoughtful.  We will be back at Christmas, so fingers crossed we’ll get to wish you a happy birthday in person!  Lots of love, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Colin, Sonya and Evie ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Auntie Ann!!  Wishing you 75 tickets in the drawer.  Hope you have a great party. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lisa ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have been a constant source of joy, strength and love through all the ups and downs life has thrown at our family.   Thank you for being a wonderful Mum!  Love always, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brid ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From my earliest memories, you captured my admiration. I so appreciate your humor, your faith and realism, and belief in the best of people. Time with you is precious. Love you, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeanine McGowan ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The first time we met was at the Fianna Fáil Cummahn in the Killiney Court many years ago. Fe Redmond was holding forth at the time.  We had some great social occasions in your house on the beach. You were always so welcoming. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Louis and Fionnuala ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember your parents coming to our house for afternoon tea one day. And I think your sister was with them. I remember bringing my mother to your home in Killiney and then in Glengeary. She thought the world of you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Louis and Fionnuala  ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have reached our golden years and eventhough we don't see very much of each other, we have the warmth of our memories and knowledge, that we can take up from where we left off the last time we met!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Louis and Fionnuala  ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Best. Grandma. Ever!!  Love, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nina, Griffin and Lucie ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wishing you much love, happiness, laughter and friendship as you celebrate your 75th Birthday.  Bill and I send you much love and many hugs (especially me).  Look forward to having time to catch up when you visit next.  May your heart be joyful.  Love, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jan Deegan ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What a lady! I love your regular visits to Donaghmore. Auntie Ann, you are a great conversationalist, and so interesting with lots of stories to tell. I love to hear about the family and about your travels. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie Deery  ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You were always a great family person, able to handle the gang with such ease, although I do remember u threatening to put Patrick out of the minibus in the middle of Dublin City! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie Deery  ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I recollect great times at your house, u had no bother adding us to the gang, and we loved every minute! Thank you.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie Deery  ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Big happy birthday to Mrs D. Where does the time go, 50 already ha! Hope you have a great day ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barry  ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that you have a big red car grandma ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cillian ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love giving hugs to you ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Caoimhe  ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Ann, hope you have a great night with family & friends. All my love, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carol ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wishing a wonderful mother, mother in law and grandma a fantastic 75th birthday. Love ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[C, J, C, C & T ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To my wonderful mother in law, your positivity, faith and outlook on life inspires me as a woman and mother. Thank you. Love,  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are inspiration of what we women are capable of; strong, educated & loving with great inner beauty.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Suzanne O'Connell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>