<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order>
<subOrder>
    <orderId>1282-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[3/30/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Leslie Kemm]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[531 Winston Way]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Berwyn]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19312]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia>NotAvailable</shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Birthday!!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Chuch]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Tommy Brennan]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how you taught me the value of saving money and investing wisely before I ever even had any money!  I love you! XO ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chrissy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kellogg stocks, Hershey stocks, a “non-smoking” fund, car loans, an illegal golf club, dob obedience classes, and MANY MANY gifts in between. Your generosity and sharing nature never end THANK YOU, THANK YOU!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chrissy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for loving my family & always welcoming us.  You are generous and kind.  I love you!
 	   

]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cathy Sutton ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are my best client Chunch.  I love our visits.  Call me if you need me.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jamie Sutton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you.  I like following Shaner at your house.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Zack Sutton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I live visiting you & you are so nice because you give us free $5 bills with the Finders Keepers game.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shane Sutton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I come to see you I feel a good feeling that I can’t explain about you and your life.  You make me feel special.  You care about me a lot & give me money for glasses & it makes me feel special.   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Devon Sutton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday!  Your financial advice has always been a great help.  You’re a “wealth” of knowledge!!  And playing pinochle with you is always enjoyable.  I’ll never lead with a King again! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ken]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You once told me that you liked when we would talk because I always look you right in the eyes.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, David]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Though I’ve only known you for a short time I enjoyed the many times we spent together doing your hair.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Jackie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I really enjoy the times we get to spend together when my parents go away.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bridget]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always look forward to seeing you and playing hide the money.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Spencer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I think you are a very wise and generous person.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Nathan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your wisdom is second only to your generosity.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Rob]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for inventing “finders, Keepers” and for always being so nice to me.  I love dancing for you!
]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Morgan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Like a fine wine Chuch, you just get better with age.  I really enjoy our visits and look forward to more!  I love you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[“Helen, my children are your children”.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ann Brennan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whether a brand new color TV, car, piano, picnic area, Phillies tickets, you have always been there for us – standing so humbly in the background, letting everyone else take all the credit.Mom always said you were a father to the four of us and I couldn’t agree more.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Tommy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I really enjoy coming to visit you and plying Finders Keepers.  I had fun playing Fish with you, Mom Mom and my friend, Alex.  You are so funny.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Sydney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have enjoyed the many Easter parties we’ve spent together and how you beat me at Epper more than once with your special hold on the egg.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Austin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanksgiving dinners at Mom Mom and Pop’s bring many fond memories of you to me, especially your prayer. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Zachary]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanksgiving dinner is a special memory of you I have, we would all talk about which one of us would get the pleasure of sitting next to you each year.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Jimmy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have many fond memories of visiting you and Gran in Philadelphia.  I look forward to many more visits in NJ. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Heather]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for always being so kind and generous.  I enjoy our visits and how sweet you are to Jake and Nick.  I’m glad you and my Grandmom (Ceil) became friends.  I’ll always remember the delicious and abundant figs you grew on Fairfield Street.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Jen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[C – Caring
H – Helpful
U – Unique
C – Charming
H – Heartwarming

I love you and hope you have a great birthday!
 ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Nick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for all the time you let us come over to talk.  I enjoy spending time with you.  You are a very sweet and kind person to everyone.  It’s very generous of you to play Finders Keepers with all the younger kids.  Happy Birthday! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Jake]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I loved that you let me wear your beautiful high heels (especially the blue ones that sparkled), your makeup & your mink stole when I was little.  I still remember how happy it made me.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Patty-Pat-Pat]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always appreciate the little things, even if it’s just a letter or a quote.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Simply put – Chuch, you are the greatest Aunt in the history of the world!  A million thank yous for all you continue to do.  I love you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tommy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You were always there when I needed you as I grew older and now it gives me pleasure to be here for you as you grow older.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Jimmy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have such fond memories of playing pinochle and having cocktails with you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Phyllis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are one of the most generous people I know, always helping family out whenever they need it.  You’ve taught me many valuable lessons and I love writing you letters.  I hope your birthday is a very special day!  Love you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Some of my earliest memories include you being my confirmation sponsor and Gran on Fairfield Street, the swing in your basement and trips to Pennypack Park to feed the horses, which was always fun.  Thank you for being wonderful to the boys, Jen and me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Godchild, Frankie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whether it was a family gathering, holiday party or time down the shore at the trailer, you have been a very important part of those great times.  Thank you for always being so kind and generous to our children.  We hope you enjoy this birthday and many more to come.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Cindy and Mike]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We wish you a very Happy Birthday Chuch!  Thank you for always being so nice when we would see you at the Christmas parties.  We hope you have a great time enjoying all your memories on your birthday!   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kaitlyn, Ryan and Lauren]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>