<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order>
<subOrder>
    <orderId>1283-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[3/30/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Leslie Kemm]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[531 Winston Way]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Berwyn]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19312]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia>NotAvailable</shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Best Teacher Ever - 2014]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Mrs. Booz]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Your Second Grade Class]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mrs. Booz is nice.  She lets us go out to recess early and stay out longer.  She also gets chicks in her classroom.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Danny Johnson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The thing I love most about Theresa is that she shares personal stories with the kids about her past, her family, etc.  It’s nice for the kids to relate to her as a former student, mom and wife – not just an authority figure.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maggie Johnson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I appreciate Mrs. Booz’s enthusiasm for the school and the district.  It’s clear she is passionate about her job and the education field as a whole.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maggie Johnson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that Mrs. Booz puts as much into helping build good character as she does in helping the kids learn.  I also appreciate her candor.  It’s refreshing in this PC world we live in. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leslie Kemm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mrs. Booz helped me learn more than I ever did before and she was the best teacher ever.  I like that we made books for Mother’s and Father’s Day.  I also like that when I got in trouble she would always talk it out with me to make sure I didn’t do it again.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chase Kemm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mrs. Booz is great because she makes sure we have the most fun and do cool project, like the chicks. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[James Ryland]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Theresa is wonderful, enthusiastic, caring and patient.  She gets to know each child and supports their individuality and personal needs.  We feel like we hit the teacher lottery. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amanda Ryland]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mrs. Booz is the sweetest teacher.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lauren Ciccarelli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that Theresa and I share a love for Diet Coke any time of day, no rules! (according to Lauren)  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kristin Ciccarelli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I liked having you because you are an amazing teacher.  You were so nice to us.   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sea Sea Perrin Hee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The Perrin Hee family feels so fortunate to have had you this year. Sea looked forward to going to school every day to be with you. We loved volunteering in your class and watching you make learning so much fun.  Thank you for a great year!  You made it special.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lynnsey and Mike]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that Mrs. Booz plans stuff for us to learn about.  I loved when we had the baby chicks in our class.  Mrs. Booz taught us how they hatch and how to hold them.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ben Wolf]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love the way Mrs. Booz always looks for – and sees – the best in Ryan.   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary and Anthony Williams]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Mrs. Booz because she is funny! (But not at the wrong time) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ryan Williams]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mrs. Booz is willing to talk things out.  She makes learning fun.  She has everything you need to be a great teacher and she is one.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Landon Ross]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite thing about Mrs. Booz is that she has been so nice and helpful to me. Thank You for a great year Mrs. Booz! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Riley Bosler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you Mrs. Booz and have a great summer.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nate Chiaro-Fulton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Mrs. Booz because she helps us with problems. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charlie Newhall]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Mrs. Booz because she challenges our children. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer Newhall]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It has been a fabulous year with you.  I bet the kids next year will really enjoy your teaching because you’re so good.  Have a good summer.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Zach Cohen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Mrs. Booz because she’s really nice.  I love Mrs. Booz because she does things that other teachers don’t do, like have chicks. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sophia Santarsiero]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mrs. Booz is special because she lets us have chicks and butterflies and movie parties. She is awesome! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Luca Webb]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mrs. Booz is a wonderful teacher who created a classroom filled with learning, laughter and love. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tina Webb]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how Mrs. Booz taught me about China.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[DJ Peterson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I appreciate how Mrs. Booz recognizes the children’s accomplishments. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sonia Peterson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I came in the fall she already knew me and gave me a big hug.  We did so many fun activities like the wax museum, the chicks and Chinese Feast.  Mrs. Booz looks pretty every day.  I loved being in her class. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sophia Pechin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>