<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order>
<subOrder>
    <orderId>1290-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[3/31/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Heather Clayton]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[531 Winston Way]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Berwyn ]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19312]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia>NotAvailable</shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Thoughts]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Molly]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Victoria]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The most important thing is to enjoy your life 

- to be happy 

- it's all that matters.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Audrey Hepburn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am determined to be cheerful and happy in whatever situation I may find myself. For I have learned that the greater part of our misery or unhappiness is determined not by circumstance but by our disposition. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Martha Washington]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Believe in yourself! 

Have faith in your abilities! 

Without a humble but reasonable confidence in your own powers you cannot be successful or happy. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Norman Vincent Pearle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I believe in pink. 

I believe that laughing is the best calorie burner. 

I believe in kissing, kissing alot. 

I believe in being strong when everything seems to be going wrong.
]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Audrey Hepburn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I believe that happy girls are the prettiest girls. 

I believe that tomorrow is another day and I believe in miracles. 
]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Audrey Hepburn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I just find myself happy with the simple things. Appreciating the blessings God gave me. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[-unknown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whoever is happy will make others happy too. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anne Frank]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Be happy with what you have and are, be generous with both, and you won't have to hunt for happiness. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[William E. Gladstone]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A birthday is just another day where you go to work and people give you love. Age is just a state of mind, and you are as old as you think you are. You have to count your blessings and be happy. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Abhishek Bachchan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You don't develop courage by being happy in your relationships everyday. You develop it by surviving difficult times and challenging adversity. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Epicurus]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Let us be grateful to people who make us happy, they are the charming gardeners who make our souls bloom. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marcel Proust]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Try to make at least one person happy every day. If you cannot do a kind deed, speak a kind work, then think a kind thoughts. Count up, the treasure of happiness that you would dispense in a week, in a year, in a lifetime!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lawrence G. Lovasik]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Trust yourself. Create the kind of self that you will be happy to live with all your life. Make the most of yourself by fanning the tiny, inner sparks of possibility into flames of achievement. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Golda Meir]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I, not evetns, have the power to make me happy or unhappy today. I can choose which it shall be. Yesterday is dead, tomorrow hasn't arrived yet. I have just one day, today, and I'm going to be happy in it. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Groucho Marx]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Think of all the beauty still left around you and be happy. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anne Frank]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy is the man who finds a true friend, and far happier is he who finds that true friend in his wife. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Franz Schubert]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Summer means happy times and good sunshine. It means going to the beach and having fun. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian Wilson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Money has never made man happy, nor will it, there is nothing in its nature to produce happiness. The more of it one has the more one wants. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Benjamin Franklin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Even a happy life cannot be without a measure of darkness, and the word happy would lose its meaning if it were not balanced by sadness. It is far better to take things as  they come along with patience and equanimity. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carl Jung]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You will never be happy if you continue to search for what happiness consists of. 

You will never live if you are looking for the meaning of life. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Albert Camus]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Being in control of your life and having realistic expectations about your day-to-day challenges are the keys to stress management, which is perhaps the most important ingredient to living a happy, healthy and rewarding life. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marilu Henner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The girl who is able to earn her own living and pay her own way should be as happy as anybody on earth. The sense of independence and security is very sweet. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan B. Anthony]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[By all means, marry. If you get a good wife, you'll be come happy; if you get a bad one, you'll become a philosopher.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Socrates]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The only thing that will make your happy is being happy with who you are, and not who people think you are. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Goldie Hawn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your work is going to fill a large part of your life, and the only way to be truly satisfied is to do what you believe is great work. And the only way to do great work is to love what you do. If you haven't found it yet, keep looking. Don't settle.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Jobs]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your time is limited, so don't waste it living someone else's life, Don't be trapped by dogma - which is living with the results of other people's thinking. Have the courage to follow your heart and intuition. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Jobs]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You can't connect the dots looking forward; you can only connect them looking backwards So you have to trust that the dots will somehow connect in your future. You have to trust in something-your gut, destiny, life, karma, whatever. This approach has worked for me. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Jobs]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Coming together is a beginning; keeping together is progress; working together is success. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Henry Ford]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My best friend is the one who brings out the best in me. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Henry Ford]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Life is a series of experiences, each one of which makes us bigger, even though sometimes it is hard to realize this. For the world was built to develop character, and we must learn that the setbacks and grieves which we endure help us in our marching forward. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Henry Ford]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Most people spend more time and energy going around problems than in trying to solve them. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Henry Ford]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Let no one ever come to you without leaving happier."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mathew Toppa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We tend to forget that happiness doesn't come as a result of getting something we don't have, but rather of recognizing and appreciatng what we do have. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frederick Keonig]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You just gotta be happy, but sometimes that's hard. Just remember to smile, and that's a good enough start. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[unknown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Strive not to be a success, but rather to be of value."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I attribute my success to this: I never gave or took an excuse. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Florence Nightingale]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You can never cross the ocean until you have the courage to lose sight of the shore. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christopher Columbus]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["People will forget what you said, 
people will forget what you did, 
but people will never forget how you made them feel. "]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maya Angelou]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If you hear a voice within you say, "You cannot paint," then by all means paint and that voice will be silenced. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vincent Van Gogh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The only person you are destined to become is the person you decide to be. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We can easily forgive the child who is afraid of the dark; the real tragedy of life is when men are afraid of the light. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Plato]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[" I have been impressed with the urgency of doing. Knowing is not enough; we must apply. Being willing is not enough; we must do. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leonardo da Vinci]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are no traffic jams along the extra mile.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Roger Staubach]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A truly rich man is one whose children run into his arms when his hands are empty. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Unknown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If you want your children to turn out well, spend twice as much time and half as much money. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Abigail Van Buren]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["When one's mind is made up, this diminishes fear. " ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rosa Parks]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have entered a new age of fullfillment, in which the great dream is to trade up from money to meaning. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Roman Krznaric]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Follow your bliss...and " the universe will open doors where there were only walls. "]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joseph Campbell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Choose a job you love and you will never need to work a day in your life. "]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Confucius]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>