<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order>
<subOrder>
    <orderId>1291-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[3/31/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Heather Clayton]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[531 Winston Way]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Berwyn]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19312]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia>NotAvailable</shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Congratulations!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Gabe]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Deena]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always let Plum tickle your pitties whenever he/she wants to. Cause it will make Plum happy and mommy happy too :-)
  
]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Deena Herman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If you don't want to change diapers, you have to become a male chauvinist NOW. Once you change one diaper, it's too late - you can't suddenly become a male chauvinist. Learn from my mistakes!
My (slightly) more serious piece of advice is: don't worry. Lots of nincompoo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Yonatan Frankel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kids are as sensitive as adults. Never rebuke publicly and think what you will say before you say it. They are also very perceptive at astonishingly young ages. Set a good example and they will follow your lead :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[-Rabbi Kopel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Gabe, when you're doing work, try to do it away from the family. Make a separation. When you're home, try to be truly present. Put the devices down and free your mind to focus on what's most important.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Daniel Erlbaum]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[First, read Garden of Peace. I have found that reading to my kids at bedtime is incredibly helpful. It gives them a love of reading and a love of learning. My 9 year old son demands that we learn Torah each and every night before bed! B'sha Tova!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[-Evan Aidman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No matter how demanding your work schedule may be, make time for dinner with your kids. This single simple act will create a stronger lifelong bond with your kids than anything else you ever do with them. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ Jonathan Levin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Enjoy and savour every moment and every stage - they grow really quickly...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dov Goldschmidt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[. Train your child when he is young in the way he should go, so that even when he grows older he will still continue to train and educate himself. "He will not deviate from it" means from the training process taught to him when he was young. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rabbi Biberfel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When you look into the eyes of your son and begin to feel the love that you are prepared to give this little being, please know that it has helped me to better understand the relationship that Hashem has with his children. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Adam Levine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Give every ounce of love you could ever conceivably imagine to them. Then, hush up and find a way to give them even more. The days will be long and the years short, but being a father is the most wonderful blessing in the world.
]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Brother, Eric]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mazel Tov, Gabe!
You are going to make an excellent Abba! 
To the extent I can offer advice that is both meaningful and relevant, I would encourage you to watch "Super Nanny." This show is incredible. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Auerbach]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Without shouting, hitting, or throwing your hands up, this show properly demonstrates a Torahdicke chinuch approach. Hey, you can even make a date out of watching it!
]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Auerbach]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Having children, whether sons or daughters, changes everything. You look down at these innocent faces and can't believe that they are 50% you and 50% Deena. They evoke emotions from you that you did not even know you had inside of you. Best of luck. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[
The birth of my first child was thrilling and frightening at the same time. The sudden addition of responsibility led me to review my past and think what I could have learned that would help me in the future. What I have learned since -sit back and relax.
]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[MAZEL TOV !!! -Gary Erlbaum]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Calmly "recalculating" like a GPS; kindling their souls by parenting our own body-child; building self-esteem; keeping it about them (not our side agendas); empathy; balance; simcha… B’Shaah Tovah!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jon Erlbaum]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I don't know whether they should say "You have a baby" or "The baby has you". ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Koby Milgraum]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In all seriousness, Mazel Tov on parenthood and every stage of raising him/her is great (it gets a lot better starting at about 3 months!). And if you ever need extra baby sitting, you can always call me over for a game of pool! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Koby Milgraum]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Don't be so humble.
Gabe, you're very unassuming and do all of your mitzvos and chessed without fanfare, but when it comes to raising a child, it is important to "let 'em see what you're about" a little.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Avraham Steinberg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So, when you come back from doing a chessed or are going out to learn, or whatever... -- talk about it. Not because you're haughty, but because you have great yearnings and middos to share. This apple is very lucky to fall fro the Gabe-Deena tree!
...Mazel tov.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Avraham Steinberg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[
Gabe - never, ever forget that Hashem picked YOU to take care of this precious child. When the baby is screaming at 3 am, and you get up with him, think to yourself, "there's a helpless baby crying, and someone in the world has to take care of him.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Yaakov Lynn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[That won't stop you from being exhausted the next morning, but Baruch Hashem, in His Infinite Kindness, Hashem also created coffee.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Yaakov Lynn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Never stop getting nachas from every small accomplishment, and never stop complimenting your wife on what an exceptional mother she is!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[-Yaakov Lynn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[K'racheim Av al Banim - we ask Hashem to have rachmanus on us the way a Father has rachmanus on his children. Specifically a father. Rachmanus should come quickly and with great quantity.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shmuel Lynn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Study Torah with your newborn child. The meanings maybe incomprehensible to a baby, but its sweet sounds will leave an indelible impression of your everlasting commitment to our timeless heritage.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Avraham Shmidman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Life as you knew it has changed, Gabe. But keep in mind how much Deena has gone through to reach this point and think about the amazing creation that you have partnered in.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sherman Frager]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're gonna be a great Dad. (If you agree to feed and change the baby all day Sunday you may even be able to watch a football game with Plum on your knee.)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sherman Frager]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always keep the wife happy! A happy wife is a happy home! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chesky Weiss]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always strive to make sure your children find the home to be a loving stress-free environment... ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chesky Weiss]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Enjoy the moments (take pictures and write down funny anecdotes) as the time passes super quickly!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chesky Weiss]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As your "G-dfather" I want to tell you that I love you dearly today, tomorrow and forever. You are a handsome intelligent gentleman.and I love Deena the same way.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jerry Friedman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[On Marriage,
The best fatherly advice I can give to Gabe is to always treat Deena the same way as you did when you dated. Keep the courtship fresh and alive. Always be honest, honorable, and never keep any secrets from each other.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jerry Friedman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Have good communication and learn to compromise. The best thing going through life is to have a very positive attitude, and work together as a team. I know you will be very successful. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jerry Friedman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As a Daddy,
Cherish every moment. Record as many special moments as possible, not just of the baby but of you both. Keep the baby book up to date, throughout the years as, many parents only do the first 2 years. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jerry Friedman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Life goes by very quickly so absorb and savor every day, week year. Teach the baby everything that was important to each of you as you grew up.
I am sure that you will be a Wonderful Daddy!!!!
]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jerry Friedman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I hope you give me the chance to hold the baby, and maybe even babysit for you. You both are wished a life filled with much Mazel.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jerry Friedman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[
I notice I'm so much more relaxed with my later kids than I was with the early ones. Just remember this: everything that seems so dire is probably much less significant than you think it is. Relax and enjoy and treasure every moment. Mazel tov!
]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[-Marc Erlbaum]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are no words that can alert you other than IT IS AN EVENT YOU WILL NEVER FORGET. The spare time needed is UNLIMITED and the joy is BREATHTAKING. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sue & Phil Goldman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The joys that will come your way will be FOREVER REMEMBERED. Just enjoy this new found love and cherish it and this is what HASHEM WANTS YOU and Deena to have. You have our love during this WONDERFUL MIRACLE. Be KIND & Loving NO MATTER WHAT! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sue & Phil Goldman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Since there is a huge chance that you will be having a DAUGHTER within a short time period the following are the MUSTS pertaining to a DAUGHTER; YOU MUST PAY HER 110% ATTENTION FOR HER ENTIRE LIFE! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Philip Goldman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You must learn to be her dad and allow her to understand what LOVE IS, RESPECT IS, CARING IS! You need to make sure YOU ARE HER DAD...there will be trying moments, minutes, hours, days that you will scratch you head...but...make no mistakes YOU ARE HER DAD! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Philip Goldman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sinatra had a great song which included some of this but right now the title escapes me...someone will tell you the title, if you ask...be well!!!!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Philip Goldman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Gabe, this is the big leagues, the real stuff. Welcome aboard! First piece of advice: don't blow it. Second piece of advice: this is the greatest opportunity to build your MARRIAGE. It's funny, but true. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Rick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[. Any time you help with the new baby, you are simultaneously helping your wife, which is incredible. Any time you change a diaper instead of her, or feed the baby while she rests is a double opportunity for growth. Shtell on that my friend. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Rick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[
Simple advice. Be as great a Dad as you have been a son and you'll be blessed as I have. Doing great things for your kids leads to great things for parents. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[. I have watched you grow into a special young man whose character alone will serve as an excellent role model. I love you son. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Equally important for your child's feeling of safety to how your teach your child is how you and your wife treat each other. A counter intuitive approach that works wonders for shalom bayis is to NOT talk about problems or issues that come up between you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sid Latin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Traditional wisdom says that couples should talk about and work on problems that come up in their relationship. However, when they are absorbed in the problem, their moods are low and in that state are less likely to feel compassion, be able to listen...cont'd to pg 2]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[-Sid Latin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[to new approaches to solve the issue. So don't talk about problems, rather work on helping each other move on and get back to a more positive mood. In that mood you'll find that solutions magically happen on their own.
]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sid Latin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When the baby is very small, the abba & mommy should come whenever he/she cries. As baby gets older there are times to let him/her cry and not come in. It is difficult to know when to give in and when not to. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Josh Hollander]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have memories when my little one when at that age...and I heard her cry. I wanted so much to go in and help her. But I would stop and realize that at a certain point, not going in is what will make her a great person. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Josh Hollander]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[. The ability to not give children everything they want is the hardest thing. It goes against our loving nature. But I feel it is the most important thing in building character.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[-Josh Hollander]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My Rebbe told me that when you have the urge to give to (buy something for) your child you should re-direct that toward your wife.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Josh Hollander]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whenever your wife asks you to get up and deal with the baby in the middle of the night, always say yes. Sometimes the baby falls off back to sleep and you don't need to actually get up, and you still look like a big tzaddik.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shimon Kay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[And besides, who needs the sholom bayis issues that come from saying no.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shimon Kay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Most importantly have patience with your wife. When the baby is born your life will change in many ways. Most of the time it will all be good. Sometimes you will wish that you stayed at work. She will ALWAYS be right. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bruce Appelbaum]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Think twice about what you are going to say and if you think it will sound right to her then say it. It does not matter what you think. You will see what I mean. If Deena does not get back to her old form, do not mention it. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bruce Appelbaum]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[. Life will change for you if you do and not in a good way. If it is a girl have patience for her when she grows up, you will see what I mean. If it is a boy, WOW you will see what I mean. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bruce Appelbaum]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[. Not to be politically correct, but there is a difference between boys and girls. Learn how to change diapers, that will make Deena happy and you will want that.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bruce Appelbaum]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Gabe, All the best to you and Deena as you move into the next stage of your life together. I am sure you will be great parents. 
Since you are new to all of this, I want to take this opportunity to let you in on some advice I have for you.
]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Richie Gottlieb]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[1. Encourage your wife to nurse the baby. It allows you to sleep so much more.

2. see card #2]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Richie Gottlieb]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[2. I know everyone will be telling you that your baby is cute and smart and so much fun. But privately you will think "what is the big fuss, he/she does not do much". The truth is that they don't do much the first 6 months or so. They are so much more fun after that. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Enjoy and All the best, Richie Gott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Gabe, it's been a real pleasure playing ball with you... Mazel Tov on this wonderful simcha ! There is nothing more fulfilling in life than loving and feeling the love of your kinder... Remember, they watch Everything you do and they hear Everything you say! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Felger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Three words to always remember: Gam Zeh Yaavor - this too will pass. Count to ten while breathing in and out and then say it.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shmulie Grunberger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Gabe, Always be aware that the difficult times will quickly pass- lack of sleep, diapers, tantrums, all of it. When you can't seem to be able to see the light, it's natural to get upset.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Baruch Avis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If you adjust your expectations (prepare for the worst sometimes) you're unlikely to get as upset. Lastly, please, please do not set your expectations too high too early.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Baruch Avis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[They will learn to walk, talk, read etcetera...in good time. I see people propping siddurim in front of their 1 year old in suit and tie-it looks ridiculous for a reason-it is. Above all enjoy it, your gonna be great!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Baruch Avis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Listen to the wife! And every outfit makes her look wonderful. Dont forget the myriad of compliments, always. And as you have heard, breastfeeding is a gift from Hashem. Most important, love the kid and enjoy, expect nothing in return.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elliot Holtz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Gabe: The Zohar teaches that when we appear in Heaven after 120 years in this world, we will be asked: “Did you provide the proper education for your children?” 

cont'd pg 2]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Murray August]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Get this: The Zohar says that if a person can answer that question affirmatively, God immediately admits that person into Heaven. That’s it. No court case, no weighing of sins. If you managed to raise your children properly, you’re in!
]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Murray August]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Gabe - when it comes to happy and healthy kids, we have found that in addition to tears, tefila and Siyata d'Shmaya, the hishtadlus lies in promoting a happy home and a happy wife. 

cont'd pg 2]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, R'Jacobs & R'Lynn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[That is, if your home is a gesmack place to be and your wife feels like a queen, the simcha will be contagious and your kids will catch it, b'ezras Hashem. Wishing you and your wife b'sha'ah tova u'mutzlachas! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, R'Jacobs & R'Lynn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My man, I have no doubt that you will be a great dad. Some things I've learned along the way: 1) Never take a job that will cause you to miss your kids first pitch of the season/ dance recital. 2) Try to keep the phrase "I'm busy" to a minimum.  
cont'd pg 2]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brett Averick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[3) Deena and I agreed on a potential definition of "love" a few years ago. It was: Finding the person that you always want to be nice to. If you are always nice to your your gal, the parenting will come easy. You're a team. Good luck.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brett Averick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are a number of harsh truths to parenting---actually harsh. And they are:

1) the degree to which you are screwed up is the degree to which you will screw up your kids

cont'd pg2]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Yosef Kaufman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[2) the degree to which you do not have shalom bais is the degree to which you will screw up your kids

con't pg 3]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Yosef Kaufman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[3) quantity time is quality time. That is to say, do not have illusions that small amounts of quality time with the kid are in any way in the same ballpark

as spending lots and lots of time with your kid(s)

cont'd pg 4
]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Yosef Kaufman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[4) you have to give the kid good religion: that you’re excited about your Judaism, that it matters, and that you care about it

con't pg 5]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Yosef Kaufman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[5) And, most importantly, the whole idea of parenting is the idea that your child should never feel alone. That care manifests itself in different ways at different times in their lives. 

]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Yosef Kaufman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ As children the way you as a parent make them feel not alone is to give them fun and training (table manners, how to dress, etc.);
]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Yosef Kaufman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As teenagers you make them feel not alone by giving them warmth and acceptance as they exert their need to develop self-identity]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Yosef Kaufman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ As adults, even when they’re married and older, the way you make them feel not alone is by giving them money and council---in just that order.
]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Yosef Kaufman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Be prepared for the "Greatest Show on Earth". Becoming a father for the first time was an indescribable experience that matured me, like nothing else I had previously encountered. You and Deena will help mold your child's future by teaching him / her Hashem's way.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steven]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's very obvious to me that your parents raised you with much love and care. Pass on to all your children what your loving parents taught to you.Be faithful to Hashem and family and you will have a blessed life's journey.
I'm very proud to be your father-in-law.
]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steven]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Raising a child is like a great golf swing. If you don’t hold onto the club tight enough then it will go flying out of your hands but if you hold on too tight the ball will slice and veer off in the wrong direction. 

cont'd pg 2]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Moshe Rudenstein]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It’s when you have a good grip and leave a little wiggle room the ball will go nice and straight.

]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Moshe Rudenstein]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>