<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order>
<subOrder>
    <orderId>1297-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[4/3/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Cristina Kovarick]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[456 Winston Way]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Berwyn]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19312]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia>NotAvailable</shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Everybody Likes You Because...]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Emma Pawlow]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Your Friends]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Emma you are the greatest. You are kind, and smart, and resilient. It's so nice that we still get to see you, Caroline, and Matthew a lot. It's always a good time sledding, listening to HSM on repeat, or  playing Just Dance. Hope to see you soon, so much love!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jane D (aka Zayn's biggest fan)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Good luck buddy! Zayn will be thinking of you! ;) Thanks for being awesome, caring and funny for all the years I have known you! Boo Cole Hamels! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ana (Your bestfriend...teehee)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[EMMA CATHERINE AGNES PAWLOW I love you more than chocolate and Jonathan Groff combined and you are the strongest person I know!  Best wishes, and who knows, maybe this is the beginning of your disney princess fairytale!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lizzie <3 ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thinking of you, my most favorite other child, Em....best wishes for a speedy recovery!  Can hardly wait until you are singing and dancing to HSMusical again soon!  xoxo ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mrs. D]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Emma, you are amazing. Just a flat out fantastic person who I am so glad to have spend years with! I have know you since before I realized I knew you and we have grow closer over the years. You are so amazing. I wish you the best of luck during your surgery!!! <3 <3 <3]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelsey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Emma, you have been one of my best friends this year. You have been really funny, thoughtful, nice and helpful especially during world history or world lit. I hope that your surgery goes/went well and you feel better soon. We all miss you and will be thinking about you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Madison <3]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Emma, you are so nice and super pretty! I really hope you get better!! You are amazing at soccer and just a super cool person!! I'm so glad I got to meet you! You're awesome! We miss you! Get well soon!! :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Logan Vondercrone]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're the strongest, funniest, besets person I know and I'm so happy to have you as a best friend. Watch every hsm, eat tons of blue ice cream, sing too much disney, throw a balloon party and get better really soon! I love you more than anything, like for seriously!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[FEEL BETTER EMPAW!!!! HOPE ALL IS WELL!!! WE GOTTA PLAY SCATEGORIES AND THAT GAME WITH THE SHAPES THAT POP UP IN A SCARY WAY SOON!! ILL COME VISIT SOON!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jack Broadhurst]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To my bestie, little dino chicken nugget and my twin- you are so strong and kind. After your quick recovery I can't wait to play soccer with you and ride the biggest roller coasters! I will always  be there for you and you are one of my best friends. Love you so much Em]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anna/Annazing/Annie Quaverich]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[EMMA ILY UR SUCH A GOOD SOCCER PLAYER OMG AND WELL MISS U IN OUR GAMES GET STRONG RRSLLY FAST OK LOVE YOU????????????????????????????????????]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Abby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Emma, I love how you are always so energetic and awesome. No matter what happens you are always positive and motivated. You are one of the best human beings I know and are always ready to be the best you can be. I literally don't know what I would do without you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ally]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can always count on you for positivity and hustle! I am so glad you joined the team and can not wait to play with you more once you get better! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Annie Ulichney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It has been so much fun playing soccer with you this year. You are so nice, funny and athletic. I hope everything goes great and I'm looking forward to seeing you back on the field!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Emily Mullin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[hi emma! I wish you the best on Monday.  We've really been good friends this year and I'm really glad to have met you and played with you. You put your heart and soul into every game. Thanks for being awesome Enjoy the kids cafeteria chicken! 
~Lizzy (goldfish)??????]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elizabeth Billman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You rock! I love your positive outlook & desire to have fun. Your free spirit nature inspires me.  Anna is lucky to have a great friend who is so reliable & understanding.  Oh, and your running energy is out of control! You leave your mom in your dust! You are amazing!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mrs. Kovarick ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[EEEMS!! You're the most amazing and sweetest person I know! We have the funniest times together. I don't know what I'd do without you! Your the best Disney princess out there! I hope your surgery goes well and that you have a fast recovery. LOVE YOU!!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lauren ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Emma you are literally so kind and funny and amazing and fabulous. I love how you have so many fantastic traits that Disney can't contain you with a single  princess. They should just make a princess named Emma Pawlow. She would probably be my favorite. Love you Emma!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lissy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I wish you the best of luck in your surgery, and hope everything goes well. We will miss you for the next few weeks at soccer because you have been a great asset to our team. You are an amazing soccer player, and I can't wait to have you back out there. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kristen Edel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are one of the nicest people I know. You are always smiling and I love how excited you get about all things Disney. I'm sorry you have have to spend your spring break getting surgery. I wish I could take you with me I need someone to help me survive my crazy family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Emily]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are an awesome, funny person, and I am glad I know you. Hope you get better soon so we can play Scategories and NOT paint my nails pink again. You can get through this, I believe in you! Do it for Scategories and for Disney!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex Murphy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a really great person! Throughout the year you have been really kind to me and everyone. You are really smart and I hope you recover fast! I will see you next week. Good luck Emma Catherine Pawlow.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[max magee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey Emma, i hope the surgery goes well. have a nice spring break and get well soon. ???????? haha emojis are fun ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex dyer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are such a good friend and you make me laugh a lot. I hope to see you soon and can't wait for the summer at Martin's Dam.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lauren Kovarick ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Empaw!  You are a good friend to Anna and I like you a lot.   You are really good at soccer and big hugs! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Casey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Emma, We miss you so much! Can't wait to see you back on the field scoring goals :) You're amazing! Much love and all the best from your FCUSA family !!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Coach Sarah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>