<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order>
<subOrder>
    <orderId>1321-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[4/14/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[JULI DESJARDINS]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[627 VALLEY VIEW LN]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[WAYNE]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19087]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia>NotAvailable</shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_60]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Welcome to Parenting!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Erica Payne & Gene Haigh]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Kappa Delta 21 Club]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Santa Claus brings three presents because Baby Jesus got three presents.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Juli Jadick Desjardins]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If your child hits another child on the head, it is probably because the other child is being stupid.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jill Olson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Imagine who you might be if someone had spoken to you calmly whenever you made a mistake. Do that for your child.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jill Olson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's perfectly normal to feel like you have no idea what you are doing...at least I hope so.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Juli J]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Try skipping down the street, yelling, "LIFE IS SO FUN!! I'M SO GLAD TO BE IN THE WORLD!"  If you feel extra happy, hand out swizzle sticks. Remember that this is the way your child should feel at least some of the time.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jill Olson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There is nothing better than a freshly bathed sleeping baby.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Juli (your baby concierge)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Stay in tune with your child and you will know what to do when she goes through her challenging/moody stages.  Always (always!!!) remember "this too shall pass."  If they feel safe and connected to you they will be very resilient!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you Amy Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You set the tone.  Words are important, but they are trumped by your actions.  Developing brains watch and absorb everything you do.  Being a better person means having children who are better people.

]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lori Taylor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Read.
Read with silly voices, read while she falls asleep, read in the car, read your favorites over and over.
Read.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lori Taylor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sleep train her!!  She will be rested and happy and so will you...and don't wait to do this until she's 3 and realize you've wasted years of sleep.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Holly Boggs]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Be a coach, not a boss]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hollis ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Be prepared for anything…they will say and do lots of unexpected things.

For example, our little guy's christmas list last year: 
1) iPod 
2) crutches 
3) invisibility ring 
4) a tuba]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hollis ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You won't love every moment, but love as many as you possibly can, especially during those first years...that sweet baby smell, her chubby arms, baby voice, toothless grin & the warmth of her tiny body sleeping on your chest. Enjoy these precious moments, Erica & Gene!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo Hollis ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember, your baby came to live with YOU.  Yes, her needs are important, but so are yours.  Nurture your relationship and support each other.  The best gift you can give your little girl is to be happy!

Also, know it is okay to ask for help.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan and Mike Tallent]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Take lots of pictures!  She will be applying to college before you know it!  
Cherish each stage of her precious life!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan & Mike Tallent]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If her tummy hurts do the following:
1.  Lay her on her tummy
2.  Pat her back and bottom
3. Turn her onto her back and push her knees into her tummy or do a bicycle motion with her legs.  This helps get the gas out!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan and Mike]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always keep lots of chopsticks or straws in your purse in case you go to dinner and she gets bored!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sue B]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have one motto my sister shared when my boys were little and I was at my wit's end:

"the days are long but the years are short".

So true!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maryt Johnson Reaves ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When the children are young . . . Stick to your guns. Discipline early and stay true to your word.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[VA]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As the kids grow older, become more of a listener and keep your cool.  They will share more with you this way, and you will remained more informed.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[VA]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Erma Bombeck said "Never lend your car to whom you have given birth".  I would add: "or to a friend that likes to wave to other friends."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Juli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Meet your daughter where she is. In other words, when she is a baby and toddler, get down on the floor. When she is in middle school, be the driver of carpools. When in high school, wait up for her to come in at curfew. Teenagers talk the most to you late at night.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Merritt Orr]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You do not want your daughter to get drunk for the first time at a fraternity party when she is a freshman in college. You might not like her drinking in high school but a little experience is not a bad thing.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Merritt Orr]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the best gifts you can give your sweet girl: be a joyful mother. The impact of that is immeasurable.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Merritt Orr]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Never make decisions based on the events of one day.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Danielle Williams]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A lot of advice is unsolicited and should stay that way for a reason. Have the strength to ignore the opinions of those that don't matter to the issue. Don't waste your breath trying to correct them. For real.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Danielle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Set the example you want your child to follow. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Danielle Williams]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Get dirty.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Danielle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Break the rules (even your own) every now and again.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Danielle Williams]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hug and kiss them and tell them you love them. Every. Single. Day.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Danielle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy people have happy children;  remember to take time to make yourselves happy even if it's a sweet little nap or a pedicure (E!). You are both your daughter's greatest teacher!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you! Amy Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Just when you figure out how to do something - things will change. Parenting seems like moving from one hypothesis to another. It is simply the way it is - you can no longer operate under the illusion you are in control.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lori Taylor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Don't threaten a punishment you cannot follow through on. Example: if you booked a trip to Disney and she's acting out, don't say "we aren't going to Disney unless you stop this tantrum." If she doesn't stop, obviously you aren't cancelling, and then she has the power.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kimmy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Put off Disney World for as long as possible.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim Heilman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Be a mom first, then a friend when she's older. She has plenty of friends, and no matter how cool you are, or think you are, in her eyes you are a big fat nerd, so don't waste your time trying to use their lingo or anything.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kimmy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Don't spend your money on nice, fancy clothes. They grow out of them in about a week. You shop at Target and Costco, and let your friends and family get the expensive stuff. Idiots.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim Heilman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Everything is a phase. She will end up sleeping through the night, get over ear infections, stop putting makeup on the walls, stop talking back and rolling her eyes, and she will return from wherever the aliens took her in her teens (I think - I'm only 16 years in.)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kimmy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Good luck and Godspeed.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim Heilman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You can't always be your daughter's friend.  She will have plenty of those but only one mom and dad.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Millie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Gene, The first two months are awful.  It gets much better.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Patrick Kelly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always have crayons/pencils and paper available. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Millie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Pick your battles.  There will be plenty but it doesn't really matter if she wear stripes with plaid and mismatched socks.  That's just a sign of uniqueness. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Millie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Princess dresses and tiaras are appropriate attire for anything and anywhere. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Millie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Every child is different and unique.  They learn and grow at different rates.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Millie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Eat dinner together as a family - great time to talk. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen Ped]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It is not your job to make your child happy, you should teach them to find happiness themselves.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer Pedersen Butler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Babies are little vampires - sleep all day, up all night - get them on a schedule as quickly as possible! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen Ped]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If kids get hungry or tired, they turn into devils - be ahead of their needs.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer Pedersen Butler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Enjoy your kids! It is so amazing to have your kids look up to you and to see the world through their eyes! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen Ped]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To all of these amazing tips I give a Kappa Delta "DITTO" with my arm flying back and forth for heavy emphasis.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Juli J]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>