<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order>
<subOrder>
    <orderId>1346-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[4/27/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Leslie Kemm]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[531 Winston Way]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Berwyn]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19312]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia>NotAvailable</shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sunshine]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Kir!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Kirstin Brown]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Robert Brown]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are sunshine when you walk in a room, full of radiance, warmth, beauty and laughter.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathleen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You embrace positivity – a tremendous trait.  You always find the good in people, situations, and life in general!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lauren]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To borrow your expression - you are a "gamer" - which I love! I am so inspired by your can-do attitude, rock-star commitment to the schools, values you are raising your kids by and how you are "leaning in" all at the same time. You are my hero! Happy b-day!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heather ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What you see is what you get and I appreciate that more and more.  Smart.  Fearless.  Funny.  Did I mention great taste in handbags??]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are blessed with an abundance of OPTIMISM, and your ability to share this with others is truly a gift to all that know you!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vicki]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love your undeniable love of life, energy, and understated sophistication!  Happy Birthday sweet cousin, thinking of you makes me smile.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah G]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bold, smart, strong, fun and loving—you rock the whole package and get to be tall, too.  I admire it all and love sharing our lives on the lagoon together.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marika]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your big heart and willingness to share everything you have never ceases to amaze.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have an exceptional ability to listen, an ever-present smile, and a quiet strength, which means you are a great role model for me and my children. Thank you, and Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eric]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A cousin and a true friend.  There are so many memories that bring a smile.  But, underneath all the memories is a lovely person: fun-loving, smart, thoughtful.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love the way you really, truly listen and how it's so obvious that you're opening yourself completely up during a conversation.  It's so special to be able to count on a friend to pay 100% attention to you when you're together. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have always been a role model for me with your ability to balance your beautiful family and meaningful career, all with grace, kindness, and a sense of humor.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lauren]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your joyful, happy disposition and can-do-anything attitude make you a great Mother, community member and dear friend.  I Love you, sweet lady! Happy, happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tracy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're an awesome neighbor and great friend!  Happy Birthday!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Like a sister, a confidant, and a partner in crime, Kirstin is always there for the challenges, the toughest moments in life, and the fun. Thank you for being such an important person in my life and the life of my family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm always struck by how practical, insightful, and eminently sensible your advice is to what I think are intractable problems.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The first time I realized that you had comprehensive vision was SCUBA diving;  you always saw 50% more than I did.  I always appreciated that you were always a conscientious dive buddy, staying close and making sure I was ok.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always remember your thoughtfuless on our long mother-daughter trips.  One that sticks with me:  we were in Africa in the one-room airport shack:  "You sit here Mips, you organized the trip — I'll go find our bags, check in, get our departure time, and buy water.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always willing to dig in, listen, be a true FRIEND.  Love you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Debbie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kir, so glad to know you.  
I love you with your family.  
Inspiring.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frank]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to one of the best moms I know.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your smile and laughter is infectious.  Love having you in my life.  Who knew sorority sisters (pledge sisters even) would lead to neighbors and good friends.  Please let's not toss the good wine off the deck next time.  You need to gulp it down first.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Millie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No matter the time between conversations, I can practically feel your smile through the phone, which instantly brightens my day.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leslie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whether it's revising my personal statement for college or welcoming me over for the weekend, your warm and generous spirit always seem to brighten the day. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Daniel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are sunshine, clear, strong, warm and true. Never have I laughed so hard, received truer advice, never have I had a better friend. I love you!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer (Charlie's mom)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lately, our orbits have not rotated together, but I know your genuine friendship and kindness is always alive.  Hugs & Happy Birthday to you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michelle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are such a delightful person to journey through life with!  I admire your cheerful disposition and your poise.  Your uplifting and friendly spirit is welcoming and your hospitality is so genuine and warm.  I feel so lucky to call you my friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shannon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Eat lots of cake, drink lots of wine and enjoy the day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelly and Scott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I would have you on every team, every family, and as a friend for life...did I mention your shining and welcoming beauty.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frannie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ever since grade school, Kir's positive attitude, gorgeous smile, fierce intellect and infectious spirit has brought so much joy to the lives of all her family, friends and colleagues - everyone should take a page from her book!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Erika]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You laugh easily, love deeply and appreciate the beauty not only of your friends and family but of humanity. Happy birthday old friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tory]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Never have I met a laugh so contagious, an “OMG" said so many fabulous ways or someone who powers up a room with sunshine.  You are this and so much more Kir.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dina]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You put the k in kindness, and make our family and our world better for it everyday – thanks!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robert]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I want you to know that I wouldn’t be me without you. You turn my frown upside down when I am sad. I am always happy when I’m with you and I want that to stay the same. Happy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah  ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best mom ever! You make me smile every day, and you always make me feel better when I’m sad. You give great advice, and I love you so much. You’re #1!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Georgia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ I love how you are always willing to do whatever we want almost all the time no matter how we address it. Crying, sleeping (mostly Sarah), yelling, asking, telling, demanding, and a lot more.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cole]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you mom. No matter how we say it, I love you mom. You’re beautiful. Sometimes we just don’t know how to say it. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cole]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kir, you are my true companion.  Each year more than the one before, with all that I am, I love and honor you because of who you are to me, to our family, and to everyone around you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robert]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>