<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order>
<subOrder>
    <orderId>1375-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[4/28/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Heather Clayton]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[531 Winston Way]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Berwyn]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19312]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <specialInstructions><![CDATA[]]></specialInstructions>
    <shipVia>NotAvailable</shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 65th Dad!!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Andy Brown]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love, Les and Meg]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He is the most honest, hard working and loving father, and he is always there for me.  I love you so much!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Megan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Took me 2 seconds to decide:  Without a doubt his LOYALTY to Family and Friends!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[James T. Nixon, II]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Andy because he's never full of shit. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jesse Bennett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[the best word to describe andy is unselfishness. andy has always had a big heart in listening to the cares and concerns of those people whom he values. his level of energy allows him to involve himself in many causes that are beneficial to the needs of others.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[mary jo and bobby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The thing I love best about Andy Brown is his big, tender, marshmallow heart.  Next best is his wife, Pat.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Betty]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that he loves me and that he plays with me...and that he went on an Easter egg hunt with me]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Little Leslie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Meow]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lay Lay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love that he gives us treats, kisses us and lets us lay on his chest]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mini and Moose]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dad, you know you are my hero.  What I most admire about you is your honesty.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Loit]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Grandpa,/RI think you are so funny!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Scarlett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Grandpa,/RI love you.  Happy cheers and kisses to you!  (What he told mommy to write).]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Lucas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I want more candy!!!!  I sing Bim Baum!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Baby Sage]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Grandpa,/RI like covering you with pillows.  I hope I always do that to you. (Told by Max to Mommy)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Max]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[one word that best describes andy is unselfishness. andy has always shown an interest to the cares and concerns of other people. his endless energy has been a benefit to the many causes that he holds dear to his heart. happy 65th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[mary jo  and bobby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Compassionate and strong, tough as nails!  Best friend you could ever ask for!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Beltrams]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I admire most about  Andy is his willingness to always help other people no matter how well he knows them. He has extreme loyalty to friends and an honesty that is hard to match. I am blessed to be able to call him 'my friend'. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ron Peek]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andy- you had an opportunity to save Steve's life- by removing a little tick -instead of helping out you said /R"Steve---You're going to die!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ann Bax]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[integrity]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lee Lyon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To the most honorable "karate-an" I have had the pleasure of being great friends with during the last 26 years.   Thank you for enhancing my life and being there for me.  Happy Birthday and welcome to Medicare !   May God grant you many more enjoyable years.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peter & Susanne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mr. Brown is one of my favorite people in the world! He is extremely generous and loving and I can't say enough wonderful things about him! Love you Mr. Brown, Happy Happy Birthday! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[J'Nan, Nick and Maggie Erker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A couple years ago you & I were planning to retire at the same time. Now I have 5,000 miles on my bicycle, you are still dedicated to your company & family.  You are a Great Father & Friend !]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peter Bugjo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Not enough room on this fucking card!/R/RFather, Mentor, Partner, Sensei..... /R/RRome wasn't built in one day because we weren't there!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ben ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andy's personality can not be matched/RHis way of life is unique, from horses to his love of sports!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mason Hurst aka 'the big cheese']]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like Andy's cussing and his bright spirit!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brady Hurst aka 'the little cheese']]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andys's best quality is his happiness:/RBe crazy/RBe weird/RBe silly/RBe true /RLife is short.  Do what makes you happy./RYour mantra--my friend XOXXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vicki Hurst]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andy's word is Golden.  If he makes a commitment to you, you can bet your life on it, that it will be done.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andy's zest for life & his willingness to just go for it are inspiring!   "Keep up with him or get out of his way!" Is a fantastic trait !]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ I would love to be there.  But moving me is akin to moving a grand piano.  Pretend that  I am there playing Beethoven Emperor Concerto.  Just think of the glow in the room produced by your bald pate.  Ageing has positive consequences.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jerry Mason]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andy can do what he wants when he wants because he doesn't give a shit.. And I love it. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JT ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for everything!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ilias]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andy has a huge heart and a willingness to help people that goes beyond compare.  He's  been a great boss for 24 years!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Donna Brasel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Secretariat had a heart three times the size of normal horses and a true champion. Your heart is also three times bigger than the normal man and you are truly a champion.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jay and Tammy Rosenlund]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have worked closely with andy for 30 plus years,he has been a real inspiration and joy to work with,i dont know anyone that works harder than he does at anything, from family, work excerize,to a new fabulous foundation for our vets grads on the big 65]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[doug blankinship ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To describe Andy, who I have known for 35 years, is that he is an honest, sincere and compassionate person, that I have had the pleasure of knowing.  Happy Birthday!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peggy Copeland]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday and many more, I have know you for almost a quarter of a century and it has been a great friendship. Enjoy the day.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larry Klug]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing that I like most about you is your loyalty to old friends.  We have been friends for almost 60 years!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Ginsberg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andy you may seem hard as nails (okay you are), but you are a big softy. All my life I have known you to be compassionate, loving, and so very giving. All of my love. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amber Barnett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your steadfast friendship & loyalty is overwhelming and extends to so many... and still you would give your shirt to someone in need. All of us are lucky to be able to call you our friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday! Love, Janet Dubrava]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[For me, its not about what he has or owns, however impressive. Its his work ethics. But also in the middle of all his hustle and bustle of his life, work, family etc. Its his heart. His caring for other people. He always has time .  Warhorses for Veterans. Says it all. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathie Gialde]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One more thing, He's also loud, pushy and a pain sometimes. But I love him. Just saying.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathie Gialde]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey Andy!/R/RI'll never forget the first time I met you, I think I was coming to take Les out on a date.  I was scared as hell!  I soon realized that you are one of the coolest, easy going dudes that I have ever met in my life!  Happy Bday, I hope you have a great day!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jake]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to one of my very favorite friends! I will always love and admire you. I know no one who loves his family more than you ..... Leslie and Megan are who they are today because of the great parenting you and Pat gave them.  You are the very best!!!!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sending much love to you, Mollie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 65th Birthday Andy, & Many More Happy & Healthy Ones To Come!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Pilbeam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing we like most about Andy Brown is the fact that he sees people for who they truly are, and he takes them as they come. If you're a friend of Andy's, you're a friend for life. We are proud to call him our friend, and even more proud he calls us his friends.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Weber Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andy,/RBeI could not have had a better person to work for.  I consider you a friend and brother.  Thank you for all you have done for me and all of the Mid-States family.  Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Doug Hasty]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>