<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>1390-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[4/28/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Heather Clayton]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[531 Winston Way]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Berwyn]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19312]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia>NotAvailable</shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[scarlet]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 65th Birthday Donna!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Donna Parisi]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love, Family and Friends]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Age 3 - Walking up Cornwall st with Mom and sister. Nice dark curly hair, such fat cheeks and great big winning smile. A Picture! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Leo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[First Grade - Donna was sad, smile gone. Asked why? She was give the role as the troll in the class play. After explaining the troll was the most important part and that the whole play depended on the troll part, the winning smile came back! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Leo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Through the Years - Many ups and downs, sadness and joy, But her winning smile - her dauntless spirit - inner strength, deep faith, have brought her through it all. She has been a tremendous blessing to her parents, family and friends. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Leo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have been and will continue/R to be proud of my wonderful niece, Donna! /R/RLove you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Leo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[D is the darling of Generation Life/R/RO is for ONE of the BEST/R/RN is for one of the nicest women/R/RN  is never wavers in her faith/R/RA is for actively involved with her beloved grandchildren. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Denny and Mary]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I so admire your inner faith, it has never faltered and it sustains you in life's most turbulent waters. /R/RGod Bless!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, Maria]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can't remember the exact location, but you Mom was struggling a bit in her /Rlater years. I remember seeing /Rthe love in your eyes as you gazed at her and sought to facilitate her. I sat and stared at you and was inspired by your devotion and love. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sincerely, Cousin Vince]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember how proud and delighted I was to be chosen to be your godmother. To me you were the most adorable and pleasant baby ever. My love for you and pride in you has never diminished. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Aunt Kay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[How can I forget the night I asked you to be my flower girl? /R/RYou were thrilled. /R/ROn the big day, at age 7, you carried off your role beautifully, just like a little "pro". ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Aunt Kay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love the way you have embraced each of our children as they came along (just as your own Mom did) and treated them more like your little brothers and sisters. You will always have a special place in their hearts and mine. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Aunt Kay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I hear the name "Donna" mentioned, I think: smiles, laughter, enthusiaum, gererosity, intergity, loyalty, optimistic, faith in god, unconditional love for family and friends, compassion, sense of humor and to top it all off - beauty and brians. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Aunt Kay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have so many memories of fun, laughter and tears with you my beloved cousin Donna. One of my favorites was when we were shopping and we found the        /R"D I C K"  family card. We laughed so hard we almost peed! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Patty]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We set out for a fun day, After several stores we decided to have lunch. As Donna reached for her wallet, she exclaimed "I've been pick-pocketed, my money is gone!" We retraced our steps, the culprit was.. Steinmart, Back of the Bay, 5th Ave and 3rd in Naples FL. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Eileen and Rich]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We will always remember the work for vacation time (at Sea Isle). It allowed me and my family to get to know you and feel close to you . We will also never forget your cinnamon buns and cake upon our arrival. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[We love you, Dan and Nancy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memory of Donna is the time we were out to dinner in Avalon and a woman walked into a mirror next to the exit. The laughter that ensued was a riot./RPS- the woman was OK and never knew wee were laughing. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joseph Mingari]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So many memories!  Our relationship started many moons ago. I had just completed an extensive plan as your new financial advisor. You showed me the kindness and respect that I only receive from long time established clients. /R/Rcontinued...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin Douglass Sr. ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Continued.../R/RIt came time for you to write a check for the balance of the fee. I discounted by 25% and you would not hear of it and gave me a check for the full amount. I was speechless! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin Douglass Sr. ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have become best friends.  I have seen the loving woman of family and friends, empathy, understanding. You are a  friend I  can count on and you have also  helped me spiritually. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With Love, Kevin Douglass Sr.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You remind me of Aunt Dot, always the doting Mom and Grandmom, but also showing care for your extended family. We so appreciated the McDevitt reunions that you have has to get everyone together! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Cathy, Gary and Kids]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have always been the gracious hostess too, in the way you prepared the shore house for us whenever we vacationed in Sea Isle. I'll never forget the clean towels and sheets! We have enjoyed visiting you there. Thanks for the memories!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Cathy, Gary and Kids]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Donna is a great driver in snow. Other  cars were sliding and swerving, but not Donna!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Beth]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Trip to Hawaii/RA fun memory was watching you hang out of the helicopter and sing, "The Hills are Alive" in the rain and eatting flowers at our private lava. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Speer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks Donna for making Jane and I feel so welcome in your life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve and Jane Johnon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Newport - remember the "Beaver" - Stone Harbor - Neptune Jewel's - Victorious and Stephanie's  Shop til we drop - Broken shoulders; we were twins, dinner together, crying, laughing, soup, cupcakes and wine.  Such fun times! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dollie and Joe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One day at the old corporate office, Donna was watching her grandchildren. She came into the office and told Tracie, "Don't worry if your children have a hickie on their faces and necks, I am letting them use the vacuum to S U C K each other up! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amy Ocasio]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cooking with Donna]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Morgan and Amy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One cold winter day in 2014, my truck window broke and Donna opened her home to me allowing me to stay there until it was repaired. Her compassion and thoughtfulness touched me deeply and will never be forgotten.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joey Ocasio]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[During a rough time in my life, you tok me in an you made me feel loved. I won't forget it. /R/RThank you. I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Justin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ms. Donna, /R/RI love you and thank you so much for founding ACP. I am honored to be an employee of yours. /R/RGod Bless You!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Mr. Brian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom was attempting to dye my hair in her kitchen sink and we were laughing the whole time because she was getting water everywhere. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Jen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I miss seeing you in the middle office. There you would be, under a pile of papers yet always so pleasant. It is a blessing to see you when you visit. I love seeing your bubbly self. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Danielle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love all your funny stories! /R/RStop in and see us in the office soon!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Catie Garfalo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Linda's test sentiment]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[On the way home from 2013 Tottime Xmas party - my husband commented that Donna was the youngest spirited woman he ever met. She was so excited about her recent trip to Disney and how much she loved roller coasters. That spirit is what characterizes Donna!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anne Doughtery]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lovely meeting you ! /R/RYou are such a real person! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Last year, although she's known me for 13 years, she still called Tracie asking who that guy (me) was that was walking around her house fixing things. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joey Ocasio]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[While helping Donna clean the Director's office, she gave me the code to open the safe and told me to "break into it". When I tried the code and pulled, the handle fell off and Donna said, " I said break into it, not break it! "]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Morgan Roberts]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[This is a test message from Anne Dougherty]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anne Dougherty]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Donna, Father Donovan, my husband Paul and I visited Washington DC. We stayed overnight and had an awesome time. Love you Donna! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Theresa Murtagh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Last year for Donna's birthday a group of us met at Totaro's fro dinner. They asked me to sing and I did. A few drinks later we were all singing for the other patrons of the restaurant! Donna told me that we ended up on Totaro's website. What a fun night! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Dimattia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Donna - "Promise not to tell mom"/RBob- "Hey Dad, guess what Donna did?"/RDonna-"You promised not to tell"/RBob- "I promised not to tell Mom, not Dad"/R/RBob was 4 years old, Donna was 16]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob Parisi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[test from Victoria]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Victoria Johnson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Memories/RBack in the day- Friday night dance at the Cottman Ave Roller Rink. No one knew we were cousins. /R/RAvalon on the dock- We picked you up and threw you in the water. The top of your bathing suit came off and we put you down fast!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cousin Al]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sentiment for donna]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amy bielinski]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Donna!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nicole Yarmark]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Donna,/R/RYou are an inspiration to us!  Your energy, smile, love and passion for life is just incredible ! /R/RWe are blessed to have met you ! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Chris and Heather Clayton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>