<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>1416-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[4/28/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Leslie Kemm]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[531 Winston Way]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Berwyn]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19312]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia>NotAvailable</shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[scarlet]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[You Are Awesome!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Chase Kemm]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love, Mommy, Daddy and Kendall]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how family means more to you than anything else in the world (except maybe sports)!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I think you're really awesome… even with all that hair.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chaser-I love your huge heart and the special moments we get to share together.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Daddy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love your desire to be the best at everything you do./RYour smile can light up a room and your laugh is contagious!!!!!  I love you so much.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Daddy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love it when you help others and most importantly your puffy, wet kisses!!!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Daddy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are an AMAZING little boy and I am proud to be your father.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Daddy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Chase's extreme curiosity for everything!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pop Pop Kemm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Recently Chase and I spent some time alone shopping for me. We entered the store and of course Chase started asking questions. Our conversation lasted the entire time we were together! I loved the feeling of closeness we shared that day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Mom Mom Kemm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love the sparkle in his eyes when he knows I actually understand the stats he is reciting!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Mom Mom Kemm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I Love Chase because he is my grandson and makes me very proud./RI also enjoying talking sports with Chase, he is a walking encyclopedia, he should have been named ESPN. LOL]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grandpa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You've brought happiness to everyone from the moment you came into our lives.  I love you more than you know xo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Zanne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chase - I love your passion for sports and your knowledge of so many different things - always keep that going - you are such a special boy and I love you so much!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Auntie Lisa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chase, my precious Grandson./RI am so proud of you. Included in my/RSpecial memories of you are the times we spend together early in the morning./REveryone else is sleeping and we have our special time together. I wish it could be more often. I love you so very much./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grandma Gudel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always know how to brighten my mood. Ever since you were little you always knew how to make me smile. I love spending time with you and talking about sports, especially Villanova! You are such a smart, energetic boy and I love you more than you will ever know!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah Domenick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The things I like most about you is your knowledge of sports and how you always need to win.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael Ippoliti]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[chase, it's hard to just say one thing.. you are one of a kind.. A caring boy with a huge heart. You are a star that shines bright. A role model for Presley. You are perfect just the way you are. I'm blessed to have a nephew like you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Lauren]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like that you like all the same sports I like!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Danny Johnson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a nice friend, a good athlete and great at playing video games!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your buddy TJ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Chase is the awesome sports talks we have together. Chase also has a great sense of humor and is just plain fun to be around. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mr. Hargest]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chase is nice and friendly. He was super friend when he was an actor in my cereal box project.  He was a great sport to pretend to miss all of the baskets!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Luca Webb]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I like most about Chase is: he is funny, nice, playful, we have fun playing together at recess, and he knows a lot about baseball, football, and basketball.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jack Shaw]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love when you shut everything out around you and just want to snuggle and talk.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mommy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love your sense of humor.  You drop the funniest lines at just the right time, unintentionally, which is what makes you genuinely funny, not someone who is trying to be funny. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mommy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love when you call me "Momma". It doesn't happen much anymore, but on the occasions it does, it reminds me that you're still my baby boy!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mommy (aka Momma)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Chase!  We love your passion for life!!!  Every moment we spend with you is an adventure!  Never ever forget how amazing you are!   Yes - Bottle that energy and excitement for everything you love!!!   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Auntie Kelly and Uncle Dave]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a great athlete and a good friend. I like spending time with you. You are smart too. /R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Landon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What do I like most about you? Is it how much I enjoy talking about sports with you? Or how great a writer you are and how focused you get when you have a great idea? I could go with digging your cool jersey collection. Think I'll simply go with you being a great kid!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mr. Adlin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chase is a great friend and King of Pro-Mini Hoop basketball games!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[DJ Peterson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chase is so polite, he always remembers to say please and thank you, all of the time!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sonia Peterson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chase has the best enthusiasm for sports stats.  I will be sure to consult him for my next fantasy draft!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Peterson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chase is a great friend who is always there for others people.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rowan Hornaday]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Chase's hair!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robyn Hornaday]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like that Chase always shakes hands after a game, good or bad. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Hornaday]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chase doesn't quit!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charlie Henderson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey Chase - you never cease to impress us! We think you are the MVP of Team Kemm (although Mr. Winters thinks you might need a haircut). His offer on getting it buzzed still stands......]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Winters Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What we like most about Chase is his loving spirit and how he always brings a smile to our face.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nick & Nickie DePompeo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The one thing I love most about Chase is his work ethic! Whether it is a toss in the yard or a play off game, you always know Chase is giving 100%! I am so proud of you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Becky Porter ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Other than Chase being an awesome kid, he as me, is a great Flyers fan. After hearing about him from Kim I got to see it myself as we started to go down to the Flyers games together. I remember when he was real young we would test him on the players numbers and he knew!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Murph]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Since the very first day I met you, you've held a huge piece of my heart! You always make me smile and my favorite days are those spent with you! Always reach for the stars! I love you to the moon and back! XOXOXO/R/RLet's Go Flyers, Phillies and Packers! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kimmie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a gentleman and a good friend. We are happy to have you as our neighbor!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Devlin/Burruano Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Chase is when he uses his time to help Finn with baseball.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mr. Nieberle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chase, you are like the big brother that I never had!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[love, Finn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chase, you are so fun to be around and you make everyone smile :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ryann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like it when you play four-square with us. You are a great friend :) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jamie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love your smile & your great sense of humor!  You are always laughing & so much fun to be around!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo - momma niebs]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To my son I never had. /RVillanova games, Jay Wright shows, the pool, catches in the yard, I have loved every minute with you.  You're the best.  I love you!!  Stay Good!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marky]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>