<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>1945-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[5/3/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Monica Lai]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[102 valley road]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[media]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19063]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Mother's Day!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Terri]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[For over 40yrs Terri has been one of my kindest most thoughtful and loyal friends and I am happy to have her in my life! /R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Luv Kathy ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My mom is handsdown the most selfless person I know. She always has been. She always puts everyone before her own needs and is willing to help out anyway that she can. She is an inspiration as a mother and grandmother and we can't express enough how much she is loved! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heather Lai]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She has always been an amazing mother and role model. She has supported all of my dreams and aspirations. She is the most generous and kind woman I know and always puts others wants and needs before her own. I only hope to he half the mother/woman she is some day. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Monica ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No matter on Caroll St, Simpson St, Franciscan Way, or Valley Rd.... /RThere has always been an open heart, big hug, and a welcoming smile for all who come to see our beloved Aunt Terri.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Terri has always been my best friend, always there for me to offer support and guidance. The most religious person I know. Kind, caring, compassionate and generous. Godmother to my Patrick. I love Terri Lai.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellen Cassidy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Terry has a generous nature.  Through all the years, she has been gracious and thoughtful to ourselves, our children and grandchild.  We also admire her commitment to family.  Happy Mothers Day Terry!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John and Denise Lai]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Terri is thoughtful,/RAlways there in times of need,/RTrue friend to the end./R/RGod gave us free will to be anyone we wanted to be. I am so glad Terri chose to be herself!  xo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Betsy Mellon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Terri is truly an amazing friend, She goes out of her way to make sure she supports you in good times and bad. She has a way about her that makes you forget your troubles.She has a truly warm, sweet personality,which comes thru her awsome smile. Happy Mothers Day! Terri]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Kathy Gerace]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Though I have not known Terri very long I feel like I have known her forever. Terri is kind, out going and always has a smile on her face. I feel lucky to have a friend like Terri. Happy Mothers Day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dolly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/RFun, loving and generous!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barb Long]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What can I say about Terri, we have a lot of fun together. She makes holidays amazing with her delicious dinners, she is always there for me when I need her. She is not just my friend she is a sister to me. Happy Mothers Day! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tina ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There is no one in this world that I trust more with my dogs then Terri. She is always willing to help Heather and I out with the kids and the dogs and she is very much appreciated. She is a great mother and grandmother and is the best dog mom and dog grandmom. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrew Piselli ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My mommom is amazing. I love her so much! I always know when she is at my house before she even walks in! I get sooo excited to see her EVERYTIME. I have so much fun at her house. I love having sleep overs with her. She takes such good care of me. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maggie May xoxo ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Terry is always there for her family, friends, and dogs.     I am so lucky to have Terry as a sister who gives me special support these days.   She is the best!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mrs. Lai is the best! She is kind, caring and laughs at all of my jokes. We are all lucky and thankful to have such a loving and thoughtful person in our lives. Happy Mothers Day! Love Wil ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wil ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Best God mother anyone could have and makes the best cookies ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Patrick cassidy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the many things I like about Aunt Terri is that she has made it possible for me to know grandparents who left us too soon by sharing her stories.  It means so much to me.  I have been blessed by having you in my life.  Love you!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jill]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have been friends for over 50 years hard to believe it has been that long when you feel like your 20 something.  A good friend knows all your best and worst moments of your life.  Terry has always been there for me whenever I need her. She is the best kind of friend ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Donna w]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tea Time with Terri is the best!!/RShe is a loyal and true friend who has a way of lifting you up and brightening your day just when you need it. The world is a better place with her in it, and she makes a "heckuva" cup of tea. /RLuv you, Happy Mother's Day]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rosemary]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are so generous!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Abby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You tell funny stories!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Caitlyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ahhhhdedededhieeeee]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Olivia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom mom makes the best ice cream waffles and i olive going to her house for her halloween and easter parties.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Raymond]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love mom mom because she has great parties and she makes good hot tea with lemon.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sammy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mrs. Lai is so kind and warm hearted. When i was little, I loved going to her house to see what was freshly baked on the counter. I always felt welcome and at home, that explains all the sleepovers, Thanks for always sharing your love.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maureen Mellon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are very caring!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JJ ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My mom is the best because she always tells me I am her favorite and rarely goes anywhere without me. She takes me for car rides, and walks at the park. But my favorite thing is when she takes me to the beach! She gives me lots of treats and tells me how pretty I am! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chloe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are so loving and the best mom I could've asked for! Also the best soccer coach I ever had!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jimmy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mrs. Lai has the Patience of Mother Theresa! She's a great cook and even better person. I truly enjoy just sitting and talking with her. I take it as a big compliment when Monica jokes and says I should be her daughter! She's the best! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meg DeCarlo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Terri has been a great friend of mine for the last 40 years. I am the one who got Terri and Jim together. She is a great mom and she loves her kids with all of her heart. Thats what I love about her, family first! (the maid is a spade)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Terri is a great person. She is selfless and always puts everyone before herself. She is a great wife, mother and grandmother. She always takes care of everyone, including Chloe. I am proud to call her my wife.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Terri such a nurturing and caring person,not only to her own children,but to anyone who enters her home.She has been there for me,in good times and bad.I love your home cooked meals and talking in your kitchen! You have raised an outstanding family and you are the best!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelly Gerace]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>