<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>1964-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[5/5/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Carla Bailey]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Arlington]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[VA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[22209]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[ Because You're Loved So Much]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[LaKecia Destiny Odum]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[LaKecia Destiny Odum]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I believe you are beautiful, smart, magic and you are DESTINY. It takes courage to grow up and become who you are really meant to be. Be courageous! Be different! Never forget God loves you, keep Him first in your life. Always pray and spend time with Him. I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grammy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[LeKecia, /R/RCongratulations on your accomplishment.  Remember the lessons you were taught by those who love and care about you.  Don't allow others who come into your world to change the person that you are.  Always remember that you MATTER.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mechelle Cockfield]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[KEKE!!!!  I am so proud of you.  Keep striving to do your best.  You will make mistakes along the way but allow these mistakes to be a learning tool for the great person you will become.  I love you soooo much and proud to have gotten to know you in these last few years]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carla Meade]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The short amount time that I've known you has been very impressive for a teenager.  You are a go-getter, hard worker, super personality, great integrity and your desire to achieve something great is very commendable.  Your attitude will take you wherever you want to go]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[CDGrubbs]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Really enjoyed getting to know you this year Lakecia.  Keep up the hard work at Spelman.  It will be tough but you are strong and smart.  Don't forget to have some fun every once and while like we did in EPF!/RBest of luck!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mr. O'Neill  -epf]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[LaKecia, thank you for being you, and for  inspiring me as a teacher. I am so happy that I got to know you as a student, and as a person.  I know you'll go on to do great things in this world.  /RStay true to yourself, Sweetie. /RLove,/RMrs. O.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mrs. Olarinde]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[YOU are the apple of my 3.14]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[don't ever forget it :)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Prayer isn't always audible. Sometimes communing with God requires you to be absolutely quiet so that He can speak to you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Erlie Pruitt Jr.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you and your family! It has been a priviledge being part of your life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mimster]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Keep Christ as your foundation and everything else will come together. Be fearless! Wishing you nothing but the best!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ayesha Trice]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ke Ke,/R/RYou are already a leader, winner and top achiever!  Walk in your "destiny" and continue to shine bright like the star you already are!   God's blessings be upon you.   Congratulations on your graduation & know I'm excited about your future!!!  #BIG ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Montré & Deron]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kiki, God has given you such a beautiful and sweet spirit. That makes you priceless. Remember your value and worth :-)/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenny]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kekee,/RWe are so proud of you on your Completion of High School Graduation. /RWe look forward to you completing your College Education and becoming  our first Chemical Engineer. Keep doing what your doing and continue to make us proud of you. Know that we all love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ronnie and Jannie and Tray !!!!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations!!/R You have all you need to make your dreams come true. You're destined for greatness. Enjoy your journey and remember to have fun. :) Much Happiness and Success... Luv U]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Auntie Deanna]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My one tip to my Ke Ke is...whatever you put your mind to, you can do it!!!! The sky is no longer the limit, the limit is how far you push yourself to obtain your goals and be what you want in life!!!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mama]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for being such a positive role model in our life big sis!! Congrats on your graduation and wishing you success in your future!!!! Love you forever!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aniya,Zay,Kyla, Elijah and Khloë]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Try to visualize your future. You don’t have to know or decide now but try to picture your ideal life and focus on that path, then begin your journey.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tanaya]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on your great milestone of graduating from High School. I wish you well on your next endeavor. You have grown into a beautiful, intelligent young lady and continue to strive for greatness. Love you....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ms. Dorinda Powell ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations KeKe on your graduation.I know you will do well you are a very smart young lady.Always stay focus on your bright future don't let the wrong things or people get in your way.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love ya cousin Valerie Bell Gates]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ive watched you grow into a beautiful young lady i hope everything in your future is very bright and if you ever need anything even small you know im one phone call away]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your little big sis Lexis <3]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are my first child to graduate and I am so proud of you.  You bring me joy and much success and happiness to fill your life as you take this journey.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[love always daddy ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[kekee,/RCongraluations on your graduation and may your journey be life fulfilling. I love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Auntie Mickey and family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Life isn't about finding yourself.  Life is about CREATING yourself.  Go confidently in the direction of your dreams.  LIVE the life you've imagined! /R/RLastly, It is ok NOT to know and don't be afraid to ask for help and to ask for what YOU want.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cortez and Glenda Frazier]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations to my baby girl,KeKe you've come a long way,from a lil girl into an intelligent woman.I pray you stay focused on your journey,good luck and enjoy the rest of life, you made it!!!!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Daddy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[CONGRATULATIONS my beautiful grand daughter!!!/RThis is just one step in the direction of the many accomplishments you will achieve and exceed in you journey to become your dreams...notice I said become your dreams...I am so proud of you :-)/RWish I was there...GOD BLESS/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[GDK...Grand Dad Kim...]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[KeKe,/R/RWhen the rain comes just open your "BIG YELLOW UMBRELLA".  That way you keep the rain away.  Hold it over your head and that way the drops will just SLASH and you would never even feel it.  If you don't have a "BIG YELLOW UMBRELLA" Just put on your boots and walk]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love You,  Ms. Bea ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations! You did  good and I am very proud of you. Don't never let nobody change who you are. Do what you can with what you got.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grandma Ruth]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations niece! I am very proud of you. Don't never follow what other people are doing. Always go for it to be the best that you can be.  Keep your head up. Love ya!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Daryl]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Take it day by day./RResults don't come overnight. /RChange doesn't happen immediately. /RKeep working towards your goals. /RI'm not telling you it's going to be easy. I'm telling you it's going to be worth it./RYou can do it boo!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shakia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations, Keke on accomplishing this milestone! God knows the unique plan He has for your life. Remember you can call on Jesus knowing that your help is in His name. Pray & Trust in the Lord every step of your life's journey. Much love and many blessings to you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[So Very Proud of You, Ms Pat Mosby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Keke/RRemember that things may not always go the way you'd like them to, but life has a way of taking those new directions and turning them into opportunities. It's been my pleasure getting to know your sweet & kind spirit over these last few years. Think & Achieve BIG! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat Mosby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ke I love u and so proud of you hun!!! No matter what obstacles u face during your new journey to adulthood I want/RU to always keep GOD close to your heart and always love U and be your 1st priority, I KNOW great success lies ahead for you hun!!! Congrats again!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Auntie Courtney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congrats Keke! You're a really bright girl and I know you'll go far. Just keep your head up and always remain humble and you'll make it anywhere!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Fimiji]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are amazing! Don't ever give up on yourself or your dreams. You are capable of achieving anything when you put your mind to it. I believe in you! Hold your head high, listen to those around you who love you, and never forget how strong you are! You can do it!!!!!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All my love & care Mrs. Reyes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Decisions you make today, determine the destiny you will have tomorrow. Decide thoughtfully and wisely! When things get difficult, just breath, be quiet, listen to your heartbeat and be reminded, you are still here, YOU MATTER and there is a reason for it all. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grandma Carla]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[YOU ARE LOVED!/RYOU ARE IMPORTANT!/RYOU ARE STRONGER THAN YOU KNOW!/RBE YOU, YOU ARE AMAZING!/RYOU ARE BEAUTIFUL!/RYOU ARE SPIRIT AND YOUR SPIRIT IS BEAUTIFUL! YOU ARE IMPORTANT to YOU & me! BE PROUD OF YOU!/RBecause I am. HUGS!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[That Pretty Brown Chick G-Ma Carla]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>