<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>1992-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[5/7/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Linda Akstin]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[24 Parsonage Hill Road]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Haverhill]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[MA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[01832]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDEX_FEDEX2DAY]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sand]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[We love you]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Linda Akstin]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[for SO MANY reasons...]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you are one of the strongest, most courageous women I know.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because I can tell you anything, no matter what, and you will be there for me with wonderful advice, or to simply listen.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you are my rock, my source of unconditional love.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Linda, you are very special to Us.  So many good times together... golfing, pizza at Foxboros, dining/dancing at Hibiscus.  Boating to Snooks and Keywaydin.  Look forward to more of this next year./RThanks for sharing your condo with us!  WE LOVE YOU!!!!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Judy and Frank]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Linda Akstin because she is the "Queen of Even Steven". She has six beautiful grandchildren and treats them all the same....no favorites!/RI also love her because she has offered to give my husband Roger a personal golf lesson since he has lost his touch!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barbara Akstin Hatch]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you are so much fun to be around, you always want to play games and bake with me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alyssa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because of who you are. You are kind hearted, honest and fun to be with. I know you will have me in tears laughing when I am with you or on the phone. I love being part of your life and be able to open up to you and you never judge me. I love you Linda. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your friend Margie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love you, Linda, because you are a special lady, strong and fun-loving.Looking forward to more cruising in the Donzi to lunch on the big lake and watching the sunset aboard the Winnie Belle this summer.Great times with cousins!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[We love you!  Bev and Chuck]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you are always there to help when the kids or I need anything! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah and Eric Akstin and family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you are sweet, kind and very caring. I'll never forget how you take care of me when I am sick and are always the one to stay home with me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brayden]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because I can ask you for help, just like my mom.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brayden]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you always read the best stories to me./RI love you because you always babysit me. /RAnd I love you because you always push me on the swing.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elizabeth Akstin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you Nana because you love me and you read me books. And you play with me a little bit. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gabriel Akstin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you Nana because you're a girl and you help me whenever I get hurt.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alexander Akstin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you're Nana and you always hold me and never put me down. I love you because you give me everything I want and you always play with me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Samantha Akstin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom, I love your selflessness and your compassion for others.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eric Akstin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I think I am most grateful for the hours and hours you spent working with me because of my dislexia. I wouldn't be where I am today if you didn't do that for me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eric Akstin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that you always insist that Eric and I get out for some alone time together./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah Akstin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you thoroughly cleaned my house every time I had a baby! And offered to stay with me as long as I needed your help.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah Akstin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Linda, I love that you raised Eric so well to be who he has become because I love him so much!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah Akstin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We Love you because of your Great sense of humor and how you never forgot a 'ciggie' for me in the med cabinet.....Chris and Mike]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris and Mike Akstin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Linda, you have been a special sister and friend in my life. You have always been there for me and my family. We all love you very much and cherish every minute with you!  We have enjoyed spending time with you, Jim and family. We love our holidays, dinners, cards, etc.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Angie, Ernie and family xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that, no matter the circumstance, your glass is always half full.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Linda, you are my best friend and the love of my life. You made me who I am today and I am forever grateful.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All my love, Jim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Linda, you are the most caring, loving person I know. Your love for your children and grandchildren is beautiful to watch. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are my golf partner, the one I can count on to always tell me what I am doing wrong.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love Linda because she has shown such strength and a positive attitude in such a trying time. She has been an ispiration to us.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barbara and Roger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you have made my life special.  Spending time at the cottage  especially gave me many fond memories.  You are a strong and sincere woman.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Crisi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nana, I love you because you always know what to say to make me laugh and give me good advice.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alyssa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because deep down you are a southern girl... how else would you be so good at riding a mechanical bull.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how wonderful and caring you are with my children. It means so much. Thank you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am amazed that you continue to become more and more beautiful, even as we age. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aunt Linda-You have a warm smile that lights up any room. You host and entertain an entire household year after year for Christmas Eve with ease. You can go from beer to wine to hot tea all in the same party. I love that you are a card shark and a big kid at heart!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much love -Lana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aunt Linda- I love that at Christmas of 1998 you welcomed me because I came home to Haverhill to meet Todd's family. I love the laughs with the "winning lottery" ticket and the special times with you nearly every holiday. We are so lucky to have you just up the road!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much Love- Lana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Linda.....Linda....Linda...../Rwe can all hear Uncle Jim calling you repeatedly because you would never answer him! /RCaleb and Logan often say..../RLinda....Linda...Linda!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Todd, Lana and the boys]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mrs. Akstin- I love you because not only were you a teacher for Todd, /Rbut we were lucky enough to have you 30 years later for /RCaleb. /R/RThank you for being such a giving teacher for so many many years.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much Love- Lana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how we always played a fair game of 45s with Dave and Jim; didn't we?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gale]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I Love that you kept me on the right side of the road that one night while we were out in Maine.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gale]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Most of all,  I love that we have always felt like sisters to each other.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Gale]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I loved spending time with you on Midlake St. I was there so much, people thought I came with the house!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dave]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I know you could never forget my favorite saying at the lake... THAT'S IT! I'VE HAD IT!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dave]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love that you always make us feel like family. From coming to ALL of our birthday parties, to the countless Christmas Eve celebrations and Super Bowl parties!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt & Kyle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you are always there to pick me up, no matter how down I may be feeling.  You are my favorite Winda, with a "W"ell]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember you as a sweet, quiet woman with a deep love of family. I admire, appreciate, and love your strength, courage and grace. You are a wonderful example to all of us. God Bless]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandy (Naudzun) (Fazzio) Seguin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have been my best friend for 56 years. How can that be, we are only 50? I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bertha]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have six beautiful grandchildren, you have always shared with me. I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bertha]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A perfect day is shopping with you and, five hours later, going to lunch. I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bertha]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love because you are my best friend... and my psychiatrist. You are always there for me. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bertha]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>