<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2014-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[5/9/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Lauren Murov]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[16 Crosswinds Drive]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Olivette]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[MO]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[63132]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sunshine]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Mother's Day to the best]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Mom]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love, Your Nearest and Dearest]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best thing about you is that you are my best friend in the world. You're always the first one I want to call to tell anything and everything to, and I don't know what I would do without your trusted advice and opinion. I love you and am so thankful for you!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Lauren]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kathy/Nonny, we love you. You have always treated us like your own and we are so fortunate to have you as family. You are so very special. Happy Mother's Day to an amazing mom, grandma and person. xoxox]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rachel, David, Tori and Asher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I want to wish a Happy Mother's Day to my friend, Kathy! I get to see her every Monday to play maj. Kathy always makes you feel special. I love when she tells stories about her grandkids. I love that they call her Nonny. Of course, she adores that!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda Kline]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best thing about my friend of almost 43 years is that we never run out of things to talk about! Kathy is always entertaining and engaging and fun to be with! Happy Mother's Day to a great mother and friend! Xxxooo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stephanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best thing about Kathy is....she is the best machatunim in the world!  The memories we have made together are unforgettable and we feel blessed to call you our friend as well as family!/RHappy Mother's Day!  We love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robin and Kenny]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She has always been so genuine, compassionate and amazing towards me from the first moment I met her. She is loved and adored by everyone around her. Happy Mother's Day wonderful Kathy, thank you for always being so special. Love you bunches and bunches. xoxox]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah Murov ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From playing at your cousin, Barbs, house in the fifties to playing mahj at Schnucks, you have been the best!  Love you lots.....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susie Frank]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She is one of my favorite mah jong mavens ! (Even when she is playing cry baby mah jong!) I love spending time with her. She is smart, funny, kind and sincere and I feel lucky to have her as my friend !]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carole Thaw]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best thing about Kathy is that I get to call her my sis....  I am so very blessed to have journeyed down a path that crossed with her in 1978.  Our families are truly family and we are now starting a 3rd generation of love between our grandchildren.   Love you Sis]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Judy Meyers]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best thing about Kathy is her great personality.  We have been friends a long time and shared many laughs together.  Let's keep laughing together !!!   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barbara goodkin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I think of my loving friend Kathy, I get a warm feeling in my heart.  She is definitely what my grandmother used to refer to as "a guten neshome", a good soul.  I love her dearly and am blessed to call Kathy a dear, dear friend.  Happy Mother's Day.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ilene Schnurman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It started in the Ozarks when our kids were just 5./RThe Rubins brought rain when they would arrive./RVegas, no exception, the kids ordering wine to our room./RSitting by the pool, the weather doomed!/RWe BBQ'd and swam, making tapes for the girls.../R(to be continued....)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda Gellman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[while Labona and Shlahana were at camp stringing pearls./RThe melted makeup mirror was a nice Bat Mitzvah lift. /REveryone got one; it was a special gift./RThe Steve Erkel family won best at show./RThe crazy Gellmans can sure get down low!/R(to be continued...)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda Gellman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Back to the pool enjoying our rib and spaghetti grub./RMark sure enjoyed Bob's oiled back rubs./RSam and Sadie were very observant;/Ralways looking out the window "what's arriving next door?"/RAn audi and grass cloth, always wanting more./R(to be continued...)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda Gellman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Field trips to the apple orchards, Andria's, Hermann, Pond and more./RThose were the good old days, never once a bore./RIn Hermann, we "punned" all night about feet./RAlways ending the night with a really delicious treat./R(to be continued...)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda Gellman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Don't forget about the diarrhea song/ROur grandkids will have it down pat before long./ROur grandkids are now the loves of our lives/RBasketball, soccer and now baseball wives./ROur trip to Adriana's was very delish!/RWe still eat like chazers and end up with pants pished!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love through the years, Linda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember the kindness and compassion you showed me when I was recovering from surgery-along with an amazing meal you made for me and my family. I felt loved and cared for and I thank you for that-from the bottom of my heart-xoxo Jo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I also  have to mention the amazing speech you wrote for Julie Meyers at her wedding-the time ,effort and love  you put into that speech left a lasting impression on me- ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo Jo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best thing about Kathy is that she's my chicken!!! Plus, she makes me laugh uncontrollably and knows the lyrics to every showtune song. Love you, chicken my chicken!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chicken Jr. (Samantha Halpern) ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Impossible to choose) "the best thing about Kathy" because, even though I moved from St. Louis 17 years ago, she has remained a true friend. When we talk on the phone or see each other in person, it's 1998 all over again.         /RLove you, Kitty. Happy Mother's Day. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Debby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[St. Louis U, Rhoda's wedding, NYC visit- oh, the memories. Our connection surpasses time and distance. No one can make me laugh like you can. Whenever we speak, it's as if no time has elapsed.  Continue to think of you so often and miss you always.  You're the best!! xo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Beth Rutkow]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Mother's Day girlfriend.. You give from your heart, warm and genuine, along with a great sense of humor... And you tell it like it is! These wonderful qualities make up the special   person you are. This flatter box is perfect- you deserve it!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jane G]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[how she makes everybody feel special!/RHaving said that, I ABSOLUTELY KNOW we shared a unique moment when Blake melded us together on the dance floor. Since then, CMC, I have loved you like no other. I love you to infinity. I love you even more than that!!!!!  HMD! XOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randi( otherwise known as CMC)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kathy is so smart and funny--the funniest "real" person I've ever known. The stories and impersonations are hilarious. She can nail someone perfectly in a single phrase. ("Perpetually appalled,"in my case.) She's Funniest Girl in my yearbook--no contest. Love you, Kathy]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Merlie Sue Twirlie Lou Goldlady]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Kathy, /RTommy and I always enjoy spending time with you as you are warm and witty, stylish and smart and a wonderful neighbor and friend! Enjoy a super relaxing and fun Mother's Day!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Robyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[that she has a daughter that can manage to get everyone else to help her with her Mother's Day gift. I love you both, my little and big coozins xoxoxoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[karen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sharing our new mommy experiences together!!! Such wonderful memories!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lisa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To my old, new friend. I am SO happy we reconnected. You are truly one of a kind...funny, honest, nice and always gorgeous! All my love and best wishes for a wonderful Mother's Day with your darling family./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love always, Barb Berger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[THERE ARE SO MANY WONDERFUL THINGS ABOUT MY VERY GOOD FRIEND, KATHY. SHE IS FUNNY, KIND, SMART(AS SHE'S TOLD ME MANY TIMES)AND WE "GET " EACH OTHER./RI LOVE BEING AROUND HER! WE ALWAYS ENJOY EACH OTHERS COMPANY.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[LOVE YOU,SUZY]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[...she has the best memory!! She always remembers things my kids have said when they were little!! Ex: "aunt Cathy's dollars!"/RYou always have your listening ears on and care so much about me and my family!I love you, and hope you realize how much you're appreciated! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tami Hanford]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the most wonderful friend. You are beautiful inside and out. You are a great listener and can always be trusted. We have been friends for many years and will have many more great years together. We both love you! Have a happy Mother's Day./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love always, Kim and Elliot]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kathy is one of the sweetest people I know. I've known her her whole life. Growing up as kids it was always so much fun when ever we would get together. She's been a friend and I'm so very proud to also have her as my cousin. We LOVE you Kathy! Joel & Carol]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joel & Carol Marion]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kathy is a wonderful mother and grandmother. She gives generously of her time to her children and grandchildren and in raising her children she not only gave generously of her time, but of money to see to it that they had a great education. (to be continued...)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo, Florrey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Not all moms are this way, even if they can afford to be. And she's reliving the "mothering" part of her life as a grandmother. Lucky grandchildren! I would say all the same about Mark, too. Wonderful parents and grandparents!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Florrey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best thing about Kathy is her honesty, her intelligence, her warmth and her integrity. We have been friends since "way back when" and I truly think she is a beautiful person inside and out!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lots of love, Ava Jo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I've been lucky to call you my friend for 37 years. We've laughed together, cried together and shared some of the best times of our lives together. I can always count on you to be honest, trustworthy and give me the best advice. Good health and happiness!! I love you!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bunne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When she WINS at Mah Jongg. When she doesn't win at Mah Jongg. When she talks about her Amazing Grandkids at Mah Jongg. When she gets 5 Jokers at Mah Jongg.  And the best thing about Kathy is that she is so much FUN-even when she is Not playing Mah Jongg. Happy Mom-day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marlene ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I am with Kathy I know I will always laugh. I admire her intellect and wit. Happy Mothers Day to a person with so many great qualities.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy Berk]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kathy,/R  The best thing to say about Kathy is difficult considering there are a lot of best things about Kathy. She is the most dedicated mom and grandma I know. Her kids and grandkids come FIRST!! Mark and Us friends are a pale second but that's ok! I love her!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Club Holt Group]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kath, Kit, Frickie, or whatever crazy names we have for each other. I feel so lucky that our paths crossed 35 years ago and what a beautiful friendship it has been! So many memories and journeys we have taken together! I wouldn't change one thing! Love you always!!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Club Holt Familia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best thing about Kathy is that she constantly reminds me how fun, cool and perfect I am. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Madison]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Where to begin when it comes to ASWTW... One of my favorite people to be silly with, dedodle with, be hit with by a luckshen strap. The list goes on. I love ASWTW MORE THAN MY LUGGAGE. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jay niecey ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite thing about my ASWTW is that she loves me "as if I was sprung from her loins." She's like a second mother to me. And my other favorite thing is her excellent creative writing skills. Thanks to her, I was a shoe-in to law school. I love you, ASWTW!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Doogs, Deetles, Hilaria]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>