<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2032-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[5/12/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Janie Skatell]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[2 49th Ave]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Isle of Palms]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[SC]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[29451]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[What I like about Claire....]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Claire Kruse]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[By Family and Friends]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amazingly intuitive and insightful,wise beyond her years with an exemplary education Claire will be a shining star to make a difference in the lives of others We are so proud of the woman you have become and the future that lies ahead on the journey God has prepared.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love and blessings Aunt Kathy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Claire-Bear!  I'm so proud of all that you have accomplished!  I'm also super excited for your incredibly bright future!  You're the closest thing that I have to a sister & I just love you so much!  You're so beautiful & talented!  All my love to you!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[XO-Courtney Koester Hill, cousin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Claire on your wonderful accomplishment. We are all so proud of you. Having worked with several MSWs in the non-profit world, I am fully aware of your potential opportunity to impact lives. With your compassion you will be a blessing to so many people.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Rick Hill, Uncle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Claire!! I am so impressed with what you have accomplished. You should be very proud; I know your family certainly is. I'm so excited to meet you and I adored meeting your wonderful family! Congratulations again and I wish you the best of luck! :-)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Khorrami]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that fierce determination, a keen intellect, uncanny insight, timeless wisdom and transcendent grace are all packed into the petite, beautiful, powerful package that is Claire! She is a bright light who has the passion and drive to make the world a little better.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All my love, Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Claire so proud of you! I can still remember the late nights studying and stressing over college back at Mary Street and thinking how perfect it all turned out puts a smile on my face. You will do just as great and be just as happy as you head into the next journey!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex Skatell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Way to go girl! There are many lucky people that you will work with in the future that have no idea how fortunate they will be! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Harold]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Claire Bear, I am so proud of you. It has been a pleasure watching you grow into the strong woman that you are today. You are such a bright spirit who will certainly make a positive impact in the lives of others. I am happy to call you my pookie! CONGRATS!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tory]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Time for your graceful independence to shine Claire! Graduation is a long-anticipated, hope-filled time. I'm looking forward to seeing you flourish in life's next chapter! The question isn't who is going to let you; it's who is going to stop you. Congratulations!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenna]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["All real education is the architecture of the soul."/R/RClaire, I am so proud of you! Never stop learning and never stop challenging the status quo!  Can't wait to see what life has in store for you next!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always were the best smell of the day!  Congratulations on graduating and all that, but can you bring me some bacon next time your in town?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lily]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What is a Claire? /RBeautiful, Sensitive,Loyal,Warm,Loving,and Smart. She will go far in this world I have no doubt. I am so proud to be her Grandfather./R/RPapa]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on your outstanding accomplishment!! How proud you must be for what you achieved. We are very proud and honored to call you our niece, cousin and Family! It has been a blessing to get to know the sweet, kind and humble soul you are! Wishing you the best!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Beth & Uncle Doug]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Claire is totally awesome.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Everybody]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations! Be proud of this moment as you deserve it for all of the effort and passion you invested! I know these milestones can be daunting, but you have all of the tools to be a success. I can't wait to see what you do and who you help in the future. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carrie Cowan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Claire/RWe celebrate you, an amazing accomplished woman.You are smart, talented, and beautiful-- my cup runneth over!/R            /R Granny Sue  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I love about Claire is that she is smart, talented, courageous, fierce, a great sense of humor, kind, disciplined, generous, confident, and like her mother, she is as beautiful on the inside as she is on the outside. But most of all I love that she’s my daughter]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tony ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on your well-deserved success! We're proud of you! Prayers & blessings for your future!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Jon & Aunt Debbie ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I look forward to meeting "grown-up Claire".  One of the many things I loved about you was your ability to make, nurture, and keep your friendships, in spite of the roller-coaster of life.  At a young age you just knew more than most of us. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy Thomas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Claire is one of the most kind & loving people I have ever met. I had the pleasure of being a social work intern with Claire & watching how smart & sweet she was, really inspired me. I miss you like crazy, Claire Bear! Your family is adorable for doing this. Xo-Lil Mike]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sam Moore <3]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She's pretty. She's intelligent like her dad. She's personable, and mostly she's loving.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Grandpa Kruse]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Claire is wise, kind, thoughtful, intelligent, tenacious, strong, determined, stunningly beautiful, has fantastic hair, and has a million other traits I admire and love about her, but my absolute favorite trait is her sense of humor and wit!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kristen ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sweet Claire,/RCongratulations!! I love your genuine self and contagious smile!!!  You are one smart, classy young lady and so proud to call you my niece!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Edith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She is quiet until Wham! Out lobs this strong voice with the perfect short sentence that will sum up any discussion. Claire = Clarity. Watch out world! Proud of you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Aunt Babs]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Claire, /R/RHuge congratulations on your graduation from Columbia!  That is an impressive accomplishment, and we are all so very proud of you.  You are such a blessing to our family, and we can't wait to see what you do next!  /R/RLove,/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Erin and Hugh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Claire on this amazing accomplishment! It is a privilege to know such a strong, smart, and funny young woman. Your star shines bright!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[James Hewlette]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My sibling, my Dalai Lama, you keep me grounded, grateful and remind me to love. /R/RCongrats on your graduation!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Your brother Jordan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You embody a deep wisdom and integrity I hope my children grow to emulate - you are a great role model to them & me. I am very proud of you & what you have accomplished with your educational goals.  Continue to cultivate your intellectual curiosity in the days to come.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Josh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love Claire's intelligence, her laugh and her kind, thoughtful personality.  We miss her at Spence-Chapin already!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ann Hassan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that this seemingly sweet and reserved littly lady has an unexpected spunky side. From brunch adventures to santacon antics, I have loved our time together in the big city and can't wait to see what new adventures the future holds for us!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo Alea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What a proud day Claire, we couldn't be any happier for you.   You are sweet, beautiful, you have the brains, a big heart, and now a masters diploma too?  You've really got it all!  Wherever you go, go with all your heart./RCongratulations Claire!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Cindy & Uncle Tom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Aunt Claire because she is pretty.  She loves to play puzzles with me.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ben (age 6)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love her voice.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura (age 3)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Claire, /R/RCongrats! I am so proud of your accomplishments. Your sincere friendships with everyone around you are a testament to how you are the best combo of passionate, fun-loving and kind hearted. I am grateful to have you and look forward to many years ahead!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Annie (Mase)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Claire is very intelligent, well-traveled and knows how to tell a great wine. She also has a good sense of humor because she gets our humor. Congratulations on your graduation!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lodema and Keith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Claire, /R/RCongrats on graduation!! I am so proud of you! Cheers to your bright future. /R/RMuch love, /R/RMaggie]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maggie Mallard]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Claire - Thanks for being a really weird dancer, absurdly obsessed with Katy Perry/Toast, a wizard, and a really great pal. Congrats, Grad!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paige]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I admire your strength, I am humbled by your impassioned heart, and I will forever love your vibrant spirit. Our unwavering friendship is both thoughtful and thoughtless and for that I am grateful and blessed. I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ali]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Claire literally has a joyous spirit and bounteous soul. She is so thoughtful and caring with everyone. Congratulations! Can't wait to see what's next for you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Every good wish, Des]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>