<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2047-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[5/14/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Kristin Clark]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[1436 Coleman Rd]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Franklin]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[TN]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[37064]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Your Next Adventure Starts Now]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Morgan Clark]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Know we Love you....]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Morgan:/RYou have enriched our lives so much!  We are so thankful for your friendship.  You are resourceful, smart and loyal.  We look forward to the ways God will use you for His purpose as your next chapter of life unfolds.  We love you very much!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Hardies]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Morgan: /RYou are one amazing lady! I love the courage and strength that you have shown these past few years. Each time I see you I am humbled by the grace and joy you give to all. You make me smile and am so blessed to have gotten to know you! I'll miss you!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Coach Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Well Hello Sweetie ... Just want you to know how much you are Loved!! You are like one of my own and always will be!! So proud of you and will always be there for you no matter what!! Love You!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mama Suzanne ????]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A Great Flame Follows a Small Spark-]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dante]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["May He give you the desires of your heart and make your plans succeed"./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Psalm 20:4]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love The Lord your God with all your heart and with all your soul and with all your mind and with all your strength".]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark 12:30]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[May The Lord bless you and keep you, The Lord make His face shine upon you and be gracious to you, The Lord turn His face toward you and give you peace.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Numbers 6:24-26]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always remember you are braver than you believe, Stronger than you seem and Smarter than you think...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mor-Mor You have enriched our lives"too!We thank God for sending you to us 18 years ago!You've grown into a delightful,caring,courageous,loving beautiful young lady-smart,full of grace,joy and a cheerful spirit.May God grant you His divine favor in the future. we lov u!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mimi and Poppop   God Bless you!!!!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We are looking forward to your being in Florida! Can't wait to see you enjoy lobster, the beach and family. We are excited that you will be only 20 minutes from us. We love your visits so come when you can!!!!! Love you ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mimi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You will love someone differently as time passes. If you always expect to feel the same love you felt when you first met someone, you will always be looking for new people to love. Love doesn't fade it changes as it grows. It would be boring if it didn't.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[-let the ones you love be perfectly themselves and don't twist them to fit your own image. Otherwise you love only your election in them. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The question isn't " who is going to let me"? It's who is going to stop me?-]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ayn Raid]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[-above all else, guard your heart, for everything you do flows from it...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Proverbs 4:23]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's all about falling in love with yourself and sharing that love with someone who appreciates it...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[-talent can only take you so far. It's your point of view on the world that makes a difference. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[-life can only be understood backwards,but it must be lived forward]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[-one of the happiest moments in life is when you find the courage to letngomof what you can not change-]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's as though it were by some design that you are beautiful and life seems beautiful to me because of you...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The three sisters]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Swimming is good for you, especially when your drowning...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jimmy Carr]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Success is the ability to go from one failure to another with no loss of enthusiasm]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Winston Churchill ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Be the change you wish to see in the world]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I come here to find myself, it's so easy to get lost in the world...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Colin Powell ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have three choices. Let it define you. Let it destroy you. Let it strengthen you...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One small crack doesn't mean that you are broken. It means you were put to the test and didn't fall apart....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We are the music makers and we are the dreamers of dreams...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Willie Wonka]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Why do we close our eyes when we Pray? Cry? Dream? Kiss? Because we know that the most beautiful things in life are not seen but felt by the heart. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We gain strength and courage and confidence by each experience in which we really stop to look fear in the face.../RWe must do that which we think we cannot - Eleanor Roosevelt ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Optimism is the faith that leads to achievement. Nothing can be done without hope and confidence. /R-Helen Keller]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In the depth of winter I finally learned that there was in me an invincible summer. /R Alber Camus]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always remember, Big Mama will Never leave you at the mail box :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Big Mama]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No matter how bad you think it is, we can get through it together. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You do not have to earn my love or pride and you can't loose it....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[And the day came when the risk to remain tight in a bud was more painful than the risk it took to blossom-/RAnahi's Nin]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[College is like most things in life - it's what you make it. My advice is to surround yourself with good friends and smart people! We sure love you Morgan and are excited to see where life takes you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charles and Dana Helton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When life gives you lemonade make lemons. Life will be all like whaaat???!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From babies to tots, from kids to teens, from teens to babes! What an adventure we've had, and guess what, it's not over!!!! Congratulations Morgan! You have made it through high school and off to college you go. I am so proud of you and looking forward to our future!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Destiny Elizabeth Helton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Morgan I am on happy you are going to college. It is the best thing that ever happened to me and hopefully it will be the same for you. Don't get discouraged just keep pushing on, it does get easier. Always remember to make memories with those around you. Love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Camille Wood ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you and miss you chicken booty]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[B o o b i e]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Morgan /RCongratulations on graduating. We hope you have a great time during your college experience. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nana, Jamie and Aunt Shannon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Morgan, you are a beautiful person inside and out. You have always had the confidence to be your own person. You are kind, smart and have a strong faith in God. We expect big things from you as you leave high school.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tavenner and Sean Rogers]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations sweet Morgan! We are all so proud of you and pray for your continued success in your new adventure - college!! Xo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rachel, David, and Laing]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[CONGRATULATIONS! We are so proud of you! You are an incredible person-keep sharing that beautiful smile wherever God leads you! I pray Ephesians 1:16-19 for you, and... As you therefore have received Christ Jesus the Lord, so walk in Him. /RColossians 2:6 /RWe LOVE you!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Marty, Aunt Beth, Marty, Jack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Morgan you are my amazing daughter. I'm so very proud of all you've accomplished over the years. It's an honor and a privilege to be your mom and share your story. This is only the beginning. I'm excited to see all you will do. I'll be here cheering you on. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love & blessings, Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember Your Not on Vacation - Your there to go to school!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lord said to Samuel, "Do not look on his appearance or on the height of his stature, because I have rejected him; for the Lord does not see as mortals see; they look on the outward appearance, but the Lord looks on the heart."  1 Samuel 16:7]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Hanai Tribe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on all your achievements in high school. You will do great in college. I'm so happy your my cousin. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Nicola Rogers]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am so proud of you!! You are amazing!! I have lived you from the moment you were born and I always will. You will do great in college. I will miss having you here it will not be the same. I pray for you and your health and happiness!! You are a special girl.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I love you, Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>