<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2074-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[5/20/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Ruth Hoagboon]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[3150 la costa circle #303]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Naples]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[FL]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[34105]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sand]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Class of 2015]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Simone Hoagboon]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[With Love, Mum & Dad]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have brains in your head. You have feet in your shoes. You can steer yourself in any direction you choose. You're not on your own, but you know what you know. And you are the one who'll decide where to go./RDr. Seuss/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mum, Dad & Aiden]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeremiah 29:11/RFor I know the plans I have for you,” declares the Lord, “plans to prosper you and not to harm you, plans to give you hope and a future./R/RWe love you Simone!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rachel and Rose Johnson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We were the best of friends. We still are. I couldn't ask for a better person to have always been by my side. I hope I can continue to be by your side. I love you and am so proud of you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chloe Wills]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are kind, smart, funny, a BEAUTIFUL ballerina, and you have such a wonderful personality. You make me a happier person just being in the same room as you. I hope you succeed with all of your hopes and dreams in the future! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lauren Roche]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Miss Simone,/R/RMy real world tip is to always remember to do something for YOU in every day. Take a walk. Eat the cake. Pamper yourself. You deserve it. Find something positive in your day to reflect on before you go to bed- it's never too late to turn around your day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrea Straub]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are such a beautiful dancer and person, Simone! I have always admired your independence and strong personality. Remember to always treat yourself with love and respect wherever life takes you, and I know you will succeed in whatever path you choose.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellie Schmeits]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you so much! Thank you for always being there for me. You know I will always be here for you, even if I'm up at UF. Keep dancing my beautiful ballerina and follow your dreams. I will miss seeing your beautiful face every morning. Good thing God invented FaceTime!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah Salvatori]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To my most wonderful niece Simone!!/RYou are special in many ways…but being you is the best one.  Your smile, your enthusiasm for life, your sweetness to your family and friends... are priceless. You are loved so very much.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Kim and Uncle John]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Life is sometimes difficult. Keep smiling and pray- during the good times & the bad!/R/RCongratulations on the first of many remarkable achievements.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Helen Thornburg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Simone-- you might not remember a lot of my mom and I but we sure remember you. We both used to discuss the future you would have, and the impact you might bring to the world. Well, here is your chance. Congratulations and good luck! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Waiting for Impact ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Simone-- you might not remember alot of my mom and me but we sure remember you. We both used to discuss the future you would have, and the impact you might bring to the world. Well, here is your chance. Congratulations and good luck!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much Love: Carrie and Pat]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congrats to my MO! You are an amazing dancer, a beautiful person and, a smart cougar! I look up to you in every step you take! You will achieve many great things because of who you are! Simone Hoagboom, you are the reason why I love to see you in ballet class! Love you?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jade Brouet]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You know what has made us the happiest we've ever been?  Seeing our granddaughter graduate from college. More than wanting her to be educated, we wanted her to be a nice person.  To see that she has become both is just a wonderful thing.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[love from Grandma and granddad ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We are suppose to share "One tip for navigating the real world.." and truth is idk, I am in the same boat you are! But there is one thing i do know, that you are a strong and talented person who will do great things in the world. Congratulations and much love from Omaha]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Dworak]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Simone!!! I can't believe you're graduating!! Jeezums!! You're amazing! Brilliant! Outstanding! I'm so incredibly happy that we became friends! Good luck in all your post highschool endeavors! You will be absolutely stunning. Truly. I love you so much Simone! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Helen :) ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Simone/RReach for the stars, follow your dreams, work hard and you can accomplish anything. All the best for your future.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Miss Helen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Simone, /RYou are unique. Please keep it that way. Many young ladies lose that thing that makes them different and special in these next few years. Never settle, never stop working for what you want and what makes you happy. Remember, you have more than one start in life]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ashley Wilson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Protect your commitment/Rto God and to His Church./RWhen you inevitably stumble--when you fall, when you fail and doubt and don't know what to do--a faith family full of grace, love, acceptance, and prayer can guide you through all of the darkness to the light of Christ.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dan Durrenberger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To my beautiful niece Simone!/RYou are an amazing young woman and we are blessed to have you in our family. My one tip for the real world is from Proverbs 3:5,6.  Trust God. When you don't know what to do, look to Him and He will always help guide you in life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you!  Aunt Kim and Uncle John]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a very strong and wonderful woman! Always remember this when it feels like things are not going your way. There is no stopping you from moving mountains!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meghan Adair]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Simone, /R/RI'll never forget the amazing memories we shared as children, especially not Halloween!! I wish you all of my luck in your future and know that life will bring you amazing things. /RFrom your loving friend always ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hana ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy graduation, Simone! /RAll of your OAB friends miss you dearly. Good luck on your next adventure, and congratulations on graduating! Love from Omaha. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grace Safranek]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Mo! Make sure to keep your sass, confidence, and kind heart throughout college. I'll always be here to cheer you on. I love you so much.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Olivia Straub]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Simone, we are so excited for you and proud of all your accomplishments. We miss your family here in Omaha!!  Be grateful for something everyday. Look for the silver lining in every cloud! Congrats! Have fun! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shaneyfelts ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Living on Devon Drive, you were my favorite kid in the neighborhood!  You were raised right: thoughtful, caring, outgoing, and friendly.  You have grown into a talented, beautiful, and successful adult.  Keep it up - can't wait to read about your future accomplishments!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Erika Sykes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[All things are possible if you believe.  Mark 9:23]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jonathan and Sybil Burt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Fortune favors the bold.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jonathan and Sybil Burt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Think left and think right and think low and think high. Oh the thinks you can think up if only you try!"  Dr. Seuss/R/RI think you'll take the world by storm!  Good luck in your new and wonderful chapter in life! /RGrab your ballet slippers/Rand rock the dance world!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Congrats Simone!    Lauren Reidy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["A good name is to be more desired than great wealth." Proverbs 22:1]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jill Fieger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congrats Mo for graduating! I am so happy I don't have to say goodbye, because we still get to dance together!! I am so glad that you moved down to Florida and you have made my life so much brighter.... and not to mention crazier! You have a bright future ahead of you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linds]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Simone, I remember when you danced on stage with me for my very first time when I was 3 years old at Papillion Days. You were always supportive and nice to me at dance. Congrats on your graduation!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Savannah Ingold]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Opportunity dances with those who are already on the dance floor!"/RWe are very proud of you, Simone! We KNOW you will do very well!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, The Ingold family!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hello Mo i cant believe you are already graduating especially one year early!/RYou have been such a nice sister to me so i decided its time to give back by doing this. Love you momo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your brother, Aiden]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Simone, I know I've known you for a small amount of time but it's no difference,  I already know that you will achieve your goal 100% , I can tell how committed you are to dance, and how easy it flows in you, no matter what you will achieve what you set your mind to do.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenny]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Do not stand to the side and allow the music in your heart fade and die.  Dance to your own life's song now and forever and follow your dreams to where they take you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ms. Sheila & Sarah Nelson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Starve the turkeys. Feed the Eagles. /RThere will always a lot of things vying for Your attention. Things that make a lot of noise for no reason should be ignored. Focus on what is silent but soars mightily. Keep your dreams and aspirations with the Eagles./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heather Burt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Simone,/R/RPlease always bring your smile and positivity to every obstacle you encounter in life. Always keep that fire to succeed in your heart, and the twinkle of courage in your eyes. Your life is brightly lit for you to dance upon; enjoy your show!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julia Betts]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[With Love and Best Wishes for your future]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Norman, Lisa, Paul & family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Simone your are the most determined person I know don't let anyone dull your fire. Life is short break the rules, forgive quickly, love truly, laugh uncontrollably, and NEVER regret anything that made you smile.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Samantha Simmons]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Simone. Never stop asking questions. Do what makes you happy and don't let the haters bring you down. Remember this is the part where you find out who you are!:)  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tangyne and Mark]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Simone! You must be so happy to finally be out of high school! You should probably thank Google, Wikipedia and who ever invented Copy and Paste!;) Good luck at university!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kayleigh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[For that fun loving, happy, caring little girl who has grown into a beautiful, confident, driven young woman!! Congrats!/R/RWe love you!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cyndi Tucker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always be the strong, confident woman you are today! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sue Garry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Simone, we have loved watching you grow, even though we do so from afar... /RAs you graduate be true to yourself, be the person you want to be and reach for the stars!/RSending you lots of love and blessings all the way from London ~!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rachael, Gus, Miles & Jamie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My little Mo. You've brought so much joy into our lives. I am so proud of you and everything that you have accomplished. All my love,/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congrats on your graduation!!! It seems impossible that you're already grown up! Dream big, take chances, and (most importantly) enjoy the journey!! You will do GREAT things, Mo! Miss you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah Kors]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dance is art,/RPaint your dream /Rand follow it...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bella ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From climbing the fence, to arguing in dance, to building snowforts, and thinking we were the coolest when our parents let us drink monsters in the summer, I have so many great childhood memories with you! Best of luck next year and wherever life takes you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Krissy ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aidan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's cool to see that you are graduating early, and you will certainly be great at your next endeavor. What ever that ends up being, you will be the new kid. A couple reminders from a current freshman; classes without friends are boring, and making friends is easy! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lydia Borelli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Simone...you were my first "Marie granddaughter!" I treasure the moments of being your "OMA!" What wonderful memories for me. You ALWAYS had a smile on your face. Then again we were cast in Children of Eden!"  What a blessing you are to work with. Continued.......]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wendy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ So professional, so mature, so precious you are to me! Congratulations on graduating. I wish you all the best for a bright, happy future filled with laughter, love and JOY!! You will always hold a special place in my heart! All my love, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wendy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Enjoy the little things in life for one day you'll look back and realize those were the big things/R/RSave the pennies and the pounds will look after themselves]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mum after Grandma & Great Grandma]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ People are often unreasonable, irrational, and self-centered.  Forgive them anyway./R If you are kind, people may accuse you of selfish, ulterior motives.  Be kind anyway. If you are successful, you will win some unfaithful friends -continued...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mum after Mother Teresa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[and some genuine enemies.  Succeed anyway.              If you are honest and sincere people may deceive you.  Be honest and sincere anyway./R What you spend years creating, others could destroy overnight.  Create anyway./RContinued....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mum after Mother Teresa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[  If you find serenity and happiness, some may be jealous.  Be happy anyway. The good you do today, will often be forgotten.  Do good anyway./R Give the best you have, and it will never be enough.  Give your best anyway./R/R         ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mum after Mother Teresa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Give the best you have, and it will never be enough.  Give your best anyway./R/R         In the final analysis, it is between you and God.  It was never between you and them anyway.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mum after Mother Teresa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My Lovely Simone,/R You are a beautiful person inside and out and I am so proud and honoured that I get to be your Mum./RYou have a wonderful adventure ahead of you. Enjoy the journey and remember you  can always call day or night if you need ANYTHING!!!!/RLove you,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mum]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Simone,/RI have always admired your kind spirit and love of learning.  I remember your bright smile and positive attitude!  I know you will go far in life and do wonderful things to inspire others!  Keep dreaming and never give up!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lori Arnold (First Grade Teacher)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Congratulations!!! It was such a joy to work with you, and hopefully we will get to work together again soon! Follow your dreams, and you will always be on the right path./R   Much Love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stephanie & Gudelia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Simone,/R/RWe are so proud of you! We always knew that you had so much determination in you, never let that diminish! Keep pushing and better things are still to come! :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Straub Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We can't believe it's time for you to graduate!! Know that college is such a big transition in your life- so take the time to enjoy every little experience along the way. We are always here supporting you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Trevor Ford & Andrea Straub]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations!  I am so Proud of you!  I am so excited to see what your future holds!  Enjoy every minute!  Follow your Dreams! Take Chances! Xoxo Miss Dawn]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dawn-Marie O'Donnell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations!  I am so Proud of you!  I am so excited to see what your future holds!  Enjoy every minute!  Follow your Dreams! Take Chances! Xoxo Miss Dawn]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dawn-Marie O'Donnell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am so proud of you Simone. Quite an ACCOMPLISHMENT!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>