<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2108-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[5/24/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Katie Maier]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[350 Wood Drive]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Blue Bell]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19422]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Teaching is a Special Gift]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Nancy Chancler]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Thank you for sharing it with us!]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like that you paint on the easel with me and help me paint chickies. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ally Maier (3 Day 2015)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for making our girls' first experience at school a great one!!  You foster such a warm, nurturing and caring environment.  Tessa and Ally flourished because of your influence.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Katie and Mike Maier]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From the first time we met Nancy, we knew our children were in good hands! Her calm and nurturing manner made them trust her and enjoy school. Thank you Nancy for working so hard to make Pete and Charlie's first school experience so wonderful! Enjoy retirement! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Egginton Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You made it easy to leave my kids at school for the first time.  You made my childrens' first experience with school a FUN one.  We will always remembers you with love.  THANK YOU, NANCY! XOXO, The Curci Family (Joe 2011-2013, Veronica 2013-2015)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nancy...you were the first teacher for both Ella and Maisie and we thank you for building the foundation for their love of learning and especially their love of art! You are the best! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Hayes family ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have given our children a priceless gift - your love and nurturing ways have laid the foundation for a bright future for both Rhys and Zoe. Thank you for giving them a safe place to learn and thrive. We wish you all the best in your retirement, we will miss you!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Esibill Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We liked painting with nana. We also loved seeing the chicks. We always loved to visit her classroom and meet her kids. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kiki and Brendan Feeney ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love how patient and kind you are Nancy. We love that you see each child and their gifts, and that you put all parental concerns at ease with your gentle humor and incredible long view. We are so grateful that all four of our kids have been lucky enough to have you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Oliver, Kiernan, Tadhg & Merin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being James' very first teacher! The patience, kindness and love that you showed him was incredible. I've felt so lucky to be able to come to you for guidance and advice since I joined the staff at Ches Pres. You are an inspiration!  Happy retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo Megan McGowan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My mom is like a parenting self help book a phone call away. How lucky are the children and families that have passed through her classrooms. And how lucky are her grandchildren who experience her love, patience, creativity and humor each day. Congratulations Nana!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Partridge Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our class will miss you/RFancy Nancy/Rand I will miss your warmth, kindness and our daily interactions./RYou are an excellent teacher but now it's time to enjoy this next step./RHappy Retirement]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ann Smullen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are not only a great teacher to your students but also to everyone around you. You always give such thoughtful advice and put effort and creativity into everything you do. You live your life with such kindness, confidence, and grace. You are an example to all!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amy Koller]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nancy,/RI cannot thank you enough for the wonderful six years I have worked with you. You teach in such a unique way that I am proud when I say, "I learned this from Nancy." The tools that you taught me have helped me become a better teacher, and I thank you for that. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Ann ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To a Loving, Caring,Creative, Soft Spoken, Dedicated teacher and friend, /RMay you have a wonderful time exploring things on your new journey in life./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[God Bless and love, Kathleen XOXO]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We wish we had you as a teacher. But we are lucky to have you as a grandmother. We love reading books with you and doing art projects. Ellie will sketch the dunes this summer. Happy Retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellie, Connor and Mack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom, watching you follow your passion and find absolute joy in working with children inspired me to become a teacher, and I can't thank you enough for that.  Your dedication to teaching and to your students is admirable.  I'm so lucky to have such an amazing role model.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[love, dana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nana, you always share the best books with us.  Your love of reading and great books is contagious, and this is a lifelong gift that we will cherish forever.  We can't wait to read with you this summer!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, William, Finley, and Tucker ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["I love it when Nancy smiles at me! I like her hugs, too. And the caterpillar song. And the song about shoes. And sitting on the rug on letter R for Ruby!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ruby Shelley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We were so thrilled to see Nancy's genuine care for all the children in her classroom, and we were grateful to her for welcoming our entire family into the preschool fun! Happy retirement--it's well deserved! Blessings!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Shelley Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No one could find a better daughter, sister, wife, mother, grandmother and teacher than you. You give your heart and soul to everything you do. You have blessed my life in so many ways and I am forever grateful for all the love, support, guidance and laughter.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Maureen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Asking myself "what would Nan do" is great way to gauge the right course of action. Thank you for being a role model for common sense, integrity, and poise. I also really appreciate how you and my mom made art, music, and culture such a big part of our lives. Thank you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Adrienne Ludwig]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your ability to help me be grounded has been priceless. You are optimistic but realistic. Thank you for your love and support through the years.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Sharon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I was four years old, you taught me lessons from your first grade class. When I got to first grade, I knew it all and I still know it all. What a great preschool teacher then and now! You are a treasure.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love,  Your Genius Sister Barbara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nan, thanks for always being there when advice or comfort is needed. Enjoy your retirement and your grandkids. I hope you find a way to paint chickies. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Nanner,/RI can't believe the time has come for you to retire!  Congratulations and good luck on this new part of your life.  Thanks for being the first teacher my kids ever knew, a mentor, confidant and friend.  You have enriched the lives of all you have touched.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love You Tons, Michelle Kelly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nancy:/RYou taught my son Beau, my daughter Mia and my other son Peter ... I have the fondest memories of your gentle way with the kids ... because of you - their first encouter with "school" was a very positive one ... thank you for your gift to them! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mara Humphreys]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nancy was so calm, kind and wise.  If the 2-3 yr old was feeling shy or overwhelmed, she knew to give them time, patience and soft-spoken support.  A new mom would always feel comfortable leaving her child(ren). A wonderful, inspiring lady!!  We love her!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Baughan family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love way too many things about Nancy to list them all!  Nancy is kind, loving, generous, calm, patient, positive, gentle, caring, and curious, just to name a few qualities.  We're so grateful Nancy had a part in Siena and Lorenzo's time at ChesPres. She'll be missed!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Bedard Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your calm, caring way really helped Virginia (and us) get off to a great start at pre-school. Her time in your class could not have been any better and she continues to treasure her "Mondays with Nancy" this year. Thank you for all you have done. You will be missed!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Spellman Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nancy, you were the first person I left Griffin, Gunnar and Marnie with 3 days a week. Your kindness, warmth and nurturing way was always so comforting. Unflappable in the face of a roomful of 2 and year olds, you are Grace personified! Congratulations, Nancy!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Everhart-Feist Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Nancy, Thank you so much for your part in making Eliza the wonderful young woman she is becoming. Your kindness and nurture during our first separation helped teach us both how important her independence is, and we could never have wished for a better safety net. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Daphne & Eliza Dennis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on your retirement, Nancy!  We were so lucky to have you as Elizabeth's and Christopher's first teacher -- you were so kind, patient and calm with them (and with us!). We have the art they created with you hanging in our home -- think of you so fondly!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Dolich Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nancy,/RYour calm demeanor was perfect for Avery. I loved hearing small details of her day from you. It was a confirmation of how wonderful you are and how well you got to know her. You will be very missed! Thank you for everything! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Emily and Wade Vandegrift]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for your hours and days of love and endless patience with my four little cherubs.  Such fond memories we have throughout the years in your classroom.  We couldn't have dreamed up a better teacher and first classroom for each of our little guys! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chip and Amanda Roman and family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nancy was always a calming presence and shared her wisdom and patience with all of her children. We wish you the very best!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The DeCaro Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We are THRILLED to know we can still find you at McNallys on Thursday evenings!  Thank you for making our first school experience so wonderful.  Mollie, Claire and Cece are lucky girls.  xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meg & Ted Durkin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your love and commitment to your profession has been an invaluable inspiration in my life. The wisdom that you have imparted goes well beyond the classroom and will last with us all forever. We are all truly lucky to have learned from you. Congratulations Mom! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Chris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nancy, there are many things that we could put to words but your amazing patience with all of the children you've taught coupled with your calm demeanor always made the kids in your class feel safe.  Best of Luck as you enter this new chapter in your life!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hope, Jim, Henry & Maggie Morrissey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love her nurturing and warm personality. We value her creative art activities that allowed for exploration and self-expression. Thank you so much for giving Sienna and Xavier an amazing "first school" experience. We feel lucky to have had Nancy and wish her the best!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Faith Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nancy, you were Lucy, Molly and Henry's first teacher.  They all continue to adore school now (finishing grades 4, 2 and K) and I think it is in large part due to the fact that you made their first schooling experience so special.  Thank you so much.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Becca & Josh Budde ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you Nancy for being Jasper McIlvain's first teacher. He grew up so much in your care and truly loved being in your class. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Crocker/McIlvain Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nancy, your classroom was such a wonderful first school experience for Sophie and our family! She made fantastic friends she still sees, and has only wonderful memories of her time with you at Ches Pres! Best wishes,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sophie, Bob & Emily Mercier]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congrats on your retirement! My kids always loved going to Nana's school. Your dedication to making every child's 1st school experience a memorable one will truly be missed.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Beth Feeney ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thomas loves when his name is called to do Art with Nancy:-) Thank you for all you have done to help our children grow and learn! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The McKernan's (Thomas)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/RWhen Nan told me she was going to retire I had a Uh-oh moment. Since my own retirement in 2013 I have had a pretty good life. Looks like this is about to change. Welcome to my world Nan.  Just don’t bug me. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nancy really understands early childhood development. She knows how to create the perfect environment for young children. I'm so glad she was part of Evan's first school experience. He loved playing, creating, and learning in Nancy's classroom. Thank you!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chloe, Rick, & Evan Mohr]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nancy, We feel so lucky to have had you as Brendan's 1st teacher!  You took a shy little boy and transformed him into a confident student who loves going to school.  We are so grateful for all you did for him this year.  Enjoy your retirement & know you will be missed!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Clark Family (Brendan, 14'-15')]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nancy, you have always been a great role model and mentor. You were never too busy to listen and offer encouragement. You inspire me!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat Dennis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You made sending Bryn to preschool so much easier for this first time mom. You were kind and loving, creative and understanding. I am so glad Keira was able to enjoy this last year with you. We will miss you!/R/RWith love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chelsea, Paul, Bryn & Keira]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nancy,/RThank you for your patience and kindness. Our boys have been very lucky to have had such a special teacher! It has been a pleasure to get know you. We wish you all the best in the years to come (and plan to see you at school subbing all the time!) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Piatkowskis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for making Bennett's first school experience so wonderful. He has enjoyed "reading truck books and singing" with you! A smile is never far from his face when we ask him about school. A true gift from a caring, compassionate teacher!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Novasack Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your grace and charm has won over Jack and Abigail.  Whenever we ask where they learnt something, we always get told 'from Nancy and Anne'.  We are delighted that you have been in our twins formative years of life and thank you for your generosity!/R-Our Love]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike, Jess, Jack and Abigail]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>