<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2121-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[5/26/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Delvin Dinkins]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[1001 Plumly Road]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[West Chester]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19382]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol, I have enjoyed your warmth, generosity and kindness. Your daily bulletin was your smile and quiet laughter.  I was happy to read it. EA will not be the same without you.  You gave all of yourself to this place. Thanks for painting the stripes again and again.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Delvin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It is hard to say whether it is Carol's warmth and genuine caring, evident to all who walk into the office, or her complete unflappability that made her such a keystone in the upper school office.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peace, Greta]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You set the standards high and worked with unparalleled ethics always serving the community and never thinking of yourself.  Nobody knows the school better than you. Without you we will be rudderless. Your signature smile and grace under pressure will be remembered.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lee Billmyer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Carol:/RYou taught me to be nice to everybody even under stressful circumstances in our hectic daily routine. You stop your work, listen, smile, and help me! Your wonderful spirit will forever be present in the office! I will miss you dearly, and I am happy for you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mireya Yaros & Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol welcoming me with a smile.  Every. Day.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tony Herman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[1) Her amazing generosity. You ask for something and she's on her feet immediately looking through cabinets or closets to find the thing you need; 2) Her warm sense of humor. You can joke with Carol and her whole face lights up with pleasure and just a hint of mischief.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Doug Parsons]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol T has been the best colleague anyone could ever have! A positive and capable professional, she made EA a great place to work! I will miss her caring spirit, her eagerness to be helpful and her great sense of humor! Carol T is one of a kind!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gina Buggy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I loved your cheery demeanor every time I stepped into the office. I'm going to miss you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Annemarie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol, /RYour patience, sense of humor, and knowledge of EA traditions will never be matched again!  We will miss you, but hope to see you often!  Enjoy retirement and more time with your family!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Anna McDermott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It is not only what she has done for all of us over the years, it is also the way that she has done it.  She has been a pure joy for all of us to be with her.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Squre]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol thanks so much for so many years of kindness, warmth and understanding.  Your  kind and wise words for all of us harried teachers bring calm in the midst of chaos.  /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Helena Cochrane]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for always having a smile and being willing to listen and help us with whatever we needed.  We will miss you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grace]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Any existing superlative at my disposal to describe Carol would not even be close to give her the credit she deserves. She's the lone unsung hero without whom EA would not be EA. There can only be one Carol Tassoni and I was fortunate enough to have known her. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marc Eripret]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You'll be sorely missed Carol! I'm still trying to imagine an Upper School without you. It's not possible. Please make sure you come back and visit us often. Enjoy your much-deserved time with family and friends!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A true "Pro from Dover" who knows all the traditions, stories and fun facts of EA./R Plus she makes the best Pizzelles in the world!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anne Ravreby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol,/RThank you for always smiling and providing guidance in my first years at EA! You will be missed!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alyson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol,/RI can't thank you enough for all of your help and support.  Your calm and loving presence will be greatly missed.  Enjoy every minute of your retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leslie Trimble]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mrs. Tassoni (because that is who you'll always be to me), my life won't be as full next year when I come to school and find you've gone.  You have been a source of comfort, joy, and laughter, as well as a model of the kind of educator and woman I aspire to become.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With love, Sarah Baker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol,/R/RIt's been wonderful learning from you, seeing your smile, and watching for the gleam in your eye when you shared a bit of your wisdom./R/RBest wishes for your next adventures.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom Goebeler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol,/RHow different it will be next year without you!  I will miss your endless patience, your vast knowledge of all things Episcopal (and more), and mostly I will miss laughing with you!  We will miss you every day.  Have fun every day!  Love, Susan]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan Swanson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol, you are truly one of the kindest and most professional people I have ever worked with.  Your warmth and wisdom will be missed!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Anderson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol, I appreciated your warm welcome, not just on my first days, but every day as I asked my usual million questions.  Your smile and laugh are absolutely infectious.  I hope your next journey is filled with the joy and happiness you've brought us at EA.  All my best!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cyndy Crum]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol/R/RI am going to miss you always being there when I need to ...talk, get something done, find something,remember something- you name it!!! You are a wonderful friend and I am going to feel a void every time I walk in the office. You will be missed!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cheryl McLaucchlan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're unflappable. You're friendly. And you've got a great sense of humor. How will we cope without you? /R/RYou know...you don't have to worry about that anymore. /R/RCongratulations!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt Lake]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol, /RThank you for all your help these past 8 years I've been at EA. Your warmth and personality always made a trip to the US office worthwhile. I will miss your genuine kindness and your great laugh next year! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Angela Miklavcic]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A stalwart of the Upper school, Carol will be SO VERY MUCH MISSED!  It's going to be hard to think of Upper School without her.  She's the epitome of efficiency and organization - and a warm, caring, colleague.  A ready laugh and great sense of humor; the perfect combo!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lynne Hay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What a treat it has been to work with Carol Tassoni for the last 33 years. She is always positive, always has a smile and, certainly, a great sense of humor. Many have said that she really runs the Upper School and no one knows more about how things get done. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All the best, Andy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol, you are without a doubt the go to person in the Upper School. In your quiet, confident and  unassuming manner you set a standard of excellence without much fuss. To  me, you  will always be a "Dear and honored mother"./R/RWith love and affection,/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hank Albrycht]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol-/RYou're naughty laugh and irrepressible sense of humor will be missed as much as your knowledge of all things EA and the warmth with which you make each one of us feel special. Have fun and stay in touch. Love, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tracie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What a gift to have you, Carol, as the the face of the US Office! You are warm, funny, in the know and beyond helpful. We will miss you dearly but how lucky your family will be to have you full time. That will be a joy. Thanks for your endless devotion. You are loved!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Holly Johnston]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol was always friendly and happy to help out however she could. You'll be greatly missed, Carol! Congratulations on your retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Kerwin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We are family! We never had a conversation that didn't end with laughter. Thank you making each day special and full of warmth.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Sigel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Other than the constant smile, there can be no single way to define the enjoyment of working with Carol.  Her dedication to the school, students, faculty, and staff is evident in the number of people who remember her just as fondly as she remembers them.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sam Willis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Carol/RYou have always been there for me and all of us. Thanks for running the upper school show for as long a s I can remember!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Perry Zanki]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Carol,/R/RIt's been a true pleasure working with you these past two years.  It isn't always easy coming to a new place, but you made me feel welcome with your warm smile and thoughtfulness (like keeping me safe from those blue chairs!!) I will miss you!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Fondly,   Nicole (Chaikin)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol, you had a way of making people feel comfortable. Your ability to make people feel like they are part of a community is a gift. You will be missed tremendously next year]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelly Edwards]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol is always calm and cool, even when things are hectic. The students and faculty can always count her peaceful demeanor. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ No matter how busy she is (and she is always very busy) she manages to stop everything she is doing to help you with your problem or answer your question. Carol, you will be missed tremendously.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom Kossuth]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I love most about Carol is her ready smile and sharp wit. That I get to start my weekdays with both of these makes me incredibly lucky. /RYou are so loved here, Carol. We will miss you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen Maier]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your smile and warm personality always made it a treat to go into the office! You will be missed. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrew Shimrock]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What will we do without you? That's what I want to know! Your sense of humor, your unwavering smile, your knowledge of everything EA, your kindness .... /RI will miss YOU!!!!/RMuch love, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christele]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I loved your welcoming demeanor when I started working at EA last year. Also, your constant smile made me feel welcome always. Have the best retirement ever, and keep smiling]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cristina]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol, in my first days at EA, I was looking for very specific hanging files that would fit into the boxes that I had bought. You gave me your own folders and you did it with a smile on your face, even though I was taking up your time. Thank you for your patience!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christy Rheam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To pick one thing is impossible, but the myriad unseen and unknown things you did for us every day, with a smile and glint in your eye that said "it is all going to be OK" helped me stay positive through the years.  Your dedication to our coffee also helped!  Thank you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rob "That Old Black Magic" Maier]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol,/R/RThanks for all the laughs, knowledge, and warmth whenever I went into the US office. /RYou are wonderful!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Dilworth]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your calm in the face of any situation has helped me to stay calm--and your sense of humor has always reminded me that I feel better if I laugh. I am going to miss your steadying presence so very much.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anne Barr]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have been the rock of our school since I have been here.  It is always a pleasure to come down to the office to see your smiling face and have a laugh.  You will be missed by all!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Tanuja]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Hi Carol,/R  EA has been enriched by you. You have always been there for us with a smile and a helping hand. I will miss you!! but enjoy your earned retirement./R    ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan Rubin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol,/RWe have loved you for a long time!  Thank you for all that you have done, particularly getting Richard through Upper School! LOVE YOU!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Aldridges]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>