<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2123-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[5/27/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Lori Huegel]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[18181 SW Shady Meadow Court]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Beaverton ]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[OR]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[97007]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Yay! Madison Class of 2015!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Madison Huegel]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love, Mom & Dad]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To my beautiful daughter who has so much potential and heart. I wish you the very best on your graduation day and beyond! I am so proud of you :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[MADDY I LOVE YOU SO MUCH! Every time I am with you it's constant laughter, you are so bright and fun to be around! I hope you have an awesome time in college and I will miss you tons! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Genevieve ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maddy, you always put me in positive spirits when I am in your presence and I love being around you. You are also an amazing supporter and listener. Thank you for being you! I can't wait to see what the bright future has in store for you. I love you!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Monica David]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I cannot believe how far our friendship has come! We've gone from Girl Scout acquaintances to amazing friends! Your friendship means a ton to me, & I couldn't begin to thank you for simply being there! Good luck in every thing you do in the future, you deserve the world]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Clarice Gilray]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Madison,/RCollege is what you make of it. I am positive that someone both as funny and as smart as you are will have no problem making your college experience awesome. Proud to have you as a sister!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jacob]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To my beautiful niece,/R/RThe world is yours to harvest./RPick the sweetest fruit!/RGet a basket full!/RLive each day as if the sun was on your face!/R/RLove ya and good luck.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Duke]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are my best friend ever! It's scary to think about going to a different school. I remember crying when we were in a different class in 1st grade. You mean so much to me! Thank you for being a sister I never had. I love you so much! I never want to lose you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elsie Elling ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Madison,/RI am so proud of the wonderful person you have grown into, from that little girl who spent time with Grandpa and me.  Those are the times I will always treasure.  I love you and wish you nothing but the best in the future.   Much Love,  Grandma]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grandma Kathy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[                 congratulations on you graduation !/R/R                        we know you will succeed /R                           at whatever you try  !/R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[with love, Duke, Deb, Sam, & Ben]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I cannot believe you're grown up enough to graduate already! /R/RI think about all of you ladies all the time. My fridge is covered in pictures of the team!/R/RI'm really proud of you. I know you will be successful with whatever you choose to do./RCongratulations!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[(Coach) Alexa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maddy, you have been one of my favorite people ever since I joined leadership. You always have been and always will be a great friend who can always make me laugh. No matter what we're doing, we have fun. I'm going to miss you so much next year, it won't be the same.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christian Cancilla]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maddy! Im so glad we became friends back in middle school! Youre so funny and fun to be around! We had the greatest times in french class, you always made me laugh! Youre always there to make me feel better when im down and im so greatful to have you in my life!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[erynn friend]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Madison.  It has been a pleasure to see you grow over the years. Best of luck to you as you are off to college.  Congratulations in your growth, hard work and getting through the hectic years of High School .  Keep your head up and great job!!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ Rochelle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maddie,/RIt has been such an honor to be a part of your life.  You have grown into a remarkable young lady.  your future will be full of surprises and challenges, tackle them head on and enjoy the experiences.  Let yourself SHINE!/RLove, Tiffany ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany quincy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To my best friend,/RFor all the years that I have known you, you have always been there for me. You have taken care of me a lot and I love you for that. I hope for the best in your future!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chubby (a.k.a poopsy)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Madison,/RI just wanted to let you that you can say, "No sing Grandma",any time you feel like it.  That and playing dentist are two of my favorite memories of you growing up.  /R  Love, Grandma]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grandma Kathy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maddy,/RDuring gymnastics you were my inspiration and I always wanted to be like you. Although Claire was my best friend you were always secretly my favorite:) I love you and I really hope you love graduating!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grace Irving]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Girl. I love you so much. You are so much fun, and I'm really glad we have become better friends. Your love for fun and laughter will set you on MANY incredible adventures and I'm confident we still have some of our own to go on. College will be hecka fun for you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Isaiah Rosales]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations! I remember how I felt after graduation: a little sad that high school was over but, overall, excited for the future. You're going to enjoy college so much--I can already tell. Don't be afraid to reach out if you have any questions or want to chat!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Caleb]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My Dear Maddy, /RYou work hard, feel deeply, care endlessly, give lovingly. I so value you & appreciate the time & care you put into all that you do & into me.  Go out there and make it better!  Say what you need & express how you feel! I love you & will always be here!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much Love, Mrs. L]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Awesome, Bubbly, Confident & Strong!  That's you, Maddy!  I know you will take the world by storm!  Congratulations on your Graduation!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lots of Love, Kim Braun]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're spunky and kind. Always laughing, what goes on in your mind? ;) You're super cool, funny, and sweet. Without you, our girl scout group would be incomplete.  I'm going to miss you next year in College. Don't spend too much time filling your head with knowledge!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sannah ps. Congrats, Maddy! :D]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's been great getting to know you since middle school Maddy! It's a lot of fun hanging out with you and the squad, and doing random stuff. There are lots of laughs and memories I will never forget and I'm excited to see what the future holds! /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex Goringe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I’m so proud of your accomplishments: Graduating High School, Attending OSU, The State Gymnastics Title, and Doing things you Love. You’re Bright, Intelligent, Passionate, Driven, Independent, & Beautiful.  I’m blessed to have you as my daughter!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Madison,/R/RCongratulations on your graduation from high school. Wishing you all the very best in your future endevors!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark E Holmes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wishing you well as you enter an exciting time of your life.  I know you will continue to enjoy.  College will  fullfill your lifes wishes.  Very proud of you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grandma Carole]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Best of luck as you go through this transition to the next phase of your life.  Keep your head up, keep a smile on your face, keep giving your all. "Anything that gets your blood racing is probably worth doing."/R- Hunter S. Thompson-]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Seth Smart]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Madison - you've grown into such a lovely person.  I can't wait to see what comes next!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bonnie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always enjoyed having you come and help with the class parties in my classroom.  I can hardly believe that you are old enough to graduate.  Best of luck in all you do!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brad Silva]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're the biggest pain in my a$$ I have ever had. And I wouldn't trade you for anything in this world. I am so thankful to have such an amazing friend like you in my life. With everything you do I know you'll do amazing no matter what. I love you Madison so so so much]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rachel ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Maddie! Graduation is a big milestone on the road of your future success! We know you will be successful in life because you have already accomplished so much and you have a beautiful mind and heart, and the strong spirit to achieve all your future goals]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[love from the Shatalov family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's hard to believe that you are already graduating.  It seemed like yesterday that you were in second grade.  You have blossomed into a beautiful young lady.  Wishing you the very best!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ms. Shirley Ralston, 2nd gr teacher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maddy, remember to find time to laugh.  Laugh at things, laugh at others, but especially laugh at yourself. Life isn't nearly as serious as others will have you believe.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[V]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Madison - From a girl to a young lady seems like overnight. You have a whole life and a whole world out there. You have plans and goals and 2 excellent parents to help guide you. While they may not always be right they will always be there for you! Good luck for future.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Phyllis Naish and Philip McManus]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sweet, sweet Madison, from first grade to today you always have been such a bright and beautiful girl. Congratulations on your graduation! I know you will continue to amaze us all. I am so happy and proud to have been (and still be) a part of your journey!  Go BEAVS!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo, Cara Byrum (AKA Ms. Rennie)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Madison! I feel like it was yesterday that you were crawling around my apartment! You have grown into such a wonderful, beautiful woman! I am proud to be a part of your life! We love you like family and can't wait to celebrate with you! Go Beavers! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Audrie & family ??]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Maddy! It has been wonderful to watch you grow into such an intelligent, hard working and loving young woman. I know those same characteristics will bring you success in anything you do. I wish you the best of luck on your next adventure!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kellie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I was lucky enough to be your soccer coach when you were young. I knew then how special you were - you were a bright, happy, kind girl - a joy to be around. I wish you much happiness on your next adventure at OSU.  Learn lots and have fun! Congratulations!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[(Coach) Ali Nichelson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Maddy. I will miss our near death rides to Jamba Juice. Thanks for being the big sister I never had. And always remember, Beeta go up, up! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Natalie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations to our beautiful Madison!  You have grown up into an exceptional young lady./R"Oh, the Places You'll Go!" (Dr. Seuss).  Your future is so bright with new adventures; reach for the stars and live your life to the fullest.  We are very proud of you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With joy & love, Amy & Derek]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I know it can be difficult growing up with older siblings, but never forget that you are much nicer and funnier than your brothers!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Patronus, Vince Kirnak]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[GO BEAVS!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>