<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2128-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[5/27/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Cindy Cairns]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[79966 Memorial Place]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[La Quinta]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[CA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[92253]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Words from those who love you]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Madeline Cairns]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Your Family and Friends]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[\You must live in the present, launch yourself on every wave, find your eternity in each moment. Fools stand on their islands of opportunities and look toward another land. There is no other land; there is no other life but this. -- Thoreau ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Live your best life...Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maddie, I would wish you the best of luck in college but you don't need it. Anywhere you go, success will follow and I can't thank you enough for your friendship and support.  Try to remember that nothing is really over until the moment we stop trying.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frida Escatell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maddie,/RIt has been so fun   watching you grow up. You are an incredible young woman. I know your Mom and Dad are so very proud of you. /R The road ahead of you holds ups and downs. Remember that, "Life is what YOU make it".  Make yours amazing! /RCongrats! We love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kendell and Kloe Kline]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congrats Madeline!!! You have reached an incredible milestone in your life. My best advise for you as you begin a new chapter is to never stop reaching for your dreams! Never let anyone bring you down! And trust what God has given you and never loose faith in Him!!!!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your cousin Krystle ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[While I am still amazed at how fast time flies, it is very true. Take time to enjoy life. At the same time, work hard, whether it is for school or your job. It will make life easier for you in the future! So proud of you. I am amazed at the person you have grown into!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael Cairns]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As you graduate from high school, Grandma and I are so very proud of all you have accomplished./R"Sending you a day full of sunshine, a heaven filled with rainbows, and a pocket full of dreams. May the future ahead of you be as wonderful as you are"./RMay God bless you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grandpa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maddie,/RYou will always have a special place in my heart and I will love you always./RJoshua 1:9/RBe strong and of good courage; dio not be afraid, nor be dismayed, for the Lord God is with you wherever yo go.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grandpa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[“So many of our dreams at first seems impossible, then they seem improbable, and then, when we summon the will, they soon become inevitable.”/R- Christopher Reeve]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Mark & Aunt Cyndi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are beautiful inside and out, don't ever let anyone make you think otherwise. We are so excited to see where you take yourself in life and the wonderful things you will accomplish! We love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Mark & Aunt Cyndi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sweet Mattie!  My wisdom  don't get caught up in the drama of life.  Treat people the way you want to be treated.  Be honest to yourself and others.  Be the best you can be.  My Motto  "If you fall get up and walk it off"  Life gives us bumps but deal somehow.  love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Barbara Genier]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Life's not the breaths you take, but the moments that take your breath away." -George Strait/R /RI hope you experience a lifetime of breathtaking moments.Thank you for being such an amazing and supportive friend! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Rom-Toribio]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Maddie! You did it! Your graduation proves all of your hard work & determination paid off. We knew you could do it, and we're proud of you. Continue to learn and never stop questioning. Remember, educated people are hot!  Because they have more degrees.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Best wishes.Guncles, Carl & Barry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maddie,/RBlessed to have been friends/neighbors with such an amazing girl for 14 years. Good luck at NAU and beyond! You have a bright future ahead of you :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rachel Garcia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Treat others the way you would want to be treated. Remember life is not a dress rehearsal so be the best you can be now. Don't settle for less than what you want or feel you're worth. You're beautiful and deserve the world! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bonnie ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Maddie,  congratulations on your graduation from high school.  Aunt Lynn and I are very proud of you.  You are a very special young lady.  All your hard work and commitment to getting good grades has paid off for you.  We love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm so proud of you Maddie! You've come far! Your a bright girl with great views and I'm happy to call you a good friend. I'm hoping that in 10 years I'll see you living by a lake in the forest judging people from a distance with your lumberjack husband. Live your dream]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jacob Whitney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maddie,/RYou have grown up way too fast. I am very proud of the person you have become. You have a very bright future and I believe there is nothing that you can't accomplish if you put your mind to it. /RI love you so very much and feel blessed that you are my daughter.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[“How far you go in life depends on your being tender with the young, compassionate with the aged, sympathetic with the striving and tolerant of the weak and the strong. Because someday in life you will have been all of these.” /RG.W.Carver/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's not you aptitude, but your attitude that determines your altitude. -Zig Ziglar/R/RThis has been one of my favorites since I was in high school!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The greater part of our happiness or misery depends upon our disposition, and not upon our circumstances. -  Martha Washington]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In spite of illness, in spite even of the archenemy sorrow, one can remain alive long past the usual date of disintegration if one is unafraid of change, insatiable in intellectual curiosity, interested in big things, and happy in small ways. - Edith Wharton/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[One of my favorites! Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mads, I'm just so proud of who you have become. You're an INCREDIBLE young woman and human being. I'm thankful and blessed to be your mom. I'm so excited for your future and what you will bring to our world. Look ahead with an open mind and enjoy every step of the way.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you forever...Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["If you live to be a hundred, I want to live to be a hundred minus one day so I never have to live without you." -A.A. Milne (Winnie the Pooh)/RMaddie, I am so happy and blessed to have met you. You are more than my best friend, you are the sister I chose. I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Katie Oliver, best friend]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["What do you call the... The fuu-fuu, the fuuu-fuu, the..."/R"The thumb?"/R"Yeah that!"/R-Maddie Cairns & Katie Oliver/RI'll always be there for you, from helping solve problems to remembering what body parts are called. I know you'll do great in college! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Katie Oliver, best friend]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Take weird classes, read illuminating poetry, drink water, question social norms, speak up, learn about ancient and obscure cultures; and Maddie, always remember: have courage and be kind.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lizzy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We knew you were going to be a success as soon as we met you! Beautiful smart and such a lady! We loved watching you grow into a beautiful woman and so proud of the person you have become. Enjoy all that life has to offer and be open to all the possibilities. We love u]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cortez Family ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you and I will miss you happy graduation. You should be a sciencetest love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Cooper]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maddie, I am so proud of you! It has been my pleasure to watch you grow.  You are an intelligent, sensible and sensitive gem. You will always do well and make good decisions for yourself. Remember a life with gratitude will bring much happiness and reward.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Congrats! Love you Maddie-  YO]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey bro, alright no chick flick moments but here we go. I guess that I did look up to you most of my life but who wouldn't. You are an amazing person. Dont be clouded by the small things in life. You are bright, so shine. Oh and make sure you hang your towel up mate.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Best Sister, After You]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ok not going to lie I'm quite the jokester but in all honesty, I love you. I hope one day I can call my big sister and tell her a joke and still be able to make you laugh. Keep dreaming and don't limit yourself. Love you always sis.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dabbers]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congrats Maddie! I'm so glad I met you and that we've been friends for over a decade. You're an amazing person and I know you will go far over at NAU! I wish you the best of luck in college and beyond! Love you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Miranda T]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mads, We're graduating! It's so unbelievable, I'm going to miss you so much! You're going to do such amazing things with your life. I will always be here beside you, can't get rid of me that easy. Best friends forever, love you Maddie!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nadia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>