<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2129-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[5/27/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Lara Mathews]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[3618 Oval Drive]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Alexandria]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[VA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[22305]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Rock Man turns 50!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Dan Mathews]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Happy Birthday!  Love, Lara]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like about Dan is he looks good on TV when his boss testifies to a committee or to a Congress person. Actually I only saw Dan once on TV. But he looked great. I live in Los Angeles where how you look is very important. Dan looked important,which means he is.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Gerry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We wish you a wonderful birthday, and hope that the celebrations continue for at least another 50 years! Thanks for the happiness you bring to your family and friends, and for your tireless sense of adventure. We hope to celebrate in person soon. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carrie, Mike and the gang]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 50th Birthday, Dan!/RTwelve years ago you played a huge role in helping me celebrate my 50th birthday by providing your climbing expertise to help me and a few friends get to the summit of Grand Teton.  I will always cherish that wonderful experience.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dave Preister]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always so calm and unflappable in the midst of all the chaos that comes along with having kids (and their friends, like Karinna) around.  Admire your keeping up with your outdoor adventures - what a great role model for your girls!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Papke Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey Buddy--Happy 50! You're not old, just more mature now! NO, I won't entice you with a Jay Kim or Rules job (and you still befriend me!)--maybe another hike, a beer and some catching up though.  Happy Birthday!  Cheers, Matt ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt Reynolds]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my backcountry, climbing, and paddling buddy -- looking forward to many more adventures!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrew Shoemaker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Of Dan's many exemplary qualities, one of the best is his passion for the outdoors and ability to share that passion with family and friends. Thanks, Dan, for helping keep us connected to the natural world, whether through climbing, skiing, or backpacking! Happy 50th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jonathan Bemis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We wish you all the best as you celebrate/Rthis significant birthday. We always enjoy spending time with you in Maine and look forward to our family gatherings! You are a great sport having narrated and participated in your children's productions./RHave a great 50th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Avi and Ellen, your mishpachah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Fifty is the new thirty! May you have many more years climbing, skiing and surfing ahead! Also do not forget the Limbo! We wish you good health and joy always!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Lois and Dave]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like about you is your enthusiasm for everything. I remember driving all night and all the next day packed like sardines in your VW Bug to Yosemite. When we finally got there, you decided that we were going climbing on Cookie Cliff right away. Happy 50th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Keegan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are one of my favorite kids so it is hard to believe you are fifty./R/RI always remember your wedding and your grin./R/RHappy Birthday kid. And may you grin all the rest of your life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Flip]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Dan! To a great Nephew and a great Dad. A guy who is living, learning, and passing it on! The Family is lucky to have you, providing balance in a rapidly changing world!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barry Bernstein]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He crafts our nation's laws yet gracefully fits into the same tux he wore as a 22-year-old. He dangles from the side of a sheer cliff, but ventures on easier backcountry trails with his wonderful family. His balance, sincerity, health and joie-de-vivre amaze.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Hermens - Finks family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dan's a real trooper, game for anything even when "anything" means taking a group of 4th graders camping. A great guy, and there's no better companion for the mountains whether winter or summer. Of course, in winter, his 80's snowboard attracts a lot of attention.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Stankos]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 50th birthday Dan!  May your day be filled with love and laughter.  We have shared much laughter, a few tears, and excitement.  Bubba ate all the cookies, but I can't see the runway!  There was a bear outside the tent last night!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[We love you, Mom and Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for adding joy and a few white hairs!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[We love you!  Mom and Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Oh my sweet Danny.  I can't believe that you're turning 50.  Seems like just yesterday I was chasing my little peeping Tom out of the bathroom.  Life is precious so enjoy every minute and may the next 50 years be as good to you as the first.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, Lynn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dan, /R/RYou are a great dad and husband. Congrats on reaching this milestone ... I have to say I'm very relieved since I've already seen your blood pressure rise when you see boys around your beautiful daughters!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laurie & Jeff]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hope your next 50 years are as great as your first! And that we can do more family reunions, visits, etc. We love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Kristen and Darby ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Although I have many happy memories of my "little" brother, I remember most fondly, exploring the woods around Cranberry Lake National Park on Whidbey Island. We would eat wild berries, climb up rock outcroppings, and wander the forest looking for our "secret meadows." ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Donald Stephen Mathews]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Dan is his smile. He puts a person at ease. He comes across as quite calm, and he's definitely friendly, easy to talk to, but his smile is the best. And his family. They're top of the list too! Happy 50th Dan! It only gets better from here :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Santucci Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Katie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dad, you are always understanding and patient with me no matter what and I love that you have introduced me to the love of backpacking, river rafting, and much more. I hope you have the best 50th birthday ever!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I love you, Katie:)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We so enjoy your company, Dan. We've witnessed your love for your family, have had wonderful, intelligent conversations, and have learned many outdoor things from you. Let's plan another kayaking trip soon with the girls. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Denise and Bill]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Dan!/RYou are a wonderful, caring, patient Dad. Here's to a great year ahead! I wish you joy and good health!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Lois]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 50th birthday Daddy!  I always love all of our adventures together, whether it is hiking, backpacking or climbing. For your 60th, lets try to make it up Half Dome!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I love you! Alex]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[FIFTY/R/RF antastic father/RI ntensely intelligent/RF abulously fit/RT ireless traveler and teacher/RY oung at heart (& body, mind, spirit...)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you! Lara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always appreciated your friendly inclusiveness and intellect. You & your friends made me feel I belonged in D.C. I recall our heady discussions watching fireworks on The Mall in 1992, lunches at a deli (Gandel's?) with Tom James, & drinking in Georgetown. Good times.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dan Jett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[By no measure do you "seem" fifty! You have packed much into these years and have shared so much joy, love, and adventure with many (most of all the girls and me). Thank you many times over for that and more. Here's to more adventures than you can count in the next 50!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I love you so much, Lara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 50th birthday! /RMuch joy to you and your family in the years ahead.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dan Jett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Danny Boy! Where has the time gone? It seems only yesterday I was changing your poopy diapers. Here you are, 50 years old. May you have many more wonderful years. You deserve the best! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lots of love, Aunt Mandy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Uncle Danny,/RI've had many times where when I think of where I had happiness in my life, one of my first immediate thoughts is lying on the rock on the Dolly Sods mountain trip we took together and when you and Aunt Lara took me to see Flubber as a child...(continued)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much love, DJ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Memories will be with me for a lifetime and wish we could have many more.  But most importantly I wish you a very very very happy 50th birthday and extend my love to you and the family!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much love, DJ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Frogue]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I know Dan from the climbing gym. He's a very experienced and safety oriented climber.  (continued)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dave Berman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Two of the things I admire most about Dan are, especially with respect to outdoor climbing, he is both skilled and patient at explaining and demonstrating efficient, and more importantly, safe climbing techniques.  /R/RHappy birthday Dan!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dave Berman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>