<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2136-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[5/28/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Vicki Lustig]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[132 E Delaware Pl]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[Apt 5906]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Chicago]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[IL]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[60611]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[scarlet]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Paul We Love U]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Paul Lustig's 65th birthday]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Your Wife who loves you forever!]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paulie,/RI am so happy to be your wife of 30 years, the mother of your children, your friend and lover.  You are the best husband, father and friend.  I love you and our life together.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vicki]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul is one if the best storytellers I have ever met./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarinda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The one thing I like about Paul the most is how he gets away with his outrageously inappropriate humor.  Friendship is about happiness and laughter and I've laughed the most with one of my very closest friends, Paul.  Happy birthday, Pauly.  Many more trips coming...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Wight]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When Paul become a part of our large family he had not had that kind of experience over the years he has become a very important member of the family and with his 65th birthday as the father and grandpa great grandpa I appoint Paul the leader of the family's next genera]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Walton family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Warm hearted, clever whitted, take no prisoner sense of humour, his anecdotes unprintable and unrepeatable, except by the great man himself. With much love]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Richard and Kate Harmel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul and I are twins that were separated at birth./RBruce Merrick]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[quick and irreverent mind]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul is a great brother-in-law and I am grateful for all his love and support through the years.  I especially like his sense of adventure and travel tips that has saved me lots of time through security and customs.  I thank him each time I go through. He rocks!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Terri]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of our favorite memories is coming to visit you in Chicago for the first time.  We had so much fun experiencing all different restaurants and blues clubs.  We will never forget that darling little french restaurant where we had our first sip of Plum wine. XOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Trevor and Meghan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The thing I like most about Paul is that he is a true friend./RSomeone you can always count on, who will always listen, make you laugh, think of you first, make you look like a good golfer, challenge your thinking without judging, and enhance any experience you share in.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Malcolm Lotzof]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It has to be about that VERY dry sense of humour!/RMy favourite example was Paul explaining why he didn't need much luggage because he was able to wear the same pair of underpants for 4 straight days and why!/RHappy Birthday Paul!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[James Fitzgerald]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I've had the privilege of meeting Paul at the gym thru Vickie. I've always wondered who her tall dark and handsome husband was until finally training day came & we met face 2 face. Well my face 2 his chest. Paul is kind, a world traveler, intelligent & patient. Amazing!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul makes me laugh. He is great at relating some life episode and then proceeds to make hilarious commentary about it. A great gift. I never know when its coming, but always entertaining. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Len Siegal]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/RHi there, We love you paul. You have eth coolest sense of humour, you negociate the slopes of France by bike or on foot with such grace, and your wife is a serious plus!!! With much love and best wishes, Doug and Cassie]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Doug and Cassie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[May you be blessed with health and happiness and many more birthdays. We look forward to future times together.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Doug and cassie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Brilliant, hysterically funny, awareness of life, sensitive. That's what I'm talkin' bout,  F#ckin' A, Who's your Mama, Hit Me! ....Control my friends?  I can't even control my bowels!                                           Honored to be your little buddy.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian Y]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[With you as my friend life is immeasurably richer.  Thank you for your insight, your honesty and most of all your humor.  Happy Birthday Paul!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Kreis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Make way for VIP!!!!/R/RHappy Birthday Paul!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Kreis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Growing up my favorite thing about Paul was the stories he told. It didn't matter what the story was he always had a funny engaging way of telling it. Lots of laughs always seemed to follow. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenn Drayer ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Happy 65th to one of the funniest storytellers of our age!/R/RStill laugh out loud when I think of the John Teets stories! Hilarious!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gian Fulgoni]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul is always upbeat and funny as hell.  Super smart, great guy, and great friend. It is very cool how he and Vickie are traveling the world.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike and Linda Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul, At 65 your 2nd life begins enjoy it with great vigor. You married Vicki, gave us Kelly, & Kevin, & Sady. Thank you  We love you Grandma & grandpa Walton]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Paul,/RSo many great experiences with you! My first taste of plumb wine, Cabo Wabo, and many great dinners. I hope you have an amazing 65th birthday and I can't wait to create many more amazing memories with you and Vicki!/RHappy Birthday!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Trevor Wilde]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Like the most .... serious when needed, jovial at parties, entertaining when least expected. What more do we need in a friend. Always made the cycling trips memorable.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Margaret Fourie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Humour !! thats what i most love about Paul - he is sharp, dry, witty, all given with a poker face, and very, very funny.  happy 65th Paul - in good health - keep on walking!/Rlove Alan and Silvana]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Silvana & Alan Silverman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 65th Birthday Paul! I have loved your hilarious stories and hope you will keep them coming for many years.  Have a wonderful birthday celebration!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen McCoy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Have I told you yet how much you mean to me?/RHave I told you yet about all the happiness you bring to me?/RHave I told you yet that you mean the world to me?/RJust in case I haven't I want you to know YOU are the best thing that has ever happened to me. /RI Love You/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vicki]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Dad! It is hard to put into words how much gratitude, love and respect I have for you. Thank you for everything you have done for me and I am so thankful to be closer to you and the family in Chicago. I am lucky to call  you my father. Love you Dad!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite memories is around Indian Princesses. It is not being in the wilderness with you or destroying all the other girls and dads in any soccer competition. It is every time on the way home you turning into six flags. I loved spending those days with you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I like most about Paul is his outrageous sense of humor (how does he come up with these things and then get away with it!), as well as his desire and ability to get to the heart of the matter on any topic of conversation. A joy to be with! Happy Birthday Paul!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob Buford]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Memories/RPlane rides with you as the pilot, you putting your fingers in the flame of the candle, ER room that first night, Kelly asleep on your chest, you holding Kevin's hand as you walked through Disneyworld, our family dinners, how you can always make me laugh. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vicki]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will never forget watching some of the bigger sports moments in my life with you.  It has always been something we have bonded on and I truly enjoy it watching them with you.  The Craig Krenzel throw against Purdue comes to mind first.  Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin Lustig]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love your sense of travel.  You are someone who naturally interested in cultures and find that being out of your element brings a sense of adventurer for you.  I hope I get to embody and enjoy that same sense as well throughout my life.  Love you and  Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin Lustig]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul is the funniest! His recitation to night in hot tub followed by emergency room, to his "cat swallowed canary" smile when E and I took vineyard lunch pictures with him, and finally to James and Margs' after dinner toast to Jeff and Leslie who finally got it right!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stacy and Geoff Harris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul,  You are one of the greatest story tellers I've ever met! Witty,charming and kind! Hope you will be entertaining us with your antics for a long time! Happy Birthday!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have always enjoyed your dry sense of humor and quick wit.   Best wishes for a fabulous 65th birthday!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Valerie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Da, da, dada, da, da, da ,dada, We're on vacation /Rbut we call it work!"/R So many great times and memories. Thanks for your friendship (and mentorship) over all these years./RHappy Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael Falcon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Paul!/R/RSo many great meals and memories together over the years.... From Paris to Winston-Salem to Sydney.  Looking for many more celebrations together over the years to come./R/RWith our love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan and Michael Falcon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What we love the most about you is your quiet, subtle sense of humor shared discretely in appropriate moments./REven if some of the fine establishments around the world don't seem to have an appreciation./RWe are now banned for life, as a result. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eszter and Mark]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am not sure how a perfectly square box is able to contain your multifaceted personality./RThanks for the great stories, fun travels and delightful dinner conversations./RExpecting many more!/RHappy 65th Birthday!/R/RPS: You are (one of) a kind person]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eszter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>