<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2140-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[5/28/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Taylor Barton]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[758 North Larrabee]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[522]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Chicago]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[IL]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[60654]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[scarlet]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Barbara & Jeff]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Barbara & Jeff Kutchin's 40th Anniversary]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Friends and Family]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember our fun club mystery dinner when Jeff and Don sat at our table with fake guns in their laps and had to shoot an actress in the script, funny night!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jolee and Don Kooperman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 40th! Quite a milestone! Thank you for dating each other all these years! You make a beautiful love story -- and haven't aged one bit! Love you tons!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Taryn (aka: button/poonhead)...]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Where do I begin I've known you both for over 40!years .. OMG !! Lots of stories weve shared .. Especially the one most recent in Colorado with kutch at the hospital and YOU and me BaRB in the condo ... Wink wink .. Have another wonderful 40 years !!! Love u both!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susie and cake Kaufmann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I would like to congratulate you on your 40th Anniversary! You are role models of the gift and beauty of enduring love. The bond between you is visible to the eye. Happy Annuversary!!! I love you both, Kathy Mayer]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy Mayer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are so many memory's I have...the birth of your three wonderful children.....so many family dinners...special celebrations...trips to Wisconsin,but most of all I remember your wedding and thinking what a beautiful bride and groom you were...40 yrs & still the same]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy 40th&lots more, Nancy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Barbara and Jeff are such a beautiful fun loving couple.  Wishing them at least anther 40 years.  Happy Anniversary!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Cindy and Israel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on your 40th! What a wonderful  journey you are taking together and what a beautiful extended family you have become. We are lucky to call you our very dear friends and cherish our friendship with you. We wish you many many more years together....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob and Lisa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[....The gemstone Ruby represents a traditional 40th. It symbolizes warmth, a strong sense of vitality and is know for its luster and rarity. It is also considered a PRECIOUS stone. All of these attributes represent each of you separately and as a team-together....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lisa and Bob]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Barb & Jeff - To a stunningly beautiful couple, congratulations on your 40th! Wishing you another 40! Much love, Diane/Rp.s. Jeff, i still feel bad about breaking "the poor people of paris."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To a most beautful couple....inside and out...you still are the Barbie and ken doll couple!/RHappy, happy anniversary/RMuch love, hugs and kisses]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jackie sabath]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We wouldn't know how to bring in the New Year without Barbara and Jeff!/RThanks for 40 years + of wonderful memories!!  Happy, Happy Anniversary!!/RWe love you..]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bonnie & Jeff]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The many celebrations at your house...Details are perfect & food is delicious, but it's the gossip & laughter shared in the foyer that stand out most. Usually just the girls, sometimes the guys & once Aunt Barbara teaching the family Taekwondo!!! We love you!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brittany, Gabe, Maison & Rafi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember when Taryn, Taylor, and Zach were born. I can picture sitting in the hospital and Jeff coming out to tell us the sex of each child. In 40 years you both have brought me, 2 nieces, a nephew, their spouses and children. I love having your  family in my life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Lesley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's incredible that 40 years ago I was on your honeymoon with you guys. You marriage has lasted and you have a beautiful family. Here is to 40 more. Ricky ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ricky merel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As we just celebrated our 30th anniversary, we realize that you have been part of our lives for almost all of it. The minute we moved onto Burr Oaks we became good friends and the rest is history.   We love you and wish you 40 more and hope to be a part of that too.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Sherry & Michael]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our special memory we have was when the Kutchin family joined us in St. Maarten  for the Winter Holidays.  Great family dinners, going to the beaches and of course a fun New Years Eve./RYou are a beautiful couple  and are so blessed to have a loving family and friends.xo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael and Bonnie Friedlen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy anniversary!  May your /Rlife continue to be filled with/Rlove, health and laughter./RWe have so memories together.  We are lucky to have both of you as our best friends. We love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jackie and Fuzzy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Barbara: a class act, strong, independent, upbeat, fiercely loyal. Jeff: a teddy bear, kind, generous, charming, wickedly funny. Together you make ONE stellar couple, full of vitality with an abiding respect for one another. I feel blessed to learn from your example. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[with abundant love, vicki]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 40th Anniversary to the BEST parents in the world! You are also the cutest couple! Your solid marriage has been one of the greatest lessons you could ever teach me. I love you so much! Love, Taylor]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tay Tay, Peanut, Cupcake]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There is not one special moment…all are special!!  We love our time together..hot political discussions, Kutch's inappropriate behavior(which we love), Bab's spiritual lessons  and of course fashion sense..Always tons of laughter.  We are so grateful to have you both ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[We love you Laurie & Marty]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marty has an interesting story concerning Daddy Kutch in Colorado. We were at Twinkle's home & I had to go to the bathroom. I left my cellphone unattended and when I came back, Kutch had sent extremely inappropriate texts to my wife & his. Years later and still laughing]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marty & Laurie Goldberg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will always remember the warmth that you both have showed me when I came into the family.  Then, I got to know Uncle Jeff better and he reminds me so much of my dad.  That connection will always be there!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brooke Palmer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Keepn it short n tweet*:/RMzl Tv! Damhik, but fsho it was lafs 4 u 2. O/y! Lots of hwms. Hdydi? Lmaowtntpm. Lulas, Brb. U r my bfam, Ktch. Yolo so lltnt./RNjoy #40 b/c 2moz, it's sosdd. Don't n2n yapa to say lylafklc. Bcnul8r./R*Sgbadq-knowledge of internet slang required]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[F4eaa!  H+K, BA]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary to the COOLEST in-laws on the planet! /RLove--dougy]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sharing just one memory is impossible. Gracious and generous friends always giving more than they take./RBarbara sharing life wisdom, design expertise and, like Kutch, incomparable kindness./RKutchy patiently managing the golf games of dozens of neurotic children!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kerry n Kris Glicken and family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Barbara and Jeff, our most favorite memory is "the country"  Keeping the fire going, pac man and the donkey game noise,  eating, chess, girls dancing, backgammon, one channel, little house, big house, casino, back room,- Love, Family, Memories. /RTHE COUNTRY]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Zallik Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Barbara & Jeff,/RIt was our luck we went to detox at a spa called la Costa some 33 years ago! We met  this dashing couple we so wanted to make our friends. /RHappy 40th dear friends!! We love you & wish you another 40]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Terri & Steve Chetek & Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[All The fun times up at the country house and Aunt Barbara getting up real late coming down and Uncle Jeff already at the little house doing stuff or at the movies with Zak at the movies.  One time he went fishing at the little house. Those days were fun.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jamie Pallant]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To Barbara (Babs) and Kutch,/RYou two are one of the most special couples that Ron and I have the pleasure of calling  good friends. The love and respect that you have for one another is so evident. Your love has endured the test of time. You "get each other." Much love!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love and happiness, "the Twink's"]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When Barbara first brought Jeff to our house on Lawndale Street my mom said to me, “She’s going to marry him.  I just know it !”   I knew it too. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robbie and Penny]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Family vacations to Puerto Rico were my favorite!   We always had the most fun. Happy Anniversary Aunt Barbara and Uncle Jeff! XOXOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our friendship spans over four decades. We've watched our children mature from babies to beautiful adults with families of their own. Here's to another four decades of health, happiness and fond memories together. Much Love to you Barbara and Jeff.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ethel and Joel Handler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulation's to Barbara & Jeff on your 40th Anniversary. What a beautiful couple you are with a very beautiful family. I will always remember our trip to colorado this year what a great and very fun time we all had together. We LOVE you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Effie and David ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There isn't just one memory that is special. Every memory is special because of the obvious love you both have for each other. Also, you are both super gorgeous and fantastic to look at so that is fun. You are a lovely, warm, funny, Republican couple.. Love you so much.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carin and David]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Barb and Jeff:/RWe first met the adorable Kutchins in the city and as luck would have it we found them again in the suburbs. We have shared so many wonderful occasions, trips, weddings etc.. You are a wonderful devoted couple with a flair for life! Happy 40th]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, Debbie and Joe Feldman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Still the coolest couple I know, and the best parents anyone can ask for. Love you guys so much.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Zach]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary Grandma Babs and Kutchy! You are the best grandparents in the world! We love you soooooooo much!! Hugs and Kisses!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Zev, Shay, & Weston]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wishing you a very happy 40th anniversary! I have so many wonderful memories with you both -- Puerto Rico vacations, family dinners, college graduations, and weekends in Wisconsin.  Here's to 40 more years and creating many more special memories!! I love you!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Nikki (& Noah & Reese too)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Barbara and Jeff,/RWe wish you a wonderful anniversary- filled with much love and laughter. We are blessed to have you in our lives and cherish your friendship! Looking forward to sharing many more good times in the future!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Debbie and Michael]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Babs & Kutchy,/RUr love is true, not distorted. Thank u for teaching me patience, acceptance, & how not to react in various situations- lessons I'll take w/ me through my own journey of marriage. Clearly ur biggest accomplishment in 40 yrs is Tay, so I thank u for that!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Josh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So I remember meeting you two in Las Vegas, New Year's Eve, 1974!  I didn't even know you then Barb, but while waiting for you lovebirds, night after night, I quickly learned that our days of Early Bird seatings were a thing of the past.  Happy Anniversary!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Susan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There have been so many memories that/Rthey wouldn't all fit on this page. Jeff's favorite is when Barbara bought Kutch the Porsche. Mine is all the time we have spent together laughing. We love you and wish you /Rlove, health and happiness for many more years./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff and Jackie Levin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations! We wish you health, happiness, and love forever. We love you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maureen & Joe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>