<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2149-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/1/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Stefanie Kuhnhausen]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[125 Wilkie Drive]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Walnut Creek]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[CA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[94598]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[   All about Miss Lahl]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Our third grade teacher, Miss Amy Lahl]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[3rd Grade students & families 2015]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how you work so hard for the Lord and I love how you just get things done and don't complain very much!  You have been inspirational to me and I know to Juicie!  Love you Amy.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stefanie Kuhnhausen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you, Ms, Lahl, for all of the love and kindness you have given our children this year. I know Blake has benefited greatly from your guidance and you have challenged him to be a better student, and most importantly, a better person.  We are so grateful for you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Melissah Misquitta]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Ms. Lahl,/R/RThank you for being so nice and thoughtful and for helping me to be a smart student.  I hope you have a great summer! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Blake ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Miss Lahl, /RI have enjoyed your 3rd Grade Class. Thank you for encouraging me in Science. Also, for inspiring me to be more creative in my writing assignments.  What I enjoyed the most, was listening to music while working. Thank you very much. I will miss you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tatiana Avdienko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you, Amy, for fostering the little Scientist. Years from now, when she is on her voyage to Mars, you can say, "I fanned the flame and she loved my 3rd Grade Class!" Enjoy your Summer, and be full with the knowledge that you impacted the lives of children. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Monique Avdienko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She makes her lessons fun!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mariah McCoy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Her positive attitude and loving personality. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The McCoy Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for picking me to be in your class. Thank you for being an awesome teacher. I had a good time in your class and I learned a lot. Have the best summer. Go Giants!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dominic Seeno]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She always gives you a second chance]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Fran]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Miss Lahl, you have been a very good teacher and a very good person. Helping the students to discover what they are capable of, challenging and encouraging them in everything they do. Thank you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Angelina Aguilar]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ms. Lahl is caring, loving and fun! She has been such an incredible mentor and teacher for Wyatt. We will miss her.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rich and Leah Abreau]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite thing is Ms. Lahl is patient and gives me lots of time.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wyatt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Miss Lahl because she is a hard worker and a spectacular teacher! She also is a great helper. She is sweet, generous, fantastic, wonderful, and awesome!! I love Miss Lahl!!! XOXO!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julia Kuhnhausen ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like Miss Lahl because she is fun.  She brings crayfish and snails to class and lets us enjoy watching them!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Yaelin Hough]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Miss Lahl, thank you for helping Yaelin make her transition back to the US effortless.  She couldn't have had such a wonderful year without you.  Thank you for your hard work!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Hough family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Miss Lahl is the best teacher ever! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ryan Reilly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank You Miss Lahl for all your support with Ryan. He has really injoyed being in your class.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shannon & Paul Reilly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amy Lahl, may you be filled with power from the Holy Spirit to know how wide and long and high and deep Jesus’ love is for you.  May you recognize that God made you just as you are: unique, set apart, and created for good works.  xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stefanie Kuhnhausen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amy you have been such a blessing to our whole family. To let us work next to you helping the girls get to where they are today is an amazing sight. Your heart is truly in the right place, we will miss you./RHave a wonderful time in Europe this summer!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jens and Penny Erickson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Miss Lahl you are awesome in every way!/RYou are kind and loving. I will miss you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matilda Erickson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Miss Lahl you are the best teacher I have ever had. You really care about your students. I hope you have a fun summer!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kajsa Erickson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amy,/ROne thing I appreciate about you is the creativity that you bring to the third grade program at NCA. When teaching fourth graders about line, rays and line segments, they knew the definitions because of your chant. /RThanks,/RTammy/RP.S. I also enjoy shopping tips:)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tammy Hudgens]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Amy,/RThank you so much for making Brooke's first year at NCA an amazing one! She had such a great year due to you! Thank you for all your hard work and love you poured out to the class. Your love for the students and the Lord showed in everything you did! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lauri Whaley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amy I just want you to know I appreciate you so much. The kindness and love you have for your class is amazing. Sometimes you have more time in a day with Dominic than I do AND I'm thankful it's with you and your wonderful spirit. Thank you for always encouraging him!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heather Seeno]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Miss Lahl,/RYou are a great teacher! Thank you for teaching me. I will miss you when I'm in 4th grade, but I will still say "Hi" to you everyday./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brooke Whaley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Fun things I liked about Miss. Lahl's 3rd Grade Class: Warm fuzzies, Mr. Anchor Test, PB&J Partners, wearing slippers, bringing in stuffed animals, lunch with the Teacher, Science projects, and most of all, being taught by the most energetic and wonderful Teacher!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tatiana Avdienko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Miss Lahl makes learning science fun!  I also enjoy teacher lunches with Miss Lahl.  Coupons are great reward and fun to earn.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Madeline Neypes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm so thankful that the Lord brought you to NCA. You are a fabulous teacher and we are blessed to have you here!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Liz Dachauer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We've been blessed to have Miss Lahl as Isa's 3rd grade teacher.  She has always been so available and responsive to any questions we may have had. We know Isa will take Miss Lahl's influence a long way!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maria & Jim DeVoto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Miss Lahl is that she is patient in my learning, she makes it fun and I could go on and on!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Isabella DeVoto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Miss. Lahl is the best teacher ever because she helps us in times of need.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Angelina Chen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Miss Lahl pays attention to each student and communicates if necessary.  We really appreciate that we have such a great teacher.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wei Huang]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We want to thank you for being such a big part if Kelsey's life this past school year. As she moves through the school grades each teacher leaves an imprint on her life. These imprints will shape her to be the person she was meant to be. Thank you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Suto Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being a great teacher this year and teaching me wonderful things. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelsey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[  I love that Miss Lahl is fun and lets us have parties. I like that she can make me laugh. Thank you for being such a great teacher.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jacob Cuva ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you Amy for being so patient and kind to Jacob and your students. You are so encouraging and a wonderful and loving teacher. We cherish you and truly believe we hit the teacher jackpot this year. Have a wonderful summer.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Juliana Cuva]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a skilled teacher, Amy!  You communicate your expectations clearly, you establish routines and procedures, you firmly and lovingly hold your students accountable, and you cultivate good relationships with students and parents alike.  Thank you for your ministry!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Deborah Rickman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amy, we want to express our sincerest gratitude for your hard work this year. You should be commended for the innovative lesson plans you created in science to go with the Foss program. Madeline flourished this year because of your dedication to your students. Thanks!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jerome and Chelsey Neypes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Taking care of the littlest people takes the biggest heart and you have one big heart!  We are grateful that God chose you to walk alongside Julia this year ... to help her to grow academically and spiritually.  You have been a light in Julia's world this year!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karl & Stefanie Kuhnhausen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I admire you for having the courage and strength to address the "hard stuff" not only with students and families but staff, as well.  God certainly placed those students in your class this year for a reason and has used you to do His work. NCA is blessed to have you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA["Auntie" Cindy Van Teyens]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Therefore, my dear brothers and sisters, stand firm.  Let nothing move you.  Always give yourselves fully to the work of the Lord, because you know that your labor in the Lord is not in vain."  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[1 Corinthians 15:58]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["But they who wait for the Lord shall renew their strength; they shall mount up with wings like eagles; they shall run and not be weary; they shall walk and not faint."  Isaiah 40:31]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julia's verse for Amy Lahl]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amy, /RTrust that God is in control of every area of your life.  May you be filled with peace as you trust that He works all things together for your good. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[A friend who loves you.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>