<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2151-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/1/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Alexandra Kozar]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[1827 SW 29th Ter ]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Cape Coral ]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[FL]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[33914]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></cardcolor>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Karyne,/RIm so proud of you and all of your accomplishments. I've watched you grow and achieve so much in the past years. You have matured into such a beautiful and loving girl that deserves the world. You are going to kill it in college and after. Have an amazing summer]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stefano Clemente]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am so happy to be a part of your life. I have seen you become an amazing young woman and am so proud of who you have become. Life lesson- sometimes u may fall but the key is to get up and try again because to fail is to give up and I know you, you are a fighter.love u]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Chris.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Honey,/RPop-Pop and I just want to let you know how so very proud of you we are and wish you the best in your next adventure in life!/RYou have become a very beautiful young lady who is caring, loving and giving. Stay true to yourself and world will be yours!!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All our Love, Grandma and Pop-Pop]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congrats on your graduation! You've worked really hard and you should be so proud of yourself on this milestone in your life! Keep working hard and I know you will blossom  into the successful young woman that you have the potential to become. Best wishes for the future]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ben]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember to always follow your dreams!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Mike and Heather]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have grown up and become a strong and amazing woman. Remain focused on your goals and continue to give back to others as you have in the past and your will achieve any and every thing you want in life!/R/RI am proud to know you and be a part of your life's journey!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jon Blaze]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congrats Karyne, At 211degrees water is HOT, At 212degrees it BOILS!  That 1extra degree makes a huge difference in life- it will make steam which can power a locomotive.  FLY ON YOUR STRENGTHS!  Every day is a fresh start to do better - work harder than the day before.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Quimby's who adore you!!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm glad I had the opportunity to work with such a thoughtful, hardworking, talented and beautiful young lady./RI am so proud of all that you accomplished.  The world is yours. Take advantage of every opportunity you get, and don't forget to dance ;)/RRoll Tide!!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jamie- best tutor/cheer coach ever!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Karyne! Best wishes in this new chapter of your life. Be safe, enjoy yourself and study hard!/R/R"Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter and those who matter don't mind"~Dr. Seuss]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Kim, Christian&Elizabeth Smith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Karyne, I'm so glad we've gotten closer this year. You're so sweet and nice! I have no doubt that you'll do well in college and make a lot of new friends, you just have an amazing personality! & I really hope everything goes well for you and that we keep in touch!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Netzy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From diapers to cap and gown, you have grown into an extraordinary young lady. As you begin the next chapter in your life, I encourage you to be strong, be confident, and chase your dreams. You can do anything you set out to do. Don't let anyone tell you different!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrea ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am so happy to come to to your graduation. Good luck in college. I love you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anna]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Never allow anyone to tell you that you can't do something, or that you don't deserve something. Prove them wrong and Just smile. With hard work comes great rewards!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Funk Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[“Even if things don't unfold the way you expected, don't be disheartened or give up. One who continues to advance will win in the end.”/R? Daisaku Ikeda]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Funk Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Enjoy every minute of every day!  You are a special young woman who deserves to enjoy the next chapter in your life.  It won't always be easy but if you make the best of each day you'll always keep a smile on that beautiful face.  Congratulations! Love & hugs, Aunt Jan]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Jan Wilbur]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Entering the World of Adults! No Risk, No Reward! The 1st yr of school can be the most difficult, NEVER GIVE UP! *Find your passion & follow it *Life experiences build upon each other *Stay focused *Be your own best cheerleader! *Don't let life pass you by!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Have fun & Enjoy the Journey Hallie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Steps for success: 1. Go to class & Do your homework 2. Try out different classes that you find interesting 3. Prioritize 4. Persevere, anything worth having is worth waiting for 5. Have discipline & stay focused 6. Find your passion & follow it]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hallie xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Life is like a Camera… Focus on what’s important, Capture the good times, Develop from the negatives, And if things don’t work out, TAKE ANOTHER SHOT  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hallie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Karyne,/RWe have watched you grow up and turn into a wonderful woman. We wish for you to have all that life has to offer. Enjoy the challenges and rewards. Stay true to yourself and enjoy your journey .We love you and wish you the best.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ Aunt Mary,Uncle George and Robert]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dont forgot to laugh. Life is really tough sometimes, finding humor in these tough times will keep you from going insane. I'm not an expert in life but I would be happy to give any advice I can. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robert Wilbur ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Above all, do what makes you most happy, find that thing you love and be the best at it that you can be. In everything, always remember to be the best version of you, and enjoy life- the ups and downs, the challenges and easy moments- it's the only one you get.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Djrianna]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congrats Karyne we are so happy and proud of you. You have grown to be beautiful and smart women. A new life awaits you. and we wish the best.  Work hard and be your best and you can achieve anything you want . Never let anybody put you down,  Love always ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle joe & Anut Jill]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Uncle Joes life quote/R"there are 2 tools you need if life, wd40&duct tape.  If it doesn't move and it should use wd40, and if moves and shouldn't use duct tape."  sorry had to add some humor Love always]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Joe ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One tip for navigating the real world... dont change who you are. You are wonderful, perfect, pretty, and outstanding. Karyne you mean the world to me, when you go to college please don't change. I love you too much, as poppy once said "Kozar's stick together for ever" ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brianna Kozar????????]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Karyne,/RYou are a great sister even though I fight with you a lot I really love you?I hope when you are done college that we will have a great relationship?^_^ I hope you relize that even though you and I fight no matter what I got you back/R love you ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your sis -_-]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey baby. Me again. I got so much to say lol. But. Again. I love you. I am super duper proud of you. You have no clue how proud of a dad i am. We have been though alot. You are a very strong young lady.omg. Look at you baby. All grown up now. I love you karyne. Love dad]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[DADDY ????????]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey baby. Your so grown up. My goodness. I couldn't  be any more proud of you. How far you have come. How much you have grown up to be a wonderful young lady.  I know it has been a very tough road for you baby. I love you so much hun. Congrats baby.   Love daddy]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[DADDY ????????]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congradulations on graduating. You have so much to look forward to in life. Keep an open mind and accept as many opportunities as you can. You are a smart and beautiful person so enjoy all that life has to offer.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Grattons]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always be prepared for the worst and hope for the best]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Poppy M ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If I could give you one thing in life, I would give you the ability to see yourself through my eyes. Only then would you realize how extraordinary you are. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Always, Mommy ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your time is limited, so don't waste it living someone else's life. Don't let the noise of others' opinions drown out your own inner voice. And most important, have the courage to follow your heart and intuition]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/R/RAll our dreams can come true...if we have the courage to pursue them/R/RWalt Disney ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love You! ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Education is the key to unlocking the world, a passport to freedom]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dream on and Never Give up]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Create your happiness, don't wait for others to do it for you. You hold the keys to your smile and as long as you focus on what makes you smile all else will fall into place]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Pop Pop]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>