<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2154-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/1/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Sandy &amp; Bish Baker]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[9 Dunbarton Rd]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Cherry Hill]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[NJ]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[08003]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Bish & Sandy]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Sandy & Bish]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[A Legacy of Love]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom and Dad- Happy 45th Anniversary!! You two are true role models in this awesome game of life- living every day fully, always loving and giving with all your hearts. We are lucky to be your children and proud to call you our friends. Hip, Hip, Hooray! We love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen, Ashley, Chantry & Braeden]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[LOVE. You love us, and you love each other. You support each other visibly, but also modestly. You make decisions and stick to them, together. I’ll get better at parenting and marriage, but I highly doubt anyone can ever do it quite like you. You are simply the best.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[all my love, Chantry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Through all the chaos, you SHOWED us love. In your gestures and in your words - we all knew your love. So now, when we’re running late in the morning and Colby wants a family hug, we stop and hug her, and we hug each other. Best way to teach: DO!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[the DeLessio's]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Over the past 35 years, there are so many wonderful times we have spent together, Celebrating all of our girls growing up and having wonderful lives. Best memory?  Seeing France and Italy and other amazing places together ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maria and Harry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary, Sandy and Bish!  You came into our lives 38 years ago and we've been blessed with your wonderful friendship from the very beginning.  We've had some of the best of times together with our growing families and wonderful vacations.  Here's to many more!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris and Pat Maher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Where do I start: my second family for so many years. Memories: Bish and Sandy sending Swedish pancakes and chocolate to us at CSUN over night delivery. Sandy making tortellini at 2:00am for us in HS. Thanks for counting me as one of your own. Congrats on 45 yrs Iove u ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heather Henry Bergey ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[For as long as I can remember, 'family' has included both of you.  So blessed to have you in my life, and so thankful for all the love and support you've given me over the years.  Congratulations on 45 years-- and here's to 45 more!  Love you both.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carolyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hip hip hooray to Bish and Sandy, on your 45th wedding anniversary.  /RMay we have as many wonderful years together as you have had!  xox]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brett, Carolyn, Grace & #2]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I reflect back on my life I am struck with how blessed I am. My memories are a scrapbook of a happy childhood, a supported teen-years, & an adulthood where my mom & dad have become more than just my parents... They are my friends & my inspiration. I love you both. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love B]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nana & Papa- Thank you for showing my mom what it means to be a good parent. Because of you, my mom (and dad) know how to love a child unconditionally, and will be able to raise me to be happy in life. I am so lucky to have the best nana and pappa around!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you! Taylor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for teaching us to entertain! There is nothing better than a Baker Party!! Because of you we are instilled with the love of sharing our homes with our friends & family. Details matter (we all love them!) but spending time with those we love is most important!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cheers to more fun ahead! ~Jen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that you taught us to embrace "projects." First in school and now in our homes! I now especially love that our children love coming to you for school project help!...And that we can call on you to help with home projects - You know I will always have them!:)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Forever Grateful, Jen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We are honored to wish you a happy 45th! You both have a gift for making all of the things you do seem so effortless and yet loving - weekly sleepovers with grandkids - overlapping  sporting events- fitbit challenges- Christmas cards with matching outfits & smiles- STT]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rich and Lynne Mroz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always full of energy, always looking to increase their zest for life and always willing to go that extra mile. Love you guys and glade we can share a life and wonderful memories. "I don't want to work just want to bang on the drums all day"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Therese &Frank]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[OMG! Wow! And just how fast does 45 years go by? We send our heartiest congratulations from down here in South Carolina. Wish we could be on-hand to tip a pint in celebration. Brings back memories of many years of gormet club dinners,etc. Our very best wishes. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob and Sue Patrcik]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As long as I can remember, you have welcomed me into your home and treated me like family. As an adult, you have been an amazing example of what love is. You wrote in my wedding book that you hope Jeff and I have as much fun as you have. Congrats on your Anniversary! xo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Diane and Jeffrey Fehder]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Annuversary!! You two are very special people who we love very much - many years shared and valued - especially playing pool and resting with baby-sitters in the poolroom! Have a wonderful anniversary with all your loved ones.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandy MacGilvray and Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A True Love Story never has an ending and every Love Story is beautiful; but, yours is my favorite. You are two beautiful buds that created an even more amazing bouquet. May your life & love continue to blossom. Love Always,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nana and Papa,/RThank you for supporting me. You come to all my football,basketball and lacrosse games. You even come to my swim meets! You do that for all your grandchildren... crazy!!! I know I am very lucky. I love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cooper (9)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nana and Papa,/RThank you for taking us to Bethany every year. I love going with our whole family. It is my favorite time. I love how we hang out on the beach. I love how we have appetizers! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lilly (7)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nana and Popee,/RI love spending time with you. I love going to the museum. I love picking up Colby with you. I love that you get me sushi. I love you for fixing my Christmas ornaments. I love you for fixing my turtle and bringing him back to me. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ava (4)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom and Dad-/RYour lives and relationship have taught me a lot/RThat love and affection can’t be bought/RI have learned how to trust/RHow to be fair, righteous and just/RHaving the love from parents like both of you/RHas guided me while raising my own crew/RLove you forever]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ashley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Wednesdays because I get to sleep at your house, go in the hot tub, play dominos, eat corn on the cobb & watch movies with you. I love that you tell lots & lots of jokes! You are SOOO funny!I love going to Bethany & going in the beach & pool with you! I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Reagan (6)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sandy & Bish,/RI see time "does fly when you're having fun"!  Congrats!  You make it look so easy!  May we follow in your "happy" footsteps!!!/RPs:  See... I turned out ok after that Enchante incident ;-)!! I wasn't such a bad influence after all (LOL)!!!  xoxo-T]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tifany and Skip Cheatham]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will never forget our trip to Cherry Hill with our BC Field Hockey team! Your love for your girls, your grandchildren, your teams (we are BC!) and all of us (their friends!) is incomparable. Hip Hip Hooray to Sandy and Bish!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bouka and the Haseotes Crew]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Two women and two little girls meet in a pre-school parking lot. Years, camp outs, graduations, weddings and births later you are still the dearest of friends. What a joy and a blast it has been. Happy Anniversary. Love you both./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim and Kathy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for teaching the importance of prayer. I remember one of you sitting on my bed every night when I was a child & saying my prayers & God Blesses. Because of your teaching, our children have also always gone to bed praying, giving thanks & thinking of others.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Blessed from the start, Jen :)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mr. & Mrs. Baker (I had to go back to what I called you in 7th grade!) -Even as an 11 yr old I knew there was something special about the two of you & the family you created! Thank you for always being supportive, positive role models for all of us!/RLots of Love!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tifany "McCall" Cheatham]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sandy and Bish where do you even start describing you two.We met your wonderful Jen first and from the moment we met you it felt like we had known you forever.  You immediately invited us to your annual Christmas party which really made us feel part of your family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenny and Bob Daras]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on 45 years of marriage.  The fact that I can honestly say that I'd rather hang out with my in-laws than most other people is a testament to how wonderful you are as individuals and parents.  Also, Bish always making sure I have an adult beverage helps.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Scott Pashley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[5/23...... both special and memorable! We share the anniversary date just 6 years apart. All our parents set an example of marriage and family and you two exemplify both. Sisters forever!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much love, Jackie and Bill]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memory of Nana and Papa was when we were little, playing "naked boy" after our bath, and we were hiding behind the couch.  Nana was distracting us while Papa ran around the house and popped in and scared us so bad, we started freaking out!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Jay (14)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary, /RSandy and Bish!  /R/RToday, we raise a glass to toast your anniversary.  Your marriage is a storybook romance of /Rtrue love, support and friendship.  We are blessed to have you in our lives and look forward to many more good times in the years ahead.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, JKCRBD Shea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I would be happy to share my thoughts and memories of Bish and Sandy.  I am so fortunate to have met and worked with Bish for over 13 years It was one of my most rewarding experiences in my life.Work hard, do well, and along the way have some fun and memories,well done ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe and Ann-Marie Dixon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My second parents!   Bish--Thank you for Shirley Temples & kitkats!  Sandy--Indian & Trail Maidens were the best!  The Witkowskis love you both.  Your kindness, generosity, & devotion to family/friends is an inspiration.  Hip hip hooray! xoxo Alana, Mike, H, M, and S]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[WITKOWSKI FAMILY]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My fondest memories of Bishop and Sandy are all the wonderful days we spend on Bethany Beach.  Sandy holds endless energy all the while Bish displays incredible patience. Looking forward to celebrating #50. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your favorite son in law - Sean]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy anniversary Sandy and Bish! May we all be blessed to have such happy marriages and families. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeannette and Skip Hill]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy anniversary to a couple who truly makes marriage look good! I've always looked up to and been inspired by your example, and you're continuing to show that same love now for a whole new generation. Much love and congratulations!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jaime & Jason Bochet]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for everything you do for us. I love your dinners. I love your movies & watching with you.I like shopping with Nana & helping Papa with anything. I love going to the pool with you & really love your beach house-even if you are changing it this year!I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Brody (7)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nana & Papa/RI always look forward to Wednesday's because I get to go to your house & have the best dinners ever, more importantly I get to see the best grandparents in the world.My favorite memory with you is when we are in Bethany & I get to crack all the crabs for you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Glenn (12)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's always great having you by my side at all times. Whether it's stealing Nana's croutons and hearing her yell at me, or Papa screaming for me on the sideline of my games, I know how lucky I am. I look forward to continuously making memories & enjoying time with you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Johnny (14)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary/RYour friendship, unconditional  love and compassion is truly remarkable. I am thankful that you both are in our family's life. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you both -D]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on 45 years!  You are a blessing to our entire family and we are lucky to have such caring and giving people as an example to follow.  You have made us all better people.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frank]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Loving 'second' parents who have always made me feel like a part of their family.  Their love and kindness are infectious and we are so grateful to have them in our lives.  Hello HOUSEKEEPING! XO!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vesime Schroering and Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember my brother calling to his room to tell me had something to show me.  He presented a little black box. He carefully opened the little black box and to my delight it was an engagement ring and he told me he was going to ask Sandy to marry him.  Rest is history.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lisa Baker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sandy & Bish, you always made things look easy. It's been a joy holding you near and dear. Thanks for all your support. You have created a beautiful family. God bless you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marilynn Houston]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[56 years ago, I met a guy up the street named Bish. A strange name but thought oh well! Bish and I were inseparable from the start. We went to separate High schools but every afternoon we’d sneak smokes that Bish got from his Grandmother. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jimmy Sherin (1 of 3)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We then were off to college and Bish introduces me to Dan Cunningham. The 3 of us drank a case of Miller High Life all most every night. Bish dated several women, but Sandy was the APPLE of his eye. Sandy, Bish, and my first wife and I would do everything together. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jimmy Sherin (2 of 3)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bish & I both worked for Domino after college then moved on to different positions. Even though we now live on East and West coasts, we still talk. So many friends in between, but to say 56 years of friendship is a long time. Ann and I wish you all the "Best" ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim and Ann Sherin (3 of 4)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for always being an example for both strength of body & strength of mind. You have always "walked your talk."  Because of you, I learned early to believe in myself, take ownership & responsibility for my happiness and always have a passion in & for life!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Forever appreciative, Jen :)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandy & Bish ~ Married 5/23/70 - ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sandy & Bish/R/R/R/R/R/R/R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Married 5/23/70 -]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Happy 45th Anniversary, Sandy and Bish.  You were one of the first families we met in Wexford 34 years ago. Since then, you and your daughters have been a special part of so many wonderful memories for our family.  We look forward to many more.           ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Congratulations,  Kathie and Chris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>