<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2156-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/2/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Hannah Teague]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[31963 Doverwood Court]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Westlake Village]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[CA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[91361]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sand]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[To my beloved sister ]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Isabella Teague]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[From, Hannah]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love so many things about you that it is hard for me to choose just one. I LOVE your absolute zest for life. You are so open to new experiences, travels, people, events, charities, and more. You live life to the fullest and you are so very alive! I luv u beyond words!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how you can laugh at yourself and be silly and spontaneous. You make me laugh all the time and I am thankful for every moment we spend together. You are my heart!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that you are not vain. I love that you are confident enough not to have to wear make-up every single time you leave the house. I love that you don't mind getting wet, sandy or dirty. I love that you have the character to not judge a book by its cover. I luv u!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that you made me a mama! I love that you love Carpinteria as much as I do. I love that you love the outdoors and watching the sun set. I love that you love to travel. I love that you love home. I love that you love your Judaism and that it makes you feel safe.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You never fail to make me laugh. I always have a smile when I'm with you. I know if I ever need help with something you're the person to go to. And most importantly I love you so much Bell!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Abby Rosenblum ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love everything about you. I love you from head to toe, inside and out. I love your heart and soul and brilliant mind. I love your beautiful face and that dimple that makes me smile. I love your golden hair and gorgeous brown eyes. I love you more than words my luv!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how you are my sister and best friend. I couldn't have asked for a better role model. I love you more than words can describe. I will miss you like crazy! Love u bel!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[sissy hannah ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are our oldest grandchild who has made us very proud throughout the years.  Your confidence and caring heart is very evident in all you do.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grandad and Grandma Wilson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bella, one thing that stands out about you: is that you're not afraid to be your own person.  You're a strong hard working, young lady, with her own opinions, not giving in to others' influences.  Keep being you! Love, Uncle Sean, Aunt Amy, Tripp, Maddie, & Kendall ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Wilson's ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Bella is the fact she is the most reliable friend I know. she's always there to lend a helping hand and you can count on her for anything. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[madison axelrode]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bella, you've always been like an older sister to me. You're so funny and never fail to make me laugh. You're so fun to be around. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sophie Lantz ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're my person. /RI can't thank you enough for staying by my side all of these years & creating a life time of memories with me. I can't wait to grow old together. Kill it in Oregon. /RI love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Macy Mills]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing we love about you is how you create your own success. It's more than luck or being opportunistic. You work hard, persevere & use your intelligence wisely.  We know that you'll become an outstanding woman & will continue to make all of us in your family proud.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Papa Doug & Grandma Jan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your compassion, action, and smile not only impressed me but inspired me every day./RMy world is better because you came into it and I am so grateful.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gerald Pickett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's difficult to choose just one thing we love the most about you.  Belle, you are so very creative, driven, curious.  You are funny, intelligent, self-assured.  You are a devoted niece and cousin.  You /Rengage wholeheartedly in your life. You are a blessing to us all!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you!  The Schlossers]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your passion and zeal for life is effervescent!  We have enjoyed witnessing your growth from a beautiful baby into a self-assured young woman.  We have so many cherished memories of our family vacations together.  Wishing you all the best!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love The Lauber Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She always makes me laugh.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Darren Hackett ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bella ~ Since the day you were born, your smile, strength and conviction is what we remember most! We love you and can't wait to see what comes next! /RAnd, if you ever lose your way, Caw Caw and we'll be there! /R/RLove ya!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ken, Susan, Brandon, Evan & Ash]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are beautiful! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Ashley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bella~ You are an amazing young lady. We love that you are confident, know what you want and work hard for it. We are proud of you Bella and we can't wait to see what the future has in store for you. Love you Bella!  Uncle Errol, Aunt Sarah, Taylor, Colin and Jaxon]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Berry Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bella you're the one true girlfriend i had through high school all 4 years and that shows something really special. You're the sweetest most genuine girl. I will never forget all the funny stuff we did together. Love you so much]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brenner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bella, You are so much fun to be around. You are so sweet and I think of you like a sister. I will miss you so much next year. Love you!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Boots]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love your selflessness and willingness to be there for your friends at any time for any reason. I've been lucky enough to laugh endlessly at stupid jokes with you for so many years, and I wish you the brightest future. Love you tons bober!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kirtie ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Bella is her positivity and her brightness. She can make any conversation a happy and fun one. She can always make people laugh no matter what. Bella is crazy but that's what I love most about her. Love you bell!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Callie Naber]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love spending Sundays with you watching the Denver Broncos play...I love the fact that you are a Bronco's fan like your Dad!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love that you love gardening as much as I do even if you make me do all the dirty work...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am so happy that I have had the privilege to watch you grow up into such a beautiful and intelligent young woman. You make me sooo proud to be your dad!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Harry Potter...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you /Rfor all that you are/Rall that you have been/Rand all that you're yet to be...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are one of the greatest gifts I ever received... ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bella, You are a force of nature--with your single minded passion and enthusiasm, your self-directed individuality, your strength of purpose, your conviction to make a difference and your beautiful spirit of adventure.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All my love, Gaga]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Darling, You are a shining star! Your competence, leadership and sense of responsibility, and your commitment to your jewish culture, have provided a dazzling example for your sisters and cousins to follow.  You make our family proud!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your loving Gaga]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am in awe of your exceptional creative intellect; your ability to conceive of an original idea, to follow it through in pursuit of perfection to its completion. (yellow school bus, painted backdrop of red sea & passover play, photography, cooking, gift baskets, etc.)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I love and adore you, Gaga]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bella, as our first grandchild you hold a unique place in my heart. I love your strength, your fortitude, and your commitment to do good in the world.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Papa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love your sense of adventure, your desire to travel to and experience new places and cultures. I love your seriousness of purpose, your extraordinary energy, and your groundedness.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Papa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I also love your beauty and your very admirable sense of responsibility. You're both serious and a great crack-up!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Papa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bells, /RFirst off congratulations! Words can't describe how happy I am that I became friends with you. You truly are one of a kind and make me laugh at literally anything. I hope that everything you wish for is granted because you deserve it. I'll miss you, much love!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gaby Vilches]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how caring you are towards others and how that drives your motivation. And you're gorgeous ??]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sam Sullivan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bella, I love everything about you. You are smart, kind, beautiful, funny, athletic, and so much more! I look up to you and hope that one day I can be as smart and outgoing as you are. I love you more than words will every explain.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hannah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite thing about Bella is how she can instantly make me smile. Your contagious smile, and positive energy can make anyones day. I was lucky enough to witness this since freshman year & I hope I will forever. Oregon is lucky to have you! Good luck! Love you lots!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tamar Kazanjian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I would definitely say one thing I love about Bella is that her and I have remained so close and have alway had the best times together (which usually result in stomach aches because of laughing so hard). I love her more than she knows. She will always be my main bobe!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maky]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ I love you, and the way you can always laugh at your crazy self. I hope you have a very successful time in college. I will miss the many, many times you fall down the stairs./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Birdie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Baja Fresh... Baja Fresh... Baja Fresh... Ba ja ja Fresh! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maky]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bella has always been one of our favorites. We love the many memories that our families have shared and will always cherish our time spent with her. We wish her the best of luck in the future and we know it will be bright. We love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The LaBrie Family ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite thing about you is your positive mindset. You are always one to see the bright side  of a situation, turn a negative into a positive, or even give a good pep talk. I can always count on you no matter what and I am so lucky to have you in my life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Katie D.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I hope you love this present bells. I love you so much and I am going to miss you more and more everyday!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hannah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>