<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2161-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/2/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Saralyn O&#039;Donnell]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[16515 Champions Cove Court]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Spring]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[TX]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[77379]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Coach Shall, we love you. ]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Coach Shallenberger]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[People that love YOU]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for your love, support, advice, accountability, and most of all patience. I never would have thought i would leave the volleyball program with a mentor, and sister in Christ. I am so so thankful for you!! I love you so much!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[SL]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Shall!!/RHope you have a great summer! I'll miss your coaching next year but I'll come visit you with my diva detergent!!  /RLove you lots!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sydney Stockinger????]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can not thank you enough for every little thing you have done for me! The relationship we have built over the past 3 years has been something I will always cherish. I know even when I leave for college, you are only a phone call away! Love you lots! Xoxo?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meagan Bauer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Everyday you brighten my day  from your sarcastic jokes to your love for your "kids". You are like a second mom to me. I can tak to you about anything and everything! You are defiantly my favorite coach/teacher! Love ya Shall! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karrigan Falber]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank for you not only being a great coach, but mentor for me. We have had our ups and downs over the years, but I have learned a lot of life lessons through your program. I'm grateful for the 3 years I have spent with you! You will be missed more than you know!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[CAMERON TAYLOR ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Coach Shall is my daughter.  She has been an athlete since she played soccer at age 5.  She played volleyball in jr and sr high school and received a full ride vb scholarship to SBU.  I am most proud of her character, leadership and how much she cares for her athletes.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nena Fagan (her mom)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Life wouldn't be the same without my womba partner. I admire your loving spirit, kind heart, giving self. I also love the way you go after your dreams. I love being your twin and  so thankful for someone like you has been on the journey of life with me. Love you sis.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sissy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the sweetest and most sincere people I've had the opportunity to meet. You are by far my favorite teacher, and my only wish is that I would have met you sooner. Your awesome (and very sarcastic) sense of humor will definitely be missed. :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cece Clemons, your fav student]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being an amazing coach! I have loved being an SA for you over this past year! I'll miss you next year! But I'll be sure to come visit! (: lots of love ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Skylar Wuensch ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Coach Shall influenced me by helping me reach out to be a better person and athlete. Without her i dont know where i would be today. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Catherine White]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She has taught me to believe in myself and that if you want to succeed to must try your best no matter what]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Madi Kling]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Of all the coach's I have seen thought out the years /RYOU ARE THE BEST COACH I HAVE EVER SEEN COACH THE SPORT. LOVE DAD!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Keith Martinez]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Coach Shall's best quality is her compassion for others. She is so understanding and sees the good in everyone. I'm gonna really miss joking around with her next year. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lauren Rowe ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Coach Shall,/RThanks for pushing me beyond what I even thought possible. I am a stronger player for it.  You helped me achieve my goals. I will miss you. I'm glad we built the bridge!! ;)/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brooke "B"]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Coach Shall, I've learned so much from you this year and I can't wait to see what God has planned for you and your family!  I'm so grateful for this past year, I'll never forget what you've taught me and I am forever blessed. Thank you Coach Shall for everything!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lexi Peery]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Coach Shall taught me so much about volleyball as well as life in general. From learning a new position to knowing when "you're being dramatic". This season with her was one for the books and I'm going to miss her so much!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julia Fritz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Shall! You have been such an amazing influence on me these past 2 years and I am so thankful for you! Thank you for always listening to my problems, and giving the best advice! I'm so upset you're not the coach next year, but call me up to walk your dog anytime! Love ya]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lauryn Reynolds]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have always been a great role model, and have the best advice off and on the court. You're one of the few coaches with a great sense of humor, and I will never forget the Segwaying night! Gonna miss having you as a coach! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[McKenna Miller]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Shall, thank you so much for being such a positive influence in my life. You did a great job being a mentor and a coach to all of us, I really enjoyed being a part of your program and will miss your sarcastic comments and not spending as much time with you next year!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Courtney Babitt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[not only have you taught me how to be on time haha, but also how to love a team & work together. you have taught me amazing lessons and values that I will carry with me forever, and I am so grateful for you!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[sydney lewis ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Coach Shall we have been through so much in the past 3 years and you have influenced me in many ways! Obviously we have had some issues but I'm beyond grateful for the impact you have had on my life! I can guarantee you will be a teacher I keep in touch with next year!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeremi Ayers ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[shally!!! you've helped me so much not only in volleyball but in growing as a person. I have learned life lessons from you & am now hopefully a better person in the community, I love you so much & am so sad I wont get to see you every day in 7th, ps I call dog watching]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kaitlyn Richards ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Without you (Shalldip) , I wouldn't be who I am today. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ashley Ndip]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for always making sarcastic jokes, despite the "tough crowd" ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Piper Stephens]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Shall has positively affected my life in so many ways. She helps me be a better person each and every day and teaches me to always give 100%. She's always there for me and always offers a shoulder to cry on. I'm so grateful to have such a positive influence like her in my life. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allison Pawelka]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Coach Shall, I'm going to miss you and your funny jokes! You have made volleyball more than a sport for me, thank you for everything you have done. You're such a great person and I will miss you so much in the program! I'll come and visit you for sure! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ally Dauphinais ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Time passes fast but memories last forever. You've given me a great start with your guidance and I will never forget you. I can't think of volleyball without always seeing you. You've always made me feel important. Thanks for some great memories and the nickname, Stat.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Becca Stat]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[you have made me a better player and person. You had me set goals for myself, which really helped me this year. You taught me to always laugh at people's jokes even if they aren't that good. :)thankyou for making my fish year a blast!! I'm going to miss you next year]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Megan Murley ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for helping guide me through these past 3 years of high school. You're always there for me whether it's on a personal level or an educational level. I'm so thankful that God has blessed me with not just an amazing teacher, but an amazing figure in my life. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ashley Hays]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for making the last 3 years great for the girls and the Klein Volleyball program. It has been a pleasure to get to know you both professionally as a coach and personally as role model and what you stand for as a Christian lady./RWe wish you the best!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shawn Taylor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whenever I need help I know I can turn to you, you want the best for everyone and care about each and everyone of your students. Thank you being such a great coach and leader. We will all miss you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Emily Duncan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Oh Shally, hehe even though I'm probably a pain, I'm so honored to say you we're one of my coaches. I love being able to joke around with you and not get all upset. Even if u don't realize it, u have taught me a lot. it's gonna be weird not havin you next year!:/ ily<3]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Madison Prosise]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Coach Shall I'm going to miss you next year! Thank you so much for the opportunity to get to be in the program with you this year! Thank you for teaching me what you know about volleyball, and for always talking about the bachelor/bachelorette with me!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kenzie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[i just wanted you to know that you are an AMAZING coach and i love your sense of humor! you have influenced me so much into becoming a better volleyball player that i know i can be. thank you so much for believeing in me even when i knew nothing about volleyball (:]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ Jessica VIllatoro(a.k.a  JESS)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Shall, thank you for seeing something in me, even though I don't play club outside of school! /R/RI'm going to miss you cracking jokes during practice, and the way you communicate with everyone in such a positive way./R/RThank you for an amazing freshman year!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Erica A.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Coach Shall you were like a mom away from home,  if that makes sense lol! I have enjoyed these past 3 yrs with you and I'm gonna be deeply saddened when i graduate cuz then i will know that reality and the real world life is about to begin. I will forever miss you coach]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happiness Okeke]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/R/R A friend will be a friend in times of all kinds. /RProverbs 17:17]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jackie Edwards]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Coach Shallenberger,/R/RThank you for everything that you do to make Klein High School a great place.  You are a great teacher, coach, and role model.  You are very deserving of your District Teacher of the Year Award.  Your positive attitude is very evident in all you do]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gary Brain]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Coach Shall, you showed me how to see the positive in hard situations, work hard, and be a team player. You have made an impact on my life in a wonderful way & I will always be grateful for getting to have been coached by you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[London Furr]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Monica,/R/RThank you for being a top-notch educator and colleague! Your enthusiasm and positivity are always appreciated. Keep being you and inspiring those around you:)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alicia Eichhorn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To one of the most inspiring ladies I've ever met. You have helped me become a better mother, friend, and Christian in my walk and for that, I thank you. /RI wish you nothing but love and happiness in your future. Love you bunches...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Candi Weige]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Shall , you have gotten me through so much& have made me learn so much . My life is so crazy and I have to say knowing that I had someone in my life that is always there when I need her. It's the best feeling ever you've made me feel loved even when I wasn't . Thank you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ari Renteria ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Monica,/R/RYou are such an amazing woman, I am so blessed to have you as friend and mentor. You never hesitate to help with anything or share information that is helpful. God bless! /RLove,/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cassi Windham]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Coach Shall is one crazy lady...always smiling, talking fast, oh and don't forget about dancing (especially when Usher comes on). I will miss our days in the coaches office but look forward to our new talk spot, the bathroom hallway! Thanks for being sugh a good friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marcie Kuhl]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I hope that you enjoy this gift. You will be missed way more than you know. Thank you for being influential, and positive over these years. We love you to no end Shally!!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, VB girls & Family!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>