<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2169-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/3/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Ryan Northington]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[134 booth ln]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[HAVERFORD]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19041]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDEX_FEDEX2DAY]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sunshine]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 40th Bea!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Rebecca Northington]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[With Love from Everyone]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[MOM! Where is my IPOD!?/R/RThe same place as your CROCS!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff Pennington]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are my best friend, my partner, and truly my better half.  I hope you enjoy these notes from others that love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Re]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love your relentless commitment to family. Thanks for being the glue that keeps the River and MacLeans and cousins and baseball bound together. We are grateful and we love you. Oh and yeah, I named my child after you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Si, Jess and Bea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bea is a loving mother of four who keeps all the young Northingtons totally organized.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nana Gigi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love - no matter the time or place. Your gift has been the love you have shown to all those around you. While I'm just an observer, you have my admiration for the life, family, and love you have! I feel lucky to have experienced 22 years of "Bea"! You are the best! HB!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Oh - and you are complete smart ass too!!!! Keeping honing it for another 60! /R/RHappy Birthday from Team Chaos.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Her laugh- it is easy, genuine, and totally contagious. /R/RRebecca is always the person I want to sit next to at a dinner party. She is fun-loving, interesting, and always happy. Here's to laughing your way into a fantastic new decade!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With love, Laurie Collins]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Beautiful, intelligent, a marvelous hostess, athletic, and the best mom my special grandchildren (Jack, Lachlan, Rives, and Clare) could have! Oh, and I love your style!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat Northington]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are an incredible organizer. Calm and positive on the run with your four wonderful children, you ate a genius at redirection and getting it all done. Athletic, high energy, and an excellent cook, you often seem to be two Beas, and that is A GOOD thing!! You look 20!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Northington]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nothing is impossible for Rebecca:) 4 kids need to be in 4 different places at the same time? No problem!  Host a dinner for 5 families on an hours notice a few days after moving?  Sure!  Run a marathon a little bit pregnant?  Why not!/RYou are truly inspirational:)!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[with so much love, Todd & Ab]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What do the Peterson kids love most about Mrs Northington?/R"She drives so fast through the ford!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tyler, Davis, Colin & Fiona]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My American cousin & amazing friend, Your attitude to life I respect, love, I commend. The river, thanks giving, man hunt, fun times, Asshole, celebrations, vodka tonic & lime. Running, our connection & how we can talk, May this continue for years even if we must walk.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love your kiwi cousin & friend xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Even though we haven't seen each other in years, I am so excited to reconnect and celebrate. I loved our moments in college and watching her family grow through pictures. What's not to love about her beautiful smile and warm heart. Happy happy birthday! Can't wait!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lola Arellano Pegg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Rebecca is unafraid of chaos - since life is chaos, Rebecca embraces all that life has to offer with gusto!  She inspires me!  And, for the record, she's not just my *neighbor* from growing up - we were super tight. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[You'd better know]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bea, /R/RYou bring so much positive energy to every single day.   You are compassionate, empathetic, thoughtful and funny.  You are my role model parent and a huge amount of fun to be around.  All of which is shocking to me because you used to be such a pain in the ass. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I love you dearly, Gil]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Passion - Rebecca brings it everyday. For her kids, her family and her friends. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ONell's of Berwyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From the first moment I met you (organizing Tucker's 30th birthday party with Lachlan strapped to your chest), you have always been exuberant and tireless with an amazingly caring and positive approach to life and the ones you love.  You are a true inspiration!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[EZ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Rebecca,  I love that you are the perfect mix of drop dead gorgeous, incredible homemaker and camp counselor, and yet can still beat the boys in any challenge!  You are amazing. Happy birthday beautiful! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ashley Cassidy ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the queen of the intellectually stimulating dinner conversation.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Buck & Allison Holmes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I love about you, Rebecca.../RYour generosity of time and spirit./RYour love of a good gossip session!/RYour comfort, support and advice./RYour great sense of humor and laugh./RYour loyalty and friendship./R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo Marlies]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What an amazing, gracious and loyal friend you are. You make everyone feel welcome, always have a kind word when one is needed, and a warm smile to endear us all. You're a model parent, have a clever wit, and lest we forget, so much fun to hang with! Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ambler Selway]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bea and I used to talk of "fate" and how their is a plan and purpose to things, starting with her coming into this world as an "oops"./RBea, you've always been the wiser - fate is not pre-ordained, it's your attitude about how to live, and love!  You are amazing!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tucker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[40 years ago on Friday the 13th of June you arrived, five weeks early, a joy then and ever since, a bundle of energy, eager to tackle the world!  What a gift!  we love you!  Mom and Dad]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charlotte Grinnan MacLean]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are such an incredibly kind, thoughtful, generous, beautiful person who is /Rdie-hard FUN!!! Your zest for life is infectious and ability to do 5,000 things at once is awe-inspiring.  You are truly the essence of grace and are a cherished and dearly loved  friend! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Elizabeth & Chad Vandiver]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I love and admire about Rebecca is that she always demonstrates a spirit of grace and kindness, an elegant patience, true dedication, warmth and total beauty, inside and out. There's never only one thing to like most about her, as she is consistently wonderful.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael Diorio]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From our trips to Nokomis and Chippewa Bay to how you invited me into your life in NC and PA, you have always been a sister to me-and through it all, we have loved and fought like siblings. Your love of your family, the river, and chaos is absolutely contagious-love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ally]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I like most about Rebecca is that she has a mouth like a sailor.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carter Williams]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Rebecca - I love your passion and how you attack everything you do with gusto.   Happy Birthday gorgeous!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allison wolter ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Rebecca- the roommate I never really had (was always staying with Ryan).]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[kelly f.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's a tie......../RHer loving and capable hands/RHer radiant smile]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alison ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Rebecca has always had a knack for bringing people together, cooking a delicious meal, starting good conversations, and having fun! I can't wait to see you soon to celebrate 40!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ami Balderson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are generous with your encouragement and positive attitude toward others.  I can always count on you to lift my spirits and find the best in everyone.  I love and admire how you embrace life and all its adventures.  You bring a little piece of the River everywhere!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Oh yes - and I will forever appreciate your generosity in "letting" me out run you a few summers ago.  :-). Your joy is contagious and your competitive spirit makes life fun.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To 40 more years of you inspiring all of us!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love your thought provoking questions. They can bring a dinner party crowd to debate, laugh or tears. Whatever the direction it is always something memorable.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allison Henderson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your excitement for life is truly infectious. Life just seems better when Bea is talking about it and living it. Whether it's family, friends, sports, gardening, or the river it is always fun to hear and to watch your enthusiasm]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allison Henderson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love the time we shared at Davidson...your great dance moves wherever we were! Our mutual love for different but beautiful rivers. I love memories of laying in the sun at Lake Norman-laughing, talking and listening to music on a boom box! Happy 40th BeYOUtiful friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lots of love! Joanna Andrews]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Rebecca, You have so many great qualities, but for us the best one is that you generously share your family and friends. We have loved becoming part of the MacLean and Northington extended tribe and look forward to many more years together. With Love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paige and Brad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love Rebecca's warm heart, bright smile, spirited debates, delicious cooking, welcoming home, wonderful children, just above average husband and youthful glow. No way she's 40! We love you and we are blessed to call you a friend. xo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gillian & Dixon Shay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["A good friend knows all your stories, a best friend helped you write them." . . . . Happy Birthday to my best friend . . .I feel so lucky to have you in my life!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rory]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You love us, help us, and take the best care of us.  You are the best mom in the world.  We love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jack, Lachlan, Rives, and Clare]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Oh yeah - and you are smoking hot . . . ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ryan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No, seriously - like super model HOT.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[you know who I am. I'm watching you]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From our trips to Nokomis and Chippewa Bay to how you invited me into your life in NC and PA, you have always been a sister to me-and through it all, we have loved and fought like siblings. Your love of your family, the river, and chaos is absolutely contagious-love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ally]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your love of the river, of your children and of your river family has created such an important foundation for us as we now raise Corson as the next River Rat. Thank you for this guidance, this love and for doing it all while looking fabulous. We love you-Happy Birthday]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Camilla+Ally+Corson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[SPORTY AND FORTY!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ally+Camilla+Corson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[For as long as I can remember Bea has been one of my best friends.  She has always been there for me and has been a great friend and mentor.  I love and cherish all of the times we have spent together, happy or sad, River or home.  She is the best- I love you Bea!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Erin Clare]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Pinching, Laughing, Purple Nurple Giving, Stubborn, Sweet, Beautiful, Wild, Caring, Great Cooking, God Fearing, Competitive,  Knowingly Smiling, Pain in the Ass, Understanding,  Opinionated, Nurturing, Relentless,  Sweet, Up for Anything, Dancing Tipsy, Den Mother = Bea]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Cousin James and Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[YOU ARE LOVED.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[EVERYONE]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>