<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2171-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/4/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Jamee Rivers]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[900 East 8th Avenue]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[Suite 300]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[King of Prussia]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19406]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 25th Anniversary ]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Jeff Kennett]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Your friends at Imagefirst]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Jeff, Happy Anniversary.  It has been a pleasure working with you these last few years.  Your knowledge and enthusiasm for the company is tremendous.  I wish you the best of luck over the next 25 years.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jamee Rivers]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No matter what is going on, I can always count on you for warm hello & a friendly smile.  Your positivity is contagious!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heather Archuleta]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeffrey, /RYou have always been a pleasure to work with and know personally.  Your care and concern for others is something that I have always admired. And I love that you are always smiling! I look forward to another decade (or two) together! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lynn Cepeda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ You are the epitome of what a Customer Advocate should be.  You make sure that all of your customer's needs are met completely without fail and for that you are priceless to them as well as to us.  Thank you for all that you do, you are truly REMARKABLE]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Goldenberg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeff is everything we want our CA's to be-he is "Remarkable"!  I learned the core of my Service knowledge training with him.  Most importantly, Jeff is an amazing person & family man.  No one treats people as well as Jeff does.  Thank you for being you Jeff!  God Bless!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Geraghty]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulation on 25yrs. Jeff always comes into oss with a smile. He is always friendly and a very hard worker. I always enjoy talking with him.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Becky McMaster-OSS Health]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on 25yrs. You always come into OSS with a smile and your such a hard worker. I truly appreciate your friendship. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Becky McMaster-OSS Health]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeff, It is always a pleasure to see you, you are so pleasant and kind. You make me laugh. Congratulation on your 25th Anniversary]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Deb Sterner-OSS Health]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I've enjoyed working with Jeff over the years and seeing his excellence in action.  He is truly a remarkable CA and more importantly a remarkable person.  His sprit and commitment to Image First sets a wonderful example for the rest of us to follow.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff Berstein ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeff, I have always loved your 100% committment and belief in our company!  Whatever it takes for however long it takes...that is you! Also I appreciate that you are always positive and upbeat.  And who can forget all the funny nicknames you give all of us? :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Will Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeff,/R/RThank you for your 25 Years of service.  We appreciate all that you have done and will do to take great care of our clients and their patients.  You are truly a 'Model' Customer Advocate!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jay Juffre]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It is an honor for ImageFIRST to have someone like you.  Your hard work, dedication and desire to impact the lives of your co-workers, your customers and their patients have taken our company to the top.  I feel truly blessed to have you on our team.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian McCabe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeff,/RHappy 25th Anniversary.  Who would have thought we would have been here this long.  So here's my gift to you on this memorable occasion.  I hope the following words make you smile:/RJohnny @ China King, CBM at Alumax, Jeff to Pam's office.  Congrats on your 25th.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bryan Cunningham]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always pleasant, greets customers with a smile, hard-working, provides excellent customer service/RA true example of qualities all employees should have/RA pleasure to work with him]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Terri Moore]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[On behalf of all the staff at OSS Health I would like to say thank you for all the hard work and dedication that you have shown to our staff and patients every day. It has been wonderful to work with Jeff and share stories about Marley. Thank You!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jade Thomas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeff is very dedicated and committed to his job.  He always has a smile on his face and a kind word to share.  It's a pleasure to work with him!/RCongratulations Jeff.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lou Kapner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[.Jeff, what a positive example you set for all you come in contact with.  Your level of care and commitment to this company and its customers is inspirational!  You truly have the Fred Factor  Congrats on 25 years!  What an awesome accomplishment.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Malandra]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am very happy to be able to work with Jeff. He is always thinking of others and has a great personality. Even on my toughest days just talking to Jeff for a few minutes can make a difference. Congrats on your Anniversary!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michelle Grabowicz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeff is warm to all our staff members and fits in as part of our team.  He is willing to go the extra mile and is appreciated by everyone at North Pointe Surgery Center!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amy Waters]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeff is THE BEST & REMARKABLE.! Over the years , he goes above and beyond for his customers, he is a model for giving his and our customers the Best, Consistent, and Caring in customer service because in his words " They are good people".  /RAll the Best now and future.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lady Di at ImageFIRST. ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeff/RYour dedication to your customers is matched by no others.  It is truly a pleasure to work with you every day./RCongratulations on your 25 years.  May there be many more.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom Abram]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[25 years,good job old head always nice working with you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[the gringo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wow 25 years!! I can't believe it. Congrats on your success with this company. Go Eagles!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Manley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeff is always willing to do whatever we ask him to do.  He represents a relationship that is a true "partnership".  I appreciate all he does for OSS Health.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike Nestlebush]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeff is one of the most organized people I have ever worked with. In all my years at Image First I have never seen a cleaner and more organized truck than Jeff's. The most important quality that I apprciate about Jeff is how much he cares for his Image First family. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andre Cherry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeff,/RIt is a pleasure and an honor to work with an individual such as yourself. You epitomize the culture of ImageFirst and inspire others to follow your lead. You are the most caring individual for both your customers, their patients, & your ImageFirst family. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ed Swartz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wow Jeff 25 years with ImageFIRST.  Congratulations on such a milestone anniversary.  Your service and dedication to our customers has been truly "REMARKABLE".  Thanks for all you have done.  Here's to another 25 years!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Roberts]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeff defines remarkable in every sense of the word!  He embodies IF values not only at work but also at home.  Jeff handles a route that consists of our largest accounts and that's not by accident.  Thank you Jeff for all of your years of service - YOU ARE THE BEST! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Kennedy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I just love going to a doctor's appointment and when I see they use ImageFirst I ask who their CA is and at some point in the list that they give me they always bring you up and how much they love or miss you.  You are a great model of Customer Service for our company!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michelle Kelly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>