<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2173-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/4/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Gail Burnside]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[11545 Kings Ct]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[Town of Cedarburg]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[West Bend]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[WI]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[53095]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 50th Wedding Anniversary]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Richard and Lois Reddemann]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[From the Burnsides & Richards]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We are so grateful for your example of a loving marriage based on your relationship and mutual love of God. You are such a blessing to us. May we live our lives following your example. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Richard Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Best Wishes on your anniversary, may blessings abound.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Harold and Aunt Gladys]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Laughing, Loving, Acceptance, Grace, Tears, Thoughtfulness, Giving, laughing...../Rand that was just the first time I met you./RYou both mean the world to me, an example of the type of person I want to be! /RHappy Anniversary to you both,/RAlways in my thoughts and prayers]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carol (your favorite daughter)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember walking the few feet to your doorstep for early morning (golf) babysitting ... always being greeted by you both - smiling, welcoming, laughing... your family is such a prominent part of my youth and who I have become.  You are both much loved and appreciated!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris (Ackmann) Janowicz and family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Mr. and Mrs. Reddemann, congratulations on your 50th wedding anniversary!  I'm so happy for both of you.  As I think back on my childhood, I'm reminded of so many wonderful examples of Christian marriage and yours is clearly an exemplary example.  God Bless!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark and Alison Franke]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Richard and Lois when I think of you I think of your genuine smiles and laughter. Your sincerity and love for Jesus and your fellow Christians is always apparent. God's richest blessings to you and your wonderful family. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love ya Yvonne Bronner ????]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We all know Richard is an avid baseball fan.  Lois proves the strength of their relationship because of her total support & participation as a true fan.(Unless it's too cold or maybe too rainy)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Stedge's]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[This couple blesses me every time I am around them.  They give and give and never except anything back.  Happy Anniversary and may God bless you with many many many more.  I love you two!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie Beers]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on this very special time./RYou have both been a such cheerful faces for all of us here at Concordia./RThe Lord's blessings to you both.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jackie Heckler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We had the priveledge of getting to know the Reddemanns when we transferred to Concordia!  From the moment we transferred they wrapped us in love and have continued ever since! Such a great example of christian marriage, parenting and friends! Happy Anniversary!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Kaschinskes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What a wonderful blessing to be able to congratulate and praise our Lord with you on your 50th anniversary.  God has truly blessed you with each other and has blessed me with your influence as teacher and friends.  The Lord's richest blessings on your next 50 years!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dave and Josh Vandre]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One special memory of you both is in Oklahoma is of the care & concern you showed to me especially your light heated, but sincere way of showing that you care. You are a special couple, great fun to be around. Your are a lighthearted couple & always brighten my day.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sally Nylund]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What a blessing it was for me to teach with Richard!  He set an example by displaying his faith through his words and actions! Lois has been my prayer warrior, always updating her prayer list for me! May the Lord bless you with many more years of happiness and love!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy Henneman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear older Brother (like  65 isn't old),  the things one  can  remember overall  the  years.  I remember 50 years  ago on a night  in Merrill Wisconsin.  Chasing thru the  streets, it was  great,  it was great just being at my big brothers Wedding.  Oh! What a night...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alan W. Reddemann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'll always remember your visits to Jill and Don when they lived in Bury St. Edmunds.  I loved hearing from Jill how her dad instilled a love of baseball in her and how her mom was the savviest shopper ever. Thanks for giving us Jill and Gail!  Happy anniversary!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rachel Leininger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have not had opportunity to get to know you well personally, but we applaud you and celebrate your daughters Gail and Jill. You have blessed so many of us through them. Thank you, Congratulations, and God's continued blessings.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom and Lois Giordano]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ When I had "Mr Reddemann" in 3rd grade  I had to stand up with three fingers in my mouth for talking too much.  Also, getting an increase in pay from $.50 to $.75 for babysitting when Jill was born.  LA Dodgers, so sad, and now the Great Lakes Loons are their team.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bev Feldkamp]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[45 years, golf, baseball in Cincy, sports, parent/teacher meetings, Indy 500, Cottage, surgeries, Weddings, births of grandchildren, deaths of parents,but the grace of God goes on and on.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[God's Richest Blessings, Wendy/John]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Richard and Lois, Congratulations on 50 years.  I always see you both smiling and enjoying life and it brings a smile to my face. Wishing you 50 more! Many blessings!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Waldron & Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I've known Mr. Reddemann since 4th grade. Even though, I graduated his class he and his were a constant presence in my life, from worship to baseball they were a sight to behold. I pray you God's continued blessings on your life and marriage!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Justin Kumfer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We feel that The Reddemanns add so much to the happiness of our group at Bible class & other functions  always fun people to be with]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Olsons]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will never forget the care that Richard showed in his class for me especially when I was going through a tough time. I feel blessed that I got to know Richard, Lois, Gail and Jill and kept that friendship throughout the years. May God keep blessing your family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Greg Luchnenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on your BIG wedding anniversary!  Wishing you many more!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Oetting Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am certainly blessed to be a pastor here at Concordia - and part of that is because of how special my relationship is with the two of you.  I love you both and Thank God for you.  May God shower you with His grace and favor for many anniversaries to come.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pastor Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When we first joined Concordia and found Lois, we were so thrilled to find out her North Dakota roots.  Imagine, someone else from that state!  It was so much fun talking about places we three knew.  "Mr. Reddeman"was a wonderful teacher to our sons.  Happy Anniversary!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Russ and Donna Hanson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary to the coolest couple I know!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sue Beach]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wow! Lois (my 6th grade Current Events teacher) and Richard have been married for FIFTY YEARS!  /RYour wedding ceremony story still cracks me up whenever I think of it. /R /RMay God bless you always.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ken Ramsey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We want to congratulate you on fifty years  of marriage ! That is a major accomplishment ! God bless you both and grant you many more years together . You have been truly faithful servants in your life together. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tawfic and Sylvia Tillawi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can only pray that I can play euchre as well as the both of you when I'm that old!!  LOL!! Seriously...you are a very inspiring couple that make me smile as soon as I see you. Thank you for sharing your love and your love in God with the rest of us!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Therisa Hilt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations to the Reddemanns, long-time friends , fellow workers in God's vineyard, and neighbors when they bought the former parsonage and moved it next to us on Inwood Drive.. Together we vacated the street between us and even shared a lawnmower. God"s   Blessing"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim and Liz Ackmann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy anniversary! Hope to see you at the Tincaps this summer!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin, Lisa, Andy and Katie Wilder ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We all wish you both best wishes on your special occasion of 50th wedding anniversary!!  May the good Lord continue to bless you with many more years together!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Roy, Deb and Trent Neilson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[After 10 years here, both Yvonne and I are still trying to fill your shoes! Thanks for modeling servanthood and marriage to our congregation. Thanks be to God for 50 wonderful years centered in Him. To God be the glory!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rich & Yvonne Schwantz & kids]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[May the Lord bless you with many more happy healthy years together.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rich & Linda Kraus]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Dear Friends, Congrats on y0ur  50th. Hope the Tin Caps win 50.  We are on64, so the best are yet to come. Blessings in bundles. Gint and Norma]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ Gint and Norma Herzog]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ We are blessed to call you Friends.  30+ years of Cottage Group.  Laughter and tears./RYou both like to play GAMES!!  Showing your love of Christ in everything you do.We found  we like baseball  because of you!  Your marriage is a great example of a Christ-centered one.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[No more characters!  Love, Teeple's]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The world will always need people like you who give so generously, help so willingly, and care so deeply.  Congratulations on 50 years of marriage.  May God bless you today and always in unexpected ways.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jerry and Peggy Fuhrmann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have a lifetime of experiences that speak to your generosity. You have generously given of your time, your home, your laughter (and your baseball tickets!) The result is a full life of devoted friends and family  who love and appreciate you both./R/RHappy Anniversary!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lisa Strauss]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When you two came in town, you took us to the old Natatorium building. It had an old swimming pool which housed dolphins and sea lions for performances to lure diners looking for an unique experience. An unique experience it was with a wonderful couple! Congratulations!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Ackmann Girls from Milwaukee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary to you both! I remember going to visit you in Indiana.  My sister, Julie, and I always had fun playing with Gail and Jill.  God's blessings to you on many more happy years.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Teresa Howard Hansen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I just wanted to thank you for teaching all three of our children.  They all graduated from college, and Matthew got his MBA at I. U.  Lois, I think of you every time I make your delicious corn casserole. I have given the recipe to many people. Blessings to you both. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ron and Marcy Thieme ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 50th Wedding Anniversary to one of the best 5th grade teachers a girl could ask for! Hope you both are doing well!/R/RP.S. We still enjoy the corn casserole Lois shared with my mom years ago.  She usually makes it everytime I visit! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Erika Thieme]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love you both. The fun we've shared - shopping, dieting, golf, baseball, waking the pool, rummey! But most of all you are blessed for the care you gave Mom & Dad. You're great people and we're proud to be related. 50 years is a great start!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob and Carol]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From the day I was born you have been true family, allowing me to share your beautiful lives: baptisms to weddings; golf rounds to betting on ponies; talking us through popping corks, to every day life. I can never thank you enough for your love. Anniversary blessings!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lisa Slack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You two always find a way to "Bam! Kick it up a notch!" in everything you do. What a joy it has been to learn and grow and laugh with you for more than 40 of the 50 years you've been together. May our gracious God continue to smile upon you & find everything ON SALE!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Don and Ellen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congrats on the Anniversary!/RThe two of you have been a blessing to so many people. /RAppreciate the energy that you bring to all you do.  At church, as a teacher and spouse, or as volunteers, you have a way of making others smile. /RThanks ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve & Laurie Grim & Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bringing Andy to Valpo then him meeting you for the first time; he was very nervous & afraid he wouldn't be comfortable there. What a surprise for him! Special times ??????]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom & Chris Kuwazaki]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One summer @ mom & dads, next door to the Reddemanns, I was cutting our grass and knew Richard & Lois were working, so I cut theirs also. At school, dad said Rich told him they both thought the other had cut it and were puzzled how it got done. Ah, the power of prayer.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom & Sue Ackmann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom and Dad - You have been a wonderful example for us of a loving, Christian couple. /R/R"...Because she/he's the center of my life" (said with or without sarcasm.) You ARE the center of each other's life, with God's arms around you and us, blessed to be your family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gail, David, Nate & Nolan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Friends are like pillars on your porch.  Sometimes they hold you up & sometimes they lean on you."  We've known both aspects over our 50+ years of a God-blessed friendship.  MANY shared times to cherish.  Thanks for the memories!  Blessings on your Golden Anniversary!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sharing June 20, Jerry & Ronnie ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am so blessed to know two very special people that the Lord has placed in my life. I enjoyed my teaching days with helping Mr. Reddemann with all those athletic ribbons at the end of the year. Lois always has a great laugh and wonderful words to share!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Judy Hart]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 50th Mr. And Mrs. Reddemann!  You were always such great parents to us all!  I remember feeling welcome, warm and happy around you two.  Thanks for being such a great couple and a wonderful example for me!  Wishing you many more together ???? ????]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Becky (Borchelt)Bunnell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congrats to to both of you! Neither of you look a day over 50 years, so it's hard to believe you've been married that long. God's Blessings!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff Smith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your kindness and friendship is truly a blessing to me. What joy to talk and laugh with you both as we have come to know each other better. The reflection of your love for Christ and each other shines brightly. Congratulations and blessings for many years to come.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Luann Fyock ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I don't know of a couple that loves to laugh together more than you two!  Your faith in God is evident in all situations.  It's such a privilege to get to worship with you and serve the Lord with you at Concordia for all these years.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tracy Gayer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So many fond memories of both Richard and Lois. Loved listening to Encyclopedia Brown in forth grade and then getting to work side by side with one of my favorite teachers as a colleague years later. Lois gave Chris Ackmann and I a lesson in counting calories on doritos]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Erin Mickelini ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It was such an amazing day when our first grandaughter, Gwen, was born.  To make it even better, Lois and Richard were there to share it with us - a memory we'll always treasure.  Happy anniversary - we love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kirsten and Mark Abresch]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary to an awesome couple whom we have had the pleasure of knowing for many years. Our children were blessed to have Richard for a teacher and to this day say the scrambled eggs he and Lois prepared in class for them were the best of memories. God's bless!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim and Jenny Adair]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on your Golden Anniversary! The two of you have positively impacted the lives of thousands. We are so richly blessed to have known you! May our almighty God grant you good health and many more years of married life! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randy, Ginny, David, Nate Schroeder]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Dear Dick and Lois Congrats on your 50th.  Wehave passed this and the best is yet to come.  Blessings in bundles. Maybe the Tin caps will win 50,too.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ Gint and Norma Herzog]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Gail was the 1st Reddeman I met. Her laugh & jovial personality I thought was unique. When I met Dick & Lois I immediately saw where she got it.  Thanks for being kind & for fun H.S. memories. Happy 50th! I'm sure you will enjoy many more years together with laughter. ?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laugh & Enjoy, Kate Macke(Brubaker)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It was great seeing you at Cindy's Diner. It was fun to hear what you are doing with the church and community. Hope to see you again downtown this summer.  We most likely will see you at one of the Tin Cap games. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate Brubaker and clan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Lois & Dick! You two are such an inspiration to us!  We pray you continue to impact so many around you with your contagious spirit and joy for life. Your servant hearts and love of God radiates through all you do! To God be the glory!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brett & Anne-Marie Stedge]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Dick and Lois,/RWe certainly enjoyed your new and enchanting apartment.  We can tell that you are well adjusted to city life, especially being so close to "Parkview Field."  May the Lord continue to bless you in your married life together.  In Jesus' love.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ron and Lynn Francis ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lois, I am honored to have known you all these years--you have such an upbeat, delightful personality.  And, Dick, I don't personally know you well, but my son-in-law Mark Adair said you were the best teacher he had in school, and that's good enough for me!  Happy Day!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Judy Hill]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My boys and I played so many games of cards with Lois and Dick (and Ted and Ruth), but my most precious memory of these card games were the conversations - the support for my boys and me and the Christian witness which changed my life. God bless you both!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vera Abresch]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The memory that always sticks in my head of Dick & Lois is when Lisa came home from their house one day and said they were playing "Naked Crossword" . . . doing the Sunday paper crossword naked!  This of course was not true but has become a running joke that has lasted!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vince Slack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember Mr. Reddemann teaching us "With the Lord Begin Your Task" during morning devotions. And I always knew it was Cottage Bible Study night when I heard Mr. and Mrs. Reddemann laughing down the hall! You both set a winsome example to me of a life of faith and joy!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff Teeple]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on 50 years of marriage.  We've enjoyed getting to know you these past years.  You're  two very fine Christians who contribute so much to Concordia with your smiles and friendliness./R May God bless you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paul and Carolyn Wolf]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Have a Happy Anniversary and many more happy healthy years./RBlessings,/RJan Ward]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jan Ward]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always enjoyed my visits to Ft. Wayne.  I appreciated the family and community that you have built as well as the mid-west experience.  Those trips have been inspiration for the life I lead now.  I also blame you for taking me to Wrigley and my becoming a Cubs fan.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rob Reddemann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy anniversary to a very special couple. May God continue to richly bless you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Al & Janell Hoeppner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When the Reddemanns first came to town I remember meeting Lois at Ronnie's home.  Through our club, Vesta I have learned to know and love her.  She and Dick seem like a great couple the few times I have seen them together. /RI now say Happy Anniversary!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Evelyn Bickel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite memories of you both is thinking back to all the times I'd see you with my parents for Cottage Group over the years. Just knowing that my parents have such a strong relationship with you is a blessing. Congratulations and many blessings to you today!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrew Teeple]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Anniversary blessings to the best married couple we know! The love you have for the Lord and each other shows boldly in your lives and overflows to others. We are so blessed and thankful to have such amazing friends. We wanna be married like you are married~with 2 TVs!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marc and Kim Pape]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We will always treasure our 1987 visit with you.  You made us feel so welcome.  Fruit Pizza and the Indy 500.  We have many other special memories of you two lovely friends-family.  Warm and loving thoughts to ALL of you.  Come see us in Paradise!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Judi and Jack Moran]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wishing the two of you a very Happy 50th Anniversary, what blessed, cherished time in your life and to have your children be a witness to sucha special precious moment ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ Aliki Magana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We want to wish you a very special celebration of your 50th wedding anniversary.  May you have a wonderful time with your family - recalling memories and making new ones!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ruth and Del Proctor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my fondest memories of you two is when Rob & I arrived for Gail's wedding. You remembered it was my birthday & despite all the wedding bustle, had a cake to celebrate. It was so incredibly thoughtful & made me really feel like part of the family. Love you both!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Val Reddemann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When we think of Dick and Lois, we always smile!  They are one of the most kind, generous, and giving couples that we have ever known.  This godly couple genuinely cares for others, for the Lord, and His church.  /RPhil 1:3, "I thank my God upon every remembrance of you"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pastor Doug & Sharon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on your 50th Wedding Anniversary!/RThere are many memories but the day you hosted our 4th grade class for a seafood tasting in your home is one I'll never forget./RThanks for being such a remarkable Christian couple./RGod Bless you Always.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Vandre]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 50th Anniversary to the both of you!!! When I think of the two of you, the words love, light, laughter and big beautiful smiles come to mind. Have a wonderful and blessed day and here's to 50 more! /RLoving you always.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shauna Leigh Alexander]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>