<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2181-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/4/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Lisa Guignard]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[6423 Calle Esperanza]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Pleasanton]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[CA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[94566]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDEX_FEDEX2DAY]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[purple]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[You are special to us!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Ms. Rombach - Our Kindergarten Teacher at Donlon Elementary 2014-2015]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Your KinderCubs 2014-2015]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best teacher because you teach us, you let us draw, let us play and number bonds. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paxton lee ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best teacher because you teach us, you let us draw, let us play and number bonds. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paxton lee ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Ms.Rombach?/RYou are the best teacher because you are very nice and you taught Kathy a lot of things?when Kathy came your class she can't speaking English?but now she improved a lot. My English is also very poor?but you don't mind?thank you very much. We all love you?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Suying zeng]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are nice, you taught me number bonds, helped me learn harder words, and you are an awesome teacher.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julian Bakar]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best teacher because you're nice and you give us free choice and you let us do some fun things! :-)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Emily Hsu]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ms. Rombach is the the best teacher because... She teaches me lots of things and takes us lots of places. She lets me do special things in the classroom. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Johnny Costello ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your care and support in ensuring that our children are safe, loved and nurtured is vividly evident in all that you do. Thank you for taking such good care of our little loves.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John and Amy Costello ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Ms. Rombach,/RYou are the best teacher because you are caring and sweet. You inspires and brings out the best in me. Thank you being such a wonderful and loving teacher. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aswathy Krishna]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best teacher in the world because you are nice and you teach us well. You help me whenever im stuck. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aadvik Gupta]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best teacher because you are so kind and you are a great teacher!  I liked learning how to read and write.  I loved coming to school because I learned a lot.  I will miss being in your class!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Luke Watson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are so nice! I enjoyed the class so much and made many friends.  Thanks to you, I learned a lot and my English became much better.  Thank you for being an awesome teacher to me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chloe Lee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You let me read and I like to read. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Reese Szyrko ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best teacher because you taught me how to read, learn my heart words and let me draw.  I will miss you when I go to first grade but will come visit you.  Ms. Rombach, I love you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sydney Fernstrom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best teacher because you taught me math, my sight words and to love to read.  You gave me a hug when I was sad and it made me feel better.  You are very special and I will miss you.  You are cool! /R Ms. Rombach, I LOVE YOU!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenna Fernstrom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best teacher because you are thoughtful, caring, smart and funny!   /RYou make learning fun!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenna Fernstrom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best teacher because you taught us what embarrassed means.... like when you toot in class when everyone is seating on the  carpet.....thats embarrassing!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenna and Sydney Fernstrom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best teacher in the world because you taught me number bonds and how to count to 100. And because you are very nice.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maddie White]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Ms. Rombach!! /RThank you so much for a wonderful year. Tanay had the greatest time in your class. According to him (and me), you're the best teacher ever. Keep up the good work. Wishing you the best in all your endeavors.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chittoor Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[...I have learned so much.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grace Digman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[you are the best teacher because you read story to us and help us do cool project.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vibushi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Ms. Rombach, I like how you let us do awesome projects and play during recess. I like how you make us do free choice. I like how you get snacks for us during recess.Thank you, Ms. Rombach for doing all of this.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tanay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi miss Rombach.You are the best teacher.I wish I have you as my teacher in all my coming grades. I love u because you teach us so good,I love the way you tell us stories.My best thing to do with you is everything.I am going to miss you very much]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[love Shreya]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best teacher because you are kind. You have taught me how to write stories and opinions. You read to us and give us free choice. You have helped me do an awesome project. You have taught me to be a good and focused listener. I will miss you.  Love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vikram Hazarika]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ms. Rombach, you are the best teacher because you teach me a lot of interesting things. I really like when you let us do math tubs and free choice. We also like your weekly email updates and website too! Thank you for a wonderful school year! Have a great summer!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joel, Jill and Jones Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best teacher because you are nice, you help us with math, and you have long hair like me. I love you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amelia Greene]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She is nice and let us have free choice!/RLove,/RNureen]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You make learning fun. Saleem looks forward to going to school every day. He is always exited when he talks about his teacher and how much he learned.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aziz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best because you make learning fun. I love and look forward to going to school every day. I am always happy when I talk about you and how much I learn from you. I will miss you a lot next year. I wish you can be my teacher next year. Thank you so much!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Saleem Aziz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best teacher because you showed smile with  warm voice to children .I believe you have warm heart.You are just perfect teacher for parents who always worry about little one at school.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aaron and Aaron mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best teacher because you are so pretty!/RYou are the best teacher because you read story to me!/RYou are the best teacher because I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ I love you because you read books .You are very kind & nice always .You taught me math & how to read & write books . ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Agastya Kuluvalli ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best teacher because you are nice and special because you give people band aids when they get hurt and when they have to have a band aid when they have blood. You are loving and kind.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lily Wallen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No child ever forgets their Kindergarten teacher. You have been so kind, patient and loving to these precious little ones in your care. We will never forget you either. xo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Emily and Jonathan White]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best teacher because you are pretty.  You helped me learn to write and read.  You were always there to help me when I needed help.  I love to read now because of you.  You helped me be a better person.  I will miss you!   /R       I love you!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leila]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best teacher because you are very nice and kind.  I liked when you gave me a birthday hug.  You are very special to me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anwita]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Words cannot express how special you have been.You made every child feel very special and that they can do anything. Each of them will always remember you. You made their first experience at school unforgettable.Thank you for making it perfect! You are simply the best!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All the Best, Lisa & Mike Fernstrom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>