<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2182-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/4/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Tanya Oursler]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Arlington]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[VA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[22209]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Congratulations! Class of 2015]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Delaney Oursler]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Aunt Tanya & Aunt Kay]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love your hugs! They really express that you are happy to see me. It always makes me feel very good. I think how a person hugs says a lot about them. Yours say that you are a genuine, very sweet & kind person! This I know to be true :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Tanya]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My precious sweet little Laneybug,from the first time I held you, I knew what a special person you are.  Your tremendous love for others and for all God's creatures is a ray of sunshine./RYou show this true love in all that you say and do.  I'm so very proud of you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mimi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Delaney, you are a horse lover - after my own heart. You are caring and loving toward animals. Commitment runs strong with you. The strength of a person is shown by the caring of animals - you will excel in whatever you choose to do. Congratulations!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Abby Oursler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love your focus on anything you tend to. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Zac, Bethany & Van Johnson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about you, Delaney, is your openness and enthusiasm regarding new experiences, people, and places. I love that you seek the positive and are willing to discover the value in each new opportunity. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With love and admiration, Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love your spirit! Whether you are cutting up and being silly, leading a guitar sing-a-long, or just hanging out and chit-chatting...you always make me smile! :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Kay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I like most about Delaney is her ability to care for others, no matter what situation she's in.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Parker Hazlebeck]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are my best friend and the light of my life. You make me and everyone around you incredibly happy. Our friendship has taught me so much and I know I wouldn't be the person I am today without you. I love you immensely and I can't wait for the adventures to come]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gussie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I appreciate your hay-raking skills.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Isaac G]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you more than all the Nutella, mountains, and beluga whales in the world]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gussie (again)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about you is that you will spend 15 minutes laughing uncontrollably at the silliest things with me./RAnd I of course love your beautiful harmonious singing]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gussie (third time's a charm)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are so many things to love about you, but one of my favorite things is that you are selflessly kind. You never hesitate to do your best to make someone smile and you go out of your way to be kind. I love you so much <3!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julia Groff]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always have enjoyed your smile and sweet personality. You are warm and approachable and I wish we had lived closer to each other. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Melinda Oursler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that we share a passion for many of the same things - playing the guitar/music, snow skiing, horses, the mountains/nature.../RKeep these things in your life always. Your passions help fuel your happiness!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Tanya]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It is difficult to only say one thing I like most about you. If I take all the things I like and put them together the result is you are COOL!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Papa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Delaney, the one thing I like most about you is your sincere "Sweetness." In the year that you came to my classroom everyday, there was never a time when you seem self-absorbed, or in a poor mood. You made me feel appreciated, and that is a great gift to give.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Dickson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Delaney, /RI have been your teacher for such a short time but have enjoyed your upbeat spirit and focus in class immensely. You clearly have many talents and will thrive in college. Best wishes for much success in all your future endeavors! Keep horsing around!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dr. Clarke]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Delaney!  You are beautiful in every way ~  inside & out!! /RWhat I like most about you is your energy, your passion and your loving spirit. /RThe doors of opportunity are open & ready for you!!/RI wish you love & luck in all you do!/RLove you/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Dina]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Delaney,/RThere are so many things to love most about my first Grandaughter!! I'm so pleased that you have the love of horses and riding. A real chip off the old block. It's such a pleasure and a joy to watch you ride! Best of luck in your future endeavours.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Grandpa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Delaney, YOU are scintillating and have such a joy and zest for the moment.  What I admire the most is your concentration.  Whether perched on a horse, reading surrounded by chaos and screaming babies, or doing a yoga pose; you just attack it. Keep embracing life!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lots of Love,  Holly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite memories of you when you were about four years old; On a visti to Hickory, you, your parents and I went furniture shopping. While they shopped, you and I ran around the store, played hide and seek, and you brought a smile to every face in the store. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle JuJu]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Many people commented, "Your daughter is so beautiful". I didn’t feel even a little guilty not telling them you were my sweet precious niece. Now you are my Sweet Precious Niece, and a wonderful young lady. I love you & look forward to seeing your bright future unfold.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle JuJu]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My sweet niece, Delaney, you're grown up now!  The image that I always remember, is you as a tiny baby with a "big" spiky hairdo sitting ON the kitchen table in NJ, with your Dad behind you, manipulating your tiny legs to kick ice cubes across the table!  u r inspiring!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Aunt Tammy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Delaney has an inexhaustible reservoir of effervescent charm, enthusiasm, and joy that I find a constant source of wonder. At the same time, she has developed a mature, nuanced understanding of herself and others. She is simply one of the most delightful people I know.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin Sparks]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Real life and real living are not related to how rich we are."  Luke 12:15/R/RIn life we don't need to learn how to get more, but how to get along with what we've got, and to get on with the business of living....to seek the joy of being alive.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Missy Schenck]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Be your best me - the quality of your character really matters./RKeep the Respect Circle - respect yourself, respect each other, and respect all living things./RHold the Woodcraft Laws close: /RLove - Be kind/RTruth - Play fair/RBeauty - Be clean/RFortitude - Be brave]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Missy Schenck]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Delaney, I'm so thankful to have you as an older sister. You have always helped me when I need it. I wouldn't be who I am today with out you./R/R/RThank you for all the great memories, love you big sis! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Catie Rett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love her 'cause she plays with me sometimes and she's soft and cuddly.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Emme]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Justin is out of the country but know he thinks the world of you!  A favorite memory-you & Justin always together playing/in the pool at my house in Phoenix-you 2 would only eat MacMac(still use that term today). We love you Delaney & wish the very best in life for you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Dave & Justin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What we love most about Delaney is that she is so sweet and loving and so much fun to be with...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gramma and Grampa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The thing I like most about Delaney is her beautiful personality. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Addison Reed :)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for dealing with my inability to compliment you and with my Starbucks tantrums. You're always there for me and I love you! I'm really gonna miss you! You're gonna slay next year. :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[C-dizzle (no one calls me that)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love how well rounded and down to earth you are ~ always making those around you feel welcomed and loved!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Heidi and Uncle David]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that Laurel has you to share curly hair problems because I don't have a clue! :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Straight haired Heidi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I wish I had your hair]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Toe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(1/4)Yo, Delaney, can I just throw it back down the road a tad? Let's go back to meeting at 242 (because we were classy from day1) in our respective braids and dresses a la Little House on the Prairie. Man, we were Laura Ingles WILDIN'. I'll keep the timeline brief, but]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larkin "L-Dawg" Schramm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(2/4)from becoming weird enemies in 2nd grade to endless inside jokes in 12th, we grew as 2 hopelessly entangled plants, probably something worse than a potato. Delaney, you're my roots & I couldn't imagine a day without you. Every day I wake up to the card you gave me]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larkin "L-Dawg" Schramm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(3/4)with a list of 10 happy things you like about me, and it gets me through the day no matter how chaotic. If I could, I'd get it as a tattoo. I feel your emotions like my own: when you're sad, all I want to do is try to cheer you up. When you're hella turnt, so am I.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larkin "L-Dawg" Schramm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(4/4)I'll never have as much respect for someone's presence in and perspective on life as I do yours. You're part of me: more than friends, more than family, and that will never change no matter the circumstance. I'm proud of you, always will be. Best friend, I love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larkin "L-Dawg" Schramm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations, Delaney! I remember so vividly your work on the HDS graduation video. Your artistic ability combined with your perseverance was a joy to watch. You have what it takes! Pursue your wonderful dreams.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sheran Thompson, Hickory Day School]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your natural gift with animals is inspiring and heartwarming. Nurture this gift and it will take you far.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Jill]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[D - this year has been a hell of a year. I've gotten a lot closer to you this year and I wish I could have known you longer. Thanks for everything and I'm very honored and lucky to call you one of my friends because I have none. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love ya long time, Sawnt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Delaney! I'm not sure what the name actually means but Delaney should definitely mean laughter, happiness, fun, just everything rolled into one. Not a firecracker but like a sparkler or those trick birthday candles!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Muuuuuuch love, Grace Bollinger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Have to say I love your infectious, exuberant laugh the most. But your selfless desire to elicit a smile in others is a close second. Can't wait to see where your many talents take you in life. I LOVE YOU.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how sincerely you care about others. You are always the first to offer assistance, advice, support, and (most importantly) love whenever anyone needs it. I am #blessed to have you by my side on this journey through life. Love you long time, boo. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[emily deal]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Delaney you are oodles and oodles of fun and very much kind 12/10.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Morgan Honeycutt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(1 of 3) Early in Miss Delaney's experiences at Hickory Day School, she set herself apart as, "the female thinker, carrying the banner."  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mrs. Dollar]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(2 of 3 )  She was fearless as she represented her own views, but could immediately rise into a leadership role as communicator conveying the position of her peers.  Delaney is such a "purist" in that her ability to reflect is quite amazing. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mrs. Dollar]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(3 or 3)   I have been in the field of education for 43 years, and Delaney is indelible as the gifted young lady with the gift for the future.  Love and spirit to a lovely young lady ...Power, Strength, and Presence...Always...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mrs. Dollar]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The fact that she has an EXCELLENT sense of humor unlike most]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peter of kolbear]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Delaney is her confidence and love of the outdoors.   One year, we went to Pisgah National Forest for REACH and a trail ride. I was nervous, but Delaney made it look effortless. The view from the mountain top is so sweet because of the hike!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tina Farr]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Delaney is like the sweetest cantaloupe./R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dylan Tashjian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Delaney - thank you for always being a little burst of energy and life everyday. Your love of all things and beautiful personality make you a genuine friend. Good luck at E&H!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julia Kessel ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[D - as I read all of your sentiments, I see a consistency in how people feel about you! It makes me so very proud to have you as my niece. You are one of a kind & I know you will excel in anything you put your mind to. I know you will thrive at E&H-I am excited for you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Tanya (1 of 3)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[These attributes shine through you based on all of the people who know you:/RCaring for Others & Animals, Kind Spirit, Funny & Fun, Help People,  Love for Nature, Make People Feel Good, Loving & Sweet, Great Friend, Energy, Passion, Focus, Fabulous Personality...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Tanya (2 of 3)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Commitment, Enthusiasm, Genuine, Upbeat, Perseverance, Down to Earth, Well Rounded, & Great Hair :) I think all of those things are true about you & know why so many people wanted to participate in your gift! Remember all of these attributes sweetheart! You are a GEM!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I LOVE YOU! Aunt Tanya (3 of 3)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>