<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2272-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/10/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Randy Weinstein]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[877 Jennifer Lane]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Berwyn]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19312]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Josh]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Joshua Young]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Randy, Alex, Trevor, Jack &Tucker]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always put everyone else first./RYou make me smile./RYou are the rock of the family./RYour hotness./RYou.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can't name only ONE thing I like about Josh. He's bright, funny, generous, intuitive and has a huge heart. He's also a very loyal friend. To quote a gift he gave me, "True friends are hard to find and impossible to forget." I'm so lucky to have him as my true friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heather ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We don't get to see you often, but when we do we find you warm and welcoming.  We enjoy your stimulating conversation on a variety of subjects and find you to be highly intelligent.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Carol and Uncle Paul]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[His sense of humor...we share a love of finding the absurd in human behavior and situations, and he never fails to make me laugh.  In addition, his kindness and willingness to help when needed shows what a caring person he is. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Suzanne Malik]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Josh.  You are the most generous person I know as far as giving of yourself.  Thanks for making my son so happy]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always enjoy being with  Josh.  He is funny, warm, and so wonderful to be around.  Love ya Cuz!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Missy Ruddick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He makes me laugh out loud.  He definitely has a quick wit that I love! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian Fishbone]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It will be my never ending goal to dress as nice as Josh! Happy Birthday Brotha!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JP Hussey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What can I (we) say. Your an amazing, talent, and dynamic individual. Your my (our) rock and one my champions. Your my friend, brother, and advocate. Thank you for always being there through thick and thin. I look forward to celebrating so much more life with you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you- Rachael]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am so lucky that Randy found you and that you make him so happy.  I know you will always be there for us because you are so caring and sensitive.  I love you and am proud to call you my son.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The directions were to name one think I like most about you.  Impossible.  Kind, smart, funny, thoughtful, generous...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Jody]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Josh for his 3 Gs:  generous, genuine, and gangsta.  We miss you!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Little Mike]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like your mannerisms, which are self-possessed and intelligent. You move thoughtfully, and you interact with others with a great deal of emotional depth. You are generous, kind, and down-to-earth, and I always enjoy talking to you. Have the best birthday ever! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brandi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Josh is the best!  Smart, funny, loyal and always well dressed.  Also he's sarcastic, a mind reader, and has impeccable taste in home décor, design, and wine.  Most of all, he is so honest and loving.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ AndreaFishelberg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You bring out the best in my brother and for that I am forever grateful.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your generousity. And not just with your discount! With your sarcasm (which I love) your time, your cooking tips, decor advice.... Alex and Trevor are being given a beautiful example of how to give back. Happiest of Birthdays to you!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vicky ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My life is so much richer because I have you in it.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Grrrrrrr]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ruff ruff ruff]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tucker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love you Papa.  Why do ya always talka like dis?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Trevor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love my family and my Papa.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I cannot imagine my life without you being a part of it.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[On a scale of one to 10, I’d give you a nine—and I’m the one you need!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Are you a banana? Because I find you a-peel-ing]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A kiss is a lovely trick designed by nature to stop speech when words become superfluous.” –Ingrid Bergman/R/RKisses whenever you want.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your lips are like wine, and I want to get drunk.  –William Shakespeare]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are not enough days in forever to allow me to fully express the depth of my love for you. –Steve Maraboli]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ You must allow me to tell you how ardently I admire and love you. –Pride and Prejudice]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ You are the best thing that has ever happened to me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If love were a cup of coffee, it would be a mocha latte - sweet, hot and filled with pep.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Barista from Starbucks]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Josh is always warm and is the first person to greet you when you walk into a crowded room. Also, his name never gets old!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JB]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Josh,/R    Happy Birthday young man!  Wishing you all things wonderful today and everyday!  You are a true friend.  We are lucky to have you in our lives!  Enjoy your day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Ostroff Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Josh,/RI hope you have a great birthday, anniversary, and Father's Day!  All wonderful things to celebrate!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brid Devlin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're the best dance partner at a downtown gay club a girl could ask for. I love your fire for life and helping others and you're "wild side"! You give the best advice and I am happy to have you and your family in my life.Cheers to you on your bday-lets go celebrate!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kristen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Josh has a way of weaving himself into your heart.  He is so caring and giving.  I know if I ever need anything he would always be there for me./Rxoxoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellen Freeman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Josh!  It is a pleasure to be a co-committee person in our precinct with you. You are so organized and welcoming to everyone we meet. You always look on the bright side of things. Thanks for letting me be a small part of your "bread donation pickup". ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Arlene Talley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From the get go, Josh has been welcoming and kind.  He cares greatly for those in his life and I am lucky to have him as a friend.  Thanks for sharing your heart so openly.  All the best on your birthday, Josh!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jon Blandford]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Josh, you are such a wonderful addition to the family...a true .Renaissance man! Love talking to you about anything and appreciate your /Rsincerity and willingness to help./R/RHappy Birthday!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Joyce & Uncle Gerald]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In  your prosperity you never forget those with little or nothing; you  give your time and effort to improve their lives.  We're proud of you.  We're so happy to see the joy and love you bring to and elicit from Randy and those adorable grandkids. /RLove always, Mom&Dad]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Evelyn & Chick Young]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The things we like best about Josh are the great discounts, gifts and gift ideas from Pottery Barn Kids.  He’s also hilarious; his cutting sense of humor keeps sh!t real around the Thanksgiving turkey.  Oh and he’s very well groomed.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Jason, Reiko, Jessie, Sonny Jo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a smart, happy and handsome man with a great smile and a wonderful laugh.  You are always willing to help and your care for people is evident in all you do.  I am honored to know you and call you my friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carol Lynn Claypoole]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When fish are in schools, they sometimes take debate.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellen Degeneres]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Police were summoned to a daycare center where a three-year-old was resisting a rest.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellen Degeneres]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When you've seen one shopping center you've seen a mall.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellen Degeneres]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The guy who fell onto an upholstery machine is now fully recovered.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellen Degeneres]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Just looking at you makes me smile,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Do you remember when I was two and we were driving and you saw the deer on the side of the road and we had ice cream and you got a drop on your pants.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I want to go spanky.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Trevor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love is love.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>