<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2289-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/11/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Jill Bodian]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[1148 Fifth Avenue]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[Apt 2-A]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[New York]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[NY]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[10128]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_60]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 60th Bob!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Bob Bodian in celebration of his 60th birthday]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[From your friends and family]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 60th birthday to my golf sensei and good friend. I so respect your intellect, humor and joi de vivre. You are a great lawyer but an even better person. I am glad that we reconnected and that you brought Jill and your "kids"into my life. I am missing Mamma at JB's.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[alvin Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 60th birthday to my golf sensei and good friend. I so respect your intellect, humor and joi de vivre. You are a great lawyer but an even better person. I am glad that we reconnected and that you brought Jill and your "kids"into my life. I am missing Mamma at JB's.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alvin Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We are always so happy to celebrate your birthday with you.  But 60? Seriously? You're a baby!/R/RHappy one!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marilyn and Stuart ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bob we feel so blessed to have you in our lives!  To a great friend and a wonderful guy!  With much love, have a very HAPPY BIRTHDAY! /R/REnd Siri....stop typing... damn it ..it keeps typing.  Stop Siri! Siri stop.... ugh]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Patrick and Peter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Uncle Bob]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Celine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Bob! Love all the O'Sheas]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[O'Shea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are certain people in the world that are true friends and be counted on in times of great stress and woe...Bob is that person and has been for the Gray's ...but he does it with confidence, calm and humor... that makes you feel safe and with a high level of trust..]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Richard Gray]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Bob - happy bday ! You and Jill are our favorite new friends - thanks for including us in the festivities . The "happiness" book that we're reading says make new friends and reach out - you're good at that and you've all blended because you're such a great dad! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Willa and Kevin ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bob shares his warmth, affection and wit without reservation! I cannot believe my unique good fortune to have become his friend! Cheers to your 60 years and the joy you have shared with all who count you as a friend!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Liz Janis ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 60th to our great friend...great husband, great dad and step dad, great lawyer, great attitude, great smile, great advice-giver, great attitude, great BBQer, great laugh...So happy to share this great moment with you and Jill.  Happy 60th!!  With all our love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sharon and Bill]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Warren wanted me to ask you if you like him or Mark better?  And he also wanted to remind you that he had better grades in law school.  /RHappy Birthday Bob!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kirsten]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You will always be Batman to me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Teddy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What do you and I have in common, beside our hair styling? We are both old men lucky enough to have young, hot wives! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your pal, Ken Novack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love that Bob makes Jill happy and we love that Bob likes spinning. Watching Bob bike sends a clear signal that you want to be on his side in a legal battle!  It is not pretty but he's tough!   Happy Birthday.  We are so grateful for your friendship. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Goldstein and Bill Popeleski]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Bob!/RYou are a special person, a close friend and when we need help you are always there to steer us in the right direction./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robin & Jeff Weiss]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wishing you a Happy 30th! Hoping all your wishes come true and we see your helmet-less (and hairless) head on our next boys annual ski trip! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love from Napa, Chuck and Franciska]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love you because 1. you have made Jill so happy,thus a wonderful husband; 2. you are so wonderful with Berk  and have a great relationship with him, thus a great stepdad, and 3.,  wonderful with the rest of us,and 4. we love you , thus a homerun!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Fran and Carl]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bob-/R I think all your entire party guest list we agree... to know you is to love you. /RWishing you a memorable 60th soiree./RBTW while your at the grill i'll take  my buger medium rare!/RXO/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jill S.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We can always count on you for friendship, a laugh and hopefully, a get out of jail free card./R/RHappy 60th Birthday, Bob (Mr. Bodian)!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bethany, Bob, Sam & Oliver Millard]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your capacity for joy is unmatched; our luck, as your friends, is basking in that glow./R/RHappy Birthday Bob and thank you for sharing your happiness./R/RMuch love,/R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stacey Stowe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Have a great birthday as well as a great every day, you deserve it. Thank you for 60 years of "nachas"you have given to me]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad and Linda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Bob,/RBest wishes on your 60th! We are so happy to celebrate you and the kind man you are. You are always the first one to offer help when it is needed and we can always count on you to make us laugh.  We feel so lucky to have you as a brother, an Uncle & a friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Sherry, Joel, Bella & Ben]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bob you are truly one of the kindest, most thoughtful and generous people we know!! We were all so lucky to have you in our lives when you married Jill. We gained a new friend! We love you and sorry to have to miss this most special birthday. Love Terry and Jamie.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Terry and Jamie Underberg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I met Bob first as a client but we became friends after watching his quick wit, balanced perspective and tenacious drive in action. Bob has a loyal and devoted group of friends and I am so pleased to be in such company. Happy Birthday Bob!! You are my favorite Yanks fan]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Leavitt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We appreciate your intellect, sense of humor, generosity, compassion, approach to life and your incredible grasp of all that is bacon. We are very fortunate to be counted among your friends. Happy 60th. We look forward to sharing many many more. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Danielle and Steve Gulotta]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday BOB! May the years ahead be filled with many more happy occasions and celebrations! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jane & Ron]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bob, you're not only the man I love & adore, you are the person I aspire to be. Fun, funny, nonjudgmental, quick-witted, generous, calming, smart & kind. You make everything more fun. I'm so lucky for your love & understanding. Thanks for loving Berk like your own. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo, Jill]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bob, we have shared so many adventures together including my favorite a six week cross country trip to the national parks.  I met you with your mom in the seventh grade and we immediately became not good friends but my best friend for a lifetime.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eric ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bobby - you are a conundrum. A leader, but mellow to the core. A lover, but also a commander.  The epitome of good, with just the right touch of bad. But most of all, to me, a friend. And no conundrum there.  Happy birthday, my friend.  Love you, H]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Howard Elman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Not sure exactly what to say re approaching your 60's, but a few things come to mind.  First, be more attentive to trimming your nose hair.  It gets more aggressive after 60.  Ditto ear hairs.  Everywhere else not so much.  You seem to have the rest under control. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, Mark ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bob,/RYou've always been one of my closest friends to whom I turn for counsel, comedy, golf and just plain fun.  Happy Birthday.  Buddies for life./RGreg]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Greg O'Connell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A master of the grill and a tough litigator/RSixty years entitles you to the title of/R/RThe Grilligator!/R/RHappy B-day Bob!/RAnd no stopping skiing/R til we're 80!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andy & Jenny P.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Although we've yet to meet/RI'm sure you're super sweet./RYou must be great/Rto have Jill as your mate!/RWith us it was love/Rat the first "shalom"/RWe look forward to celebrating/Rin your Hampton home!/RA Happy Birthday to you!/RGood health and joy too!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Marla and Jorge Cornejo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Although we are not life long friends, from where I sit, Bob is the perfect combination of  the fierce business person, the amazing husband and father and the wild fun loving guy everyone wants to be with. Happy 60th birthday. 60 more fun loving ones to come!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marcey Brownstein]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Great friend, best sense of humor; One of the finest human beings I've ever met.  Four incredible years of goofing around and laughing at Binghamton-- how did we pass any of our classes?  Happy 60th birthday Stro! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your buddy, Al]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Great guy. Great family. Great lawyer. Have shared many enjoyable sporting events and dinners together. Congratulations on the big day. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Kobricks]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We're so happy to be here to celebrate this milestone with you and Jill.  Here's to many more years of run-ins at every restaurant in the Hamptons!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark and Karin Gardy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Bob,/R/RThanks for the memories at and between east coast arenas and on western rivers.  Thanks for saying "I didn't want to miss nothin'" when you tried to kill us on the Salmon and I asked (once you came up) why you'd steered us into the largest hole on the river. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob Katz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Bob,/R/RHappy 60th Birthday! Hope you enjoy the celebration, quite the milestone. I’ve enjoyed working together and appreciate your friendship. /R/RHope this decade of your 60s is your most fun yet!/RBest wishes,/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Josh Harris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To our new friend Bob----We admire your boundless energy, brains, kindness, and charm----and your fabulous wife! Wishing you a very happy Birthday and all you wish for yourself! Looking forward to spending fun times together! Love, Mindy & Larry]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mindy & Larry Richenstein]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You've made my sister happier than she's ever been. So I'd have loved you no matter what. But you're such a funny, low-key plus to all of our lives. We all love spending time with you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellen, Andrew & Hanan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Bob. Marcy and I want to wish you all the best on this very "historic event." We love your sense of humor, your warmth and most importantly how much you love Jill, the sweetheart of sweethearts!!!!/R ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marcy Finkelstein and Ann Conroy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm going to be selfish & say that some of your best qualities are ones I see reflected in myself, qualities I happen to be proud of: A sense of humor, level-headededness, a prominent butt-chin ;) Thanks for that & for being a supportive and caring father. Love you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Caroline ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Don't do anything really stupid" and "Don't fuck up" are two of my most cherished pieces of advice. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lane]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Walking to Soup Burg in the morning before school were some of my favorite days. Happy 60th Birthday Dad! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lane]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[42 years of friendship and you are still going strong.  Sorry that we cannot be there to celebrate with you.  Hope we can get together soon. All the best on your 60th- happy birthday! St. Louis Wolves!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Der (Mark and Iris)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're really old now. /R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Berk]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Everything in moderation" - I try to remember that every day as I stumble about my business. /R/RThanks for always being there. /RLove you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Berk]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Directly when I think of Bob, it's his good humor and excellent sense of humor that come to mind. But he also has an unusual knack for identifying and encouraging whatever is best in the people around him. I am lucky to count him among my friends.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Victor Mustelier]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>