<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2304-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/12/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Gloria Lopezpesini]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[409 Coldstream]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Berwyn]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19312]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Con Mucho Amor]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Andrea Carro]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[De todos tus amigos en EEUU]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're a special girl!!! I am going to miss how happy you always are, how social, positive.... and LOUD!! /RI'll always remember that I had a "daughter" for a year and how special that was. /RLove you!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gloria ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am going to miss all the things we did together and how much fun it was, you brightened my 7th grade year so I thank you for that/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marcos]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will never forget the inside jokes we had about math class and saying truuu! Andrea has become my twin this school year and I am so glad that I met her this year! We have memories and jokes that nobody will ever understand. Just never give us cupcakes ????????]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amanda Camarote]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I loved your smile, your bubbly personality, and how nicely you became part of our extended family. I loved having another granddaughter I could talk to about school, friends and things like hair and clothes. The boys have learned a lot by having a big sister. Love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nana Jeanne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memories of Andrea are watching her wrestle with Marcos, bounce on the trampoline with Nando, and bicker with Alex. I will also miss her singing of the latest pop songs and her gossip news from Conestoga High School.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Dyer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andrea,/RYou have a been a WONDERFUL babysitter for the kids!  The girls have LOVED your enthusiasm and playfulness!  /RWe are so glad we have gotten to know you!/RYou will be missed by all of us!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Troy Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I vividly remember meeting you at Glenhardie last summer.  When I heard you would be staying a year, I was in awe of how mature that decision was.  Only recently did we start to use you as a babysitter and both Jack and Carly adore you!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Murphy/Nalitt Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dre I'm going to miss you so so so so much. Throughout the year that you have been here I feel like I have become super close with you and I really truly hope we keep in touch. Thanks for hanging out with me all the time and making leaf raking fun! Love you so much dre!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jack Broadhurst]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will miss my fun, kind and fav Spanish girl! I'm so happy I met you and so glad I had you in so many classes and that we could relate our foreign struggles! I love you so much! Te amo muito! Te quiero muchissimo y voy a extrañarte <3 Conestoga no será la misma sin ti!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bruna Giampietro]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[we first met in lit and ceramics class.  We have had a lot of good and fun time together like in ceramics or just hanging out. You were the best friend that any one could ask for. If you ever need to talk to some one just remember I'm always here. I'll miss you so much!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Emily Centofante]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It was so great getting to know you. The girls loved every minute you babysat, especially the "make-up" sessions and dancing to the wii. You will be missed, take care of yourself.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Major's]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whenever, I'm at your home, Andrea, I'm always impressed by how naturally you fit into the Dyer family, as if you'd been there all your life!  You've adapted so well to having three younger brothers, and Gloria and Bill love having a daughter, too!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Un abrazo grande, Carolyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dre, I can't believe that u have actually been here for a whole year. When you go back to Spain, I might actually miss you a little. Thank you so much for watching all those MTV shows with me, especially Faking it. I hope you don't break up with Victor too soon. Love u]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alejandro ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andrea- /RTe voy a echar de menos porque eres muy especial, servicial, simpática y muy alegre. /REspero que no cambies nunca y que te vaya bien tu regreso a España con tu familia. /R¡Vuelve a vernos pronto! /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Martha]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andrea, I'm going to miss playing softball with you so much because this season was awesome and you were such a great friend and team mate! I'll miss you so much! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Caroline Brophy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm so happy we got to share this amazing year and experience together! Having you and the other exchange students as close friends has made things so much easier when we've gone through some tough times (it has also made my Spanish better ;). I'll see you in Europe!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo Eline]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will miss you so much Andrea! It was so much fun getting to know you during the softball season! I'm glad you got to come with us to mi país! You have such a great personality and I hope you come back to visit us very soon! Text me! Muchos besos y abrazos! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sophia and Porras Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It was so nice to get to know Andrea. We only met through softball but she is so energetic and fun. I really am going to miss her constant giggling and craziness. Love her!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ally Wynne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We've had some fun haven't we Baja? It has been wonderful playing ice hockey and softball with you. Remember hitting that guy in the stomach with the lacrosse ball? There was never a boring car ride with you in it. Thanks for keeping things fun! Come back and visit! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I'll miss ya-Sarah Brock-JvB 2015]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We will miss the fun and energy you bring to everything you do.  It has been a great joy to get to know you this year and we look forward to having you stateside again soon! xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Broadhurst Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Munchkin!!!! I am going to miss our trips to the water fountain every morning. I can't believe you are leaving me. I'm so glad I went up to you on your first day to introduce myself. Love you!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sophia Chusid ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andrea freaking Carro. I really have no words to say because nothing can express how much I have grown to love you over this past year. The thought of you not being around makes me want to kick my sister out so you can live with me. I'm am so greatful we are amigas]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Gina Stacey (aka Ginacolada)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Just letting you know that 270 characters is not long enough to write a see you later note. And I say see you later because this isn't goodbye. I'll see you again someday chica. Btw I'm in tears right now and you should be too. Haha te amo mucho chica española. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love again, Gina ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It was nice knowing you. Safe travels back to Spain! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Talen ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm so glad we met. Will miss you like crazy you are such a good friend but not only that you tell me like it is. You were always there for me. I'm going to miss your random jumping on people and weird snapchats. And your sass. Please don't go :'( gonna miss sooo much""]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alexis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andrea - /RYou are very cool. I like sharing my room with you. I hope you liked the room! I love bouncing on the trampoline with you and playing knock out. I will miss your hugs and kisses. I will miss YOU when you leave. ¡¡Te quiero!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nando ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mi española, te voy a extrañar muchísimo. Estoy tan feliz de que seamos amigas, eres una persona super especial para mi y SIEMPRE podrás contar conmigo. Esto no es un adiós, es solo un hasta luego. I love you so much Andrea. I will visit you in Spain. I promise.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paulina Chiriboga]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ay, mi favorita persona espanola (Alex is stupid), I'm gonna miss you! I still remember when I met you like 3 years ago and you tricked me into thinking you couldn't speak English. We've made SO many more memories, even while Dr. Rhude-Faust is yelling. Hope 2 c u soon!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Murph]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Andrea I'm going to miss you so much next year. A few things I'll miss include the way the you light up a room especially when anyone is sad you pick them up. I will remember you always and I know you will do amazing things in the future. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jaelynn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey bae, /RYou were my buddy on the field and off the field!!! You always make me laugh and smile. DONT GO BACK TO SPAIN!!! Love you -kate ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate Bailer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andrea:/RHa sido un placer conocerte pues eres una persona muy especial. Te deseo un futuro brillante en el que no dejes nunca de soñar y tener ilusiones. Esperamos verte más veces y que esta despedida no sea un adiós definitivo. Un beso,/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Verónica  ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I’m so glad I was your AFS Liaison! We loved our day in Philly with you. Despite the bitter cold, the smile never left your face as we walked to the Flower Show, the Continental for lunch, and back to Reading Terminal for those amazing Bieler's Donuts! Come visit soon!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barbara, Adam, Avery & Lexi Bashe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our most memorable experience was at your birthday party. We all had a lot of fun and sang to High School Musical. We danced to random music and broke the pinata. It was the most fun that all of us had together. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey nugget! I'm so mad I didn't meet you earlier! Regardless, I will forever cherish every moment! Your presence makes everything so much more fun & lively! I promise to keep in touch & I really hope I get a chance to visit you soon! I love you my little nugget!!<3 Xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your long lost twin, Freya Shah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>