<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2313-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/13/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Elizabeth Smith]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[13914 Bora Bora Way]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[#225]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Marina Del Rey]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[CA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[90292]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDEX_FEDEX2DAY]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sand]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Father's Day!!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Milan]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[We love you! ]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dad,/RI'm so grateful for every moment together and feel so blessed to have you as my dad! Your wisdom, generosity, unconditional love and laughter make you the best dad a girl could ask for! I love you tons!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love always, Mrs. Beely]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Milan, I'm so proud to be marrying your wonderful daughter Elizabeth.  You've been so supportive and it makes us happy to see you and Kate so thrilled for us.  I look forward to calling you my father in law and I hope to make you proud.  All the best this Father's Day.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Milan, I admire the relationship you and Kate have. I think that you two are one of the cutest couples I know!!! Milan and I love seeing you both so happy and enjoying your life together. You are both a great example of a happy marriage we all strive to have. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Anika]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Milan,/RThank you for being such a good father to Tiffany and your other children too. I also want to thank you for the significant and positive role you have as a grandfather. We all love and appreciate you very much. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Ben]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Boppa, thank you for everything. As your oldest grandson and the best looking, I would like to say I got my good looks from you. You are a stud. Happy Father's Day. You are way better than my dad. I like my dad a lot, but you would've been way better! I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Abraham]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Boppa,/R/RHappy Father's Day! Thank you for everything you have done for me. You have created such a great legacy, and I am so glad you are my grandpa. Keep the cologne coming!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Olivia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ (Part 1) /RDear Boppa, thank you for everything you do for me. I really appreciate the walks in our neighborhood, the banjo, how generous you are, taking us to dinner and loving us unconditionally. I will always remember your smell:) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eliza (part 1)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 2)/RI love when you talk about your cases with us. They are very interesting. Happy Father's Day! I love you so much! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Eliza]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 1)/RDear Dad,/RI'm so grateful you're my dad. You love me for who I am. You encourage me to question and learn. You support me in my endeavors. You love my kids. You're generous with us. You come to visit. You inspire me with your work ethic. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany (part 1) ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 2)/RI have fond memories of watching you study topics and write them down at your desk and file them away. I loved listening to your classical music, your Beatles, and your Carpenters. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany (part 2)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 3)/RI really loved it when you would play the piano late at night when we were going to bed. I loved it when you had a huge water fight with me and Courtney. I loved traveling with you. Those are just a few memories. But mostly now, I'm grateful we are friends. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Tiffany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Here's hoping that my "Ancient of Days" brother has a most splendid Father's Day this year! Your children are MOST blessed to call you Dad. I love you dearly.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 1) /RDear Milan: Here’s hoping your Father’s Day will be magnificent. The fact that your children go all out in honoring you on this special day speaks volumes as to the kind of Father you are. I can only speak of the great example you have been to me as a sister. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charlotte (Part 1)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 2)/RYour constant caring attitude and genuine love are so appreciated. I love your phone calls and love the fact that you keep in touch and the words of wisdom you impart to me. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charlotte (Part 2)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 3)/RI admire you so much and am proud to be numbered among your siblings. I hope this day is very special for you and remember you are very loved by me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Charlotte]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What Savannah loves about "Beach Grandpa".../R"His HUGS! And I LOVE him!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Savannah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What Blythe loves about "Beach Grandpa".../R"He taught me about his teeth. If you don't brush your teeth they will fall out" and "I love his hugs"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Blythe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What James loves about "Beach Grandpa".../R"I like how he counts backwards! He is so funny" and " I liked playing rockets with him."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[James]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 1)/RMilan one of my fondest memories of you is from our wedding. It was such an amazing part that you were able to marry us. I remember during the rehearsal during the vows there wasn't a dry eye anywhere. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anika (Part 1)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 2)/RIt was reassuring to me that I was marrying the right person and becoming a part of such a great family and that everyone there felt our love for each other. Thank you for being such a great emotional support during that time.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Anika]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Milan is a very special person in so very many ways:/R/RReason #1 of many: He is a true renaissance man with a lifelong passion for learning. He loves classical music but can also be seen listening to country or Beatles and Elton John. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Reason #2 of many: He loves history and loves to read about major events, political trends, different philosophical approaches and societal evolution. He is a news and political junkie, but never preaches, though he enjoys a good discussion on almost any topic.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Reason #3 of many: He is a good teacher because he is patient and is always willing to approach a topic from any angle that may be helpful so as to present the issues in an understandable way. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Reason #4 of many: He is a good listener-- he can listen without interjecting opinions, he is compassionate and thoughtful in his responses.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 1)/RReason #5 of many: /RHe is a very happy golfer- he loves to go to LACC, or any interesting course, and hit the ball. It doesn't matter too much how he hits them (though he likes to win a few bucks -- $10 is a great bonus to brag about! ) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate (Part 1)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 2)/RHe is just happy to be out, engaging in a fun game, joking with the guys, or playing with Chip, Milan, Chape, Chris, me or the grandkids. He loves being out there and just relaxing on a beautiful day. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Reason #6 of many:/RHe has performed much in the way of community and public service. It has always been part of his life and most rewarding for him.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 1)/RHe has always appreciated the areas in which he has worked. For so many years he provided invaluable counsel to so many clients whether in real estate, corporate, business or family transactions. He has always been respected for his thoughtful, wise advice. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate (Part 1)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 2) /RWhen he walked into a room for client meetings on significant transactions with other lawyers and parties present, Milan was always immediately in control-- he has always had amazing " presence". Today that presence accompanies him into the court room. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate (Part 2)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 3)/RHe is respectful of the advocates, and is proud of our constitution and our system of justice. He is just the right person to be in his position on the 9th Circuit, and it is absolutely the best job for him. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate (Part 3)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 4)/RHe revels in it every day, and performs his duties with enthusiasm and with his ever present thoughtfulness. It is evident that he is well respected by his colleagues! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate (Part 4)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 1)/RReason #8 of many: Milan is a wonderful father. He communicates with all of his children and Brittany frequently. He is always available to discuss an issue and, if asked, is happy to provide caring (very thoughtful) advice. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate (Part 1)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Reason #8, Part 2)/RHe loves and is well loved by all. He is patient and available at all times. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate (Part 2)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Reason #9 of many: He loves spending time with each of his grandchildren, and hearing their questions and opinions. He enjoys all of his siblings and he keeps in good contact with all of them. They all appreciate his love and attention. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 1) /RReason #10 of many: He is also my great love and my best friend. He is a wonderful husband and companion. We laugh a lot, have lots of fun, enjoy our music and our lively discussions on issues and events and support each other in all parts of our lives. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate (Part 1)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Reason #10, Part 2):/RI am incredibly lucky to be able to share my life with him! He is perfect for me...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate (Part 2)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Milan , I wish you a wonderful Father's Day and every day-- you give so much and bring so much joy and interest into so many lives! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With lots of joyful love, Kate]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dad, I'm so grateful for all the sacrifices you made to help produce such loving, caring children.  As a father now, I know how difficult and stressful it must have been to support and raise 6 children. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All my love, Milan III]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dad, I'm so happy that you are able to enjoy this special time in your life with Kate and your “dream job”.  Seeing you happy, always brings a smile to my face.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Milan III]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The kids still think Beach Grandpa has a problem with counting…… 1, 2…… 7……..9 and James, Blythe and Savannah still play the “measuring tape game”, albeit with a few paper cuts when the tape snaps back to their hands…We love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[MilanAnika, James, Blythe, Savannah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Supposedly you can't quantify wisdom, but when someone's personal library is larger than that of a small university, it's gotta be saying something!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 1)/RDear Milan, /RYou are so wise and always offer sound advice and important life lessons. You are comforting and understanding, and make your loved ones feel protected. You are silly and goofy and know how to bring a smile to anyone's face. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brit (Part 1)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 2)/RYou laugh and love with all your heart. I love you very much and am so grateful to have you in my life. Happy Father's Day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Brittster]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 1)/RDear Milan,/RHappy Father's Day!  You may not be my dad, but you have shown parental concern for me these past fifty five years.  You've listened to me talk when I've been troubled about something, and you've offered advice, or sometimes just a listening ear.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica/Bow (Part 1)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 2)/RThank you for all the phone calls and the thoughtful things you've said to me or done for me over the years.  I am grateful to have a big brother like you; brilliant, cultured, funny and loving. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica/Bow (Part 2)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 3) I've heard that you were a dad who helped with homework, and spent individual time with each of your six children.  Your kids were truly blessed by your consistent, meaningful presence in their lives.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica/Bow (Part 3)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 4)/RAnd I am sure you are one of the biggest reasons they have all gone on to be confident, successful adults./R/RTo my brother Milan:  One terrific dad and one wonderful brother.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love and hugs, Jessica/Bow]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 1)/RIn good times and bad, in victory or defeat, whether in life's triumphs or tragedies, there is one constant remaining in the greater Milan D. Smith Family. It is simply this.. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gordon (Part 1)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 2)/R...when a shoulder is needed to lean on, when a joke is helpful to gladden the heart, or when wise counsel is necessary for life's better directions, Milan D. Smith, Jr. is always there, for all of us. /R/RHappy Father's Day, Milan! /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Gordon (Part 2)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Milan has great hair and gives awesome advice and wisdom.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Boppa because he eats a lot of candy everyday.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Camden]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["I love him."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Poppy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Boppa is very funny and he is fun to play with.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grayson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 1)/RDear Dad, /RI am so grateful to have you as my father. Thank you for all your guidance, wisdom, patience, consistency and love over the years. I couldn't be more blessed. You set such a high bar for parenting. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Courtney (Part 1)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 2)/RI hope my children some day feel the same amount of respect and love for me as I feel for you. I love you./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Courtney (Part 2)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I loved going to the courts with Boppa and meeting the other judges. We had lunch afterward and were able to talk a lot. I like talking with Boppa./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Sophie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It was a hard time when I lost my job and Milan was there to give great advice.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Chape]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[M-My rock. He is always there for me./RI-Incredibly patient. He gives so much time to us and others./RL-Lacrimonious (if I used the word correctly :) He is not afraid to show us this side of himself./RA-Admirable. He is an incredible role model for all of us./RN-Never late!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Amanda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 1) /RTulips will always make me think of Dad. We shared a great moment in France when I was 7 with chicken pox and he took me for a walk showing me all of the beautiful tulips. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amanda (Part 1) ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Part 2) /RHe shared a great story about their waking with the sun and closing at night to go to sleep. They are still my favorite flower.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amanda (Part 2)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Reading the Christmas story out of the Book of Luke each year is always something to look forward to with Dad.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amanda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dad is an amazing friend and father. I cherish our long visits, his great mind, his consistency, his gentle heart and thoughtfulness. He is one of the most amazing men I know. What a blessing it has been to have been guided through life by my amazing Dad!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Amanda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like to sit with Boppa.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Thomas (Don't forget the "cwanes"!)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like to sit next to Boppa at our dinners. He is really funny.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Tobin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>