<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2316-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/14/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[jamie jones]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[1870 pandora ave]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Los Angeles]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[CA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[90025]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Lindsay Jones]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Lindsay Jones]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[from all your admirers...]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whatever Lindsay does, he puts his whole self into it. Making music, crazy travel, parenting, friendship-- you always get his whole heart, his entire brain, his complete devotion (and a little obsession). He comes at life with everything he's got. /R/RAnd that's a lot.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jamie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What makes Lindsay great? Obviously it's his effortless and soaring bass playing./ROh...and his wit, modesty, friendship and care...for all things (which inexplicably has come to include the Yankees - I know, I know, Huck, blah, blah - it's disturbing to me). Love ya!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jason (ie "Lindsay's Dad")]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He can take any adversity he encounters and turn it into a hilarious anecdote that provides laughter and joy for many for far longer than his moment of sadness, anger or frustration. What a gift that is. What a gift he is.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michelle Duffy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lindsay Jones is a good and true friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marc Damon Johnson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Loving father, wonderful collaborator, truly gifted designer, decent human being, awesome to be around. /RLindsay is inquisitive and curious, innovative, funny, thoughtful, generous, and most important he is kind./R/RHappy Father's Day Lindsey]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rick Sordelet]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ I have watched you grow from birth to the amazing person you are today. I am proud of you, especially of what a wonderful father you are to Huck and Sadie. You are gifted, creative, and caring. May every new day for you be another great story to tell, a joy to share.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Linz,/RWe love how much fun and humor you bring to our lives when you visit.  Wishing you a great Father's Day!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christopher, Amy, Ruby Anne & Loie!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What can I say /RTo my Lindsay D?/RAs dads go/RYou're fabu/Rand oh so sweet/RI'm a lucky mom/RTo have such a treat./RHappy Father's Day/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love to the moon and back--Mimsie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[This man never is boring. Never can be in the room without our hearing a faint drumroll of the hilarious thing he is about to say. I don't see him enough but every time I do I leave levitated by the encounter.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Juliet Funt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'll always picture Lindsay as the teacher who dressed in shorts and t-shirts (in the winter he just put long underwear under the shorts and t-shirt). He was the teacher who never grew up and I hope never will.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rachel Rudnick Piscopo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are extremely dedicated to your work, always giving it your all!  BUT, most of all you try even more at making family life for your wife and children more fun and more enlightening each time you arrive home.  One thing for sure is that everyone loves Lindsay!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gloria and Dick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The spirit of the child lives in the beauty of the parent. As you open your arms to the unknown, your children learn fearlessness and your family thrives on kindness.  And that is you, Linz. Through your hope, compassion, and courage these great lessons become gifts]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex and Chrisanne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[While I still want to kick his ~#$ right now...hey, this thing won't let me #%!$ing curse?  God damn it!  Woohoo, that got through the filter!  Anyways....I've always admired Lindsay's taste, knowledge, passion, and collection in music.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paul Peterson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From the time you could talk, you made me laugh and have brought much joy to my life. Happy Father's Day to a great dad and a perfect nephew. With love, always. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Carol]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[LIndsay,/R/RYou continually amaze me with your ability to juggle your time so that despite all the demands on you, you still get everything done!!  Great!/R/RAl (alias MixMix) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Al Mixon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Linz told me once that he is definitely the guy I can call ANYtime. Having a friend like that, even if I never do call at 4 in the morning, is really valuable/important. It says something meaningful about the depth of the friendship. I love my old pal Lindsay Jones. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lynn Baber]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(HANDS UP IN THE AIR)/R(with great exuberance)/RLINDSAY JONES!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Con Parker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What this man does in one week, would take me a month to do.  And another month to recover from.  Lindsay's boundless energy and passion for life reflect in his bright, inquisitive, tenacious childrens' eyes. Amazing dad. Amazing man.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Holly Long Lieber]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your total dedication to your art, your collaborators and your amazing family is what make you SO GREAT! It's an honor to call you a friend! Here's to Spatula]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff Dublinske]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lindsay Jones never met a stranger. And his conversations become the best stories I've ever heard.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen Hough Majidzadeh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You teach your collaborators to better understand sound. And you listen to them. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heather Gilbert]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey Magic Fingers...Magic Inventor/Rof all things audible...you rock and are one hilarious man who helps me create the impossible!  /RHowever the very best thing about you is when in the middle of tech ... you call your kids every night. Now that's real magic.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[barbara gaines x]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lindsey goes above and beyond to help and support everyone around him. He's a great collaborator and friend, as well as a great father. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cricket]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Lyndsay Jones is a great father. He makes me want to be a better father. I see how his children love him and look up to him and I see the same things from my children when they are around him. Bottom line, amazing father and a great man. And I'm glad to call him family]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shep ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lindsay Jones can drive a car while reading a magazine, booking a show and taking down a 6 pack of diet pepsi (used to at least) all the while never looking at the road.  Pretty impressive.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Noyes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lindsay always makes me smile, from his music, to his stories, to his his beautiful family. Everyone I know of Lindsay's friends are like him, funny, talented, loving and smart. I am honored to counted in their company.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Peryam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One reason Daddy is so great is because he's really really funny. He's really really nice and caring. And he's really smart, and always there for me. And when I'm sad, he makes jokes. /R/RI love him. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sadie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Daddy is always there to make jokes, he'll see us whenever he possibly can, even if that means coming on a school day when he can only be there for 3 hours, and he'll talk to us every night and morning he can. He's super caring and smart, and I love him so much. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Huck]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lindsay -- Happy Father's Day!  I can't think anyone who can tell a story like you do.  When I think of you, I am grinning ear to ear, recalling all the times you made me laugh out loud uncontrollably.  Keep em coming.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda Pachino]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lindsay, you are one hell of a friend. More than a friend, you're a part of my family. You rock the horses @%! with a whip./RLove you Mr. Jones]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Oscar Ybarra]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Funny, smart, kind, brilliant designer, hilarious, inexplicably humble, a joy with his kids, hysterical, clever, charming...Did I mention he's pretty damn funny?/RFrom a tiny dressing room in 1993 to your Broadway opening in 2014, it's been an honor to call you friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Richard Shavzin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He is the best storyteller, composer, collaborator, and friend I know! /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Will Pickens]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>