<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2317-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/15/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Patricia Lopez]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[7927 WINSFORD AVE]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[CA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[90045]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDEX_FEDEX2DAY]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Father's Day]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Joe Catallo]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love, Patricia XOXO]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I couldn't ask for a better dad. All of your guidance, love and support through the years have made me the person I am today. I am very lucky to have such a strong father figure in my life. I love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Patricia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Joe, to me, always radiated class. Ya can't teach that.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Tamburrino]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I've known Joe Catallo since I was a kid. He was an idol to us being big and strong, but just as much as gentle as a teddy bear.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tony Catallo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Serious though, we do love when we see u and when I get u on the phone occasionally. Hope to get back there to see u soon. Take care of yourself and Happy Fathers Day]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JOEY AND LISA PETROCELLI]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remembering our Sunday dinners all around the table in the front -- Spaghetti, meatballs and the constant flow of people at the front door after church. Oh how I long for those old days -- All of my people all together.  Remembering you this Father's Day and always. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Carolyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Uncle Joe trying to pick up pennies we glued to the concrete walk way]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joey Catallo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Joe-- One of my favorite memories is when I was in the Army stationed in NJ.  Because of our common last name, I was able to easily get a weekend Pass from my Sargeant because I told him I wanted to visit my "brother".  /RThank you for your Friendship????????/R         /R       ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Louis Catallo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Joe, this is Joey P. from the right coast. Lisa and I love you and feel like we've known you our whole lives. Love when we get together to go out with that nut Hank, even though u throw nickels around like manhole covers.   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joey & Lisa Petrocelli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I was a kid over 50 yrs ago, I always remember Joe as a hot ticket, approaching 30. Everyone would always ask him, "Joe when are you getting married?" He would always look like he was too late, and would ask what time is it? Love ya Joe! Happy Father's Day!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Emile Ianni]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We fondly remember your visit to Island Lake Cottage (bar fight), our visit to CA (& almost bar fight!), & your trip & stay at our house & race track with Mel & the winning circle with Wild WillyWorthy. Good times good times! That was the 60's. Now bedtime 9 pm! Miss U]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frank and Carolyn Tata]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There was a special evening when Hank, Joe, Becky and Mark were listening to Frank Sinatra very loud and all of us were drinking copious quantities of vino on the porch. We were literally "DANCING THE NIGHT AWAY". This was a very special time in our lives.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Jacobs]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Through the years, Joe, you were always giving me information on how to get ahead financially.  I think I should have paid better attention.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Art Gardner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite memories, Joe, will always be of our meeting at El Camino College in English class. I was cheating on my spelling test and you called me on it.  Lots of other good memories but I don't dare share them!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hank Francovig]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[At the beginning of our family life, you used to play the accordion for us.  That was very special. Hawthorne Youth Camp was fun.  I remember the time I beat you in a race, heel to toe, Joe Miller was over. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lori ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's fun looking back to the old restaurant days.  Me at the Cockatoo and you and Mal at the Gondolier.  You were always an all around friendly guy.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frank LoCoco]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[How do I see and remember Joe?  Extremely dedicated, devoted and faithful to the Casalverano Club.  Keeping our Italian customs and traditions alive.  Respected and loved by all. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John LoCoco]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for all the years of being my baseball coach and taking me to all of my games. I still remember the surprise of you coming down the driveway with the 1987 Mazda truck.  The Italian Club functions with music and lots of good food were very happy times.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marty]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We've been friends a long time, Joe. I first met you at the Gondolier with Pete Pozzuoli.  I appreciate the advice and help we have shared through the years.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lino Vidotto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Joe Miller was visiting one afternoon. He said he'd give me $5 if I beat you in a race.  We ran like crazy from the house to the corner & back.  I won by a nose.  Thank you for all the many times you helped me financially. I will always be grateful!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carrie ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A favorite memory is the home on Freeman & all the love & hard work you put into it to make it so very special.  The big wood fireplace, wallpaper, our bedroom with the french doors that opened up to the patio & yard.  Primroses & privacy! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Another great memory is riding around town with my handsome Italian Stallion in your white Thunderbird.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember, Joe, when you and I drove up to San Francisco to see my girlfriend Lois and her sister?  We went canoeing and it was so hot and humid that we all took a shower but we only had one towel!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jack Grillo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember the trip to Detroit and going through Kansas we drove 90 mph trying to outrun the tornado! That was scary as hell!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jack Grillo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I really enjoyed playing cards with Joe and our crazy Italian gang when we would get together at his house and also at Fred's garage. Joe always brought his special homemade olives and of course lots of wine. I enjoyed getting to know him  and swap fish stories!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sal Grammatico]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will always remember the times at the Hawthorne fair cooking hot dogs together....I had a stomach ache after, not sure if it was because we laughed so hard or if it was because we ate too many hot dogs!! Haha../Rthose memories will always be In my heart..]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dario Franchi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Joe taught me everything I needed to know about parenting. As kids he took us to Disneyland. I distinctly remember my dad taking everyone's personal request for vanilla, chocolate or swirl ice cream cones. Joe said ten vanilla cones. Vanilla never tasted so good !]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Francovig]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have two fond memories related to Uncle Joe:  Driving down Imperial Highway to Dockwiler for a fun day at the beach. We thought he was so cool! Going to the jewelry store to pick out a ring as a gift for Confirmation. I picked a pearl ring with two small diamond chips]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[XO Debbie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are so wonderful man of smile always greeting with great smile to everybody. Make us happy. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jason Jeon and family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cheers to you Uncle JOE (Just One Excellent) guy!!! Your wonderful spirit and dazzling smile is truly unmatched. We wish you the best of love and happiness now and always. /Rp.s., James would like to challenge you to a foot race, one glass of vino each. :)XOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[James and Stefanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey Joe, remember that time we killed that horse and put its head in the owners bed to scare him??  Good times!  Good Times!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tony & Diane Rodriguez]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are quite a few memories, but my favorites have got to be setting up the Memorial Center for the Italian parties. I don't know what was more fun...making sure the tablecloths were straight and the room just perfectly decorated or the party itself!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gina Marsella Cicchini]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am standing in the outside teller line at Wells Fargo on Hawthorne Blvd in the late 70's. My Godfather approaches and stands next to me. He tells me he is depositing a check. He pulls out the check, snaps it open and says "$10,000". He probably still has that money.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Sullivan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My Godfather pulls up in his truck in the mid-70's and tells me that he is heading to Canyon Lake. I asked him what that was and he says "the future".]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Sullivan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Playing doubles tennis on Saturday mornings with my Godfather, Marty, and my step dad. Good times.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Sullivan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Holiday dinners at my Godfather's House. Great food prepared by Pat, lots of laughter and conversation and then the anticipation of my Godfather going up to the attic and coming down playing the accordion and a sing-along ensued. Good times.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Sullivan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Long before Joe met his lovely wife, Pat, Maury & I brought a Norwegian model friend to one of the Italian functions. Every time he tried to dance with her, his sister Clara would say "Joe promised me this dance."  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mona Nardone]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Joe is always entertaining with his hilarious jokes.  What a great guy! Happy Father's Day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mona Nardone]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Joe,/RDo you remember the night we stole my father's car? We got lost, and did not get back till late at night, and everyone was waiting outside for us. My father beat the hell out of me. Lol /RHappy Fathers day Joe Catallo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mario Vennettilli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have known Joe for as long as I can remember. Joe is a strong handsome Italiano! Funny too! Last time I saw him, I was getting my hair done. Him and his friend came in and began to give me a massage! What a hoot that was!/RHappy Fathers Day ! /RLove to him always!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gina Zaccaglini]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Joe - So many happy memories with you & your family. Birthdays, anniversaries, going to Getty Museum,  to Italian Club picnics, to Myra & Magdy's dressed up Hawaiian style or for the 80's. Aways appreciated you asking about Mary Lou's mother. Have a great Father's day.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Lou & Harry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Joe is so funny!!! He has always made me laugh and feel cheerful with his sense of humor. And I love his deep "Goodfellas" voice :). Happy Father's Day Joe!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Erin Perencevic]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In my large family we had a lot of kids and not much money.  Birthdays were never celebrated.  So when I turned 70 and you guys made a big fuss over me with dinner and a birthday cake it meant a lot!  You and your family always make me feel special.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Willie (Vito)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember fun and happy get togethers at the home of my Aunt Frances before Lino and I married.  A lot of family and friends would gather there and you would play the accordion and we would dance.  So you could dance too we'd play records.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anna Vidotto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I came to pick up Patricia and Joe answered the door. He asked me "Who are YOU?"  I said "I'm Alan."  He opened the door and said "So YOU'RE Alan" and grabbed me by the shirt. Then he asked me to turn off the sprinklers. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alan Lopez]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember all our trips to Home Depot and Costco and sharing delicious Costco Hot Dogs for lunch! I always think about that when I go to those places as an adult, especially when I bite into a Costco Hot Dog!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your pupata always]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Joe,/RAs far as fathers go I consider you as family. I have always enjoyed our weekly meetings in Canyon Lake, filled with wisdom and laughter. It would be a highlite of my week. Have a GREAT FATHERS DAY!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike and Carol Augustine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Joe, you're a real 007 man who never failed in his mission.  You have always been on top.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob Marsella]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Joe do you remember the time when you would take the Italian kids to the beach and when we left that day we were sitting in the back of your truck and Emile Ianni sat on the top of the quarter panel and we got pulled over by the police and you got a $35.00 ticket.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dennis Catallo & Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>