<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2318-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/15/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Brittany Tuosto]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[745 Fifth Avenue]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[FL 25]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[New York]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[NY]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[10151]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Father's Day, Dad!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Ronald Tuosto]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love, Brit]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[This coupon is good for one shopping trip with Brittany Tuosto.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Courtesy of Brittany Tuosto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ronald is special to me because he was my confirmation sponsor.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ronald is special to me because I told my 3rd grade teacher you were my older brother.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christopher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ronald is special to me because he will make sure I don't starve in college next year by taking me to Teresa's.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Samantha]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ronald is special to me because he became MY cousin too!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ronald is special to "US" because he keeps Christmas alive all year long!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Cousins]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron is special to me because he has made his dad extremely proud of what he has become.  A superior provider for his family and an extraordinary father to his children.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/RRons' transformation was not easy.  As a young teenager he had to learn that investing hard saved monies with shisters doesn't pay./RThat not cleaning his room would result in his clothes being thrown out of his window and into the driveway./R    ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He had to learn that Superman was a fictional character and that he Ron couldn't fly./RHe couldn't sneak in through basement windows without being detected./RHe couldn't paint the garage walls with tar and not be punished./RLearned that going to school paid dividends.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron is special to me because not only is he my only sibling, aside from my husband, he is my best friend.  Remember the days when I used to clean your room?  Hee!Hee!Hee!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Nino]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He taught me what it meant to be a flyer fisher, ranger fan, and a man.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael Tuosto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron is special to me because he is more like a brother than a brother-in-law.  He is warm, gregarious, welcoming and has a great laugh. I always look forward to seeing Ron at a family get-together because you know it will be a great time for all.  Happy Father's Day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anthony]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron- I remember you were always like a second father to me in high school. You always welcomed me with open arms into your home. I will never forget piling into the buick and going to the movies. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jess Frisone ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for a lifetime of friendship !!!!    Also regards from the Gemini   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron is special to me because he makes all my wishes come true ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Teri]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron is special because he always puts his family first ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Teri]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You make Christmas special for everyone. I believe in Santa Claus because I get the best presents ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Teri]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am thankful everyday for you.... I love you very much ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Teri ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron is special because he takes it to the head,  trying to get sun for Brittany and myself  while boating in Disney ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Teri ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I know I can count on you for ranger ice cream ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Teri]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Buster...thanks for helping me learn to play golf ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Teri ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[he opened 'er up!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael Tuosto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He votes R up and down the ballot. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael Tuosto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Every kid deserves a great father like Ron. My kids are lucky they have an Uncle Ron in their life! /R/RI don't know where I'd be without your guidance and friendship. /R/RYou are a caring, dedicated and amazing father and I love you. /R/RHave a great Fathers Day. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Glen Donaldson ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron is special because he helps me remember everyone's name.  Finds  my phone, fixes my car, waters my flowers, brings me my lunches when I forget them at home and he loves when I'm happy!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Teri]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Have you ever seen Frozen?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brit]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dad:/R/RYour unconditional love and support have made me feel safe. I am the luckiest girl in the world to have been blessed with you as my father. I could never tell you often enough how much I love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brit]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have always admired Ron for ALWAYS putting his family first.  I feel very lucky to have worked with him for so many years!/RHe's the best!! /RHappy Father's Day, Ron!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barbara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[when he was born he was colic, and unless you experience a child like that you can never appreciate what I'm going to write.  To keep him quiet I had to put him in the play pen with a newspaper or magazine to rip apart.  At night I had to clean out the play pen..daily!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I would leave Ronald sitting in the baby tender locked.  I walked into the dining room and His Majesty was on top of the washing machine which was close./R/RThe punishment for disobeying was to face a corner of the room sitting on a stool.  Not Ronald.  he got up, took my]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One day Ronald took it upon himself to wash the kitchen floor by emptying a whole can of Ajax on the floor..I can't tell you how long it took to clean the floor!/R/RWe moved to 23rd Street whn Ronald was three years old.  One day I had to run up the street to get Jeannine]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[from school.  Ronald decides to eat a half of a pound of fried bacon which was on the counter for lunch./RHow would you like to hear your son at 5:30 am telling you "do you plan on staying in bed all day?"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One day, he was laying on the floor looking up at me and asked if he was adopted.  My response was if you were adopted I would have sent you back a long time ago./R/RJeannine was in high school and Ronald had me all to himself for two years.  When he would come through ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[the side door he would make me sit down on the step to hear his joke!  I wad the censor for daddy.  I told him the joke wasn't too bad, he could tell Daddy.  Well, Mr. Tuosto takes his left hand puts it on Rons' right arm and said, you said it today, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[you are not to repeat that joke again.  Ron looked at me I at him and we bursting not to laugh./RNow I must add although he was a bit of a pain, he turned out to be a kind, caring and giving person.  Any Mother would be proud of him as her son.  My Champ!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Never put anything in writing."                    ~ Ron Tuosto]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ian Healey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being a great second family to me. I will never forget the Christmas morning outfits, trips, heading back from games, or just hanging around the house.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ian Healey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Will never forget the "colorful" stories and commentary we have shared over the years, can not wait to do it again soon.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ian Healey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron's friendship has  always been something that we could  on. Through  thick and thin his support and good wishes helped  make the tough  times easier. ... and the good times better! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Daidone Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I still love Turner and Hooch and miss our campouts to this day.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brit]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember when Michael and I used to beat you up with your own slippers playing Bear?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brit]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our many trips to Disney are still some of my favorite memories.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brit]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>