<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2319-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/15/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Jennifer Brown]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[135 N Vireo Drive]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[McKees Rocks]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[15136]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Celebrating You...]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Carl Brown]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Your Friends and Family]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/RYou've been there for me in every capacity of life sharing your wisdom...and even wiping the puke from my mouth when I was in labor with Evan. And now, you're my "father" figure. I think my Dad would agree with my choice. /RYou...I cherish./RHappy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenny]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I went into the service I thought I no longer had to share a Bedroom & got 49 other roommates./RStay well, I do not want to go back to sharing a room, especially in a nursing home, with you.  Happy Birthday  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are an amazing father and an incredible human being. I hope you know how special you are to me and everyone in our family. Thank you for being an inspiration and always being there for me when I needed it most. I love you and hope you have a great birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Pap, thank you for all you do for me and my family, it is really appreciated. Thank you for teaching me about the outdoors and mainly fishing, I would not be the fisherman I am today without you. Maybe one day you can catch the big fish I do! Love you ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Evan ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Uncle Carl,/RHappy 70th Birthday! Some of my greatest memories are fishing with you on your boat in Erie and Ocean City. You and Aunt Jo are like a second set of grandparents to me and I thank you for everything you have done for me. Have an amazing birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Scott ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We've shared so many great times and experiences over the past 70 years that I can't single just one out. Every time I think I have the best memory another one jumps into contest it. I'm so proud to be able to call you brother./RHappy 70th Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ed]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey Carl,/RYou're always there to help everyone & I  just want to let you know it's a pleasure having such a good friend, brudder & Steeler fan.    ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cheryl]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My husband of almost 25 years.  The love of my life.  God blessed our family.  You have made us laugh at times we didn't think we could - mainly with how gullible you could be....Nunya....remember that - love you always and thank you for always being their for us.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wife of the 70 yr. old birthday boy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always refer to Carl as "big guy", because of his big heart to always help, his laugh that is so infectious, and lastly, just one on the nicest people I know!  Happy Birthday Carl!  Love you, Jitter]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sharbaugh Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carl has been like a father to the three of us! We love you!/RC is for the CARING you have showed us!/RA is for the ACTION you show, movin and shakin as you fix everything for us./RR is for resilience, you never back down from a fight!/RL is for the LOVE we have for you!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Hill's/Brancho's]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will never forget the time you dropped a sofa bed on my foot and I learned to speak a whole new language.  I so loved the birthday parties at Russellwood when Carl and his mom.would come over and Aunt Mary would bring the cake from Jenny Lee.  Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jack & Deb]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dad, you've taught me a lot.Growing up, I saw first hand what a good work ethic is.You taught me how to become a man, a husband&how to take care of a family, which I will always be greatful for.  Also,learned not to spray bug spray directly in my face, spray hands&apply]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[We love you,Justin & Lyndsay Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carl I have very many special memories about you. However my favorite : when Jo Ann answered the door at your home and let Santa Clause come in and the "what the .............look on your face" is /Ra memory I'll never forget. Love you Carl/RBob]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob Sharbaugh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Though we do not see each other as much as we would like to, you have always been there for myself and my family.  You are an amazing person and a wonderful uncle.  I hope you have a wonderful birthday.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dave, Janet, Matt, Dani & Abby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Uncle Carl HAPPY BIRTHDAY. Even though I call you uncle you have always been more like a third grandpap to me. Thanks for all the fond memories made at camp. If it wasn't for you I would not love camp as much as I do now. Happy birthday and may you have many more!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Megs :)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to one of the nicest people I know...the other one is your wife.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marlene]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am married to the most "Interesting Man In The World" - those days we will never forget in Mexico and OC where everyone wanted your picture and autograph.  All those women are jealous that I not only have the "Most Interesting Man In The World", but he loves me!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday, Uncle Carl. I love you and thank you for letting me visit you at the beach. I always have so much fun with you and Aunt Jo. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Aman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Uncle Carl, thank you for being such a wonderful part of my life. I'm so grateful that you're healthy and so happy to be celebrating your 70th birthday with you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Cindy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[remember all the great times growing up, I always slept at your house and we played ball in the alley and St. Francis school yard.  You always came to Norwood to stay.  Don't forget your friends Jo Jo Mag and the man in the black cape.  Wishing you a happy 70th birthday]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob (Lucy) Connor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Pap! Thank you for always being there for me and helping me pick the right choices in life. Also, thank you for teaching me new things about fishing, crabbing, and baseball. I'm glad I have you as a Pap. I love you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Zachary James Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Uncle Carl I love that you are such a caring and compassionate person. You have always been so supportive of me and I appreciate you so much for that! Thank you for being such a constant part of my life and my kids. I wish you so many more years of happiness!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cari Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 70th birthday Uncle "Carlo". I love you. Thank you for letting me stay at your house and taking me fishing.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Evadoo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for your support and encouragement. I appreciate you traveling for my games and being there for me.  I love visiting and fishing with you. Happy Birthday!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Demitrick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carl took me to my 1st Steeler game vs the Lions. I wore a Barry Sanders shirt, my favorite player. After Sanders tore Rod Woodson's ACL, grown men began to throw beer at the 13 year old Jagoff & the season ticket holder dumb enough to bring him. We left immediately.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anthony Romanelli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Carl, /RWe would like to wish you a Happy Birthday to one of the kindest, sweetest person we've had the pleasure of knowing! From the bottom of our hearts, all of our love! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike, Susie, Michael, Natalya]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Pappy,/RWe've made so many memories, like when you and Grandma Jo were watching us and the Corona beer commercial was on TV we were talking about the talent show in OCMD and I was doing my Mexican dance and you were the DJ. Hoping to make many more. Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I love you, Paige]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey Unk, /RNext time your down we need to play some more corn hole & go fishing. You can drive the boat & I'll cook the fish./RHope you have a Happy Birthday.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ken]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Where do you start with a man who has been on the planet for 25,550 days. So many great memories, vacations, weddings, boating, the beach. Remember when you put your Speedo on backwards? /RHappy Birthday Big Guy.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Cumberlands, Bud and Lee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[First time we met Carl was at the firemen's fair and we fell in love with our nephew-in-law! Happy 70th! Many more happy memories in OC and family days! /RLove you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Tony & Aunt Pat]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carl, /RThis is to advise you that you have litigation pending against you for exposing my client to the naked man on the picnic bench. Please forward any and all birthday money to my clients as payment. /RThank you, /RIma Scumbag, Esquire]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cindy and the Handsome Detective]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>