<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2334-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/16/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Patrick DeSpain]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[888 Brickell Key Dr]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[Apt 1000]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Miami]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[FL]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[33131]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sand]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Congrats! ]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Patrick & Naya]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Alicia, Chris & Hudson]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I married my best friend. The one I laugh with, live for, dream with, LOVE.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alicia & Chris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love each other like there is no tomorrow./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandy & Gene]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Wife Happy Life]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gene Stence]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Nayade and Patrick: finally the dreamed day by all and especially  for you,  has come:  the wedding day. /RCongratulations./ROn this special day and in this new phase you are about to start, I desire to be the beginning of a whole happiness, love and joy life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom Clementina]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marriage is a big step in the life of a couple and its success is based not only on love but on trust, mutual understanding and tolerance./REnjoy every day the power of being together and your dreams come true forever./RI am very proud of you./RBlessing of love for both]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom Clementina]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Para Nayadita y Patrick:/RLes deseo una unión que perdure para siempre./RMuchas bendiciones.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rufina]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Queridos amigos Patrick&Naya:/RDesde Tenerife, Canarias deseo enviarles mis mejores deseos para una vida matrimonial llena de amor, respeto, comprensión y comunicación, bases fundamentales para la anhelada dicha conyugal./R Muchas felicidades hoy y siempre.........]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Milagros Gutiérrez Carrero]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Patrick and Naya,/RCongratulations some more!  I wish you both love and happiness always - and beer/wine and/or liquor the next time we get together!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Phi Alpha - Steve Priepke]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nayade, Patrick mis mejores deseos en esta nueva etapa de sus vidas, toda relación requiere amor, comprensión, amistad, paciencia estoy segura que ustedes reúnen todos esos atributos para ser felices por siempre.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Celina Cardenas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As you see each other, treat each other, and think of each other, you will see, treat and think of yourselves. Never forget this - for in supporting one another you will grow to find your True Selves, and come home to Love.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rev. Lisa Graham, George Rueda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Que alegria poder compartir esta experiencia con ustedes de corazon y desearles una vida llena de buena comida, buen vino y de todo lo que es el buen vivir que es lo esencial en la vida, lo que nos une y nos llena de grandes memorias. Félicitations!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paola y Carlos]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mi querida Naya se tira un pedo y se desmaya! Jajaja que alegria verte tan feliz, y hubiese querido acompañarte en tu boda alla y disfrutar de un viaje mas juntas pero desde aqui te deseo todo lo mejor siempre!!! Besos!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pao]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Querida Nayade:/RCuanto me alegra saberte amada por Patricio, querida por tantos, ya sabes lo que me hubiese gustado acompañarlos... Es un placer conocerte cada día un poco más y con toda mi luz les deseo mucho de todo bueno a esta nueva pequeña familia! Un abrazo fuerte]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hecmara Arellano ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Follow YOUR instincts and your OWN LOVE trail... ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Emily & Guille]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[This may sound repetitive but I wish you health, patience for tough times, lots of fun and that you may grow old together walking along similar paths. We hope to be part of your lives along the way too!/R/RLos queremos!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andre, Taty, Emma&Robert Boudreaux]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To The Sultan of Miami,/RCongratulations oh 'great one'. The jungle awaits you & your beautiful bride for a recuperation visit....visa waved for his RH. /RLong live the beard!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[jungleboy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[This was the best second wedding between the same two people we've ever attended. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robin & Aaron]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Take a moment to look back on this day and realize that everyone here, and everyone who couldn't be here, love you both dearly and want nothing but the best. /R/RCongratulations!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robin & Aaron]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So excited for all the wonderful adventures together ahead of you! Never take each other for granted. Humor goes a long way. See you in the Philippines soon! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elaine and Marc von Grabowski]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lots of patience and communication. Sometimes you lose it, but remember how much you love each other. We are very happy for you two, but very sad for not being able to be there with you. Love you both  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Fran, Olivia and Mari]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always be kind and generous to one another, and listen carefully to each other's hearts. /R/RAs Lao Tzu said: /R"Kindness in words creates confidence. Kindness in thinking creates profoundness. Kindness in giving creates love."  /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Claudia Robaina]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Laugh. Together. Always!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hichiro]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[May your Love be renewed with every breath. /RMay your Life be filled with Love, Happiness, Beauty, pigeon poses, amazing moments, adventure, kids, laughter, health, Peace, and  lots of S@$E&*X/RMany Blessings to you guys/RI love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gisele aka Coucou]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am so happy to see two of my best friends in the entire world come together in this merger (err, wedding). Your relationship is the definition of synergy. 1PD+1NB = lots of magic. Enjoy your special day, and even more how special your lives are because of one another.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Harper]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Confucius says marriage is like poker - you start with pair and end with full house./R/RSo go forth and multiply!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chek Tee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Have a wonderful journey together. Laugh, forgive, and always be there for each other.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Drew & Geshu]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A husband celebrating his 50th was asked the key to a long marriage. He stated that his wife made all the small decisions; he made the big ones. Asked for an example of a big decision he replied "I don't know, we've never had one"/RWishing you happiness, big and small!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Tim and Linda Taylor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["By all means, marry. If you get a good wife, you'll become happy; if you get a bad one, you'll become a philosopher." /R- Socrates -/R/RPs: I'm sorry Patrick, you have now lost your opportunity to become a philosopher :)/R/RAll my <3 for the two of you./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Catalina]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hola Nayade y Patrick, nos hubiera encantado compartir un momento tan especial, pero lamentablemente las condiciones de nuestro país no nos lo permiten. Deseamos toda la felicidad y armonía para su nueva vida y que siempre haya comprensión y comunicación entre ustedes.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rosalba y Carlos Goncalves]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Patrick – Don’t every stop dating your wife!/RDear Naya – Don’t ever stop flirting with your husband!/R/RFalling in love is easy ; Staying in love requires work./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Varun & Amreeta]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Patricio: love her, die for her, take her to dinner, buy her jewelry, be interested in what she has to say.../RNaya: show up naked, bring beer./RLot of LOVE&HAPPINESS for you guys... Los queremos mucho!!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karem & Luis H.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wishing you a life together filled with love, laughter, wonder and joy. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bryan Palmer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["The minute I heard my first Love Story I started looking for you, not knowing how blind that was. Lovers don't finally meet somewhere. They're in each other all along." Rumi/REvery time you look at each other, find yourselves, so you will never be lost, but lost in Love]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Los quiero mi Nayi y Patrick! Gi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wishing you both a lifetime of happy memories, amazing travel and great friends./R/RSo very happy for you both as you begin this next chapter and thank you for allowing me to be a part of it!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Roberto Castro]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My dearest Toyis & Patrick./RWelcome to the club of those who find that one special person you want to annoy for the rest of your life. Both should be patient, because if Naya continues doing Yoga like that, she'll live 150yrs. I wish you enjoy it a lot together!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eduardo y Gabriela]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Patrick and Gangsta:/R/RWe are so happy for you guys and excited to celebrate with you.  I love that we live 1 mile away yet we need to travel across the globe to get together./R/RBest,/R"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lidia and Mike""]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Les deseamos muchas felicidades y recuerden tener siempre... ¡PACIENCIA!/R/RCongratulations and remember always to be.../RPATIENT!/R/RLos queremos mucho!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mario y Joana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Naya & Patrick, best advice is to keep your relationship alive by doing all those little things that you love from each other.. have fun, laugh and play, life should be an enjoyable and great journey. Wish you all the happiness and blessings in the world.  /RLove!!!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandra & Chris ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations, Naya and Patrick! We are so excited to be apart of your big day! Best wishes for a future filled with happiness and love! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alicia Scalera & Ty Armstrong]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A little Patrick told me one time A man has to do what a man has to do which was a special moment to me Now another special moment as we celebrate your love and life time committment with Naya on your journey together We are blessed to increase our family by one more]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[We love you both very much Mom &Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We wish you many years of happiness. Marriage is always a give and take adventure. Remember to be loving, caring and creative.  Take those 7 green rabbits with you to help you find your way. Make sure you respect, comfort and love each other for all times.  We love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom & Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No estaremos, pero estoy seguro celebraremos después y por todo lo alto./RPatrick, you made a great pick, the better teammate ever; y tu Nayadita, tienes a alguien al lado que con solo verte, muestra lo que te quiere./R/R¡Los queremos!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[#GomezBlanco Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hola prima,muchas felicidades de parte de todos nosotros. Pórtate bien!!! Besitos.,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maria & Familia. ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["A successful marriage requires falling in love over and over again, always with the same person."/R/RLive for today, plan for tomorrow, party TONIGHT!!/R/RLove you both with all our hearts--]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike Sholl & Deborah Iquique]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tanti Auguri per un felice matrimonio e una lunga vita insieme! /RPatrick benvenuto nella famiglia!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Antonio "cousin Chris" Amendola]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[amor vincit omnia/RChe la vita vi sorrida sempre Cugini!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Roberta Gasparro Amendola]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Queridos Nayade y Patrick, Si cada uno se ocupa de hacer  feliz al otro, se encontrarán con una vida maravillosa en pareja y en familia. El yo se convierte en nosotros y la felicidad es infinita. Los queremos mucho y les deseamos amor eterno.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jimena,  Andres y Camila :)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the happiest parts of marriage is seeing your loved one smile, give each other as many reasons to smile as possible!/R/RWishing you both a long and happy life together!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dan and Natassja Gangeri]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[May you always find love, joy, health and happiness in your lives now bound in marriage.  Congratulations!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy Brodbeck]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There was once upon a time a Princess and a Prince.  They embraced their new life together living by the rule of love and acceptance. They also worked very hard to leave behind fears, expectations and old beliefs. /RAnd they lived happily ever after! /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leyla De La Espriella ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The first time I saw you together, I really felt that it was and will be a wonderful couple forever./RI'm so glad you are married already, and I really wish this will be forever. I love you both!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Xiomara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mi mejor deseo es que se amen toda la vida y se respeten, sin respeto nada es posible./RSean felices, los quiero muchísimo.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Abuela]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[La promesa de mantener el matrimonio toda la vida, resulta más económico que un divorcio./RLo más importante, es procurar que tu pareja sea feliz./REn un matrimonio la vida de uno es el complemento de la vida del otro.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Abuelo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mi vida! Que maravilla tener a Patricio Miguel para que te compre las carteras, y él a ti para sus Ferragamos! :D/REstamos felices que emprendan este camino juntos! Felicidades hoy y siempre, estamos listos para los sobrinos!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[We love you. Maqui and Leito]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We've both had the pleasure of being roommates with Patrick. Naya, if you are willing to do that for the rest of your life, you must truly be special. Congratulations to you both!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David & Allison Bradbury]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Don't sweat the small stuff. Have fun, eat well and don't forget to share. Life moves pretty fast, if you don't stop and look around once in a while, you'll miss it. /RMarriage is finding the person who puts up with your $*$#, and still loves you at the end of the day]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike and Jess Mazel Tov and L'Chaim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It is incredible how our opinion of someone potentially can change entirely once we get to know them well. Patrick is also one of the kindest and most honorable human beings I have ever encountered and I am proud to call him my friend and very special adopted brother]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nicole Mirmelli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Y'all are beautiful fire. Burn fierce. Burn brightly.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ethan Von Zamft]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The vows they really wanted you to say:/R/R"Naya, I vow to massage your feet each morning and admit I'm wrong 5 minutes into an argument."/R/R"Patrick, I promise to do your laundry every day, including skid marks, and do the furry handcuff thing every Sunday" /R/RBonne Chance]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex W]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Greetings from SF! I've not had the chance to meet Naya… but knowing Patrick, I'm sure you are warm, kind, and…funny! So to you, Naya, and my birthday twin…or DOBblegänger…or solmate: my sincerest wishes of happiness! The best thing to hold onto in life is each other!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom Lloyd]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Naya and Patricio Miguel! Sending you immeasurable blessings for a sacred wedding and life full of love, laughter and adventures together. We love you more than a cut with a cardboard knife! Just remember, the secret to happy marriage is: dont fart in a hammock.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan, Will and Mela Duprey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ex amig@s! Les deseamos lo mejor. Usa el yoga en lo meche de bodas y todas las noches!!! /R/RYita, vas a tener que traducir pa Patrick. /R/RBesos]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve y Ale Lopez]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We are truly honored to be at such an amazing event for two amazing people.  All the best to you both!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ryan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We’re all a little weird. And life is a little weird. And when we find someone whose weirdness is compatible with ours, we join up with them and fall into mutually satisfying weirdness – and call it love – true love.” ~ Robert Fulghum]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ferrer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>