<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2338-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/16/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Leslie Gudel]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[531 Winston Way]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Berwyn]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19312]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Congratulations Alli]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Alli Rademaker]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love, Your Friends and Family ]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You've moved from the "little kids table" to hanging with the grown ups, in the time I've known you & I really enjoy your company and conversation.  You're interesting and smart and have such a bright future.  Congratulations on graduation.  Look out UD, here she comes!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leslie Kemm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alli,/RYou are so kind and outgoing! We have been friends since middle school and share so many great memories. Even though we don't talk much, whenever we reconnect we always have fun! Good luck at Delaware,/Ryou will do great!! Congratulations!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah Domenick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It seems like just yesterday when you were on the New Eagle bus.  Thanks for being so good to our family .... from helping Anna to watching Rico !]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Kovarick Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Alli, you are one of my favorite human beings. If you lived in California you could take me for long walks and you could bath me and brush my silky coat. You could teach me new tricks and we could swim. Ahh, the things we could do! Lots of love]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maddie aka Littledog xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Well done Alli/RNow you can go out and wow the world by being the best you can be!/RLots of love]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen, Ralph, Kirsty and Rob]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Over the years our family has shared many fun times with Alli! Alli is not just a pretty face, she's the best Charades player ever!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Higgins Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alli and I had sports nutriton together and we had the greatest time in that class, even though she stalked me and Ben! Me, Alli and Cameron were always the only group laughing when we went to sit down to eat, she made that class bareable. Thanks Alli!/R/R/RPS stoga squash]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carolyn Lee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alli was my first friend in math class. She made me feel welcomed and wanted as I was the only sophomore in the class. We not only became friends in class but great friends outside as well. She will forever be my favorite Starbucks buddy and I wish her the best of luck.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Annie Daggett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will never forget the amazing times we had in Italy together. I loved being roomies :) /RHave so much fun at Delaware! I'll miss you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carrollanne ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi friend!!! We met through Mrs. Hyatt's English class junior year and I had you for the stalker essay. I am so glad we are such great friends! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Claire Frisina]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alli - Over the years I have so enjoyed being your teammate and friend. You are an absolute joy to be around and I think you are absolutely hilarious. Please never change Al!!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite thing about Alli is that she shares my absolute, over the top love for bulldogs. I think we discovered this bond during English together with Mrs. Hyatt junior year and it has made us closer ever since.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sincerely, Ryan DuTot]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When we were killin it at Space Bar in Italy. And at the beach in Rome that was such a gt. I wish we could go back again ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Emily Pastva]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are fun, intelligent, and caring.  We wish you all the best in college and know the future is bright with you in it!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Devlin/Burruano Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have enjoyed our family trips together and have watched you grow into a beautiful young lady!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jamie Kemm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Keep this as your one (1) /R"Get out of jail free"/Rcard!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sergeant Jamie Kemm-PA State Police]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always brighten up a room with your smile!! I wish you the best of luck on your next journey!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jamie Kemm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Alli! We are so proud to have such a hardworking and diligent daughter. Then there is the beautiful smile, great sense of humor, and compassion for others – especially kids (and dogs!). You always know what you want and manage to get it. You will go far.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom and Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alli/RI love sleeping with you every night, especially when I can put my head next to yours on your pillow. You also make me feel better when it storms. /R/RGood luck at UD. Pity I cant go. I will miss you :(]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Taffy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alli/R/RI love it when you pick me up and show my fat stomach to everyone, because I am proud to be a fat cat!! And dressing me up on Christmas ... that's the best!/RI will sleep 20 hours a day on your bed when you are gone so that it will remind me of you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peaches]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Alli!  We have watched you grow up from a little neighborhood kid, to our teenaged babysitter to the beautiful young woman that you have become!  Best of luck in college ... we can't wait to see what you do with your life!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The McGaughans]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alli is an awesome roll model for our kids.  Each of them loved to hear that Alli was coming over to babysit.  She made them each feel so special!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[the Nieberle family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have shared so many funny and great memories (all the concerts, pool days, and trips) but my favorite memories are of when we would just hang out, laugh, and take silly pictures (or videos showing off our talent of speaking in different accents) in our rooms. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Montana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Watching you grow up throughout the years into a beautiful young lady!  My fondest memory is the weekend we spent in NY for your 16th birthday celebration!  How obsessed you were with One Direction that we didn't see you for two days!  What a great memory!  Congrats!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ilene]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alli,/RYour smile is infectious and lights up the room! You are a beautiful, intelligent young woman with a bright future! Much love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jackie and Toby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As we've watched you grow into a beautiful young adult you've always made a point to say hello and tell us what's new./ROne of our fondest memories is the weekend you and Marc spent at our house./RCongratulations Alli and we hope you'll always be with us on Christmas Eve!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Tracy and Dave]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Never lose your smile and your positive attitude, you will go far and I will always be keeping an eye on you, wherever you may be :-) ... so be careful, I WILL find you !!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Raymond]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our group always trying to hang (you me Brit Haley and em) but all of us always being way to busy!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sam Hobson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on your Graduation!/RWishing you success in everything you do and most of all have lots of fun doing it!/RStay the way you are and come and visit us often in SA.  We love you lots]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sally & Co. xxxxx]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alli, you finally made it. All of those years of making sure we got the same amount of candy, and having to share the same bed on vacation are finally over. Live life in college. You'll never have another experience like it.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marc]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have known Alli in many different capacities. She is the little sister of my son's best friend. She is the daughter of Ivar and Mickey. But lately I have gotten to know her as a strong, independent, amazing and intelligent individual. I love her spirit and honesty.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Alli/RCongratulations on your graduation! We are very proud of you!/RYou are a very special young lady and we wish you lots of success for your future./RStay the way you are and enjoy every moment of what you do!/RLots of love and hugs]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sally Rademaker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>