<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2341-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/17/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Mia Fey]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[2853 Jean Lane]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Westlake Village]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[CA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[91361]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Ryan's Sixteenth Birthday]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Ryan Graham]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[From: Payton]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Besides being really good at racing 'Elmo Car'...she is smart, beautiful, a talented student athlete, super kind and the type of niece and cousin to our boys that makes me so proud - all the time.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA['Cul kis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have loved you Ryan since  day one when I held you in my arms for the very first time and continue to love the wonderful young lady you are today..SWEET SIXTEEN!/R/RLove, Ama]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barbara Stern]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[hmmmm. One thing?  Her love of her family]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Her Best Friend]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like what a good friend you have been to Payton and that you are a big snuggler. I don't like your piece of shit Father though. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pierre]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are so many things I love about my favorite granddaughter, Ryan Graham. She is intelligent, beautiful and an accomplished athlete but the thing I love most is that she always tells me my garage smells good. Happy 16th and keep both hands on the wheel.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Papa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[thanks for always giving me cute clothes. One thing I like most about ryam is the way you pronounce bull. happy birthday to my older (favorite) sister ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[bulla]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how no matter how long we are apart or don't see each other whenever we are together it's like nothing has changed and I cherish every memory I have with you and I'm excited for more to come!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Makena Cavarozzi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[MY HERMIT. I think you can guess who it is just by the first two words. BOOYA YOU"RE RIGHT ITS HATER #2. I can't believe we have been friends for 9 years! Our friendship has continually grown since elementary school and now we're all grown up! Have an amazing 16th girl!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[SophPaps/Hater#2/FellowHermit]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I love about you, Goose, is how you are super enthusiastic you can be about big things, and little things too! "Yassss Mom, a Starbucks!" or "I love these socks!" You always makes me smile.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ZeMom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how every night, you still want me to tuck you in and kiss you goodnight. No matter how old you get, this is always special to me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Ryan's sense of humor! Whenever I hang out with her, I have the best time and always laugh. Ryan, you are a wonderful person with a kind heart. Happy birthday! You deserve nothing but the best.  /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alexa Adalian ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ryan!! You are such a great friend to me and are always there whenever I need you! I can always count on you to listen to my complaining or make me laugh (biiiitch)!! You never seem to not make me smile! Hope you have such a great 16th birthday "dude"!!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brooklynn Gigliotti]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi RyRy!! A whole (almost) three years ago we were facing freshman year together. Ry I couldn't be more thankful we did it together.  Thank you for being there for me no matter what. To 16 years of being an incredible person. HAPPY BIRTHDAY RYRY!! I love you always]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ava]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can honestly say I couldn't be happier and more proud to call you my best friend. We have the best times and laughs together and I'll cherish those memories forever!! Thank you so much for always being there for me Ry! Stay beautiful xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hayles]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always wondered who you were in Ms. Lang's F Block Biology class. I am so thankful I made the decision to peruse a friendship with you. I couldn't be happier to have you by my side throughout high school. congrats on another year of your life. love you so much rhino;)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tessa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Is her honesty and loyalty! She is a genuine friend who doesn't care what others think of her. She's motivated and good at what she has a passion for (soccer, being a true friend). But most of all I like that Ry always has my back :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ava Toluie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ryan is sure of herself and she knows who she is. She won't change for anyone and she definitely doesn't need to. She's been an amazing friend to me and I'm so incredibly lucky to have met her. LOVE YOU RYAN. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lujain Hussein ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[your contagious laugh and beautiful smile]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Erin Lamothe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that you are always true to yourself and don't care what anyone else thinks, you can eat more steak than anyone I know, you can laugh at yourself, you are a beast on the soccer field, and you have the stength and character to achieve anything you want in life! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you Ryan! Aunt Theresa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My sweet, smart, sensitive, snuggly 2nd child Ryan, on your 16th birthday I want to thank you for being Payton's BEST friend! You are always there for her with cheerful advise and a shoulder to cry on. I LOVE having you as part of our family, you brighten up our lives!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mia Fey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how when I take you and Payton somewhere you make me feel like I am one of your friends!  You always include me in the conversation and make me laugh! I love you sweet Ryan!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mama Mia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[RYAN HAPPY BIRTHDAY! We have become so close this year which I'm grateful for. You are so funny, sweet and a really good friend. Always remember that I love Ya and so do our boys ;). I will always be there for you. Have a great day. Happy Birthday!! <3]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[MehriMP]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how you can always put a smile on my face. Whenever I'm in a bad mood or something happens I can always count on you to make things better, I love you for that.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michela DeFalco ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the many things I love about Ryan is her honesty and loyalty. She is always there for me and always knows how to brighten up my day. She is one of the few people in my life I know I can always depend on.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kasie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy sweeeet 16 Ryan! You're such a loyal, hilarious, generous & kind friend (the list goes on). One that is true & rare to find. You always put a smile on my face & make me laugh. You are a treasure of a friend & you deserve the best birthday! I love you! /Rxoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Olivia Miele :-)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ryan! I love everything about you! You are tall, beautiful, smart, driven, funny, and SLEEPY! Good thing it's just like your loving cousin. :) love you!! And happy 16th!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Erica and Shelby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ryan, you are one of my favorite people. I love your huge heart, thoughtfulness beyond your years, and that you have a deep love for your family. Also that you share my love for binging TV shows and movies all day. :) Have an amazing 16th birthday and love you tons!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo Michelle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like how when we were kids and we fought you always protected me when mom got mad. Especially when she put soap in my mouth and you got me juice to wash it out.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how no matter how mad you are at me, you will always have my back when I need you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Payton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how you always laugh at my jokes when nobody else does, no matter how stupid they are. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Payton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A few of my favorite things about you are your undying loyalty and support, your ability to cry in ANY movie, and your contagious laugh. I love knowing that I have one friend who I know for sure will be in my life forever. I hope you like your present Ry, I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paytom ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>