<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2344-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/17/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Maura Webb]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[64 Oak Ledge Lane]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Wilton]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[CT]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[06897]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Best Wishes]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Lou Cuglietto]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[From Your Staff at JFK School]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for inspiring me to continue my own education so that I may better serve our students. I will always be grateful to have become part of the JFK family under your leadership. I respect your vision and your willingness to dig in, and not just in the garden.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maura]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ /RI remember when you first came to JFK, and no one knew what to expect.  Having been through several principals already, you were a calm, positive, helpful ("Can I do anything for anyone?") spirit that our school needed.  I can't thank you enough...you will be missed.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paige Sileo : )]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[While you did not hire me into this district, you are the reason I feel at home here in Port Chester. I never really felt successful until I landed under your leadership. Your passion for this school, your students and staff is something to be admired.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Juliett Davis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have been a brother, a father and a mentor to me.  Although we didn't always see eye to eye, I know that everything you said and did was to make us stronger teachers and our school a better place.  You will be missed.  I am lucky to have called you "boss".]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Enrique]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ At our 1st meeting you got up abruptly & said- If you want a challenge this is the place. And you were right./RYou have taught me to do things I thought I couldn't do. Thank you/RI will miss you coming in and asking- "What can I do for you"/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ava]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our school is a much better place because of your dedication and care.  I am proud to be have been part of your staff and will truly miss you.  You gave me the "ammunition" to be the "secret weapon" and I thank you! Best Wishes and God Bless!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Darlene]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for alway making me feel welcome and a part of the team from day one.  Now you have more time to spend with loved ones.  Enjoy your retirement!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anne Bueti]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'll never forget meeting you my  first day of student teaching. I remember being very intimidated but thinking I'd love to have a principal like you one day. I've been so blessed to have you as a leader every step of the way. I am grateful for all you have taught me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jamie Rubino ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It was so great to be able to help you open ELC! Now 7 years later we have grown into a huge family. I will miss you coming down the hall saying, "Mary Norelli!" Good luck and may God continue to bless you, your work and especially your family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Norelli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[  Congratulations, Lou!  I remember standing outside of the new classrooms with you, and all you could see was math labs, and science labs.  All I could see were kids, kids, and more kids!  Stay the optimistic dreamer that you are!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Zidik]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am forever grateful to have started my career under your leadership. The skills I learned working at JFK have set me up for a lifetime. I think of you often- you have made such a huge impact on my life. Wishing you the best always. Thank you for everything.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marlee Rio (Santa-Donato)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mr. C you have always been like a father figure to me thanks for all your support and guidance throughout the years. I am proud to be a teacher here at JFK and you a huge part of that. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeanine Maiolini]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["The role of a great leader isn't to give greatness to other human beings, but to help them extract the greatness they already have inside of them."/R/ROver the course of my ten years here at JFK, this is exactly what you have done for me and I will be forever grateful.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kristin Pascuzzi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mr. Cuglietto, You have held us to higher standards; pushing us to do our best and never settling!  You have been a father figure, a mentor and most importantly, a friend. Thank you for the guidance and for making JFK the great school it is!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Melissa Coletti]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Having the 5th graders watch the NCAA tournament in the auditorium and the knowing the betting spreads of the game & history of the schools...  Real life lesson being taught. LOU'S STATEMENT "AS LONG AS YOUR POSITIVES OUTWEIGH YOUR NEGATIVES." The greatest boss ever!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Rinello]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From my very first day at JFK, through my professional and personal successes and downfalls, you have always had my back! I will forever be thankful that my first boss was a caring and thoughtful one. /RHappy retirement! Enjoy your family and keep your sense of humor-HA!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love always, Michelle Capparelli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Who will insist that I open my window and turn on my lights every day once you're gone?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mayra Estrella]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["A leader takes people where they want to go.  A great leader takes people where they don't necessarily want to go, but ought to be.”  Thank you for pushing us to do our personal best, making us go where we didn't want to go, and for being a great leader!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Erica Fuller]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It seems like yesterday we walked the track and you encouraged me to return to teaching.  /RThank You!/RYou always challenged us all to imagine the possibilities and JFK is better for it!/RHere's to the next chapter and all the possibilities yet to be!/RHappy Retirement]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Beth Curley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You hired me 3 years ago and I love my job more and more everyday. Thank you for making JFK my home. Thank you for having faith in me when even I wasn't too sure of myself. For that, I am eternally grateful and forever indebted to you. JFK won't be the same without you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Giselle Noriega]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for believing in me. I am so lucky to have started my teaching career under your leadership. I'll always remember you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heather Resnick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lou,/RThank you for fifteen years of leadership, support, and vision.  Your unwavering devotion to our JFK family has truly been an inspiration.  May the next chapter in your life be filled with success, happiness, and a sense of humor!/RIt's not like this everywhere...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karla]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for believing in me and encouraging me to be a leader. I always appreciated our long chats about school and life./RCheers to you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Christine Rascona]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wishing you happiness and blessings as you begin your new and well-deserved adventure!  I am grateful to have had you as a teacher and leader.  I will always remember how incredibly proud you were of our teachers and students.  You always encouraged us to be better.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nadia Papa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are so many reasons why I will not forget you! But I am most grateful to you for believing in me, and giving me my start in the best elementary school around. Perhaps one day we will meet up for that "soda" and laugh. I will try to always have a "sense of humor!" ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Clara Barreto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I knew from my 1st day of student teaching that JFK was the family I would join because of your leadership.  It sure has been a roller coaster ride, but you've always supported & believed in me. I can't thank you enough for all you have done for me. I'm truly grateful!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Go GIANTS!!! -Diana Pennino]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mr. Cuglietto,  you have been a mentor to me over the years.  Thank you for believing in me and always getting the most out of me.  I have grown as a teacher and I can thank you for that.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rich Gregory]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Every child has a different learning style and pace. Each child is unique, not only capable of learning but also capable of succeeding."        -Robert John Meehan Thank you for being a principal who believed in all his students!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michelle Cardoso]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ The circumstances in which I started this job were very complicated, but Mr. C was there to support and help whenever I needed it. I am so grateful that during such a difficult time, I was blessed to work with such a supportive and loving person. Thank you Mr. C!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love always, Cristina Alampi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mr. Cuglietto,/RI still remember the time I saw you for the first time at the High School's auditorium. Fifteen years have gone by and you still look calm, cool and collected (and not a day older). Enjoy everything that you do from here on. You will be missed at JFK/ELC!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maria Genovese]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/R Thank you for believing in me. Your passion and dedication inspires me to grow as a teacher. /RHappy Retirement!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Lianet Lopez ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mr C.,/RAt my first lit team meeting you said "We had shoes of leadership to fill." You inspired me to search for my perfect pair. Thank you for the motivation, belief and excellence- the model of true leadership. You will be missed!! /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cynthia Ponce]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being such a great role model and leader. I have been very fortunate to work with you and learn from you. JFK is truly a better place because of you. You will be missed, my friend. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Judy Diaz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mr.C.,/RI am the teacher I am today because of you. Thanks for taking a chance on this random teacher from Costa Rica and for always pushing me to be the best I can be./RNow, we can truly say that for you, "No more looping allowed:)"/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Melissa Cruz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[This is your emotional clone talking. Thank you for all the gentle pushes throughout my career. Mediocre wasn't an option. Because of you I shine, I fight, I love and I always think big. I'm honored and proud to say that I am A product of the Cuglietto legacy. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy Capparelli ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[   " A good leader takes a little more than his share of the blame, a little less than his share of the credit." - Arnold H. Glasow/RThank you for always making me feel valued and protected...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shawna Squillace]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mr. C, /RI believe that there are so many things that I could write.  The one thing that stands out to me about you is the way that you care about the students and the staff.  You truly have a big heart!/RThe one thing I will not miss is the late literacy meetings!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jaimi Kennedy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Lou/RDedication, perseverance, loyalty; all virtues that you have shown over the years. Once we had a conversation about the similarities between baseball and teaching. These were values commonly related to success in life. You have achieved that.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda Stelluti]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Compassion is not a weakness, it's a strength". For me, it has always been one of your strongest qualities. I have been blessed to work with you. Thank you for being a friend. Who will I be able to brush up on my Italian with? Mi mancherai,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JoAnn Pace]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Working with you for the past month has made a tremendous impact on my career to become a better teacher every day!!! Thank you for being so supportive and making me feel as if JFK was always my home. /RXOXOXOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Josie :)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/RWhen you interviewed me, it was a hot August day. You interviewed me in the garden. I knew from there if hired what type of administrator you would be; a man dedicated to his students and school, a man who was aware of his surroundings.  Wishing you the best!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Luz Camacho ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I wish you and your family all the best in your new journey! Thank you for being an amazing leader and for teaching me the way!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Yannyn Suarez]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have seen with my own eyes the way you have transformed JFK into the amazing school it is today.  Your dedication and drive are traits that I have always admired about you.  I also will never forget your huge heart...how you jogged over to Sarles Lane for me:) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandy Castillo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lou,/RI don't know what to say or how to say it so all I'm going to say is... THANKS!/R/RCongratulations and good luck.  Enjoy your new adventures!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[  Cindy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Mr. Cuglietto,/RThank you for your support and inspiration. Your experience, knowledge, dedication and presence will be missed in the school. /RWishing you all the best!!/R/RHappy Retirement!!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Liliana Grajeda and family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lou,/RYou have taught me many things these past 7 years...above all to be strong and never stop pushing the limits.  I am grateful to have started my career under your leadership. Never stop being a wise guy because I know I won't! Thank you for always believing in me!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Monica Barreto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will miss you and your "Good Morning" call and your "How can I help you?". It was a privilege and a pleasure to have worked with you. You will be greatly missed./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maria Torres]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mr. Cuglietto,/RThank you for always being an inspiration and an amazing leader. You've made me a better professional and for that I am forever grateful. A famous man by the name of John. F. Kennedy once said, "Things just don't happen.  They're made to happen."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allon Plummer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Many thanks to you for leaving your footprints behind. JFK has become a better school because of your hard work and dedication. Thank you for allowing me to be a special part of JFK when we traveled to D.C. to receive our blue ribbon. Best of luck and God bless. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cheryle Washington K, 1, "5", 2 ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>