<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2352-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/18/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Allyson Carson]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[16840 SW 36th St.]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[El Reno]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[OK]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[73036]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_200]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Walk on the pink side of life]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Ann Ackerman]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[LOK Friends and Classmates]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[That ever present grin.  It was always refreshing to see!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ed Fulmer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wishing you the best as you retire and embark on another journey. My experience in LOK was a blessing, mostly due to you and all you invested in us. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer Meason ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann always took the time to share her experiences, ideas and her coaching with each of us during the recent LOK class.  She cares so much about Oklahoma and making it a great State to work and live.  She’s an inspiration for all of us.  Many thanks!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anita Vanderveer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I enjoyed knowing Ann. She was tireless, helpful, and being with us during our LOK 22 weekends which were a lot of fun.  Ann will be missed here at Leadership Oklahoma!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike Coats]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I was pleased to see that a member of LOK Class I was still around. Thanks for guiding LOK through the past years.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tim Dowd]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It is always great to be around someone who is fun, happy, informative, and in PINK!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chip Oppenheim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your appreciation for our military!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lee baxter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will never forget that beautiful smile, that great sense of humor, and the outstanding ability to make everyone feel a sense of importance and that they belong. (And of course, the pink bell!)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelly Harris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I enjoyed most about working with Ann is always seeing that passion and energy for helping others to grow as leaders.  Walking away from the Leadership Oklahoma experience knowing her legacy will always be a part of the future!  Class 28, Ann's favorite.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Donnie Jones - LOK Class XXVIII ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So many things to love about Ann Ackerman...although pink will never be my favorite color, Ann will always be one of my favorite people.  She's kind, intelligent, beautiful, fun, caring, and chose a great man to spend the rest of her life with.  (You owe me Wayne)!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sammye Norvell Cravens]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always enjoyed her newsletter articles!  They were timely, newsy, and relevant.  Thanks for all that you have done for LOK and the Great State of Oklahoma!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brenda Calhoon Sheik, Class XI]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ your "pinkness",  your yell to get us all in line and to shut up.  and your ability to deal with all of the type "A's" in the class. YO!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen Cunningham ( XXVI best class)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have loved working with Ann, and have gained a life long friend. Ann has the ability to keep the focus on the Board, Alumni and Class members, and never puts herself in the spotlight. She is a very good administrator and manages to keep her sense of humor intact!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robin Roberts Krieger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are a zillion reasons for loving Ann, but most of all that huge heart, always thinking of (and on occassion chasing) others, juggling an incredible schedule with a bounce in her step, sparkle in her eye and phenomenal smile on her face!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bev Binkowski]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Her ability to control some of the rowdiest folks I know with a smile on her face!  Also, loved those pink boots!  Congrats on your next endeavor--your future is very bright!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Penny Voss]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You've stayed true to the mission while growing the Leadership Oklahoma organization quite magnificently.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jocelyn Lee Payne, Class VIII]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Your unbridled enthusiasm for LOK and the impact we can make inspired me.  Your hard work and passion for making a difference has encouraged Oklahoma leaders throughout our state to remain engaged in positive change for generations to come./RPeace & Joy,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[kent carter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[All the program trips for two years all over Oklahoma, late nights with the classes, driving in winter weather-all treats with Ann!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy Hall, Class III]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Anything is possible with sunshine and a little pink!"/R/RYou set the bar high and by that example, influence all those around you to strive for perfection.  /R/RWe'll miss you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allyson, Lee Anne and Tina]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is a firm, pragmatic leader who persuades with her cheerful, friendly attitude. Add in all the pink for an inspiring and refreshing combination - a pleasure to work with!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lou Kohlman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is the whole package. She is professional to a fault, and her follow through and attention to detail is impeccable.  But what is even more significant is how much she cares about people.  She is always willing to listen and has an amazing sense of humor.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Mélon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, I have so enjoyed knowing you over the past years! You have done a super job with LOk. You will be missed! Best of everything in your retirement! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen Rose]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Ann wrote the book on "AWESOME" /Rcomplete with a pink cover. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carolyn Cummins]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["POSITIVE OUTLOOK"/RI have known Ann since 2007 in LOK class 21.  She always seems to have a positive outlook no matter what the situation holds.  Her Optimism and enthusiasm is contagious!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Roger Rinehart]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann can relate to anyone.  No matter a classmate's background, she would make you feel welcome and important.  She also is professional and runs a tight ship.  She could do this without being mean.  A great attribute. /R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tim Rodriguez, class XXVII]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In my head, the first image is always one of you laughing. And it always makes me wish I saw that much humor around me!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ted Streuli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love working with Ann on things because she is unflappable and always puts a positive spin on any issue.  She also has great expectations for all she comes into contact.  I'm so happy to have experienced LOK with Ann as the CEO and proud to call Ann my friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Betsy Guthrie-Brunsteter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the best things I ever did was take the leap and come to work for LOK after my class graduated in 2007. It was an experience I will always cherish for how it made me a better person and hopefully what I gave back. /R/RThanks so much for everything you have done!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Doug Fuller]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[For Ann the best was doable. She was positive, seeking higher level, and anything less was unacceptable. A true leader.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tony Zahn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, I've loved sharing our fondness for PINK  and know you will always wear that color beautifully.   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Patti Mellow, Class XXV]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I value her efficiency, organizational skills, collaborative leadership style, intelligence, counsel and her friendship.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Don Betz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have LOVED getting to look at your gorgeous face. You never age! Why? After years of watching you, I'm sure it's your zest for life,great attitude, happy heart, and smile that shows in your eyes and comes from inside. No griping for me! I'm gonna look like you! Thanks]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy Parrott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She is kind, but has just enough bite to keep you motivated! Incredible friend and very genuine.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hayley Thompson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Ann not only promotes LOK and Oklahoma but she also promotes the individual leaders themselves, connecting them and opening doors. Way to go Ann! You've made Oklahoma a better place for lots of us!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sheryl Siddiqui]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for your service! Have a wonderful retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sheryl Siddiqui]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, congratulations on your retirement!  Most of all congratulations and THANK YOU for a tremendous job in leading LOK for past (how many?) years.  I think the success of our organization is because of your tremendous leadership.  Best wishes!  ...and GO POKES!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Herschel Beard]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always loved your no-nonsense sassy demeanor that said "let's have some fun but misbehave and you are BUSTED !" Speaking for all orange people with authority issues, thank you Ann for leading, guiding and nurturing hoards of grown up children.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anthony McDermid]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I enjoyed your ability to be so organized while working with the chaos that happens with LOK sessions and events, and all along using that pleasant smile. I feel honored to know you, Ann Ackerman, and expect to stay in touch going forward. You will be greatly missed.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gilmer J. Capps, LOK XXV]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Ann inspires by example.  She is kind, smart, humble, exacting, and never takes herself too seriously. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tanya Case]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann:  Of your many wonderful qualities, I most appreciate your smiling, friendly, loving, affirming presence.  Thanks for the great job you have done for LOK.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Gossett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Like all great educators you were always pleasant, but ultimately firm. Our state is a better place because of all the young leaders you have polished and launched. /RWell done Ann! I will always hold fond memories of our time together long ago. /R/RClass I rules forever!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Rainbolt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As a Charrter Member of LOk and Fellow Class1mate with Ann, I've quietly observed her Effective and Faithful Service in the Development of Leaders that will send Ripples of Positive Impact on Making Our World Better Than We Found It! Thank You Ann may God BE With You!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dick Rush, Class I]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hello Ann, I have know you for a number of years, you are a real class act!!! Kind, smart, charming and sweet all at the same time. You have inspired a lot folk's to set there sites for the star's. Be safe and I miss you./RCheers]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bradley Z. Naifeh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always enjoyed Ann Ackerman's true love for The State of Oklahoma!  It would just "ooze" through.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Warren Langford]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember a couple of very deep conversations that we had during our McAleseter weekend as well a very personal conversation that we had this past year in Tulsa that are a testament to your deep level of care an concern.  You will be missed, Pink Lady!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Thomas Boxley, Class XXVI]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for sharing your time, talent, energy and ready smile with leadership Oklahoma. You made a real difference! Congratulation....enyoy retirement./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carl Shortt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, you are a beautiful person inside and out. I value our friendship. LOK promotes friendships for life. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Deena Fisher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I enjoy most about Ann is her positive attitude and the spirit of joy operating in her life.  Her smile is contagious and I always feel better after speaking with her.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Greg Elliott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always enjoyed how efficient and professional Ann was, especially when working with members of the adult classes.  She always had everything in place and confirmed 2 or 3 times.  As a chairperson of the Adult Program Committee, she was always a joy to work with!!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dana Shadid]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann has been inspiration to me for many years, beginning as my college professor./RYou are my mentor and role model.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Blankenship Pointer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You were a positive influence at all meetings.  I loved your can-do attitude.  You will be missed.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charlie Sherman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, /RI always loved your smile and your pleasant manner in which you interacted!  Enjoy your retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan Paddack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Knowing I won't be the only one in pink! /RSeriously, your quiet confidence, wit, and leadership are contagious]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ann Hargis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I think of you Ann I think of two of my favorite quotes - "The best protection any woman can have...is courage" and "Life shrinks or expands in proportion to one's courage."  You are certainly the most courageous woman I know and such an inspiration to me!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Stallings]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[With Ann, pink isn't just a color, it's an attitude and a way of life!  Think pink!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Angela Marsee, Class XXVII]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Drill Sergeant Ackerman:  A lumpy bunk and cold shower are always yours on Fort Sill. Thanks for your support and love of our Soldiers.  You are loved in return. /R/RPS: One pink tshirt for sale. Worn once and even then with great trepidation.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jimmy Dailey, Class XXV (the MAC)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Martinis!!! It was such fun!/RI'm sorry I've missed/Rmore times together but I'll never forget the ones we had! Good luck in everything you do Anne--and come visit us on Sullivan's Island! Love, Cheryl]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cheryl McMurry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[her pink-ness.  hooah! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randy K. Macon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is the consummate professional.  She treats everyone with dignity and respect.  She represented LOK in such a way that others knew the quality of the organization because of the qualities of its leader.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Albert Johnson, Jr., LOK Class XXII]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks so much for your leadership!  Enjoy new experiences and new adventures!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jane mudgett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, I loved watching you master the role, learning new skills and fine-tuning the old ones.  I wish everyone enjoyed work like you have enjoyed serving as CEO of LOK.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy Sharrock]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I enjoyed most about working with Ann Ackerman is the manner in which she corralled 50+ type A personalities on a monthly basis -- not too timid, not too aggressive, but rather just right.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anil Gollahalli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, it was apparent that you genuinely care about other people. You worked tirelessly to make sure everyone had the best experience possible. That type of concern can't be faked, it can only come from the heart. I wish you all the best. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom Bates ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is a loyal, dedicated and professional lady whose leadership will be missed.  Best wishes in your retirement!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Young ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We wish you the best time of your life in your retirement!  We know you will never truly "retire".  We can't wait to see what this next life chapter brings to you!  You are an amazing woman. Go out there and enjoy life!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Suzanne and Jim McAuley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A special thanks to you for making my Leadership Oklahoma experience so amazing! I am so thankful for the opportunity and I hope you know what an impact you leave on others. Congrats to an amazing woman! "Pink isn't just a color, it's an attitude." Love you Ann!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mikhael Reed]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always made each weekend a lot of fun while being very informative about the important issues we face everyday in Oklahoma!  Your professionalism and friendship is truly admired and appreciated!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gregory Smith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is always positve and happy and was a true inspiration to former alums and others who would interact with her.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Phil Kliewer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Believe it or not, the thing I most enjoyed about working with Ann were her emails to the class to keep us organized and informed. Her eye for detail and her communication, made her a perfect fit to run such an organization and keep all the cats herded!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sherri Wilt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is a "get it done girl!" but also lots of fun!  Always enjoy our "catch-up" lunches with Ann, Nance and Nancy.  And look forward to doing this more often now that Ann will be retired!  Much love and happiness to you and Wayne!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pam Troup]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Everything everyone else has said but also Ann's tact and handling of situations. So many times she would gently smile, start off with a long 'Wellllll....' and get through situations with absolute grace. Thank you for not quitting after your first year round class!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sam(onia), ClassXX]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann was also so positive and upbeat. She was good at herding cats too. I feel lucky to have been in an LOK class that she led. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ziva Branstetter ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, as a member of Class I, you were always a voice of reason and organization.  I really appreciated your accepting spirit.  You made this small town girl feel comfortable and valued from day one.  I wish you the best in your well deserved retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandi Liles, Class I]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, after having been out of state for almost 10 years, it was wonderful to reconnect with LOK. Thank you for including me in the program committee. It has been a joy to work with you and get to know you. Marion will obviously do a great job, but you will so be missed.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dawn Byram]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I admire Ann's ability to gracefully navigate a variety of personalities.  She makes each person feel important. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen Wicker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/RAnn's love for Oklahoma is inspiring, contagious and limitless.  Thank you for guiding a generation of leaders to listen, learn and engage in our future./R/ROne day we will find you providing security near the Thunder bench in a beautiful pink jacket!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian Byrnes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann- If we could find a mountain of pink onyx, I would move we sculpt a monument in your honor for the service and leadership you have given, so faithfully, to LOK and Oklahoma. You are officially AWESOME!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John D. Harper]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is a kind, caring and giving Oklahoman who is always willing to lend a hand.  Her service to LOK & the state has had a huge impact on shaping leaders and helping them grow to be even better.  Many thanks for your service to the program we all love so dear!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Dorman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your passion for our State and for LOk are contagious!  Both are better because of your efforts.  Forever grateful for your friendship and for the opportunities you provided that allowed me to be more deeply involved in this program.  Best of luck in the next chapter!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Monica Neal]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your enthusiasm for every weekend, and seeing all of us, even though you'd experienced every subject and each city so many times.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan Harris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations, and always remember that it took someone with a keen mind, a strong knack for organization, a thick skin, and most of all a good sense of humor to be such a successful leader among leaders. You've earned a break. Best wishes to you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob Nelon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Narrowing it down to just "one thing" is virtually impossible...but what rises to the top of a long list...is the strength of her integrity and determination to do what's right. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rhonda Hooper]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the perfect colleague and friend.  Intelligent, loyal, caring, helpful, dedicated and visionary are just a few of the words that describe you.  It is an honor to call you my friend.  I wish you the best.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jerry Steward]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is a dear friend, one who leads with a calm, even demeanor. She is always kind and courteous to everyone, a brilliant, logical thinker with an uplifting PINK personality. She has helped many organizations grow and prosper, including LOK. Now on to the next adventure]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With many hugs, Carol Troy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, you are a treasure.  It is such a treat talking with you about our earlier Leadership Oklahoma days, especially all you have meant to its success and progress.  Thank you heartily and with abundant love.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy Grigsby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have been an amazing CEO for Leadership Oklahoma....the perfect person for connecting leaders, creating passion for our State, and inspiring action.  Enjoy your retirement Ann!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin O'Connor, Class XXIII]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I loved getting to know you.  I loved being in your last class.  I love your passion and professionalism.  I love you in pink.  I love you as our LOK mom.  I love you for being able to herd the strong willed so eloquently.  I love having a new friend. I  just love ANN! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michelle Hardesty, Class XXVIII]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always looked forward our early morning breakfast meeting as IHOP as we both tried to figure out what the heck we were doing!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lee Symcox]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I enjoyed the fact that Ann made us all feel like we were critical to the success of the program during the year we participated.  No matter what organization we represented, where we came from, etc.., it was clear that we were important.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Towler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Even when traveling to every corner of the state on what is normally someone's "free time", no matter the weather or the high maintenance Type-A participants or that she's probably heard it all before (a few times), Ann is always cheerful - and that cheer is contagious!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[G.T. Bynum]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The one thing, I enjoyed most about working with Ann is she can always be counted on to go above and beyond what is expected. Ann served on the Red Cross board, helping so many and without recognition. Ann, you are a wonderful friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Debby Hampton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We will miss Ann’s ability to bring patience and serenity while, under the surface, moving forward with exceptional haste.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Edwards]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From our time together in LOKC & LOK to present, you have been an amazing person to call a friend - always fun, smart, committed and a positive force wherever you are.  You deserve a happy and fulfilling future.!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cynthia Cope]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is a fantastic leader and one who has always been inclusive, engaging and encouraging.  She has done an awesome job in leading with sincerity, laughter, and care.  Congratulations Ann and much happiness to you always.  /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie Knutson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The thing I enjoy most about Ann is her demeanor. She carries herself in a way that is graceful yet very approachable. We all love Ann and wish her the best in her new chapter.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aaron Fulkerson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, you have touched my life and so many other Oklahomans through your leadership and time with Leadership Oklahoma.  Your friendship, dedidication to LOK, and leadership will always be cherished.  May you be richly blessed in your new life adventures!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jodi R. Cline]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I've always enjoyed working directly with Ann during the sessions in the Guymon area. She has such a great smile! I enjoyed seeing her smiling here, especially wearing pink cowboy boots. She always made "calm enjoyment while being completely in control" look effortless.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lucinda Masterson Ray]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["A truly great mentor is hard to find, difficult to part with and impossible to forget." Thank you for taking a chance on me 8 years ago. I have learned so much from you and believe I am a stronger leader because of your leadership. I will miss seeing you in the office!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lee Anne Stone]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In all honesty...we could have simplified LOK alot by just getting the class together every month and let them learn from Ann.  They would have learned confidence, passion, commitment, love for our State, and the most appropriate ways to wear pink.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brent Kisling]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann has tireless energy (could be the diet coke)!  She could change plans on a dime when needed.  Through her leadership she has left her mark on LOK and the state of Oklahoma!  Thanks for mentoring hundreds of leaders across the state!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Krista Roberts]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always respected you and trusted your judgement.  You are a true professional and a great leader.  Thanks for all you have done for Oklahoma.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wes Stucky]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will surely miss your ready smile at conferences!  You always brightened my day.  Even though you won't be there in person, no one can take our wonderful, irreverent, rowdy memories away...so let's just concentrate on that.  Enjoy "life after ALA."/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jan Sanders, Pasadena (CA) Library]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Oklahoma is a better place because of Ann.  Through her drive, dedication and sense of humor, she has positively impacted the State's future more than she realizes - and we're thankful for her.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jay Calhoun]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, I'm so glad to have had this opportunity to know you better.  You have such a happy spirit.  You are a joy.  I wish you much more joy and  happiness as you embark on this new chapter in your life.  Stay in touch. XOXO ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charlotte Edwards]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your ever ready smile, your positive attitude and your total dedication to all things LOK are what I love about you. I wish you the very best. Please stay in touch. Warm regards,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ronnie Irani]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ "I really enjoyed Ann's spirit of fun during my Leadership Oklahoma experience.  Ann worked hard to make our sessions both educational and enjoyable."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen Rieger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is an excellent example of a beautiful, brilliant woman with grace and class. She's also been a great mentor, even when she wasn't aware she was one. And no one looks hotter in pink.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Clytie Bunyan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, you were always positive and professional....and preferred to deflect any praise to staff, board members and committee chairs.  You are the ultimate LOK ambassador!  We will miss you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Scott Jones]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, you are the consumate professional and have contributed so much leadership to Leadership Oklahoma.  I know that pink is your favorite color and you wear it so well!  Good luck to you as you enter a new chapter in  your life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Janet Cunningham]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The iconic figure of LOK retiring? You my dear friend will be missed, but always remembered. Love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Paul]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/RAnn, congrats on your retirement.  I've enjoyed getting to know you better through LOK.  You are one impressiesve lady!!! I'm sure our lives will intertwine again as they did with econ dev, then LOK.  I wish you the best in your future endeavors.  Have fun!!!!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Janet Smith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To know Ann is to know "Pink"!  Ann embodies all that pink stands for:  love, beauty, charm, politeness, sensitivity, femininity and the romantic.   Keep these with you as you begin the new chapter of life.  The best & God's richest blessings always!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carolyn Stager]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To know Ann is to know "Pink"!  Ann embodies all that pink stands for:  love, beauty, charm, politeness, sensitivity, femininity and the romantic.   Keep these with you as you begin the new chapter of life.  The best & God's richest blessings always!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carolyn Stager]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Ann!  I hate it that I won't be able to attend your retirement party.  I have a previous commitment out of town.  /R/RIt was a pleasure to work with you over the years.  You have a great personality, a good sense of humor, and you are always on top of your game!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Best Wishes!  E. Scott Henley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Leadership Oklahoma has developed into an awesome partnership, implementing change and improving our Oklahoma traditions.  Thanks for everything and have fun exploring this wonderful state.  Best wishes]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Anne McCaffree]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, I wanted to thank you for all the work you did for all of us in Class 28. You made this one of the most memorable experiences for me and so many others. You will never be forgotten. Best of luck to you in all your future endeavors. Joe Cunningham]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joseph Cunningham]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann loves pink as much as I love orange.  May she have a pinkalicious retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jamie Payne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I saw Ann as the consumate professional. Leadership Oklahoma was a life changing experience for me, and Ann's leadership was a large part of what made it so special...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Don Gooch]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the teacher and mentor one never forgets. You are all wonderful things Oklahoma. You are the rock star of leadership. Thank you for your service to LOK!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie Bohannon- Class 23]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, thank you for your amazing leadership of LOK.  Your vision, strategy and passion have contributed significantly to improving the state of Oklahoma.  You will be dearly missed!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandy Pratt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Ann,/R/RI will never hear "Yo!" or see pink without thinking of you! :) I truly appreciate your attention to detail. You made the LOK experience extremely special!/R/RThank you! Best wishes for a wonderful retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julia Chew]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Ann always makes folks feel like they matter.  She's sincerely present in every interaction she engages in and makes others feel valued.  I pray her next adventure is all she's hoping for and more!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leslie Hicks Kutz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is always upbeat & positive and a pleasure to work with. I will miss her!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robert Campbell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The one thing I enjoyed most about working with Ann was her tireless commitment to addressing the challenges and opportunities facing Oklahoma and working to develop leaders to address those issues to make a difference for our great State. Thank you Ann!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Wagner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I enjoyed watching Ann work with LOK Class members, sponsors, Board members and session committees.  Ann is never above whatever it took to get the job done and support each class.  I enjoy and appreciate Ann!  Happy Retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Adrian DeWendt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Annie, My first thought had nothing to do with work. You joined us with the Cooks at our Grand Lake Home. While having wine on the upper deck, we see a naked Ed Cook running to and diving off our swim dock. Congrats on two great careers. God's sweet blessings,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Lynn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, everytime I see pink, I will think of you.  (unless, of course, it is someone with pink eye :)  Have a wonderful, love filled time.  Hope to see you soon.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Natalie Shirley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I loved working with Ann because she was appreciative and always cool, calm and collected. All the best to you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anita Risner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The one thing I enjoyed most about working with Ann is she always kept me very organized and didn't make fun of me when I wasn't.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Russ Harrison]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann-/RIt was an absolute pleasure getting to know you. The LOK experience was a success because of your leadership and dedication. I wish you the best and know that the impact your have made on so many will be felt in Oklahoma for generations to come. God bless you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jason Hopkins]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The thing I enjoyed most about working with Ann was her ability to work with a myriad of people and groups that are all part of the fabric of Oklahoma.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill McKamey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is very business-like and efficient, but she and I discovered several personal similarities that enhanced our friendship. She has a knack for connecting with each person on a unique level. I admire her ability to make each LOK member feel special!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marilyn Geiger Kaplan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your book of rules was impressive- the fact that you had them all memorized even more so.  We never got a copy, but it was comforting to know we could depend on you. Ex: "Sharon, it is rude to bring a single malt scotch to an event where the hosts furnished OK wines.":)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sharon Robinson Class XXI]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, you are truly awesome and always made each of us feel valued and important to the team.  Your warm acceptance and kindness to all greatly contributed to a stellar LOK experience!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura Culberson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann/REnjoyed getting to know the original "Lady in Pink". Many wishes for a very happy retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gail Huneryager]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Loved Ann's inexhaustible supply of energy and her passion for pink!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ann, Chuck, Kelsey, Spencer and Sam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how Ann always made me feel like an important member of every board and committee meeting. She took time to visit with me personally and was appreciate of my time and contributions to lOK. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lana Reynolds]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ONE enjoyable thing about working with Ann is impossible although I will share two of her traits that I admire the most--professionalism and sense of humor./RThank you for all you did for LOK!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kay Martin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Loved celebrating my 50 th birthday with you in Turkey!  What an awesome trip./R  Thank you for serving LOK.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy Lippert]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your leadership has made being a part of Leadership Oklahoma a complete joy.  From being class member, to serving on the board, to just stealing a chance to compare thoughts, it's all been amazing and you have been at the heart of all of it.  Love and hugs.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laurie Tilley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is cheerful, efficient, enthusiastic and dedicated. She made my Leadership OK experience!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brooke Murphy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I enjoyed watching Ann stand tall as a strong and confident leader and commander-in-chief while entertaining us with her storytelling talents and sense of humor. I feel fortunate to be part of the monthly LOK Class 24 ladies night out dinner & wine club. Think Pink!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marcy Price]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, your cheerfulness, your competence and your sense of humor are always appreciated. You have held the torch that all of us might continue see the way.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim and Lynn Howard]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann. You are the definition of a classy lady.  Thanks for all you do for Oklahoma and LOK.  I did enjoy stealing the clapper from your pink bell.  Just so you know, Sue Ann got it out of your purse.  Enjoy Life./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dr. Joe Leverett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann always followed through.  You never had to remind her to do something she said she would do.  Although she was not an accountant, she had many of the positive attributes of accountants, i.e. OCD and AR.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larry Pulliam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, what a blast to have gone through Class I together.  I will always remember those times and working together all these years!  You are the best and I look forward to keeping in touch.  Love to you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindy Ritz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is my friend whom I trust and value her opinions, guidance and genuine care for me and others. Always humble about herself and supportive of those around her, Ann is a very special person I treasure having as a friend. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Teresa Rose Crook ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I enjoyed most about working with Ann...her passion for ensuring all participants learned about our state, politics and industry!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ryan Stafford Double Deuce]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, it was an amazing year!  You're a very classy woman, and an excellent person.  I will fondly remember your gracious demeanor.  Especially when you "shared" your steak with me in Tulsa.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Adam Leaming]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, you were always so positive and compliementary when visiting Enid. I always felt like you had everything under control in a subtle calm way. Thank you for all you have been to LOK! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Martie Oyler LOK Class XIII]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann--/RIf success is counted by the number of friends you've made along the way--then, you my friend, have been extremely successful.  I have enjoyed immensely getting to work with you & thank you for leaving your legacy scattered all across our great state.  Paula Huck]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Best wishes!Paula Huc]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you... for your profound investment in all things LOk - from the global to the minutiae.  I loved "sweating the details" with you, you know, and the fact that you understand so profoundly that that's where the sparkle and the magic come from.  Salut!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve D. Wright, Class XVIII]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, you did an amazing job motivating and managing so many different personalities and making each of us feel valued and important. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lance McDaniel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is one of the most organized individuals I have ever had the pleasure of working with.  Each year at the opening retreat, Ann never forgets every item that needs to be available for the opening night reception that BancFirst, SSC and JMCM hosts.  Remarkable!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen James]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You were always a model of efficiency which I respected and always blessed us with your beautiful smile regardless of the stress and aggravation our willful leaders put you through./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vicky Simpson Wilcoxen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It has been said that leaders don’t create followers, they create more leaders.  Ann certainly has positively influenced hundreds of LOK leaders and she is leaving some pretty powerful pink high heels to fill.  I love her “can do” attitude and her commitment to Oklahoma]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cheryl Evans, LOK Class XXI]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No matter what, you alway maintained your composure.  You kept whatever drama may have been occurring out of our view to maximize the learning experience.  Ever so gracious and caring for each of us, you're an excellent leader--with great shoes!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Swigert]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, /RIt's been nice getting to know you better through your work and leadership with LOK.  You helped take the organization to a new level and stature and have been a great encourager for member involvement./RStill hope to see you often!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cathryn Render]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ My greatest engagement with Ann was on a trip to Turkey!  She did an incredible job is corralling 26 strong personalities, while still maintaining her "calm"./R/RI was also in her first class as Ex Director - Class XIX!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Glenda Love]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, Your ability to always remain calm, cool, and collected (at least to observers :) ) while 'handling' the many and often challenging personalities of we LOK'ers is what inspired the network and collaberative aspects of LOK.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Scott M. Stidham]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'll always remember that night you stormed into the Phi Delt House!  No wonder no Chi O would ever date a Phi Delt!  I have always admired you.  Love you and all best wishes as you start your next chapter!  Go Pokes!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Clayton Taylor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann has the ability to make everyone feel special.  She is kind and caring, in addition to being the consummate professional who is focused and determined.  It has been an honor to work with her, and I look forward to continuing our friendship in the years to come.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michelle Briggs]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Everyone from LOK knows the fantastic job Ann has done as CEO. Jean & I want to especially recognize the outstanding job she did coordinating all the details for two International trips. Russia, Poland, Istanbul, & Cypress were all more enjoyable having Ann with us. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[We'll miss you: Jean & Bob Harbison]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Working with Ann has been a great honor.  She always has a special way to bring the best out of people. Positive, insightful, encouraging, helpful, kind are words that come to mind when thinking about Ann and her leadership style./RAnn, you are a blessing.  Thanks]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charlie Baker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I appreciate what Ann allowed us to accomplish through the Saint Crispin's "Experience," engaging each class in hands-on arts experiences that made each class member an ambassador for arts and arts education throughout our state!  It's been a blast!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ken Busby - Class XVII]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Leadership has been defined as the art of getting someone else to do something you want done because he or she really wants to do it.  By this definition Ann is truly a gifted leader!  It has been a blessing to get to know and work with her over the last few years!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tim Munson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann's ever-present positive attitude - it's contagious!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Seat]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, you helped make me a better person and ensured I got my LOK experience.  For that, I will always be thankful!  You are a ROCK STAR!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cara Cowan Watts]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann has been so fabulous to know and work with since I have been in LOK. She has been instrumental in furthering the mission of Leadership Oklahoma and has earned the respect of leaders across the State in the process. I am proud to call her a friend and mentor. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michele Campbell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>