<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2357-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/18/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Ashton Smith]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[123 Fenner Lane]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Raleigh]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[NC]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[27603]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDEX_FEDEX2DAY]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[For Tim]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Tim Lehan]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[From all of us]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are such an incredible part of my life and such an inspiration. You give selflessly to so many and we're all lucky to count you as a friend. Here's wishing 30 brings your best year yet!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ashton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will never forget bonding with you over our love of Cee Lo Green and the Glee soundtrack as we drove around Raleigh buying Halloween party decorations! I miss our days working in the same office and seeing you every day. Love you & happy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Corey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim is the best husband and friend anyone could ask for! We've shared countless laughs and shenanigans together - there's never a dull moment. Happy happy birthday dear friend! I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kaler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Tim! We hope you have a great day and best year yet! You totally deserve it! love you lots and lots!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Xoxo, Lisa,Patrick,Garrison, Lupton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'll always remember being at Topsail and having a "wardrobe malfunction". Without hesitation, you offered me your shirt...and then somehow I lost it! I'll use this opportunity to both thank you and apologize. You are such a thoughtful, generous friend. Happy 30th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amanda Edwards]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday, Tim!! Hope all is well and that you have an amazing day - you deserve it!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex Knepp]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wow, where to begin? The trip up to Penn State to move furniture when you just had surgery. The homeless woman biting my back in Chapel Hill. Weekends at your lake house. The karaoke night at the beach. Just a few of the countless great times. You're the best, bud.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Everett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim..../R/R/RHAPPY BIRTHDAY/RHOT STUFF!!!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[XOXO, Cabell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It has been fun to get to know you through your giveback to the community and being a great friend!  Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nathan Hanna]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whoa!!  I can't believe you are 30!!!  It feels like yesterday we were celebrating 25!  I wish you love, success, and happiness in this new decade!!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lexie Batchelor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happiest of birthday's to you! Sending you love & happiness in the year to come! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Caroline Gaona]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[With each passing year I see new things I love about Tim.  This year it is my appreciation of not just what a wonderful son he is, but to also see him show love to a sister far away and a brother who is getting ever closer to his wedding.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The other Tim Lehan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Tim. 30 is a big year... a great year...and knowing you it will be your best yet. I remember meeting you for the first time out with Tom and Tera, and I have been impressed ever since. You inspired me to join the Clauses. Have a wonderful birthday]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex McTighe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim, /R/RYour genuine smile, generous hellos and your distinguished way can turn 29 into 30 with extraordinary style! We wish you the happiest birthday! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Warmest Regards! The McTighes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will always be thankful for the kindness and compassion/not to mention the words of wisdom you had for me during my 'coming out'  journey...and boye was it a journey ;-)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Antoine (The Twon) Ponton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can always count on a smile and a kind word from Tim, and each remark is from the heart.  There have been many situations recently that I reflect on how Tim would respond.  Thanks for being such a wonderful friend!  Happiest of Birthdays!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lyndsay Hanna]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite quality of Tim is his generosity. We know about his commitment to The Capital City Clauses, but I benefited from his generosity in a personal way. Without batting an eye, he offered me the use of a family car when mine broke down. Thank you for all you do!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anthony Greco]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To the one guy who threw the best party ever, for some start-up non profit organization nobody had ever heard of. Nobody else I know would ever do that, and I couldn't be more thankful./R/RCheers to you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chase + Vs. Cancer Team]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim! I hope you have such a happy birthday and very fun celebration of being a successful human by 30! I hope we can share some time at the lake together soon when Charlotte returns from Paris! Until then, best wishes and love to you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amy Littleton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hiring Tim made me feel like I drafted LeBron! Wayne & I often lament that we're not going to find another Tim & that we need to lower our expectations-he set the bar so high! I am so proud of Tim & the life he has made for himself. Wishing him a wonderful, boozy 30th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Willett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Timmy! I love and miss you! I hope 30 isn't as hard for you as it was for me!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ashley (Lehan) Barnoski ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember the time we had to hide from a storm on a stranger's dock because Amanda and I showed up late to the lake and delayed the boating excursion?  You were so nice to us then and always have been. Everyone needs more friends like you; kind, genuine and authentic.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[YFS, Dan and Amanda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim is one of the only people I know that can bring a smile to your face at the drop of a dime. His happiness and enthusiasm are absolutely contagious. I consider myself fortunate to call him a friend. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom Simon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Timmy, you are one of the most sincere, caring, and thoughtful people I know. You care for others more than yourself and you always make the individuals around you feel important and special.  I am blessed to call you one of my best friends. Happy 30th birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robby Lawson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My wish is that your future real estate dealings are all easier than Lauren and Seb's. :) And, of course, we wish you good cheer, good health and good times!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary-Ann Baldwin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Here's to the Happiest of birthdays, Mr. Lehan!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat Price]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will always appreciate how welcoming and nice you were to me when I came to Chapel Hill. Happy Birthday! Wish we could go back to Munich with everyone again and celebrate.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian Lux]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kind, Thoughtful, Passionate are three word that come to mind when I think about your amazing spirit.  My favorite memory with you has to be co-starring with you in The Pajama Game. And splitting up the top and bottom of that pair of PJ's for the grande finale!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Libby Bradley Burton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim, you're an incredible guy and one of the nicest people I've ever met. The world would be a much better place if everyone was as selfless as you are. Thanks for everything you do, and for inspiring us all along the way!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Zack Medford]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have been a wonderful nephew, and a joy to be with since you were little. I especially remember the times you spent in Oak Ridge with Susannah going to Showkids camp in the summers. I loved watching the two of you do your songs and dances. (1/2)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Barbara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(2/2) It also gave us a chance to have you to ourselves, which we never were able to do before then./RI am proud to be your aunt, not because of your accomplishments which are many, but because of the special person you are, inside and out.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love always, Aunt Barbara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Excellent anniversaire Tim!!! /RJe te souhaite plein de bonheur pour tes 30 ans :) Bisous ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Oriane ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Tim! Hope it rocks as much as you do!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karla Smith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim always greets me with a smile and a hug. From a friend I have known for many years but may only see a few times a year that means so much! Thank you Tim for your kindness and friendship. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ann Beal]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember that time I called you from Houston.  I was so ready to come home, but I was not sure I could.  I was afraid my options were going to be limited, and I was scared.  You reminded me of the person I was and made me feel like I had the support system I needed.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelly Harvell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Tim! I hope that gorgeous smile of yours is sneaking up on you all day. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Morgan Siem]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As I think back on 29 years of birthdays, I still remember your laugh and smile at 3 years - when you saw your Jeep./R/RHappy Birthday/RYou Make Us Very Proud]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom and Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our favorite memories of you are when we were house hunting!  Your playing with Wyatt and helping guide us to our perfect home are greatly appreciated. We'll never forget walking into our home and your being as excited as we were when we saw it. (1/2)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With love, Aaron, Leigh, and Wyatt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(2/2) Thank you, and have the best birthday ever! Here's to another year of celebration!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With love, Aaron, Leigh, and Wyatt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The first time we met, it was by chance. Ashton as always, is to blame. I can't express how much your friendship means to me. Your laugh is infectious. When you walk into a room, everything gets better. Happy birthday love, here's to many more years and memories.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tera]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[YAY!  Happy birthday, Tim!  I wish you loads of happiness in the next year!  I can't wait to celebrate soon!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kaylor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A smile down the hall/RBlur along the sidewalk waves/RTim in motion happy/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike and Corliss]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Tim!!/R/RYou have grown into an amazing and inspiring person. It is a joy and a privilege to be part of your life. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan Smith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim, you've exceeded the bounds of friendship time and time again. Especially this last year ... it's hard to imagine the start of our marriage without your patience and support.  Man, we are lucky to know you! Happy birthday, friend. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sebastian & Lauren Montagne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wishing the very best birthday to a very special guy! May this be your best year yet. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elizabeth Kirby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memory of Tim? All of the best times in college. There are too many! But staying up all night on Halloween to get riser tickets, that whole 1st summer at Mill Creek, and the trip to Seattle to visit Shoafie are pretty high on the list. Happy 30th, my friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Katie Cambron (Loopi!)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He will probably never fully realize the exact extent, but he has made impacts in my life, both large and small, that not only will I never be able to repay, but I will never be able to adequately express my gratitude. He is simply one of the best people in my world.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[M. Crawford]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Still manage a good laugh (or two) every time we think back on that cruise when Robby & Bardin snuck into your & Matt Thomas's cabin and placed what appeared to be a used -- anyway, we're sure you remember the rest. Thanks for being such a genuine guy, Tim. Happy 30th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[S. Burner & M. Lafferty]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim!  I'm sorry I can't be there in person to make you a horribly lopsided funfetti birthday cake.  Miss you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meagan ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim, you've been making sparks in Raleigh since I first met you and now this city is on fire. You have incredible energy and Raleigh is so lucky that you've channeled it into making downtown a better place to live. Shine on, friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Braden Rawls]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim, I hope you have a birthday that rivals the "keg in pool" night. Also, I don't remember anything about the "keg in pool" night so maybe just a little less alcohol this time.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shoaf]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Tim! This past year has been great getting to know you even better. We look forward to another 30 (plus) years of having you as our friend. Best wishes!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gregg and Brian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being the best boyfriend a guy could ask for.  Everyday with you is a celebration and I look forward to many more./R/RHappy 30th Birthday, Timmy!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stephen ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Anything you want, Timmy.  (insert lipstick print here)/R/RHappy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rachel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'll never forget the time you stayed at the City of Raleigh Museum with me, ruffling pompoms for Timewarp, well into the night! It was just the two of us, and without you, it would have been just lonely 'ol me! Here's to friends you can count on. Thanks Tim! Happy Bday]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heather Allen Zucchino]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wishing you a very happy birthday, Tim!!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Fortson Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim, you are such a wonderful friend and I am grateful that you are in our lives. My greatest wish for you on your 30th birthday is for you to continue to get healthier and stronger over the next year. Enjoy your special day and may this year be your best one yet!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Caroline Griffith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[1-2-3]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stephen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can always count on a big smile and a fantastic laugh when I see Tim! Happy Birthday friend! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Merritt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your energy is contagious!  I love the passion you bring to even mundane tasks.  You're awesome!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Adrienne Lester]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim - Happy Birthday!/R/RWelcome to the 30-somethings club./R/RLook forward to catching up soon.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Seth Dearmin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim,/R/RI hope you have a wonderful Birthday and many more in the future!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wesley Batchelor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 30th birthday Tim! We wish you much happiness! Hope you enjoy your special day! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Travis & christy smith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim, I love your genuine belly laugh, your honest character, and your loyalty toward your closest friends. I look forward to having you in my life for the length of it.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[PZ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Brett and I miss our Tyler's nights with you! We both talk about how we have never had a friend as genuine, positive, and truly kind as you. We're always in awe of how you make sure everyone around you is happy. You're one of a kind, Tim! Hope to be back in NC with you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brett and Ali Page]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Here's to the best dance partner, deb escort, and partner in crime a girl could hope for.  Wishing you thirty more years of music, laughter, and stories.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Caitlin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey there Timmy!  Happy big one--hope that your 30th is a blast.  Wish I could be there to celebrate but I'm sure the Raleigh crew has got you covered. Hope to see you before long, feel free to come visit in SF anytime!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom Morgan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Tim!!! I feel so blessed to have grown up with you, be neighbors with you, and share a friendship so special. I will always think of you as my brother who I will love forever! I hope your 30's are amazing! Oh, and for old times, 20 years later... SPLASH!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathryn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Timmy!/R/RYou will always hold a special place in my heart as my Munich beer and bunk mate. And for the rest of our lives know that I will always be just a thin cardboard partition away and there to hold your hand. Lots of love and piso mojado my friend. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Coco]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being such a wonderful friend and advisor as well as all of the numerous things you have done and continue to do for those who are less fortunate in our community.  Wishing you all the best for your 30th Birthday bud & health & happiness for many years! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chad Griffith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim is one of my favorite people & his friendship means the world to me. He always has a huge smile, gives great big hugs, and has one of the kindest souls I've ever known.  I'd spend part of every day at a UNC ball game with Tim if I could./R/RHappy Birthday, my buddy!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Danny]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim's smile lights up a room, and when he laughs that chuckle of his, everyone who hears can't help but smile and feel happy themselves! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Cooks]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I turned 30 so long -- so, so long ago -- that I should have some elderly wisdom about milestones and aging and how it feels to no longer be in your 20s.  But, I don't - because it feels about the same, which, if you think about it, is pretty great.  Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Blake]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday to a guy with the best smile and a huge heart!! We love you Tim!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jonathan and Matthew ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My dear brother... There aren't words to say how much I love you and I've missed you this year. Fav memory; laying in bed at the beach house talking about Grey Poupon and Europeans. I think I was 10. Wish I could be there for your birthday, but I certainly send you love]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Little Lehan <3]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tell him how proud I am of him and that I am also proud to be the person who taught him how to cheat with a marked deck of cards. That's what uncles are for.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Perry ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy happy birthday! Tim, I think you are awesome and have a genuinely good heart. You do so much for so many people that it makes me want to be a more charitable person! Thank you for all you do! Would love to spend more time with your always smiling face! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anne Siceloff ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim- /RHappy birthday! We are privileged to call you our friend. Here is to a happy 30th, and wishing you all the best. Hope to see you soon./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, James & Elizabeth Kirby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hap Hap Happy Birthday, Tim! From the "First Inaugural Frank A. Sinatra Party" to "Bluegrass Sundays" at North Street to the UNC game in Charlotte this September, so glad to have you as a friend. Happy 3-0!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ryan Schuetz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy, Happy Birthday, Tim!!! Thank you for being the kind, wonderful, hard-working, awesome, fabulous person that you are! I'm proud & lucky to call you my friend! I hope your 30th is the best year yet!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christina Coffey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>