<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2358-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/19/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Rebecca Brittain]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[4400 Memorial Drive ]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[apt 2240]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Houston]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[TX]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[77007]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[purple]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 90th Birthday Mammaw!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Helen Brittain (Mammaw)]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[From your family & friends]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mammaw, you are the most patient, loving, and giving person I have ever known.  I aspire to grow more like you every day. Thank you for loving and nurturing us unconditionally, and being like a mother to us always. I love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rebecca Brittain]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A very sweet and loving sister, always listens and gives the best advice. A truer and great friend. God Bless you, Helen.  Tons of love, Hugs and Kisses.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sister, Dorothy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aunt Helen, I have such wonderful memories of my mom and dad and brothers coming down to Houston and you all/RComing up to Ohio . Also when Nip , kids and I came down. Wonderful memories. We love you always. May God bless you on this special birthday!!! You are amazing!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sharyn and Nip Roberts]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[  I hold dear to my heart the visit I made to Texas as a young teenager and how all of the family scared the crap out of me with the creature that was going to break in and get us. GC really had me going and you went right along with him.  /RGod Bless Love Debbie & Denny]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Debbie Nero Anderson Happy Birthday]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember going to texas when i was little with my mom and dad to visit Aunt Helen we had such a great time. I also remember family reunions. Aunt Helen always has a smile on her face its always a fun gteat time being wirh her. Happy Birthday Aunt Helen God Bless ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michelle Laigle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memory of you was coming over Sunday afternoons and you cooking a buffet of different foods until I would eat and eat and eat! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Angela Finn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I admire most about Maw Maw is her gentle soul. She is the kindest most loving person. From my heart to hers...I love you!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bonnie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are too many things that I admire about Mawmaw to mention but the most important of these would be that she never missed the opportunity to share the Good News of Jesus Christ and the scriptures. She is the angel in the family and we are blessed to have her.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Missy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Please wish Mammaw all the best for her 90th.   When we saw her, she is always smiling and in a great mood - a real inspiration to everyone.  /R/RPlease give her a big hug from the both of us.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hank & Sherry Reuser]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that she never lets me leave hungry! And always has ice cream!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Scott Black]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom,/RI just want to wish you a happy 90th birthday and to tell you how much you mean to me.  You have always been more like another Mother to me than just a Mother-in-law. I always admired your relationship with our Lord and your strength. Love you so much!!!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sharon Brittain]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Spending the night and waking up to a 5 course breakfast, brunch, and a massive lunch meticulously prepared.  Also, the fun Mammaw had at Rudi Lechner's.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nick Brittain]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I cannot thank you enough for all the kind things you have done for me. Everyday you set the best example of what a woman of God is with your selflessness & love. The appreciation our family has for you is unending,  I love you always!!! ??]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peyton ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Every moment spent with you is better than the time before.  It is impossible to think of just one time that is the best since every time is the best with you.  There is not a better person on this planet than you or ever will be.  Thank you for being you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eddie, Ivy, Jordan, Steven]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Gosh Mom....I have a lifetime of wonderful memories!  I've always said there is, never could be, anyone like you!  I thank God to have been blessed with you as my precious Mother.  Thank you for all your unconditional love and support!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With all my love, always...Linda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mammaw can cook anything and it always tastes amazing! She can make something delicious out of nothing. She also makes the best sweet tea in Texas. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Beth & Nathan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whether it's 3 in the afternoon or 3 in the morning, you always get the same kind and caring attention from Mammaw.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Beth & Nathan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mammaw always sets a great example as a mother, a grandmother, a friend and a Christian. We should all strive to be more like her. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Beth & Nathan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your are the only "MOM" I called Mrs. "B".  Since Feb. 1976 you have been the only mother I had, oh boy, some men are so lucky and I guess it was my turn.  Thank you MOM, for everything!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your favorite son-in-law]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Helen, thank you for being a true friend without guile. I laugh remembering us skiing at Lake Tahoe with GC and Susan. We fell on the bed tired and sore, saying we're not going again, but were first up and dressed next day! We had fun at the casino! I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Glenna Fox]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember one meal while visiting from NY; I had a plate full of your delicious food, but you said "you didn't eat my salad!?!" I said OH I am so full Mammaw, I'll take just a little. Next thing I know you MADE a salad for me! There wasn't one before! :) heh heh heh]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Brittain D'Andraia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mammaw you are the epitome of nurturing, a prayer warrior for all, a true matriarch, and the ultimate blessing to our family. You are a Mom to more than your own kids-- to your grandkids, too. I pray God continues to bless you in health & joy! I love you, Mammaw.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Brittain D'Andraia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom, thanks for loving, caring, giving and sharing! We made beautiful flowers, oil paintings, crocheted afghans together, and memories with our kids, Christmas, beach-Disney trips, scrabble, bulls/cleots! /RYour help & love! I cherish the times we shared! I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan Brittain]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you Mammaw for always being an inspiration by working so hard at taking such great care of us all that are around you by keeping our stomachs full and are hearts warm with your love. We love you so much and appreciate you always thinking of us. Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brittains of Miami]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mammaw, Your kind soul, loving nature and wonderful food have created memories I will never forget. I cherish every minute we spend with you when we are in Houston. Happy 90th Birthday, Love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tony ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I consider Maw Maw a living saint. She is one of the most giving people you will ever know and she always puts others ahead of herself. I would like to think that one of the many reasons she's so sweet is because of all the sweets we all bring her on Sunday's! Love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One memory I have of Mammaw and always admire is encouraging family to get together and spend time together. I remember the Brittain family always gathering on the weekends at Mammaw's. She always welcomed me with open and loving arms. Happy Birthday Mammaw!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sara Conner Jones]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mammaw, /RI love you and you are the greatest grandma that I have ever met or that I will ever meet.  I don't know what I would do without you, watching me all those days while my mom and dad were at work, giving me all the food I want for breakfast, lunch, and dinner./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Quinn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Mom/REveryone has a birth mom, but God TRULY blessed me by bringing you into my life.  You are my spiritual mother, and you are also my friend.  You and your family have become my family and it is more than I could have ever hoped for or dreamed of.  All my love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Selina]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom,/RYour the anchor that pulls this family together. Sundays are an example of that. Your love is always there and felt. Thank you for all you do and who you are. Love always...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Oh Aunt Helen when I think about you the memories are always such sweet ones. I remember your soft voice, your adorable laugh and how loving and kind you always were to me. Happy 90th Birthday Aunt Helen! I love you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Natalie Cardinale]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We remember coming to your house where you always had a smile, a hug and lots of food!  Full of love, warmth & hospitality!  We love you and your family!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vicki & Jimmy Jones (and girls!)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always remember your kindness and being so thoughtful of others. My love and God Bless you,  Sister Edith]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Edith Rispinto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember you washing my hair at your house when I was six or seven years old. The shampoo was yellow, looked like egg yolks. It had the most wonderful fragrance that I will never forget. You were so kind and gentle, like an angel. That day I claimed you for my own.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[My Undying Love, Jody Carol]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I cherish the memories of sleep overs at your house on Eastbrook. We'd get to pick out all our favorites at the store, watch Star Search, and you'd lay down with us in the back room to sleep, but we always woke up to you on the couch. Your presence gave us comfort.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I love you!!  - Rebecca Brittain]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mammaw, you're a 2nd mother to us, and we were blessed to have you live so close and do everything with our family. Field trips, pick us up from school, endless meals, vacations, take us shopping and for ice cream, giving us all your time even after working all night.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA["I love you more", Rebecca Brittain]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are an angel on earth and everything I aspire to be like. You've left impressions on everyone's lives that you've ever met with your genuine kindness, giving, nourishing, listening, praying, caring, healing, and comforting ways. You are the foundation of our family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[-Rebecca Brittain]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember the day you told me you were going to start working at Walmart. I was devastated and cried at the thought of not having you all to myself everyday. I loved spending time with you before I was old enough for school and remember the scent of your old blue car.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rebecca Brittain]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From the first time I ever sat down in Mamaw's kitchen I soon found out not only is she a great cook, but one of the most caring and lovable ladies I have ever met. Mamaw loves to do for others and that is when she is happiest. Mamaw's best achievement...her 4 children.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Perry Porter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mammaw you are such an excellent cook and what some don't know about your secret ingredient is that you pray over every bit of food that you serve WHILE you are cooking it, to the nourishment of our bodies in Jesus' name! And of course you don't let anyone go hungry! :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Brittain D'Andraia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mammaw I'll never forget the day you let me "practice" driving at dusk in your Ford. You screamed as you saw a snake on the road-- so George, Rebecca & I did too! You asked me to drive over it; I drove back and forth over what turned out to be a belt and oh we laughed!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Brittain D'Andraia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Words to describe Aunt Helen:/RKind, Gentle, Sweet, Loving, Caring, Patient, Godly, Great Cook, Hard Worker, and Giving, “Wonderful Hostess” Aunt Helen’s Favorite Slogan:  “God Forbid……” All these words spell LOVE!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Niece, Stephanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In my lifetime I have never met anyone as Spiritual, Saintly and such a Sweetheart as Helen. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love to you, Glenn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Oh what sweet childhood memories I have of spending Friday evenings at Aunt Helen and Uncle George's house!  So much laughter,parents talking,cousins playing. Precious Aunt Helen,you have the kindest, sweetest, most gentle heart. A blessing to us all!  Much love to you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cindy Brittain ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Aunt Helen/RFrom the moment I met Bill's Brittain family, I felt welcomed and loved by you all.  The affection and generosity of spirit that permeates your family is a sweet reflection of your unconditional love and devotion to all of us. HAPPY BIRTHDAY!!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[with love, Sue]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'll always remember your wonderful company and delicious food on Sundays after church. Thank you for making me feel like part of the family and stuffing me with genuine Italian home cooking! Happy birthday! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelly Sweetin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'll always remember Sundays at your house with the Brittain family, and getting to play with the big Lego town in the front room. It makes me feel loved when I see you because you're always full of enthusiasm and cheerful. Youre joyful spirit brightens everyone's day.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Walter Conner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are an everlasting bloom in a wonderful garden where only love and beauty grows!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love,  GC & Marie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a saint and your prayers saved me./R/RLove you.../RGreg]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Greg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To the Queen of the Brittains: my favorite memories of your wonderful home are filled with family and food. While riding bikes with my cousins we always stopped in for some love and a snack! Happy Birthday Mammaw! Love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elizabeth White Riggs]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mammaw, one of my favorite parts of childhood was packing my suitcase and spending the weekend with you.  We always had a lot of fun together, no matter what we did.  But, you were always the best part.  Your love and nurturing made every moment of childhood special.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[George]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember how you always liked Chick-fil-A so much, that almost every Saturday we would load up into the AMC Spirit and make a special trip to Pasadena Town Square. After filling up on chicken and waffle fries, we'd get a mint chocolate chip ice cream, and we were set.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[George]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always liked waking up at your house on the weekends, peaceful and quiet, with the smell of pancakes in the air.  I would sit down to eat some pancakes; but, 4 weren't enough: I had to eat 8.  Then, it turned out, the 8 pancakes were small, so I needed 4 more.  Etc.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[George]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite moments was when we all stayed up late on a stormy night and watched the Shining together.  You got so creeped out by the movie that you were screaming, but you could not stop watching because you wanted to know what happened next.  LOL]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[George]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember the wig that you kept on a styrofoam head in your closet.  When we were kids, we were always afraid to go into your closet because we thought that it was an actual spare head that you could switch out with yours.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[George]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mammaw, you always make The Best Food Anywhere.  It is actually hard to find a good meal elsewhere in the world because, by comparison, they never come close to your quality and perfection!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[George]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you, Mammaw!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[George]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mammaw you used to back out of the driveway and pull out onto Federal Rd in your AMC Spirit; you would peel out nearly each time, because you were anxious to get out of the cars way on Federal Rd. We laughed hard and you'd say, "Whaaaat?" and down play it! Heh heh heh]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Brittain D'Andraia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Spending the night at your house growing up made the best memories-peaceful early am on Eastbrook, you praying all night, your black bible out, trips to Debbie's beauty salon, grocery store & Diamond Shamrock trips, Golden Girls, skin so soft and so much LOVE]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Brittain D'Andraia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>