<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2382-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/23/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Martha Williams]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[14 Wesley Xing]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[St. Simons Is]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[GA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[31522]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Nathan!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Nathan Williams]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[I love you, Martha]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your amazing love for our communal beach days! And your delicious lima beans. But seriously, I love the fact that you let me come over to your house and be silly with Martha, and just shake your head and smile.  I love how much you love my children. Happy Birthday!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sara, i.e your female counterpart]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thing I like most about Nathan is his Strut!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Schlegel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your amazing sense of humor, you make any and every occasion more fun.  Additionally, you are a great brother and friend, who I love and admire dearly....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frances]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nathan is the right mix of serious and funny!  When I wanted to set fire to my ex-husband's truck in my front yard he offered to bring the marshmallows...and bail me out of jail!  They just don't get any better than you!  Wishing you a year of JOY, LOVE and LUCK!    HBD]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Diana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love the "Nathan smirk"(usually accompanied by a shoulder shrug/eyebrow raise)... and you've shared that trait with Hattie! You are a wonderful person and we LOVE spending our lives with you and your precious family. /RHappy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meg ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nathan was the only 13-14 year old that could run a John Deer Riding Lawn Mower  as fast it would go and in the dark holding a flashlight in his mouth and not hit a tree,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[jimw]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nathan, i hope i stay on your xmas Kringle list forever,love those Kringles,happy birthday,mike and jeannine patrick]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[mike patrick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Nathan is that he is a good guy that always worked genuinely hard to control his rage.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jason Sanker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday to one of the few attorneys I don't mind hanging out and drinking a beer with.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dusty Lewis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nathan is a compassionate bulldog. An oxymoron in itself, but a truly generous and compassionate person with a drive and fire for what he believes! One of my fav people!!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Audrey ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nathan, you are so the man I can only hope my daughters will be fortunate enough to marry. Happy Birthday!!! And...let's go fishing together. Lots of love to you. Thank you for loving Martha and being such an amazing father. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Louise Albritton ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[While there are many things that I could list that I like about Nathan, one that stands out to me is Nathan's fun loving, friendly personality.  Always easy to hang out with and always up for a good time.  Happy Birthday Nathan!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jamey Hornbuckle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In addition to your dashing good looks, one thing I like most about you is your loyalty and commitment to those to close to you.  Proud to be in the circle!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jason Clark]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love your sense of humor, and how you always make family vacations so special and entertaining. I love you so much./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Nathalie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nathan, I have a small photo of you and Bill Cox in my office.  Every time I see it I smile.  Those were good times at the PD office in Hinesville.  I still take a great deal of pride knowing I assisted you in your first domestic case.  Happy birthday my friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jean Bolin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're a pretty cool dude, no question 'bout it. Even though you're not a Texan, I still like you. Your epic coolness would climb if you moved your family to God's country (the land of trophy bucks), but I'm still one of your biggest fans.  Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Hinckley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love the way Nathan smiles when he looks at his girls. You can see how much he really loves them with that kind smile. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lynn Lewis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He is able to learn from mistakes, including his own, and let go of disappointments once they have been thoroughly analyzed./RHe is a loyal friend who stands up for his family and friends and community. He listens to other folks as much as he gives his own opinion. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Myra and John Wetzler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He takes us fishing and hunting. Which is cool.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jackson,Prestley& Harrison Wetzler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best thing about Nathan is how he shoots a shotgun. He makes me seem like an expert which is very kind of him. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matthew ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The one thing I like most about Nathan is his fun-loving, easy-going nature.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Robinson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I truly enjoy Nathan's mime performances on the pier.  Sometimes I really believe that he is stuck in that box.  /RSeriously, though, the thing I like most is that Nathan is a straight shooter. He calls them like he sees them.  And you can always take him at his word.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chuck Moulton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your Strut!  I work with my boys each night trying to emulate it.  Because I know if they can master that awesome gait, they’ll be prepared for success!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Douglas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Nathan is that he always supportive of those around him.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jarrett Bridges]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A great thing about Nathan Williams is that he invests in Eli Herndon in numerous ways.  Than you for that.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jarrett Bridges]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nathan, your thoughtfulness and genuine spirit are two of the many qualities you possess that come to mind. Your drive to not accept things at face value and to go deeper in pursuit of truth is inspiring. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Thea Ramirez]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nathan is a forthright and honest guy who is not afraid to fight the good fight.  Not enough lawyers like that left in the world.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Atkins]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like that Nathan really respects women in business and treats them as equals. He is a straight-shooter with a wicked sense of humor. He is a champion for the underdog and is always gracious. It is such a blessing to know him!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ashley Hornbuckle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He was such a cutie as a little boy and has grown into a handsome "young" man, with a wonderful smile, true compassion for others, and a family man at heart.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gloria Griffin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing that I like most about you, Nathan, is that you are the brother that I always wished for. Thank you for your kindness, loyalty, generosity, love, protection, and for poking fun of me like every brother must do. You really are the best. Happy Birthday!Love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate Hinckley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are one of the coolest guys I know; I love your laid back style! I hope you have a Happy Birthday and catch lots of fish in that pretty new boat of yours!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Crystal Ferrier]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The thing we like most about Nathan is his total unpretentious nature!  What you see is what you get with this man.....and we love him!  Happy Birthday!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ginny and Jay Burns]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nathan is a determined and unique individual who maintains a steady boat in troubled waters. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Cook]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Personally, I can't even see past the moment I walked in our cabin in Peru to see you standing with your "back" to me after your towel seemed to have "fallen off".  It's as if time has stood still since then...  Birthdays = birthday suit memories!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heard]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Natey, there are SO many things I love about you...but if I had to pick just one it would be the unique combination of being the manliest man I know while also having the most thoughtful and loving heart. I love the way you love my sister and your precious girls. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Saree]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Just one? /RThe pursed lip head nod is most definitely in the top three. /RYour kind heart and generosity are so evident in the way you love my children (and me & D). And your willingness to help people and stand up for what is right is inspiring!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Whitney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He's a good cook and he takes me fishing and hunting. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[His courage in taking a chance on an inexperience young lawyer, and the patience to not fire him after one year. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hope you have the happiest birthday! We love you and your family and are so thankful to have you in our lives! Thank you for letting us be a part of it. All our love! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Zaks]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The thing I love the most about Nathan is his great sense of humor, always brings laughter to every event.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larry Dyal ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[How, when I am in tough legal pickle that I cannot figure out the answer to, you will take my call or email (during what I know is a busy day) and walk me through the issue. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paul]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nathan is one of the most honest people I know.  He stands up for what he believes in and the people he cares about.  Most importantly - he is the kind of friend that makes you a better person./RProverbs 27:17]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Herndon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So blessed to know you and your precious family through Wesley.  I will never forget how instrumental you were in helping us during the most challenging time in our  lives.   Ya'll add so much spirit and spunk here, and we so grateful to call you friend.  God Bless!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paige & Scott Gober]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The smartest guy I know.  A loyal friend that will offer a hand when you are in way over your head and then thank you for the opportunity.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wrix McIlvaine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Loyal through and through... /Rthat's what I think when I /Rthink of you, Nate-dog!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Helen Rentz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Friend and a great lawyer!  /RHappy Birthday Nathan!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff Ward]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the things I like most about Nathan is that no matter where I am or what I'm doing...Nathan will stop to say hi and ask how I am.  Nathan is genuine and we always have a laugh when we talk.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marty ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nathan- You are a great husband, a great father and a great friend!  I appreciate and value our friendship.  Happy Happy Happy Birthday!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alan Welch]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that Nathan never minded saying "I love you " no matter who was listening. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Your excitement over our "project" was inspiring. I thoroughly enjoyed your sense of humor and sincerity!!!  And I won't forget your advice on Halloween candy either!!                                              Happy Birthday!!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It has been a blessing getting to know you and your family at Wesley.  You are always in our prayers and we look forward to many more years of friendship with you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Searles Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing that I like about Nathan Williams is that he is a good dad.  I also appreciate that he likes hunting and trucks.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sam Norris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your ability to see the forest through the trees.  You're an all around genuine person and the best boss EVER!!  Not to mention you're a phenomenal zoo keeper too! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Catie Newton ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the many things I like about you is the love you have and show for your sweet girls and their mommy! ...and when you are a diva it makes me chuckle!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brandi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He is a man of great integrity-not just in his professional career but also as a husband and father.  He truly shines the light of Christ in his daily life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Limburg ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that you are brave. You are the best daddy ever. I love you daddy./R/RI like that you protect me from bears and bad guys and goo monsters. I like that you laugh. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sally & Hattie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ To a friend who is always quick with a smile and is one of the most genuine people I know.  Have a wonderful day.  Happy Birthday.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Glenn Jones]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love it when people assume we are related because, come on, we would all love for Nathan to be our crazy cousin!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Misty Leigh (Williams)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love your desire to see justice be done, even if it means dealing with tough clients or spending your weekend reviewing documents or researching. You appreciate that justice often comes at a cost, and as long as it isn't hurting your family,  you're willing to pay it.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Martha]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nathan is a great personal injury attorney.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Melissa Cruthirds]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A guy who is awesome all the time? Nathan!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Busby Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love the way you love my daughter, and the way you love my granddaughters. I also love the twinkle in your eyes. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sally Wilson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Where do I start? I love this man. My first son. The one who adores my sweet Moppy. I love him. His sense of honor, the way he loves my granddaughters, the way he provides for his family, the rock he is for all of us. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Wilson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best. And we love the same restaurants. And even though I don't really like to hunt or fish, I love to go with him. Too much fun. Always there for us. Happy birthday Nath. I love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Wilson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>