<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2385-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/24/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Laura James]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[528 S. Primrose St.]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Monrovia]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[CA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[91016]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy First Father's Day!!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Caston]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love, Carter Stone and Mommy]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No words can begin to express how much I love and treasure you, not only as my partner but as Carter Stone's father.  I never truly appreciated what that word meant until you.  To a million more Father's Days celebrating how amazing you are./R/RI love you forever!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[On this your first "official" Father's Day we wanted to show you how amazing you are and how much you being the father that you are means not only to us but our extended family too.  /R/RWe love you beyond words!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carter Stone and Mommy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ I have personally witnessed the love and care that Caston exhibits when handling his son. His patience and willingness to sacrifice his busy schedule and time to ensure that his son comes first is rare and makes Carter the luckiest little boy in the world. Good job!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rick ( Grandpa )]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're a great dad by making your day available to witness this blessing we call Carter Stone. You are hands on and this he will remember when he's a man. You also keep like minded individuals around him, so he has no choice but to be Amazing and successful. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenai Benson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The one thing that makes Caston a great father is that he is present everyday in Carter’s life.  The bond that he is creating with his son is the foundation to an amazing father/son relationship for decades to come.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christina Booker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Caston you are a GREAT father because you know how to BBQ.  That is a lost art my love and you know Carter Stone and I love to EAT!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My friend, The Gentle Giant, /Ron 4/13/15 u posted on Insta…/R"Sleeping with Dad. These little moments R what keeps me going. Soon he's gonna B too big 4 this so I’m going to get as many of these as I can"/RThat moment of vulnerability creates bonds unbroken, Ur that DAD!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Fathers Day<3 Lyn Lane]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Caston, you always offer me advice worth listening to...and for sure, No holds Barred! #carterstone your in great hands]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Destinee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are an amazing father because you love those around you without conditions.  Carter Stone will always know that his father loves and supports him no matter what.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[His mindset that he must succeed by any means necessary. Cas has tought me many things and he's one of the most knowledgeable guys I know.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chaz Logan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a great Dad, you give your son mega love, hugs and kisses.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Moms]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You make Carter laugh!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Moms]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You’re an awesome Father cuz you go shopping and buy your son clothes and shoes.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Moms]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Caston, I want you to know how proud of you I am. You got it right the first time. The love and patience you show my grandson is a blessing. You put Carter first on everything you do. As Carter grow he will return the love you give him. Happy Fathers Day.../RGrandpa]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[James Grigsby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Caston, the love and support you show for Carter is amazing. Its wonderful to see a father so hands on in his child's life. I hope your first father's day is a special and fulfilling day that you will cherish forever. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bari]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Compassion.  I have talked with you on several occasions about life situations.  You have a perspective on things that is very similar to a "voice of reason".  You have kept me from axing people out because of your compassion.   I love you, Brother.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cobi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best father because you will beat your head against ever wall to provide the best for our family. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dada - u r the best because you make me laugh all day and we watch sports and "triple D" together. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carter Stone]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're a great dad because you will always be there for Carter and you will never let him down.  You love him unconditionally and there's nothing more important to a man than his father's unconditional love.  Happy Father's Day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bianca]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're a great father because Carter can count on you in the clutch. If he takes off his diaper just because he knows how, you put it back on for him. If he plays with his food, you provide structure for him. Keep it up and Carter will be a way better man than us both! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Brother, Beau]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When it comes to rules. There are none .The Man who makes his own, never to be put into a box. Great quality to pass on to young carterstone. Keep up the fine example.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lehnman Johnson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The one thing that makes you a great father is that you are present every day in Carter’s life. The bond that you are creating with your son is the foundation to an amazing lifelong father/son relationship.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christina Booker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are an unbelieveable father because you are willing and able to work in the studio until 3 am and still wake up at 8 to take care of Carter Stone.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Caston,/RA great man and father once told me that fatherhood requires four things: investment, discipline, charity, and fortitude. In your short time as a father, you have come to epitomize each of these properties. Keep doing what you are doing. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marcus Casey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What makes you an amazing father is your love, patience, understanding and daily commitment to Carter Stone. You love that little guy to infinity and beyond and it shows in how he interacts with others. Keep up the great work pops! Love ya xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shani]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Caston... you're a great father to Carter because..Ur smart,you have a loving & forgiving heart, Ur loaded w/ patience, you'll lead by example, you'll teach him to respect his mother & women & the bond you've developed will never be broken. I'm so very proud of you...Xo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Caston....It brings my heart JOY to see you as a Father, such a Loving, Caring, Hands On Dad. Go You Amazing DAD! /RHappy 1st Fathers Day]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love You, Aunt D]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cas, you are a great father because you display the patience and commitment necessary to properly shape and nurture a young body and mind.  It's been a pleasure to see you embrace the role of a father.  Happy 1st Father's Day my brother, enjoy!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cuzzo Jai]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What makes you such an awesome father is the love, dedication, patience, and time given to my handsome god son. This positive influence will surely mold Carter into a great person. /RCheers to you sir! /RHappy Father's Day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joanna Borbon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing that makes Caston a great dad is that he understands  the importance  of putting  in that quality time with Carter.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Auntie Arlene ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The thing that makes you a great father is the endless ability to sacrifice. To see you put up and give away whatever it takes to secure the ones you put before your own desires is leagues above honorable. Truly, you are a role model.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Spex.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your enthusiasm for parenting and supporting Carter Stone is truly contagious! Wishing you many more years as his provider, mentor, friend, confidant and father.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Auntie Gail and Gabie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best father because you protect me from the scary things. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[CSG]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are my favorite tickle monster!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You don't get mad at me when I kick you in my sleep /R(just mommy, lol)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carter Stone]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a fantastic father because make our son feel safe and loved.  He know that his father will always protect him to the best of his ability. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a fly father because you keep the young king in fly clothes and shoes. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[LJ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best father because you love and support our family with all of you.  We could not ask for a better father. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are great because you are trying to make the world I will grow up in a better place. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[CSG]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are great because you are trying to make the world I will grow up in a better place. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[CSG]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing that makes Caston a great father is the fact that he treasures the blessing of fatherhood. That in turn is feeding all of his actions as a father. He loves and appreciates the blessing so he takes it all on with love and dedication. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ryan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are great because you are trying to make the world I will grow up in a better place. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[CSG]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love and consistency!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Selflessness. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[LJ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best because you keep (or at least try to ) keep mommy sane. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[CSG]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best because you keep (or at least try to ) keep mommy sane. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[CSG]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Unconditional love is one of the greatest gifts a father can give a child, and Caston gives Carter that gift daily. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jaime B. ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cas makes a good father because he's one of my best friends in life sooooooo I'm 99.9999987% such that translates into being the best father in life. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jubal]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[On Father's Day and every day know that you are loved and appreciated for all that you do.  With all of our love!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Our entire extended family!!!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>