<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2395-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/26/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Joanna Patterson]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[1741 forest cove trail]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Allegan]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[MI]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[49010]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sand]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Cheryl's Memory Box]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Cheryl Patterson]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Happy 60th Birthday!]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember being out on the boat with Tom and Cheryl. She said she'd give me a hair cut. I said, "Ok, just a trim. I mean really trim"! She interpreted that as...she wants a lot off. Lol. It took awhile but it finally grew back! :) haha]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lisa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can't really limit this to one occasion, because Aunt Cheryl has been there for me for so many years, in so many different places, and in so many varied capacities-- although one thing has remained constant: she's always looked out for me like a parent. Happy 60th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Visser]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cheryl has always been like a mom to us,she is a great secretary and has been able to help our family with questions about life situations and also with work./RShe's always been there for are family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Beemans]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ever since I was little, AC & I have joked about her being my "real mom", but the love, care & support she gives me is no joke. We've made unforgettable memories; countless sleepovers, Big Star, teaching me to ski, helping with my wedding & more! Cheers to AC, love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tara Kolkema]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The first time I ever drank was with Aunt Cheryl (go figure) on my first ever trip to MI. Derek and I had dinner at her house and she gave us wine and an amazing pear and chocolate dessert! I also remember painting her toes for her then. Such a fun first MI experience!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amy Schaap ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cher, you are my rock! You've been with me through my most joyful and darkest moments. There's never been a time when I couldn't count on you. We have laughed, cried, played (oh boy, have we played!) and shared our deepest thoughts. I love you my sister and my friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cheryl, you are a crazy girl! From the first time I met you I knew you were trouble. I could not have asked for a more perfect sis-in-law. We've created some awesome memories in a short time and I look forward to more "60's" memories. Love you and happy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[That time when I stayed at Aunt Cheryl's house in Grand Rapids for a week. We watched A Walk to Remember and My Best Friends Wedding - Aunt Cheryl cried.... A lot....  And then cried some more.  She made me a camo dress and I taught her how to do a messy bun. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alicia Barnhart ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Oh where to begin?? From sliding on cardboard in the snow at Ryans Woods, to opening your home for our wedding, you mean so much to us.  But we can't forget that you're my shower buddy!! Happy Birthday Cher and a blessed year to come.  Love and miss you..]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike and Connie Zych]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Every moment I spend with you is the best moment ever!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, your favorite brother Mike]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our ski trip to Tahoe, you were my sister in law but that trip you became my sister and friend.  Loves to you sis and Happy Birthday! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cindy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nana, why is your skin so wiggle-y?  I love playing kitchen and restaurant with you.  Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Landon ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From karaoke and Bada Bing in St. Marten to St. Patrick's Day in Saratoga, love making memories and look forward to many more.  Happy Sassy 60! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shannon & John ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Nana! Look forward to you accessorizing me for a long time to come.  Xoxox]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cathryn ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I' ve felt since 6 months after we met that if I died tomorrow I have had more love and wonderful moments than most people will have in a lifetime ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your loving husband Tom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Words can't express our gratitude for all you do for all of us and how lucky we are to have you in our lives.  Looking forward to many more memories!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John, Shannon, Landon, Cathryn ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nana, I love you so very much. /RI love our special shopping trips and swimming with you in Florida.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Booboo (Lexi)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nana, I love going on walks and riding bikes with you in Florida. I love you so much!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bambam (Jake)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will always remember karaoke and fireworks at Big Star Lake, relaxing in the Bahamas, and our great talks! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[On June 22, 1955, God blessed us with a precious, beautiful daughter who we named Cheryl Ann Schaap. She was the start of our special family!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom and Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hmmm where do I start. A 10 foot snow storm in Tahoe, the catwalk back from Beaver Creek to Bachelor gulch in a freaking blizzard. Sitting on buckets during our first flip on Church rd being told what to do by our foreman(dad). The bar crawl in the badlands of PG!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Thomas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The whiteout driving back from Tahoe. Our palace of a room behind the hotel in Reno! Pretty sure you and Jo were very scared that night. Nothing better than catching the first chair at B Gulch and being the first ones on the mtn.  The Griswalds do Napa!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Thomas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will never forget all the 4th of July's we spent at the cottage complete with matching flag tanks from old navy ???? or shopping trips to SAMs club.. I've never seen a cart so full or so many crumpled up dollar bills on the bottom of one's purse lol...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brittany Garvelink]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for all the great memories Aunt Cheryl and a special thanks for helping out with our wedding. Love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ryan and Brittany Garvelink]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite moments with AC was spending the whole day at her house cooking, making jewelry and jamming out to "Good is Good" by Sheryl Crowe!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelsi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always enjoy my time with you. It doesn't matter what we do it is always fun.  Making jewelry, shopping Lia Sophia, trying on Cabi, shopping antique stores, boating, cooking Mexican food, partying with the cousins, the Forks, you name it!  You are the best!  Happy 60!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Carol]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Fun times with your favorite nephew: spontaneous ski trips to Bittersweet while my folks were out of town, the many fun boating trips in Saugatuck, and lots of great family get-togethers! Happy Birthday AC! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Derek Schaap]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[While visiting with Cheryl and Tom in Punta Gorda one year, we were taken on a glorious boat ride in Charlotte Bay where we stopped for lunch at Cabbage Key and on the way back, Cheryl took us shelling at her favorite secret island.  I still have shells from that trip.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gloria Rising]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/RI well remember when my wife and I visited Tom, Cheryl and  Cheryl's family and friend at their beautiful home in Michigan. I especially remember her hospitality, her father and his humor and my kayak adventure on their lake (don't worry I'll get you a new fishing rod)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Don Rising]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A good friend and great business colleague. A major gasoline contributor to a senior spring break. The mystery person who got the boat on the trailer and the only person that can get 20 pipefitters to sit thru a 2 hour insurance meeting. Happy 60...many more to come!!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bruce]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Making me get the flowers]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The favorite]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Being the boss picking the little bushes at VanLente's/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The favorite]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Riding the horse]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The favorite]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for being my big sister /R         Love ,Mark]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The favorite]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My freshman year of college I lived part time with AC. I remember lots of ramen noodles and fun times! She made me feel like that was my home too. /RLove you Aunt Cheryl!! /R/RHappy Birthday!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jodi Carpenter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nana, I love Thanksgivings in Florida and seeing Santa.  I also love putting makeup on with you and wearing your jewelry./RI love you so much!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Emma]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nana, I love playing on the water slide with you in Michigan.  I also loved seeing the fire trucks in Florida. I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Noah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I don't know if there is a specific memory that stands out, because with Cheryl, you're guaranteed some sort of craziness:) Thank you for your love and support, no matter what. Happy birthday AC!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Adam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aunt Cher, my most fond memories of you involve learning to embrace my sassy/girly side :) From eating ice cream and watching the Sweetest Thing to shopping and building necklaces to match my prom dress, you have always been so much fun! Happy birthday! Love you!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Morgan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will never forget my very first trip to Michigan.  Thank you for welcoming me into your family from day 1.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>