<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2407-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/26/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Samir Modi]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[660 Washington street]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[Apt 19 E]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Boston]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[MA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[02111]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDEX_PRIORITYOVERNIGHT]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_200]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Sweetheart!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Vedika]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Sweet Sixteen Darling Vedu!!????/RYou have grown into a gorgeous young lady and am soo proud of you ... From a baby to holding your own ... Wow!!! Wish you the most of the mostest and best of the bestest./RGrown up and all but for me always the baby of the fam?????]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charoo masi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Vedu your are very soft spoken, lively and shy girl...I have never seen you loosing your temper ...you are always smiling and very mature than your age.. God bless you and give you whatever you have been longing for..with lots of love..:)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anil ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like about Vedu is her steadfast and determined love of Marshmallow Fluff. If it's in the vicinity she'll find it and consume it. Killer instinct to succeed. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sindhu]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I know that we don't get to have a heart to heart baby and somehow life just carried on. There are many things about me that you don't like and many things that hurt you and hurt you. I am sorry for all of them. I love you and you are my world. Without you I will die.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There is so much I want to say to you and there are so many things that I would like to do with you baby. I hope that we are able to do all those and more together. You have grown up to become a beautiful young lady and I know that you will touch the stars.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Warmth, love, care, joy, laughter, wit, Instagram, Facebook, beauty, amazing ideas, beautifully stunning art, style, inner strength and smile are things that you truly possess. These are qualities in you that bring meaning into my life and lives of others.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Vedu, our littlest beauty has grown up to be a talented young lady. Vedu is most caring and loving. Her art is just awesome and she has become a star. God bless you and may you have a wonderful year ahead. May all your dreams come true. Loads of love]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ritika and Alok]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Vedu! /R/RHappy sweet 16!! /R/RLOVE THE NEW VEDU! CONFIDENT, QUIET BUT FULL OF LIFE!! SENSITIVE AND LOVING AND WITH A SPARKLE IN HER EYES!! /R/RLove you baby! /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ASHIM FOO!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Adorable, affectionate and a sweetie pie.. Wishing her lots of love on her Sweet 16th! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shiamali chachi aditya chachu Dhruv]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Vedu, /RWishing you a very happy 16th year ahead. Your our little star !!! You are an amazing child and we are so blessed to have you in our lives. Vedu, I remember when you were born feels like yesterday. God bless, love you may all your dreams come true.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ritika and Alok]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Vedu makes me laugh!!???? she has become a bigger mad hatter than I expected !! God bless Her always..my dear Vedu may you savour the joy of life to the fullest and create much value in helping others become happy with your crazyiness and otherwise! Love yu my baby ????????????????????]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Abha masi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[VEDZ you are one of the spunkiest and most hilarious people I know and it's been dope getting to know you- from delhi to singapore scenez I always have the best time with you and I am excited to make some more memories with ya in the years to come :)))]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sehyr]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Vedika! I loved having art with you, you are so amazing at it and I love having you to make me laugh during class! I hope we are in the same class nex year again ???? have a lovely birthday you amazing gal xxx]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[sieun ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My lovely Vedz, I'm hoping that you're being treated like a princess on your very special day #sweet16. I'm so glad to have met an amazing girl like you. One thing I like about you is that you don't give up no matter what. Keep being amazing Vedz, love you loads xx]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelly Mullally]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[i remember that one time we were hanging out with Karam and Daniyal at HV. Looking forward to more fun times bud :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Afnan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can still remember your first day in school as if it was just yesterday. All the nights we used to play underwater, you hugging me tightly and putting you to sleep by singing bum chikka chikka bum for you. See how time has passed us so quickly. Today as you turn 16]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I want you to know that I love you with all my heart and no matter where you are, you will have our memories in your heart. We're together though we're apart. Never forget that baby that i will always be with you besides you just like you will always be with me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY VEDIKA!!!/RGrade 8,9,10 was really fun being in the same class as you. I really hope we share another class in g11! Have a great birthday and holiday with your family and friends!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nana Ishibe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My dearest, dearest Vedu,/ROur relationship has had its share of ups and downs, but the best part is that hugs always follow frowns. I know that sometimes I get angry, at times nag you & be grumpy but among all that I want you to know is that I love you & always will.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing that I like most about you is that you're always so cheerful and really funny. Its been great to get to know you for the last 3 years! Hope your exams were good :) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Arnav Patodia ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 16th Bday Vedu! I'm sure all your 15 years have been great but hope from this  year life brings you extra special things. /RLittle Vedu has grown up so fast.Wishing you wings to fly high & reach for all your dreams.Have an amazing year.Love, happiness,good fortune]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jojo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Vedika Modika, happy birthday my love! Hope you have a brilliant one, miss you very much, you crazy coot. Just wanna say you're a madly talented and beautiful lil thing and I hope we spend enough time together this summer - it's long overdue!! Lotsa love n hugs n kisses]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kaamya ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Vedu, you grew up too fast! Here's wishing my favorite niece a very very sweet sixteen, and a long and prosperous life. I hope your journeys bring you to New York more often. Lots of love, kochi chacha and family]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Arjun]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing that I like most about Vedika is her devotion and amusement. She always puts her best to whatever she is doing and always with a smile or laughter. Happy Birthday Vedika, I hope you have an insane 16th. You truly deserve it! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nikhil Sahgal ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I've known you for the past 10 years, & through every moment in those 10 years, I've always known I can count on you for anything, whether you were in Singapore or Delhi. So thank you for being such an amazing friend and I hope you have a great birthday! You deserve it!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mehr]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Vedu - darling one - whenever I see you - I see a glowing smile. Your laugh is inflicting and your being so warm that you just melt anything around you. So happy to be part of our lives. Wishing you - a life full of just smiling, laughing and warm people around u love u]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lalit Modi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Vedika ...        Knock knock ...I am here ! Sweet 16 for a beautiful creative light that you are ../RWishing you a very birthday ! /RCelestial blessing shower on you . We love and adore you ../R/RLove u /RMinal]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Minal Modi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Vedu, seems like you were just six yesterday! And today you have blossomed into a beautiful young lady, an artist, a blogger, a writer, an original thinker -wow! -so many talents! I wish you a lifetime of learning, love, health and good friends./RLove you lots]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bullu Amma]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Vedu, /RWishing you the most wonderful and Happy 16th birthday. You are so special to all of us./RI remember the memorable holiday we had in Disney. Now you have grown into this beautiful young lady. Beautiful inside and outside. Love you. Hugs and kisses Lali Bua]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lali Singhania]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Vedu, it is a delight to see you grow in to what you are today. Your most innocent smile combined with your shy and humble persona makes you so adorable :-) Happy sixteenth and keep smiling, always... God bless!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aneesha]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Vedu from being the shy,quiet little baby of the family you have grown into a confident , mature young woman! Can't believe ure turning 16!!! God bless u always sweety! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sirat mami ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing we like most about Vedika is that she is so compassionate./R/RShe won our heart, when one summer she wanted to visit us rather than going with her friends and we loved having her around us./R/RWe wish all the very best for this cute fun loving girl of ours./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[VK & Alka Gupta (Nana & Nani) USA]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy happy birthday my darling! One thing I like most about you is your spirit and creativity ! You are such a wonderful light to have around and you are so beautifully talented! Love you lots ! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aliya ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[...Vedika is her caring personality and her excitement for many things! You light up the room when you smile, so don't stop! Happy Sweet 16 Vedu!! I wish you all the best this coming year and hope to see you very soon! Enjoy your celebrations. Miss you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ashima Masi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Vedu your smile and charm is infectious ..I still can't believe you're already 16 !! Here's wishing you the most marvellous 16th Birthday Vedu Baby !!! And here's to many many more Happy times ahead darling !! Lots and lots of Love and A Massive Big Birthday Hug ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paro Masi ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Didi , happy 16 th birthday . You are very nice . Lots of love ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ADITYA MUKARJI ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Vedu , happy 16 our darling . Love your infectious smile, warmth and loving personality . Stay blessed and happy always. May you glow more n more with each day. Tons of love n hugs ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anu Bua and Deepak uncle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[VEDS words can't even describe how much I love you, you make my worst lessons with Gary ten times better and you make my day a whole lot more exciting. I'm more than thrilled to have gotten to know you better these past 2 years and I honestly can't wait for IB with you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alicia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Vedu what I admire most is the artist in you and your wonderful sense of purpose of wanting to give back.  You are articulate, fun and adventurous besides being loving and kind.  I love you lots.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charu Bua]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Veds, happy sweet 16! Thank you for being my constant source of "honesty" in the boarding house, don't know what I would have done without you. Hope you have an amazing day, love you lots.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Yosha ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Vedz! Thank you for always being there, for being supportive when I'm unsure, calm when I'm upset, and a constant. I don't know where I'd be without you to confide in, gossip with, laugh with, cry with. I love you so so much. Have the best day!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kaavya]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My Dearest Princess /RWish you a very happy 16th!! /RYou guys are all growing up too fast yaar. I love you Vedu and miss you in Delhi a lot but I am so happy that you have become such an independent individual. Have a great year baba. Love you always xoxoxoxoxoxoxoxoxoxxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pranav Bhaiya ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing that I like most about Vedika is how much fun she always is to be around, there isn't a single moment when she can't make me laugh and almost be in tears. Love you loads vedu x]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anoma]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing that I like most about Vedika is that she is SO caring and is ALWAYS there to love, console and support her friends. You are a wonderful friend veds and I am so glad to have you. For your sweet 16th, laugh, play, party, eat your heart out! ENJOY <3]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lots of love, Shennie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I love about Vedu is her steadfast and determined love of Marshmallow Fluff. If it's in the vicinity she'll find it and consume it. Killer instinct to succeed.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sindhu]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing that I love most about Vedu jiji is that she gets me sweets whenever I want.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wooj]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing that I love about Vedu jiji is how sweet and funny she is. She is also the BEST person to shop with because she gives you really good advice. (No offence to Jayati jiji).]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chhoti (Uma)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Ved! I hope you have the best day and get treated like a princess because you deserve it! We've had our ups and downs (grade 8 Yakult incident :P) but at the end of the day you're always there for me and I'll always be here for you gal. I love you so much]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[enjoy your special day! -Annabel XX]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Vedz!!! You're 16 now (but don't look a day over 12;)). I like that you are very good at being mean about other people together with me. Don't do anything stupid this summer! Or at least nothing that I wouldn't do... ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bev ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Veduu! Happy birthday my lovely! You've always been such an amazing friend to me and have been by my side through so much. Thank you for everything vedu! You're such a sweet, caring, hilarious lil poop. I love you so much and hope you have the best birthday ever! xx]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pikuuu]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Vedika, /RWishing you a very happy 16th birthday!!! It's a BIG milestone!! I hope the world is ready for all your craziness to come! /RLots of love]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shreya]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am very happy to be one of the lucky few people you call friends. You have your entire life ahead of you and I am so sure it will be amazing for you and the people close to you! Happy birthday Vedika, live every day to the fullest!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nik]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If there is someone I know that is going to make the world a better place to live in, it will be YOU! Your maturity, sensitivity, and sense of humor surprise be daily! You will forever be my baby sister/fellow cool hunter/cuddle buddy..LOVE YOU X]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[P Diddy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey Vedu,/RHappy Birthday!! :)) Once I leave we are probably gonna meet even less (idk if thats possible) but I'm always gonna be there if you ever need me. I've been practicing counting stars btw! (become a lil better) We'll do it again soon. Have a sexy year!! Love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Armaan Grewal]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 16th Vedu! I wish you are always blessed with lots of happiness. Keep smiling like you always do. Lots of love]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Reet mami ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love you so much vedu! So nice to see you grow up so much. Many amazing things ahead of you. Hugs and kisses!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amish mama]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My Dearest Vedu,/RHappy happy birthday! You have grown to be a beautiful lady in mind and in soul. I am so proud of you and the person you have become. You are loving and kind, compassionate and generous. Always stay the same. I love you so so much ?? Happy 16th my love ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Avanti ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Vedu! I miss seeing you around the boarding house, but I hope you're still having a great time in Singapore. One thing I like most about you was how pink and cute you used to be ;) Hope I see you soon. HAPPY HAPPY BIRTHDAY!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Diya]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The world does not what is going to going to hit them... Vedika Modi, a beautiful young woman who is about to take the world by storm and break many a hearts on the way. Chacha and I are proud bystanders in your journey applauding you every step of the way. Love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chacha-Masi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cute, shy and adorable while at the same time a glint of mischievousness in your eyes! Wish you a sweet 16 with lots and lots of love!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sid & Swanti]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 16th Birthday Vedika! I hope you have a fantastic day and year ahead. I can't express how happy I am to have gotten to known you after I joined the boarding house so thank you for being there. Good luck for the next 2 years! Stay in touch. Love you and miss you <3]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Raunak]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Veduu! Happy birthday baby! One thing that I like most about you is your capability to make anyone laugh and how absolutely crazy you are. Here's to you turning into an amazing and confident person from an awkward little kid. Love you hubby! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Udita]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Veds,/RHAPPY BIRTHDAY!/RYou are finally a 16 year old and one step closer to being more mature, wise, rational... just kidding don't worry you're already at that stage. I've loved getting to know you this year and we better stay in touch while I'm in college!/Rxoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ayla ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Vedu!! Happy Birthday! Thank you for always having my back and for sticking with me in Mike's class, I honestly don't know what I would do without u. I'm really glad I offered you that cookie on the plane from tabitha (LOL) Love u so frkn much, have the best day!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Beth ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Vedika!??have an amazing one and hopefully we see each other soon when I visit Singapore or India :) can't wait to see you in a white shirt and go through all the things I went through! Happy birthday beautiful and keep in touch !! Xx]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sally ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[happy birthday veduuu!!/Rhope you have a fab 16 with ton of cake n food! its been a great 2 years of sum gary bant but i'm going to miss having science with ya :(( hopefully we have classes together next year. see you soon gal ilysmxx]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[salmon (sam smith)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To the giggliest bundle of love and energy,/R/RHappy 16th my chotu! As clichéd as it may sound, I can’t believe you’re so old! In my head you’re always going to be 6, or maybeee 7 (if I really try hard to come terms with reality).]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shri Dii]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The amount of silly things we have done together is unreal BUT the most surreal part of it is that somehow with time, our ideas have gotten madder and actions more insane. Remember the time we teased you with Iman?! (or however you spell that poor little boy’s name).]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shri Di (Part 2..bear with me)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From your ‘You’re a FUNNY BUNNY’ phase to the times you sat and ate 46 ka cold masoor ka dal chawal; to say that you’ve been my life- is a sheer understatement. Even now, you amaze me by all the little things you do, Vedli. Your passion is contagious! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Almost there...(Still Shriya)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Only you can make me admire and acknowledge the true work and beauty of an art work! Your chic style, obsession with white and weird ass music- all make me understand that, even though you’re absolutely crazy you have the biggest heart and the most caring nature.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Last one left (I promise)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Yes, Isha and you have stared and laughed at me, every time I have fallen while dancing but even then I love every photobooth. I can go on forever but instead, I’ll say that you are one of a kind never ever change.I know that nobody is perfect, but you're pretty close!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you forever Jaan, Love- Shriya]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sweetest precious little one...wishing you a very happy 16th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aditee & Manish]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Vedika I love how every time you enter a room you brighten it up with your incredible smile. I wish you a very happy sweet 16th! Party hard and have fun on this special birthday. Sending you much love.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ruchir ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how you're super weird (even if you don't like to admit it) because it means that I can be myself around you & we can be weird together so I really love that. You're the funniest person -sometimes gross even (mr pimple popper wth)- but that's what makes you great]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shirley Cahyadi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my bestest friend, you are so close to me I think of you as a sister and thank you for being there always, I literally don't know what I would do without you! you make it easy for me to trust you with anything, you're always there and thank u ilysm x]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ Laasya ??]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey happy birthday loser<3 i hope you hade a great day and year ahead ( well you obvio will im coming ) thank you for helping me with everything and always giving me advice and stuff! /RLove youu loads ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rhea grewal]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[For the past 13 years that I have known you, you've been the constant source of happiness in my life. I know when something goes wrong you'll always be there to re assure me that everything will be fine. love you, have the best 16th ever. Here's to more years together!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nimran]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey vedu, /R/RWish you a very happy birthday. Hope you have a great one. Love you little sister ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Devansh Jain ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Vedu, /RI had written an entire essay but this thing doesn't allow that :( So I guess all that I have to say is happy happy haaaaappy sixteenth birthday you caring, amazing & talented girl! I hope you have the most amazing birthday because you truly deserve it.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lots of love and hugs, ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Vedu, /RIt's that time if the year again where you get to feel like a queen, and I really hope you get pampered and have the most amazing birthday because you truly deserve it. So Happy 16th birthday to you, you creative caring and talented human being! love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Riya ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To the sweetest most talented Vedu-I've seen you blossom from a baby to a lady. I've seen you embrace change and challenges. I'm so proud to know and learn from you! Love you always. Yash maamu ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Yash Maamu ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love, love, love you, little Vedu. You're the most beautiful, talented & charming sweet 16 I know.. Keep smiling, it lights you and everyone around! Happy Happy Birthday baby..]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Devika Maami ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happppy Birthday Vedu Didi.. Love you loads!!!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anushka Gupta ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 16th darling Vedu.... May that sparkle in your eyes shine forever and that cherubic smile make you more beautiful every day. Love you! /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Deepti masi & Nilanjan Mausa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I like most about you, VEDU, is ur ultra-infectious SMILE !! The sweetest, warmest & most loving niece of ours is turning 16 this July. Wishing you all the beauty, joy, love & happiness that life has to offer, as you embark on this forever-to-be-cherished milestone]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shuchi Masi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the most special person in my life. I love you so much vedli. Can't believe you're already sixteen, how time flies! Vedli you're growing up to be such a beautiful and strong person and i couldnt be any more proud. You're my absolute  star <3]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Isha didi ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Vedli I love that we've spent every moment of our childhood together: from raiding yum&yummy,to watching skyhigh and playing the-all so intense-hide and seek.I cant imagine any part of my life without you.Even though we dont meet/talk as much we'll always be inseparable]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Isha didi ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Here's to all the laughs, giggles, cries, screams-to all the cheek pulling, biting, squeezing, hugging-to all the plays(where me&j were always boys -.-), dance competitions, pinky pearls and more  nothing would be complete without our complete craziness :*]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Isha didi ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Also, now that you're turning 16 I promise I will try and be less protective ( not guaranteeing anything though) Just can't imagine my " Funny Bunny" growing up. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[isha didi ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So vedli, here's to all the years to come with lots more greek hotties, to Risdee acceptances, countless games of mono deal  -to years filled with love, courage,excitement,compassion and lots and lots of your madness! Love you endlessly.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Isha didi ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The one thing I like most about Vedu jiji is that she is ways very calm no matter the situation for example she is probably very calm right now about her sweet sixteen unlike most other sixteen year old girls would be as this is very important for teenage girls, I think]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andreas Horder]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Vedu our little princess ,  /RWe are proud to  see our little baby grow into such an extraordinary , talented, sharp, witty & a kind person. May god bless you with a future full of achievements & success/RHAPPY BIRTHDAY /RLove you deeply ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nana and Nani]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happiest birthday Vedu! I can't believe that you're already sixteen. I'm so proud of you. You've grown into such a confident and funny girl. I wish you all the best and hope you have wonderful life experiences and learn a lot. Lots of love always!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mehr didi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're turning 16.. What. I can't begin to explain what you mean to me but you're my go-to person, my younger sister, my comfort zone, my idiot and so much more. I have a lot I have to say but I've prepared a little something else. For now, happy birthday my love!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rhea aka your fav gal]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Vedu,/R/RHappy 16th birthday. Love your artistic abilities and you lovely you looked for your prom. We are sure both parents are very proud of you. Loads of love.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[SMRS Wadhwa(s)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Vedika! Hope you have an amazing birthday, two years of IGCSE business has been so GGRREEEAATT with you!! Also all those long English lessons with Mr. Millichamp! I couldn't of asked for a better artsy friend! Eat lots of cake xx/RP.S. Thanks for always braiding my hair!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maya Bond-Webster]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Vediks! You're finally growing old, little one. You remind me a lot of myself because of how weird you are. But let me be a little boring and say hope you have an amazing year ahead. Hope it's crazy, you spastic child! Love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hardik Arora]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Vedu! A very happy birthday! May all your dreams and wishes come true. Wish you a year full of happiness and joy! You have the cutest smile! Keep smiling! Love always ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kunal ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Veds! /RHappy happy birthday!! I can't believe that you're turning 16 already! You mean the world to me and I'm mad lucky to call someone so incredible and extraordinary mine! I'm so proud of the person you've grown up to be. Have the best day munchkin. I love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jayati ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Vedu,/R/RFrom the little girl that we once knew look at you now a beautiful young girl, boy how time has flown. Wish you all the happiness and love. God bless you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dimple and Devashish ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Doll, It gives me immense joy to see the cutest baby I had seen 16 years ago transform into a gorgeous young lady!! You are sensitive and fun; compassionate and driven. My beautiful beautiful vedu, I wish you all the success and joy in the world. And then some/RPria masi]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pria ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear darling Vedushki, /RCan't believe my little baby is turning 16 !!!!! We are so proud and thrilled with the young lady you are turning into... May this birthday bring with it all the joy and good fortune that is ever possible.. Love you ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Vedu…where to begin!   /R/RYour kindness, creativity and unique humor bring joy to us all and I'm proud to call you family.  /R/RHappy Birthday my skinny comrade!/R/RLots of love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shiv Chacha]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're: /RValliant /REbullient /RDependable/RInvaluable /RKind  /RAdroit /R/RYou're special and one of a kind. I love you more than words can describe! /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jayati]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Vedika, you are a marvelous young lady with an inner light that sparkles with brilliance.  I admire your curious and creative mind and how well you express yourself in art and words. Wish you a life full of learning, growth  fun & joy/Rlots of love/RSuti baba]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Suti baba]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It' been beautiful and inspiring to watch you unfold, grow and blossom. From the little shy girl who was so unsure of herself to the smart, witty, bright and confident person you are today.  It's been an incredible journey to watch...May all that you aspire for be yours]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you Mom ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Vedu, /R/RHappy 16th Birthday our little jaan! Hope you're having a fantastic day! Can't wait for you to come home and say 'maaaaaaaami'! You are so special and so very talented. Seeing everything you've achieved makes us so proud. Wishing you all our love!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vivek Mama and Shalini Mami]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Roses are red,/RViolets are blue, /RWhat can I say to Ms. Vedu/RBesides “Happy Bday to you!’/RYou’re smart, /RAmazing at art/RYou even won a Greek’s heart!/RI wish I was like you at sixteen, /RSadly I can no longer be a teen,/RI guess I'll dress up like you this Halloween]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vish]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love the way you make strange faces and despite it look so beautiful. I love how crazy you are & all the crazy silly things you keep on doing. I love how you make an entire room brighter just by being in it. In short. I love you - my other half, better half, only half]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jayati ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing that I like most about you is hard to say. Every inch of you is extraordinary. I love your sense of humor, your energy, your brilliance, your smile, your talent, your heart, your style - the list goes on and on. I love everything about you. <3]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jayati]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday munchkin! Here's to many more years of late night cuddle sessions resulting in me taking over your bed xxxx ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[J]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sweetheart.../RYou are truly very special and I see you blossoming each day. You have tremendous skills and grit in you. My one wish for you is that you realise your strengths. You can be whatever you choose and want to be. As u turn 16 just remember that I believe in u]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>