<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2412-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/27/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Jacqueline Aguanno]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[1 Pierrepont Street]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[Apt. 8B]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Brooklyn]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[NY]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[11201]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 89th Birthday, Big Joe]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Joe Aguanno]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love, Joseph & Jackie (& many more)]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite things about you is how caring and sentimental you are. I'm touched when I see your eyes get misty because you have been affected by a situation, something someone said, or even one of your wonderful jazz standards. Joseph gets this trait from you....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jackie Aguanno]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My Uncle Joe is one of a kind.  I never heard him angry, always there when you needed him; and what I remember very clearly, is how he always pampered my Aunt Gil and still does.  As I said above, he is "ONE OF A KIND."  Love you Uncle Joe.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marilyn Marino]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What a special man, my brother is. Always even-tempered and always fun to be with. We've had many good times together and never a harsh word between us. I love him with all my heart.  Joe, may you have health and happiness today on your birthday and always. /RFran & John]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Somehow related by marriage, but definitely bonded by LOVE! Plain and simple, I LOVE THIS MAN! Special in so many ways! Loyal, sensitive, loving, and thoughtful, add in a strong social conscience and and there you have "Big Joe"! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rose Istrico]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Uncle Joe was always my favorite. He was special, he bowled, played stick ball and was a pro at horseshoes. I will always cherish our visits to Arrowhead Lake and Mays Landing. He will always be a "ten" in my eyes.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Artie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Big Joe, you truly are a gift to our great nation; being born on the fourth of July was clearly no coincidence. May this be a very happy birthday and your best one yet! Happy birthday and much love!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anthony, a.k.a. The Scarf]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Uncle Joe, What an honor to have fireworks displayed across the nation in celebration of your birth. Cheers to you! Lots of love.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heather Istrico (inherited niece) ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Uncle Joe,/RJust wanted you to know just how special you are.  I have some wonderful memories of you and Aunt Gil as I was growing up.  I couldn't ask for a better Godfather.  You are loved more than you'll ever know.  Thank you for being you.  XoXoXo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Debbie, Frank, Corey, Ryan & Jesse ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Memories from the cross country trip Dad and me took in September 1982.  Five days from Laguna Beach to Staten Island!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charles]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The trips to Brockport each August with Mom and Dad to take me to college.  One trip especially in my memory was the side trip we took to Niagara Falls.  Another memory is Dad getting a speeding ticket in Horseheads, NY.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charles]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dad's joy in beating Aunt Fran and Annette in family Jeopardy during the Thanksgiving trip to Aunt Fran's and Uncle Johnny's in Ocean Pines in 2012.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charles]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The move to the Atria in January 2015]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charles]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Always be there for all of us whenever we needed him! His great sense of humor too.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charles]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[     HI JOE/R  WE WERE PLAYING A ROUND AT GREEN TREE. I RECALLED YOUR WORST TEE SHOT EVER. WE WERE ON THE SECOND TEE BOX, YOU HIT A LOW LINE DRIVE. THE BALL HIT A RAILROAD TIE ALONG THE CART PATH, AND BOUNCED STRAIGHT BACK ABOUT FIFTY YARDS./R    HAPPY BIRTHDAY ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JOYCE & CHARLIE]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of our fondest memories is the trip my son’s home in North Carolina with Joe, where we went to the Master’s. We had a great time!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vince and Jean Ciarrocchi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We also enjoy going to dinner with Joe and Gilda and recall the bottle of wine Joe brought with him to dinner and re-cork, after pouring himself a glass – and saved until the next time we went to dinner.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vince and Jean Ciarrocchi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We often wondered if it was a particularly good bottle of wine, but we never were offered a taste!/R/RJoe, may that bottle of wine last until you’re 105! We hope we get to enjoy dinner with you again (before then), even if we don’t share your wine…/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vince and Jean Ciarrocchi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for saving my life when I passed out in the bathroom!/R/RTom and I always enjoyed having lunch with you and Gilda on Mondays at Peter's Diner in Turnersville. /R/RHappy birthday!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barbara from across the street]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have been a constant presence in my life since I was born.  I love you and always think of you on the 4th of July.  I love your caring and encouragement and your sense of humor.  Happiest of Birthdays to you!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Annette Arena & Jack Belgum]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To my Uncle Joe,/RSince I was a kid I always looked up to you but not until I was an adult did I truly value every moment we spend together, every conversation, every I love you before we hang up the phone. I'm so lucky to have you in my life! Happy Birthday. I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Niece, Denise XO]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The way you stick your tongue out to one side when you're thinking of something clever to say. Which, by the way, is always funny. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Denise]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can never forget your birthday. Born on the 4th of July...and I follow 2 days later on July 6. I always feel like we have a special little birthday bond XOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Denise ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Joe, /RHAPPY BIRTHDAY!/RYou are a loving husband and father. You have raised a beautiful family to be proud of. We celebrate YOU, dear Joe. You are very special!/RHealth, Happiness, Love always,/Rxoxoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mayra and Art Baskin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY MY FRIEND!/RYOU ARE SO MISSED! WISH WE COULD MEET AT MILL ST./RHAPPY BIRTHDAY MY FRIEND!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Bob and Hope Knight]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We know you moved up to the Bronx, because you couldn't find Eggplant Parmesan like your mother made. We hope Arthur Ave. has satisfied your long quest. /RDon't set new scoring records at Winged Foot!/R/RFriends forever. We love and miss you. Have a great one.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy and Bob Goodman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember the time we all went golfing Joe hit his ball into a Green Side Bunker. I'm watching him trying to hit out - 1 swing, 2 swings.... After about 5 swings Joe picks it up and throws it out! Joe what did you get on that hole-3? LOL gotta love him! And we do!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim & Ellie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When it comes to finance, no one does it better than Joe Aguanno :-) /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gertrude Jones]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Joe's best quality is the love he has for his wife.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gertrude Jones]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Joe, you finally done it. You left us for the "muckity muck" of New York. You Ranger fans are all the same. /RHappy BirthDay]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gil & Trudy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Now that we are at the pool, I really miss you stopping by for a visit.  Hope everything is good with both of you.  Miss you both./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellie xxoo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Famous quotes.."Nobody remembers Big Joe'' (not true of course), "I'll buy again'' (always true). I very much miss "Hello, old, old, old pal, need something?" Just remember who got the prune juice in Syracuse!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frank & Ann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We miss you & Gil a lot!  Hope to see you soon./R/RHappy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frank & Ann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The way you fist pump every time you are 'right' (I can imagine it in my head right now!). Love you XO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Denise ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ "I have ties older than you" (to my new boyfriend)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, Denise XO]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dad..you always make friends with everyone around you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for teaching me how to ride a bicycle...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday to a great guy and good friend. I miss spending time with you - whether on the golf course, the pool, Phillies games, and our dinners. You have a great sense of humor and always tell it like it is./RBest wishes and good health to both you and Gilda.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your friends Jim and Peg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I still golf, but don't enjoy it as much as when we had our group from the Oaks. We had a good camaraderie. I forgive you for running into me with the golf cart and I still say the best beer I ever had was the $4 Yuengling you bought for me at Frog Rock. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your friends Jim and Peg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I couldn't choose my father, but if I could I would have chosen you./R/RHappy birthday.  Stick around for many more./R/RLove - Joe Jr.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joseph Aguanno]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Uncle Joe-I think you know how much I love you. One of my favorite memories is on Thanksgiving a few yrs ago when we played Family Jeopardy. Just having all of us together & seeing you happy made me happy. In the end, that is what it is all about. Love & Family.  xox]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dianne, Steve, Matt & Chris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I forgot to add Happy Birthday!!!/R/RLove you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dianne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Have to add this one..when you came to my house on LI for my Mom's 49th B-Day, after you entered you said it took you so long to get there that you had to adjust your watch for the time zone and then you said you had to leave so you could make to to work in Monday! LOL]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dianne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love your love of SocialTea cookies! Nana always used to hide them in our food pantry so that she would have them on hand when you came to visit. Whenever I see those cookies, I always think of you and those visits. xox]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dianne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So, this Flatterbox is another thing I did on the computer.  Aren't you glad you didn't take it away from me? /R/RIf I could have chosen a father, you would have been at the top of my list!  You're a 15!/R/RHappy birthday and much love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jackie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So, this Flatterbox is another thing I did on the computer.  Aren't you glad you didn't take it away from me? /R/RIf I could have chosen a father, you would have been at the top of my list!  You're a 15!/R/RHappy birthday and much love,/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jackie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>