<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2415-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/27/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Elizabeth Wermer]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[1953 Zach Scott St]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Austin]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[TX]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[78723]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Dad!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[David Wermer]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love, Beth]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I was young you were painting the dining room wall at the Brown Road house. I sort of let the dog in and she rolled up against the newly painted wall. You chased me thru the house and outside with the paintbrush in your hand. Happy Birthday !!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim and Bonnie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember how much you loved Davy Crockett in 1955.  On Sundays you would run around the yard with your gun and singing the theme song from the show – and always with a smile on your face and asking how much longer till it was on TV.  Definitely your favorite day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our favorite remembrance of David is when our children were young, and our families would gather around the Wermer's pool at their Meadowbrook house.  David was so young-looking and tanned--he loved that pool!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David and Mary Garza]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Uncle Dave,/REven though we are many miles apart, you have always been near in my heart. Family is something I hold dear & I'm thankful for the time we've spent together over the years. Love ya lots!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shelly White]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Having David as a part of our family and in our lives is a joy everyone should experience. /R/ROver the years we loved visiting with David, Anne, Beth and Jeff.  David, you are in our thoughts and in our hearts./R/RLove you always,/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barbara White]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[David’s kind, gentle, and unassuming demeanors are integral to the completeness of him.  Complemented by his innate goodness and intelligence, he does not need us to know it.  I am lucky to have him as a brother-in-law, but always think of him more like a brother.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jimmy (Anne's "Darling" Brother)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What can I say about Uncle Dave?  The first thought that comes to my mind is how kind, selfless, and caring he is.  Those qualities play perfectly into both his chosen career, his family, and a nephew who occasionally has technical questions.  Sending my love.  :-)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bryan M. White]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Of course, there have been many special moments.  I remember, years ago, one summer day in Fire Island when we both shared steamers and nice cold beers./R                          ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cousin Rita]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always have a smile on your face. You should be so proud to be the patriarch of such an outstanding family! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brittney Barnette]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[     Coronado Island - September 2014/R/RWhat better place to meet someone for the first time than in one of their favorite places. It was indeed a pleasure having our families together for the weekend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrea & John]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have a fond memory of our families sitting around the table at The Noble getting to know each other. Your Knuckle Sandwich looked awfully good, so that will be my selection next time./R/RWa - Hoo - Wa/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John & Andrea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have a general, composite recollection of David & his nickname, "Room air," from our formative days as residents at Jacobi. On call, he never failed to get difficult newborns stable and on "room air" by the morning.  Gracefully able, he was the guy to be on call with.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Cruvant]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I was never in a bar in Mexico with David when he shot up the place. But I remember several quiet conversations with him about taking care of those babies, and how much it hurt to lose one and how good it felt to "graduate" one. It  is his "calling" and he has answered.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Clarke Heidrick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[David, welcome to Medicare! Ironically, your one comment I can remember is a rather sobering borrowed quote, "Work sets us free." This comment and its sardonic humor helped me survive the hellhole of internship; thank you. if you didn't say it, I thought you did. Thanks]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ridge Benton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When we were kids, you & I used to sneak off after a family meal & ride our bikes down Brown Rd. where we could throw rocks in the river.  We thought we were getting out of dish washing!  Such fond memories of the two of us on our bikes, the wind in our faces, laughing.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy Cook]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember when we were kids - playing "war", climbing trees, playing kickball, playing tag, playing with our dogs, playing in the field behind our house, and then getting to stay outside to play until dark and catching lightning bugs? Always playing.  Very happy times. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy Cook]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There is no way that I can write about only one special moment! You know that I talk in circles : )/RSeriously, with a friendship as deep and special as the one the Heidricks have with the Wermers, we are blessed to have a lifetime of moments./RWe love you David!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Xo, Catherine Heidrick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my best memories is Dad, Jeff, and I huddled under my tent bed in the house on Meadowbrook. We were hiding from Santa who had come to deliver the presents. Dad had to go into work that night, but Mom said Santa knew and had to start somewhere!/RI love you, Dad./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Beth]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From first time I met you (Abby's wedding), you welcomed and accepted me as a part of Joe's life -and his family's - without making me feel that I was on display. Your genuine warmth and sense of humor made me like you instantly, I am blessed to be part of your family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Penny Wermer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Best statue joke ever told in the gardens of Paris. Still laughing about pigeons and poop./RAll my love./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Problem Child]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dad and I took a road trip to South Dakota and Wyoming a few years ago. Between the monuments, caves, hills, and forests, Dad helped me through a particularly low and unsettled phase in my life. I am forever grateful for the time we spent there.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Two words: TV time.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nikolai]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember when David brought Anne out to Colorado to meet us for the first time, when I was 14. David had often been to our houses, but had never brought a girlfriend, so I knew Anne was special - when he proposed to her on that trip, I was delighted - and I still am!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shelly Van Dyke]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[David has always been great to turn to when we needed advice when we were getting married and as young parents.  His suggestions on who to call when Luke was first diagnosed with diabetes really helped us have trusted information during a scary time.  We love you, David]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alan & Shelly, Trevor, Kate & Luke]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sharing Pappy Van Winkle flights at East Side Showroom! Great whiskey, and even better company to enjoy it with. Here's to many more of both. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[David, you have been so special to me for many years and now you are special to Gil and Dylan too! And you have given us a great gift in Dr. Mirrop, because of you we know Dylan is in the best care as she grows from a baby into a big girl and we are forever grateful.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brant, Gil, and Dylan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We had just been married. I went out to get the mail. It was raining and when I returned David said, "fan mail from some flounder"? I married a guy who quotes Rocky and Bullwinkle!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anne Marie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[PBLT@Noble, roast beef@Rules, anything in Paris, "No!!!!" to the hostess the first night on the ship in Alaska, "Take my picture!!!", "The babies are all on ROOM AIR...", retirement exemplified, optimism personified, you're the best./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, R & J]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>