<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2417-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/29/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Carey Gillis]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[772 Darby Paoli Road]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[BErwyn]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19312]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[scarlet]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 40th Dixon!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Dixon Gillis]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[FROM YOUR FRIENDS AND FAMILY]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Rozi- you are the love of my life!  Thank you for all that you do for our family we love you so much!!!!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[C-Dogg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The first time that I met you was outside at Nudy's!! =)/RA special moment I recall was when you showed up at our Girls' Night Out at Azie and/Rbought everyone Lemon Drop Shots (a virgin experience for me) and just hung out like one of the girls!!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lizzie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Being greeted early afternoon with a beer to shotgun. /RYou can imagine where the rest of the day went... to Hell. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike & Tracy Viola]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the only guy we know that would open porn on an iPad while out to dinner.   You are awesome!/R/RWelcome to "Club 40."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anthony & Jenn Fuscaldo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Special Moment - 1.00am Kitchen Dance Party at our house.  Seeing you and Carey work so hard that night to the smooth sounds of Bon Jovi, Eazy-E, and Ratt made clear why we always look for your names before RSVP'ing to anything.  Always in a good. Happy Birthday Dixon.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laurie and Jeff Collins]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a great source of joy in my life.  You are actually a "second" son to me.  You have included me in your family, opened your house and hearts to me, and generally just put up with me.  You have made your mother proud and she smiles on you every day from heaven.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy Lee Smith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your energy and enthusiasm for life is inspiring and contagious.  It also makes me drink too much when I am near you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Northingtons]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the most genuine people we know.  Always smiling and even though can crush anyone with his hands, don't think we have ever seen him upset or in a bad mood.  Love spending time with Dixon.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mackays]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Too many memories to pinpoint just one, but I'll try...too hard! "Hi, I'm Dixon Gillis", Brooks College, Norway, KSBC, old school Avalon, Camp Tampa, Trinity, St A's, Penn Crew, San Diego, Henley, 40's, Team USA, Vesper, Phillies '98, Monster Jam, OSU, Stars & Stripes!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt Guerrieri]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can write another one!!? You're the man Dixon!! I'll never forget the day we met. You made my experiences at Kent/Penn so much more alive! I can't imagine going through life without you. I'm so happy for you and Carey and wish you all the success in the world!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt Guerrieri]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dixon there are many times that I remember spending with you & Carey when you were dating, but 1 of the main ones that stands out is when we did black tie blowing & on the way home you stopped & bought all of us burgers.  That was so generous of you and hit the spot!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karin Brower Corbett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are so many moments to share its impossible to pick just one. When we first moved to Philly, you welcoming us to your family and became our extended family. That meant a lot. Superficial wise, you fucking feeding me non stop and making me fat my first year! LOL]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ianni ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of your best qualities is your ability to light up a room with your smile!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Scott and Sheryl]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Every moment with Dixon is a moment to remember. Flyers Game with some Freezer Company, East Falls at Tucker's Lair, Center City nights on the town. Tucker bachelor party.....oh and that Halloween party at Dixon's house!! so many fond memories. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin ONell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the only person /RI know that has a /R"coochie red" /Roffice and a mirror that /R"has all its balls". /RYou are a kind, fair, and thoughtful person who /Ralways makes me laugh /Rand keeps me on my toes. /RHappy Birthday and /RCheers to you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember asking Dixon what EGBAR meant. He smiled and said it was something his mom always said. "Everything is going to be all right." We should all be that positive all the time.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robb Frees]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dix, I remember the early years in the drained pool, the barn, Muggsy, Magic, Dudley, Struck, Schmuck.  The middle years with a full pool, full bar, attempts to erg, attempts to golf at Merion.  Happy 40th! I look forward to our now and future years- more of the same. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Jase]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dixon Happy 40th bday.  Have a great day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Buonanno's]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I absolutely love Dixon. I work with mainly good-looking women at a place called Vincera. And all my women rave about Dixon... That really pxxxes me off. When Dixon drops by I cannot get anything done! Except for that, Dixon is the greatest - kind-hearted, loving, etc]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dr William Meyers]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I absolutely love Dixon. I work with mainly good-looking women at a place called Vincera. And all my women rave about Dixon... That really pxxxes me off. When Dixon drops by I cannot get anything done! Except for that, Dixon is the greatest - kind-hearted, loving, etc]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dr William Meyers]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always are looking out for others. /R/RIn my case, you came to my rescue from a 13 year old punk who was picking on me at the carnival tea cups in MV. We both know that kids regrets making fun of me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Drew Saunders]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your acting in the film 'Kimberly' was very convincing, and your portrayal of an oarsman on the silver-screen inspired me to take up rowing.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Demetrios Hadgis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dixon,/RYou are a kind and loyal friend that the Magee's can always count on to have fun with! So many laughs every time we are together! Too many great moments to chose just one. Happy 40th Dixon! We are so happy to celebrate with you! /RCheers! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Magee Nation]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your Merion golf shirt - golf pro questioning it and you pointing out that he sold it to you! Had the whole table laughing. /RHaverford and PENN Pride. St. David's Church. Shay connection.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frank L Coulson III]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I met him as a customer. But his outgoing, no nonsense approach to how he wanted in his home made us a match./RI could frankly talk to him, and he would ignore my suggestions./RWhen things are completed, his smile and radiance overtook the home. Congrats and Blessings.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Choc]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Donnie--I will never forget the early days when you lived in Fairmount and we would meet bright and early on the corner of 21st and Wallace to go for bike rides out to Valley Forge.  What great memories!  Happy Birthday Duder.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Mirage]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dixon gives the best high-fives!!  That is, if you like to have broken bones in your hand after you get one. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paolo Costa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best house warming gift I ever received was from Dixon. A case of Budweiser 40 oz bottles. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paolo Costa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dixon has the most beautiful mid-shin black golf socks anyone has ever seen. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paolo Costa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[While Dixon is a great man, there is nothing more important than a legacy...4 beautiful children!  Sabby in particular is one special kid.  Full of spirit and a zest for life, I can't imagine the apple fell too far from the tree.  We are lucky to count you as friends! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, The Gawthrops]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You, your amazing wife and beautiful children make this world a better place! Wishing nothing but happiness to you and your family in your 40th year./RHappy Birthday, Dixon Gillis!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsey & Howie Wisch]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You, your amazing wife and beautiful children make this world a better place! Wishing nothing but happiness to you and your family in your 40th year./RHappy Birthday, Dixon Gillis!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsey & Howie Wisch]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hard to pick just one: Being booted from bball tryouts for smelling hands. Working maintenance at Irwins (penalty for water fountain wrestling). Riding back from Avalon in mud brute mobile (sans pants). Touring Sunnycroft in a wagon pulled by a tractor. HBD Guyie!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Morris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the first times I met you at the St. Davids vs Merion Silver Plated Cup - whereas you had to leave for a kids game-but ensured that there were no brews left in the cart prior to your departure. The true spirit of the event and preparation for watching kids sports]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alan Guralnick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 40th Birthday Dixon! Thanks for the many years of great friendship! Thanks for welcoming me into Haverford School many years ago! Never forget our fun times with Buck Stanley! Look forward to many fun times together in the future. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John and Beth Yocum "Yocs"]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[And in the end, it's not the years in your life that count. It's the life in your years. - Abraham Lincoln/R/RHappy 40th Birthday, Dixon...You are THE MAN! /R/R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate & Travis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/RThe Man, The Myth, The Legend...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate & Travis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[St. Davids - Merion, the first year you were in tournament, still remains the bar that all other fun is measured against. The course has many memorable moments but I tend to reflect on the comedy at the bar. Good times my man. Welcome to 40! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff Fleming]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I was so honored to be a bridesmaid in your wedding!  It was such a memorable day and highlight for me, during an otherwise difficult time in my life.  You and Carey set such an amazing example and I will never forget it!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany Wolcott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Christmas dinners at your house are so special to our family.  You have you have been the leader in a family tradition of celebration and love.  Here's to many more!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Abby, Kingston, and Jax Wolcott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have shared many moments and hours with Mr Gillis inthe past six years  as his driver, that is actually a lie on the driver part . Dixon and his entire family and friends ALWAYS! !! Has treated me as family and as a close friend and with the up most respect. Thx E.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elan .]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Fall 2007 - Enjoying many beers with you & Jake at the Temple football game when I first started dating Tiffany.  Finished every single beer before going back to the game. It was my first introduction to an awesome family.  Great time!!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rob Wolcott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dixon,/RHappy Birthday! I have had the special honor of documenting your growing family! I feel blessed to witness the mayhem first hand. Your are truly one of a kind! Caring, considerate, observant, intuitive, funny, charming and not afraid to show it. xo The Beckers ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[SAS and Rob Becker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One special moment? They are all special moments with you, Big Dix!  Thanks for being an awesome friend to the family (and like a brother to me). Your enthusiasm and joie de vivre are second to none - and make every occasion more fun. Happy 40th! We love you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Rolling Rd Shays (DIII, G + E)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have grown up with Dixon and his family. When Dixon was 8 our families went to Skytop together and we were at this really nice resort eating dinner. Dixon wanted to make us all laugh so he dropped his pants and mooned us and the restaurant...Some things never change:)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim and Steve carey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dixon is a very funny tall guy. His wife makes great hats. Happy birthday Dixon!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Malenfants]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite memories of Dixon is the vision of him killing it on the dance floor at Bill and Karin's wedding in Jamaica.  And of course - who can forget when Peter gave me the heimlich at Smith and Wolenski's after the Phillies game - Great times, great times!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peter and Sam Murphy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Bday Dixon! I will not forget, and remind my kids often of the lesson you taught S&J at the CHS awards ceremony when you introduced them to an old friend. You demanded they not be snake hunters, but rather look the other person in the eye. Great lesson for kids!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Scheffer family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We don't have one special moment, but many special memories associated with our children - birthday parties, sporting events, school functions. You and your personality make the events memorable, fun, and entertaining. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[the Pijawkas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aunt Elaine and I admire you for the love and respect you give to family and friends and how you’re able to view each day as an opportunity to celebrate life.  You’re a positive force, generating joy and laughter wherever you go.  We wish you the happiest of birthdays!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Elaine and Uncle Tom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Had to overcome DG's reserve for a Denver nite out 4 years ago. Bought a fistful of tip money and persuaded him, finally, to let a nearnude dancer sit in his lap. Cndy str!/R990 at 3:15 am for 18 eggs and 1 lb. of bacon.  Gone and on the road by 5:40 am. Scrnsvr scrwd.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Nt Thy Drove Old Dixie Dwn - Jr]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dixon, you stand out for always working to make others feel welcome in your presence.  Plus you are a super fun guy!  We are lucky to have you in our friend family.  Here's to at least 40 more!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meredith Huston]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A favorite memory of you and your lovely wife is when we met for dinner at White Dog few years back.  We were sharing stories and Carey and I were both pregnant.  It was so fun getting to know you better and Drew was  critiquing the food!  Would love to meet up again! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen & Drew/ Happy Birthday!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Touch Football...Banana Cognac.  I had never met the infamous Dixon but he was coming to the game today.  Here comes a laid out SUV, music bumpin, with a cooler full of Hoegarrden, and a cool ass dude coming on the scene.  I was hooked.  The rumors were true.  Great guy]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Scott Carter and Kelly Honer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dixon- We're so excited to celebrate your birthday with you! We've had many good times over the years, and our favorite memory is probably of the rickshaw ride we took through Avalon~ We wish you a /Rvery happy 40th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Mike and Karen McGovern]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 40oz to my greatest friend! Here's to the Fun Bunch to Haverford studies to the Hofbrauhaus to a Bronc frosty Great Adventure to a goose-out trip back from the shore to Kiahwah, and to friends, family, and 40ths. A great ride for the Brutes so far! Love ya D-Bone!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[T-Bone]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In the short time we have known Dixon, what strikes us the most is his genuine and magnetic personality.  He is always looking to do for others and making sure that they are having a good time.  We feel blessed to call him and his family our friends.  Happy 40th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grant and Katie Galef]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No better time then your 40th birthday to remind you that I love you like a brother. You're larger then life, guyeee! Your enthusiasm is inspiring, and your positivity is contagious. You make all whom surround you....better. I'm thankful to have you in my life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wally]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dixon always makes me smile and feel better about things. He is a special person because while many people are giving, loyal, funny, and caring, he embodies all four of these attributes. /RDid I say he always makes me smile? :) :) :) /RYou do, Dixon!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Colleen Hutchinson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We recall a trip to NYC and drinks/lunch at an Irish pub. Only you could have had the crowd singing the EAGLES fight song and the bartenders serving you beer with a sticky note with a hand drawn Eagles logo. Few but you could pull that off bro!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday - Andrew & Deb ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A favorite Dixon memory was when the New Eagle gang went to dinner at Carmel. Ordering from iPads instead of menus seemed like a great idea... until Dixon came along! Not only did you pull up adult videos on the iPad but you blamed the waitress for it! Happy 40th Dixon!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Drew and Julie Spaulding]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Oh, Gillis:  Moshpit slams.  Beer slams.  Walking down the hall-slams. Medals in crew, we won a few!  Xmas parties with your Mom's cookies. Mallory's runs when playing hooky.  Nearly 40 years of hanging with you - looking forward to the next 40 too!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Signing the agreement of sale for the new home named  Howerton Hill 2014 /RWe had to do it after many cocktails at Merion Golf Club for  dinner!  I could barely see the agreement by the time you two signed !!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandy and Paul (Didju)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dixon, you bring an unbeatable energy everywhere you go.  Some of my most fun high school memories are of living it up on the dance floor with you leading the charge.  More recently it was a blast to hang out with you at David's 40th where you led us in singing H-Bday.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anne Ford]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dixon accompanied Carey and I to our 20th HHS reunion this past fall and we had a blast. Most of the fun we had came from Dixon making sure we always had a drink in our hand and a story or joke to listen to! The perfect date and friend... Happy 40th Birthday Dixon!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kati and Mike Lisansky (SULLIVAN)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I already sent in but  I forgot to add the last part /RAbout making an offer at a restaurant /RTrying to stay sober to fill in the agreement of sale /RThis was in January 2014  and said to Dixon when do you want to settle on your new home ? "June 20th my birthday"  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandy and Paul McAlaine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Dawg!  Sorry we could not be with you to celebrate but know we were thinking of you.  Thank you for your friendship and I hope that our bond grows tighter with age! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt and Jen Tucker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dix,/RYou are always considered by me and many others one of the most thoughtful as well as the most fun people to spend time with.  If there is a definition of what I would like to emulate, it is that in friendship./RYour Lifetime Member-Member Partner,/RChris]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hondo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dixon and Carey,/R/RGreat time at your house for Dixon's 40th.  Loved the kegstands, fireballs and the festive backyard.  Nice toast too.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peter and Heather Conlan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whenever I see Dixon's infectious smile, I find myself smiling too.  I recall being at St. David's for the Pageant, seeing some uppity animals enter and people getting concerned...then came Dixon in the door, smiling, and he hoisted a goat over his shoulder to save us!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rod and Doc Herrell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Life on steroids and appearances too.  Contagious enthusiasm. Drinking 40's while rolling in "the brick". Damaged women on the dance floor.  Fire alarms in every sense.  Singing with vibrato for Stairs and the Brierley ladies.  Many laughs, many memories...Love you Dix]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Collin Bell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>