<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2420-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/30/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Heidi Portalatin]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[63 Yacht Club Drive]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Lake Hopatcong]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[NJ]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[07849]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_200]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 25th Monkey Moo Moo]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Ryan Moody, Son, Friend]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[ - Mom (2015)]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey Coach I can't pick just moment, we have had so many good times. If I had to pick one though I think it would be that time you quit your job and moved to Europe with me! :)/R/RHope you have a great birthdy brother! I love and miss you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nimmy Covich]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The first time I met Ryan, I was dog sitting for his family and he was staying for one night at the apartment. What I thought was going to be an awkward night, ended up being a night of jokes, drinks, and the most delicious short ribs in Jersey City!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Claire Goater]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[3 months ago...lovely dinner.... A drink or two ; ambulance....hours pass.... And you were the sweetest guy ever!!!! ?????? Happy birthday!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cris ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Disney for the first time and Dad was running militant pace and made us get up super early to head to the parks.  We lasted 2 days on day 3 we had a mutiny and  both broke down crying in the middle of the Disney parade.  Dad gave up and let us sleep in rest of the trip.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Janet Moody]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am so blessed to have been part of your life!  You make me and Dad so proud!  /RYou have been a joy to watch grow up into the amazing man you are today. /RMy heart bursts with pride and love!!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Janet ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have the clearest picture of you Ryan, heading off to school, with Elliot.  Your shirt was firmly tucked into your shorts (as always) shoes and socks matching, and, of course, you had to be the first in line and on the bus!  You were our little "tigger" :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julia and Rick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ryan,/R/RYou and I have had our ups and downs together the past seven years. You've been there for me in times when no one else has.  I owe you my life buddy and I just wanted to say thank you.  You are my brother and I would do anything for you.  Happy 25th. Love you kid]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I look at you, I see a handsome young man, but I also see a little boy, with arms around my neck, kisses and that same wide perfect smile. Happy Birthday dearest Ryan.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunty Jan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Make it stretch...Asante Samuels...maize in your pants...HAD shampoo...man with red turtles...coconut man...Bambi ;(...print shop...same burger order....how do you sayyyy, mmm, NO. Here's to many crazy adventures and many many more to come! Happy birthday buddy]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ribble]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[remember that time we met at Anitas......I think there was a receipt involved? Enough said! Love ya and I hope its a great one :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Veronika ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ryan,/R/RAfter meeting you through Julio it was so funny we ended up at WM together! Our entire semester of acting class was just one hilarious blur with that crazy Westburg. I'm happy to be back in NJ & can't wait to have more crazy times with ya! Happy Birthday :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cream]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[This is not really one moment but something that sticks out in our minds is all of the duty face tickle fights we had which ended in Jess and Lex on the floor of our 221 bedroom laughing so hard we could not breathe!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jess Hecht and Lex Gerber]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Darling Grandson my special moment is of you in a photo with Aunt Bronwyn and wearing your English school uniform. Your blazer and cap with St Mathew logo and short grey pants and Bron wearing her straw hat. This was your first day of school aged 5. So adorable.  LOVE.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ Christine/Grandma.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's crazy you're turning 25! It seems like we were roaming the streets of Welby Terrace not that long ago. Hope you have an amazing birthday!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Fiona McDonald ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From Yates Hall to Winston (Wendy), Canterbury (Bud) and now the Big Apple-we've always had a bond that was stronger than family. 270 characters can't do our stories justice but Miami, UT (go Vols), the Lakehouse and Italy have set the bar high for trips to come. Prego.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brandon Heroux]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I really enjoyed when you came to Boston and watched my spring game! Then we went out and had a lot of fun! I hope we can do it again sometime and that you have a great birthday !!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Hernandez]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To my Wednesday night buddy--We've definitely shared some smiles, laughs, sneak outs, late nights at the park, ups and downs, but-most importantly-we've shared a special friendship I'll never forgot. Love you to pieces! Happy 25th Birthday, sweet boy! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rachel Proctor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember you as a talented young football player on the Vikings in Ashburn, and followed you through the Bulldogs and the Tribe.  Your determination through adversity and your character define your future.  I'm proud to know you, Ryan!  Happy Birthday!   Best always!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Scott Stewart]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ryan, your mom and I have shared all the ups and downs of raising you and Graham.  From SB and Mickey T. to W&M and now.  You are a grown $%* man.  I am very proud of your accomplishmenst and what you have overcome.  Congrats and mad love to you young man.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt Greening and Graham]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It all started back in college when I told you I was going to live with you... And then I didn't. BUT, now we're roomies!!! So many memories, so many trips, and so much more to come. Love you buddy - happy birthday! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gottlieb]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday, MooMoo! Hope 25 is the best year yet :) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kayleigh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Ryan! I will never forget all the special birthday occassions we've celebrated with you...however, I think the most memorable one for me was when you were in the 7th grade and had a DJ at your "hawaiian luau" party, we had lots of fun groov'n to the beatz]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, Aunt Nic & Cousin Maxie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can't believe you are turning 25!  I still think of you as my curly haired cutie lil cous...always so friendly and loving.  You are actually still all of the above and should be super proud of all that you have accomplished in these 25 years.  Love you bunches!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rachel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ryan, Happy 25th!  Always remeber the story about both our moms were in the hospital together! I have an awesome picture of us together when we're 6 months old! Then we reconnected at SBHS our senior year. You always had a contagious smile that lit the room up. :) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rachel Zeldin ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Rynasourus, where do I even begin? Maybe 14 years ago when we were in in-school together?lol but look at us now both on track with our careers, healthy, and loving families. You're like a (little) brother to me and I appreciate our friendship more than words. Happy 25th]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Melaphant]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[: I met you when you were just 5 years old and at your birthday we celebrate it in the spanish way , I remember your face when we wait for you with a pinata , a table full of desserts and hoping you like it , it was your first introduction to our culture ./RI love you .]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Spanish grandma  Clara Pedraz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I cannot narrow it down to one moment in time... there are some people that light up the room, that make people smile, that keep the conversation going, that make every moment more special... that are the glue that binds us all together!  YOU are our family's GLUE! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[We Love You! ~ The McKnew Zoo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Laxmas freshman year when you gave me a lap dance in college deli. We werent really friends yet but that is when I knew we would be best friends. Thank you for constantly making me laugh,and always being there when i needed it most. You are the brother i never had.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Ally ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember that time when you came out of the closet... wait I mean the time when we came up to New York and started roasting on jax for liking monkey balls. I will always remember those two moments. Love ya and happy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Noah Butler ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Oh Ryan! You are just a spectacular person. I remember you starting high school and starting football and being so excited. You have been nothing but an above board young man! Always sweet to your mom as well as to Cameron and me when we would hang at your pad! Love ya!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kristen (Watson)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Nephew!!/RHave a great day :)/R/RI hope that one day I will finally get to meet you in person./R/RPlease visit England soon as I'm too much of a scaredy cat to fly for that long :( /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Auntie Katie Bradshaw]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey x-roomie....oh yea and step son.....have fun at the Lake House  but stay away from my nail gun! quarter of a century sounds old to me so don't call me old man anymore! Keep it real....Happy 25th...love Julio]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julio A. Portalatin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[so many memories but 2 that make me laugh:  Ry trying to school his aunt on beer pong except we weren't drinking beer I stuck to wine but Ry drank gin.  Bad next day for Ry.  And doing the wobble with him at his grad party.  See Ry we have moved on from the robot.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love always, Gigi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ryan,/R/RHappy birthday!!! You're the coolest cancer I know ;-) thanks for always being such a great friend, I'm so glad we've become so close these past 2 years.  Here's to many more!! :-)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Corrine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Ryan, A quarter of a century old. How did that happen? I have many memories of you and Geebo running around the house everyday after school. You loved my oatmeal and gummy bears, summers at the Rivah with Bronwyn and her friends and of course bball&states]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen Elliot]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Well what can I say!? When I hit you on your head when you were born I may not remember it but I'm reminded of it constantly ;) maybe you should let it go? Hehe I love you to the moon and back Ryan have an amazing birthday! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Bronwyn :) ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday dude! I have one word to say to you...../R/RFOCUS!!! ;) /R/RYou are awesome! See you soon! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Danny ;) haha]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Between summer pool parties, wine pong in the basement, and vacationing with the family, we always have a good time. Happy birthday buddy!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julio Portalatin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 25th Birthday Ryan! So many of my happy HS memories include you and our fun little foursome (LOL). You're such a funny, sweet guy and I hope you get everything you wish for! :) xoxo ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[MNB]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[25?!?!?!?!  Say it ain't so!  I loved watching you and Dan wreak havoc in high school and lots of fun times at the river!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Peg (Fry)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ryan! Happy Birthday! I am so happy that you have become part of the fam! You add so much fun and love to the dynamic and we are so lucky to have you as a part of our lives! The Dominican is going to be a blast this summer- can't wait! Lots of love - ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex Hernandez]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ryan.....William.....Moody.....my #2 Son.  So many memories....so much love....seems like just yesterday you and Timmy were just little boys.  It is so hard to choose just one memory, but I'll choose BACON!!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you!!!  Mama Miscovich]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ryan was the first kid I can remember who went out of his way to shake my hand & introduce himself. With Coach Moody's guidance, we grew up competing alongside one another both winning & losing (but mostly winning). All-Star, thank you for having my back since Day 1.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tu-Tone ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congrats on halfway to 50 you filthy animal! There are quite a few memories, but the one that sticks out the most has to be the official visit when it all began. Or maybe its when you buzzed my hair on accident lol. Still rocking it. Hope you have an awesome day brotha!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Derek]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[After they lost the State Title game his Soph season after he fumbled on the 1 going in, to win the game. He came home distraught! We were sitting downstairs and I gave him my State Championship Medal and I said when he wins one he can give me mines back and HE DID!!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Wooten's Adam, Annia, and Faith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Ryan/R/RHappy 25th Birthday, hope you have a great day./R/RIt would be great if you could visit us in England as Katie and I don't like flying and I have only seen you twice when you were about 2 and 4 years old and look at you now, tall and handsome!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Debbie Bradshaw]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am so proud to have you as my grandson I just can't believe that you are 25 Wow!! It only seems minutes ago that you were born. You have grown into such a hansome, bright young man. I hope that you have a wonderfull life full of laughter and love.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I love you lots Ryan, - Grandad ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Ryan! It was so awesome to grow up with cousins like you, Matthew, Elliot and Bronwyn. I'm not surprised that you've grown into a successful, handsome and polite young man. Although I do have a memory of you biting me at Aunt Julia's house haha! Love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I knew the day you arrived we would be closer than any Aunt/Nephew could be. Never forget the Gremlin voice, laying in the bunk beds laughing our @!$es off, wet willies, farting, punching until we are bruised and knowing that no matter what i love u 2 the moon and back!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Leesa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you tons and can't wait to see you soon!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lily]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[RYAN,/RIF I COULD GIFT WRAP THE GLOBE. I WOULD GIVE YOU THE WORLD!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[DAD]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[RYAN -/RThere used to be a graying tower alone on the sea./RYou became the light on the dark side of me./RLove remained a drug that's the high and not the pill./RBut did you know,/RThat when it snows,/RMy eyes become large and/RThe light that you shine can be seen.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[DAD]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[RYAN - /RALL I HAVE AND ALL I DO CANNOT COMPARE TO MY LOVE FOR YOU.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[DAD]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[RYAN -/R/RI am so proud of you son, everything you have accomplished, and I am looking forward to what your future brings.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[DAD]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[GOOD FOUL !]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[COACH MOODY]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The day you were born was the best day of my life.  /RI could never imagine how much love I could give or feel for one little person but you wiggled, giggled and smiled at me thoughout the days and changed my life in ways you /Rwill never know. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I Love You,  Mum]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cuz,/RWe've shared so many early memories together it's hard to choose just one. We've shared homes, birthdays, and first days of school. From riding f@#king dolphins to high school graduation... I love you like a brother, man. Happy 1/4 century. The best is yet to come.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elliot]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ryan, What Color are you???/RI'm Peach!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[MUM]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[All moments with Ryan are special. During Mary's wedding I twisted my foot. He helped me to the car and home to get my aircast. He was so attentive. Then he danced with me and made the cast seem like it wasn't even on! He is the sweetest guy! Mackenzie is a lucky girl????]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Teri Kelleher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tim and I think the world of this guy and can't imagine life without him! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tim and Teri Kelleher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I knew Ryan as a baby & toddler. Then last year after a 19 year absence got to see what an incredible young man he has become. Happy birthday Ryan x]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leesa Western ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The first time I met you, Ryan, you were a little guy and yet behaved like a young man. I will never forget your charm, wit and willingness to jump in and help. Things haven't changed much; you still are one of my favorite people. Love you Ryan- ??????]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Duer Hoff]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[At our fun weekly dinners in NYC, it didn't matter how well dressed you were or how good looking the restaurant staff thought you were, the most thing that most impressed everyone we met were your impeccable manners.  Happy Birthday to one heck of a great guy!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I was sitting on the hallway floor with my feet on the stairs leading down to the family room at our house in Kingston Chase and Ryan was combing my hair.  He said "Grandma, your hair is bootiful."  He was two or three years old and such a/R charmer]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JeTaun Moody, paternal grandmother ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When Ryan was a young boy and we were riding in my car, we had a routine where he and I took turns saying, "Ryan, I Love you more than the stars.  Then Ryan would say I love you more than the sun."  We continue with the comparison to the moon and universe. CONTENTMENT]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JeTaun Moody, paternal grandmother]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wishing you a fun birthday, prom date! Happy to see you doing well in the big city. Never change, kay?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jess Dunn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember you coming to my home as a toddler. You and Taylor played outside in the pool and had the best time laughing and just being kids.It was a joy to see you then and to see what a great man you've become. And you still have that million dollar smile]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrea Creighton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My Monkey Moo Moo/R/RWe have gone through many up's and down's  over the years but always been there for each other... /R/RRemember I will always be there for you no matter what.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite memories with Ryan is playing football together at Stone Bridge. Although every season was special, he particularly had an incredible senior season and a spectacular State Championship game that helped us win the '07 state title. A great moment shared]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Goov]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ryan, happy birthday man! Definitely miss the good old middle school high school hangouts, country concerts, and of course wrecking people on halo. Hope all is well with you up in the big city, hope to see ya soon, enjoy the day man!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt Wallace ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bleep bleep bloop bloop: Ryan some of the best times I've had in life you've always been a part of. The years passed have provided great memories. I look forward to the next one shared! Love you bro bro. Bloop. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Goov]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Ry, hope you have a perfect week!  Wish we were home to celebrate with ya'll!  Sending Hawaiian sunshine your way!  Miss and love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amanda ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Ryan. I miss your hugs and smile. There are so many stories through the years with you and Collin. I so enjoyed watching you grow up and be a part of Collins life. But definitely the funniest moment was when you asked "you named your dog bastard?!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maryellen ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[December 8, 2005!  Heart, effort, desire, diginity!  I will always remember watching that day be a part of turning you into the awesome young man you have become. Miss you Kid.  Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Fran Glenn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday cuz. I still haven't forgiven you for taking my LEGOs ;)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matthew]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Ryan!!  My first memory of you was 19 years ago (wow) while having lunch with Justin in the cafeteria when you were in 1st grade.  I remember seeing a little boy with a great smile.  I'm happy to see that smile has not faded.  All the best to you!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lisa Marsh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We haven't spent much time with one another, but every time we do it is always a fun time getting to know you. I'll always remember going out after Sarah's wedding and spending the night at your dad's house! Happy birthday Ryan! You deserve the best [second ;)] cuz!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelsey xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are *%$ at FIFA peasent]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[King Jackson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ry, you are my person. I wouldn't change any hardship you and I have had to cross. I would go back & do it all over again. Your kindness & compassion ignite my soul. 1 Universe, 9 Planets, 204 Countries, 809 Islands, 7 Seas, & yet I had the privilege of meeting you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[To the Moon & Back - Mackenzie ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always know exactly what I'm about to say & you beat me 2 the punch saying it in my exact tone of voice(only 4 octaves higher of course)I can't even get a word in, all I can do is laugh, even when I'm mad as all hell. You keep this journey quite an adventure]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mackie-cheese]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I think about Ryan, I immediately think sports. Several years where he and all our boys enjoyed various sports activities together as a cohesive team. It's been fun to watch you grow from a boy to an adult. Happy birthday Ryan! ????]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda Sharp]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It’s hard to believe the young boy that we used to know has turned into such an incredible man.We wish you the very best with all of your future endeavors.The sky is the limit for you; enjoy every day and make the most of every opportunity that comes your way.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Zimmerman's]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ryan saved the day at Nick and I's wedding rehearsal when he drove all the way from the church to the hotel to grab the most beautiful bouquet my sister had made for me that I had forgotten. I'll never forget it- I appreciated that more than he will ever know. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nick and Mary Grillo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Since 2008, I'm very thankful that I've been able to call you a best friend! I wish you nothing but the best as you turn 25! Do it justice or I'll put you in the birdhouse..ha!    Go Vols! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dude Bailiff (Tyler Bailey) ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I know it's your birthday and I love ya....butttt I am not helping you move your stuff, sorry ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[erma]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[High school parties at my house...'nuff said :) Happy birthday kid!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Molly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The memories are too plentiful (and inappropriate) to list. Happy Birthday!/R/ROne Love.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Britty]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My lil nephew is steadily growing up & I am proud to have witnessed it over the years.  From taking him to the mall as a toddler, to watching him play football in high school & at W&M.  We all are very proud of you . . . Happy Birthday from Sam, Donovan & I.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Keith Moody]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I only met Ryan briefly last year but thank you for showing my mum and I around New York. You and your family made our stay so much more enjoyable. Hope to see you soon and Happy Birthday x ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mattaya Western]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'll never forget all your birthdays at the pool and the numerous days we spent hanging out after school playing basketball, football, and all the other shenanigans.  You were always there for me and are truly a great friend.  Happy Birthday! Hope to see you soon!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Devlin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will always remember our conversation after the 2005 state game and then watching you become the best WR in school history. I appreciate the time a got to coach you. ----- I also will NEVER forget the modeling job]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mickey Thompson ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To be honest, limiting our friendship to 270 characters is nearly impossible. College would not be the same without you and I'm  so blessed to have found you and our group as friends! I'm so excited for our times in NYC to start.. And oh yeah, you stink at FIFA!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nonie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always looking out for my fellow Loudoun athletes (Loco baby)....remember seeing #9 streaking downfield vs UVA making a big play on the way to a huge Tribe victory.  Best part of my job is seeing my boys grow up and become young men. Happy Bday my dude!  Proud of you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jason Simms]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ryan, After reading all of these funny, inspirational and heartfelt sentiments, I can not feel any prouder of the person you have become, the love that is in abundance for you, and the friendships you have made so far in your magical life.  /RThis is a testament to you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[You Made me a better Mom ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When you were 3, you and I were with your mom in a very crowded office. I was holding you. I saw the look on your face change as you realized you had an audience.....with a big smile on your face, you started dropping the F-bomb over and over again. Hysterical! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura McHale]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ocean City putt putt]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[angie and rachel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your mom and I always smile when we think back to you going over backwards in my papasan chair when you were a little boy. The expression on your little face went from shear joy to shear terror very quickly. A fond memory!/RAll my love to you on your 25th birthday, Ryan!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura McHale]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Ryan! The best memory in my mind I have of you is when you would come to my soccer games at SB and wait for me at the good ol green explorer with an ice cream sundae:) have a good one!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Katie Ansell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Well Ryan it is to see how you have grown into a nice well rounded young man. I wish you a very happy Birthday and many more to come. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Coach Mack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ry - you're always there as a great friend. The memories of our friendship started your frosh year at girls gym house, to the late night convos outside by the fire at the lake. /R/RHappy Birthday bud!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Max]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When reflecting on Devlin's childhood I picture you as a big part of it.  Playing in the neighborhood, riding bikes, sleepovers, & of course birthdays! You were inseparable!  Happy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda Salem]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember when I came over to the states to visit years ago and we use to hang out with your dog buddy and play video games. Hopefully will see you soon. Have an awesome birthday. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah Bradshaw ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Ryan Moody!! I still remember when you and Bryan were in Kindergarten and you guys were so adorable and funny! He always had such a great time and even when you moved away you still invited him to your birthday party! Hope your day is special-like you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim Mill]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Enjoyed coaching Ryan in youth football, and watching him grow through high school and into college. He has grown into a wonderful young man. Ryan always greets us with a big smile and hug. Happy 25th Birthday Ryan!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Morrisons]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[St. Maarten, 2002/RDinner in a tiki hut after a beautiful day at Orient Beach. Ryan looked forward to ribs for days and ordered dry rub ribs that were so spicy he couldn't eat them. Add thunderstorm and thatch roof set ablaze by torch - such fun memories!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Trisha Staugler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[St. Maarten, 2002/RSeven of us crammed in a clown car traveling the island. I took the time to teach Ryan French: pousser (pron. puss-ay), which means push in English.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Coach Jay Staugler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hampton, VA, 2005/RThe highs are amazing, but sharing the lows is what makes us family. A dropped pass, a team devastated by loss, and Ryan with the world on his shoulders, or so it seemed then. You showed true grit in handling it all so well.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Trisha and Jay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember that time I made you do push-ups in a fountain in Puerto Rico? Oh, and the time you got iced at the lake house? Yeah, me too :) Thanks for always being a trooper and being fun! Happy Birthday, Ry!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Caity Jones]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Ryan! We hope you have a wonderful 25th birthday! Hopefully we will see you soon!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate and Brent]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Halloween '03, we ran around the neighborhood T- Ping houses. We thought that someone called the cops, so we ran back to the Coble’s house and hid. We all panicked every time a car drove by thinking the cops were coming to arrest us for throwing toilet paper.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenn Fairchild ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Matt and Moody have been friends for some time. I remember meeting this hunk-a-love and immediately could tell he was such a great friend to Matt. Moody-we both love you so much and your friendship means the world to us! We hope this is the best birthday yet. Cheers!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt and Stacia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Countless memories with this guy./RA good one was back in the day and we were at the mall. We were sitting on a bench and there was this puddle of water that someone had spilled. People were walking by and slipping in it and we would continuously laugh our #@$es off!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Collin "Collo" Pearson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[During AYFL, on Gils team, I accidently slid down the street on my back when riding bike. Rule was no bikes during the season, so Ryan put cream on my back for the next couple of days and kept the secret of what really happened. That's when I knew this guy was my friend]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matty fin I ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can remember Ryan at Julia's in Cattail Lane when the rest of the children came in from the garden really dirty Ryan would always look immaculate, always straightening his shirt.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love from great nan and popa xxxx]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A lot of great times & memories over the years my friend. Hate to miss the celebration but have a great birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wes Steinman ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>