<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2421-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[6/30/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Drew Saunders]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[136 Todd Lane]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Briarcliff]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[NY]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[10510]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[scarlet]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[40 Years of Memories]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Katherine Hase Saunders]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[From all your friends]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I first got to know Kat playing paddle. I'll never forget how much fun we had playing in the Sadie Hawkins tourney  a few years ago. We spent a great day together as teammates and friends and we've only grown closer since. That's why I call Kat "Champ." She's the best  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brendan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We will forever recall fondly, that cold December day when we spotted the rarest of beasts.  The Yeti, to that point only legend, was seen attempting to hibernate on Todd Lane.  I was forever changed.   Look forward to many more years with the two of you, great friends]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With Love, Erin and Tim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Mezapalooza!"  someone told me dancing is an expression of laughter.  Trust me you can dance!  Happy Happy Birthday.  xoxo/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Caroline]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our special moment with Kat was when she told us that secretly she wishes she had gone to the University of Florida.  She told us that when she's alone she dresses in orange and blue and does the Gator "Chomp Chomp Chomp"!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you Kat! Mark & Betsy Mitchell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kitty - Your bright smile is what I picture first when I think of you!  I love remembering the days of no cable on HI, meeting Drew on the dance floor of Chatterbox, and closing down the bar in St. Augustine!  /R"Well behaved women rarely make history" - Marilyn Monroe]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandy Marchiafava Fowler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of our favorite memories from our wedding is dancing to to Wagon Wheel with you and Drew. Every time we hear it we think of you! Your fun loving spirit and dance moves are infectious. Happy Birthday Kat! We love you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ash and Mike]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are many memories I have shared with Kat, but the one that sticks out most in my head is the night she found out she was pregnant with Van...she knows the rest:)  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The night Kat was found weeding our lawn at about 1am!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Duffy's]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[All I will say is that Drew was in Superman underwear...YIKES!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Duffy's]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always greet me with a big smile and your patented "Stoo-bee-doo-bee-do." Oh yeah, and you dancing on the coffee table at the paddle hut is pretty spectacular too. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stu Woody]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have so many fantastic memories with a fabulous friend...Blunch, Hudson and Beau diaper play dates, Soho w Special Ks, fireplace dancing, 'booty music', paddle...and can't wait to make many more. Happy 40th Kitty Kat. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Blondie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Kat! Your infectious smile and infinite grace light up every room you enter! Shine on! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsay & Patrick waterhouse]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Having a baby is one thing, but having a baby down the hall from dear friends also having a baby brings it to a whole other level. Watching Drew and Paul toast to fatherhood with silver bullets on the NWH maternity floor?  PRICELESS. Here's to more shared milestones. xo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heather and Paul Brennan ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Classic ladies lunches/RA Well Appointed Home/RFlying Pig/RGucci Baby!!/RBest Closet Ever/RAnd lastly, Southern Roots!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tammie Gonseth]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The first time I came to your house, you hadn't been there long, and I remember being completely impressed by how you had decorated the house so beautifully already including an entire collage wall of picture frames - pictureless at the time  - but you were all set! :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Caroline Comfort]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember the time you gave me the fantastic Bucknell wood chair as your first ever extended family Christmas gift?  I do.  I still recall all the excitement on your face when you revealed the gift to me, hoping you got it right.  You did.  I love that chair.  Thanks Kat]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/RHere's to many more Korean meatballs, $1 paintings and cocktails! Happy Happy Birthday! Cheers!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sojin xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Kat,/RAs you always say "my winter friend"....we really got to know each other through paddle and luckily our friendship is not just one season.  You are a girl of great beauty, immense kindness and amazing grace.  I feel honored to share this special day with you!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cheryl Barrett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Anytime I get to spend with you is always special, but getting ready with you for my wedding was something I will never forget! (And thank goodness it's not on the video) Happy 40th Birthday!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, Stacey Millhorn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To the best paddle partner and friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan Komosa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kat, I remember that we first got know you at your wedding with Drew. We all went "Wow, Drew, how did you get so lucky?"  Its a few years later and we are still saying "WOW, Drew, how did you get so lucky!!" Glad you and that great family of yours are in our lives. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dana Comfort]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember your utter delight at having a cook, the best snorkeling in Barbados outside the house gate, entertainment by the resident Green Monkey family....AND BEST, a laundress to do all the ironing for a week.  Your treasure is simple pleasures.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sunny]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kat, you will always hold a special place in my heart. I have the best memories of our years as roommates and you are a true best friend! Some of the best: Coolie the Cat is missing party, Rolling Stones concert, Rare Olive & FGF nights, Bayshore walks & talks. Love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday! Melanie Skijus]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My Dear Friend Kat, You are the best friend a girl can ask for. No one knows me better and is there for me like you. Raising our families together/RIs the greatest gift I could ask for. I love you and always remember.... Snap, don't get up in my/RStuff... Happy 40th!!! Xo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate Sanzenbacher ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sweet/RFunny/RSensible/RTrue/RConsiderate/RBeautiful inside and out/R/Rwe are truly blessed to have you in our lives....love you Sistah!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ Kim & Rocky]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Happy Birthday! You have always been like an older sister to me.  You are beautiful inside and out and such a wonderful mom.  Enjoy your day & year! I hope to see you soon.  Much Love, Jacki]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jacki, Brian, Mae and Eli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that you will do anything for a friend or family member, except let them win at a board game or pétanque. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Cinda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tentacles, Auntie Kat, tentacles. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Morrison]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love coming down the hill to see you because you make it fun. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Quentin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Pizza and red wine by the pool while the other two danced with the inbreds in the center of some foreign town]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Danny]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our trip to St. Tropez --/RWhat a roller-coaster!!!/R/RYou're not moving, you're topless, to you are moving and we are getting engaged./R/RI have enjoyed the roller-coaster ever since./R/RI am so lucky and love you ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Drew]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I don't think I can define it in one moment...Kat, being in your presence immediately brings a smile to my face and makes me happy.  Your southern charm and grounded and upbeat perspective on life is contagious.  We love you so much!  Happy 40th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo Jen aka JBW]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 40th Birthday to a very special girl! You are one of the nicest, prettiest, and funniest people I know! Love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tatiana Mischenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You don't choose your family but I am so Glad my family Chose you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Please don't hide your CRAZY... We adore you just the way you are.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Raynes Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hudson, Paige and Van are my world.... Thank You for bringing them into my life. I Love being a part of your family... My NY Home away from Home. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Duke]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kat and Drew's 30th Birthday Party. The Infamous "Chunky Dunk" that brought down the house and the family/Rhot tub! /RKat laughed harder and longer than anyone, it was infectious.  /R"It must be some kinda hot tub time machine", 10yrs later, here we go again!  /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen And Larry Waterhouse]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I first met you on the rooftop of the Gansevoort Hotel at a surprise 40th.  I was visiting from Ohio but knew I was moving to NY.  In our brief interaction I could see what a sweet, kind women you were and my fears of moving were greatly reduced knowing you'd be there:)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Erin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Kat/R/RWho knew that the day you were born 40 years ago, that you would be a gift to so many of us all the way up here in NY?!  You are the gift that keeps on giving! We love you and wish you the Happiest of Birthdays and many more!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Clare and Frank]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom my favorite times with you are when just the two of us go to the city together. I hope we do it at least every year forever./R/RI love you so much]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hudson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I hope I never grow to old too cuddle with you in the morning while you have your coffee./R/ROur cuddle time is the best./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Van the Man]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom I love it when you do cartwheels and cheerleading moves with me in the kitchen or backyard./R/RYou are the best mom ever./R/RI love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paige (your little gymnast)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I knew when I first met you that you weren't from around here, nor was I. We had an instant connection and I liked you from the start. We soon learned that we are both Cancers, which explains a lot. You are such a fun, warm and loving person. Thanks for your friendship!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sherry Couto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kat, I love my walks with you at Rockwood park.  You are a special person and I am so thankful for our friendship.  I am looking forward to celebrating your 40th and many more to come.  /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much Love, Laura P]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You braved a blizzard to join my birthday weekend. Not only are you a fantastic friend, but a genuine party-girl & a hot-ticket... truly! Good thing you did not go up in flames whilst dancing at the mantel. And! Brimfield was a delight from dawn to dark!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rebecca Beaton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Any time spent with Kat is special! Unfortunately we do not get to see each other enough but when we do its always a blast. We will have a glass or two or three and just laugh. She is a beautiful person that I am proud to call my friend! Keep praying Kat, go with God ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The Limited at Gulfview Square Mall circa 1991/1992!! Need I say more?? I have fond memories of working with Kat at the 'coolest' store in the mall! I'm so thankful that we have remained friends after all of these years. Happy, Happy Birthday, Kat!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Stephanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I know it's cheesy, but I'll never forget when you won the SigEp Sweetheart pageant!  You were so yourself up there with such grace and self-assurance. I remember thinking, "I hope I have that level of confidence one day."  I was so proud to call you my friend that day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I love you Kitty! XOXO, Jimi ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Kind hearts are the gardens, Kind thoughts are the roots, Kind words are the flowers, Kind deeds are the fruits, Take care of your garden And keep out the weeds, Fill it with sunshine, Kind words and Kind deeds"  /R      Henry Wadsworth Longfellow/R Happy Birthday Kat!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathryn O]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["I was as close to her vagina as any man ever was!"/R/R#Thats40babe #rejuvenation/R/RSt. Augustine 2015 ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Asmus]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 40th to one of my favorite people on the planet. Once we established that undergarments are not optional while sitting on furniture, I knew that I would love you forever!  We've been through so much together and I look forward to making many more fun memories]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ Katie Hawkanson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are one of a kind my friend!  So glad you have come into my life!  From cooking class to now drinking Paloma's...you make the move to Briarcliff 1st Class! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wendy Ahn-Kehoe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are an incredible big sister! My college days would not have been the same without you! Even though I'm older you have always been someone I look up to and admire. Your laugh is infectious. Your beauty is immeasurable, you are amazing in every way! I love you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Coral]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[i can't choose just one. You were my first friend to own and frequently wear a business suit in college; helping you move in Tally and to DC, drunk eating your burned pizzas, Bar Food/Pink Panther (thank goodness for Drew) but most importantly my best friend for 20 yrs.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meredith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have so many fond Kat memories... from makeup shopping in NYC to sharing a bottle of our favorite Prosecco. (The one who's name I can never remember) My new favorite memory is from our recent girls trip to FL. We had a lovely chat that was ULTRA enlightening. Love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Smith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The time I had to negotiate your antique purchases for you after being yelled at by a vendor for making a lowball offer. /Rand.../R...for being there for me after William was born./RHappy Birthday, Kat!/RLots of love,/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Daria Culver]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My fondest memory is listening to you belt out "Who Let The Dogs Out" on the way to Rocky's. You are always a class act!/RHappy Birthday Kat.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Craig "Clumsy" Culver]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Too many memories to mention!  And many more to come for sure!  First playdates with Paige and Campbell, tea parties, so many fun times made memorable by your kindness, inclusiveness, and graciousness!/R /R"A girl should be two things: classy and fabulous" --Coco Chanel]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ Meg Curry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the things I've enjoyed about you Miss Kat is that we both share the ability to speak (and sometimes understand) Spanish when we have had a drink to two!  Another enjoyable thing is that you are a real sweetheart.  Happy Birthday my friend.  Love, Jinx]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jinx ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 40th Kat, welcome to your 40s.  I have so many fun memories together, but probably the most come from the paddle court.  We have had some good laughs and look forward to more to come.  Have a wonderful day, XXOO ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Diane Chapman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We always laugh a lot when we get the Kent crew together, but my favorite memory is when just you, Daria and I went up to Brimfield for the night. While you might not have the tough negotiating skills like Daria, your amazing style and keen eye is undeniable! xoxox]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen Niles]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Oh Kitty Kat!  Most of my favorite times as an adult have been with you. From our wild single days at Four Green Fields to wild family get-togethers in FL and NY...we have been through it together and had so much fun along the way!  Happy b-day my dear friend!  XO! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Catie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To the sorority sister I never had (but definitely needed):/R I  hope that you never learn to navigate Dogwood.  I treasure our walks...your counsel & guidance, your patience & sincerity, your infinite kindness & contagious laugh, your elegance & grace...your friendship.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Mick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[How blessed I was to have Kat as my first regular paddle partner.   A supportive,  competitive, fun and kind person, we had a lot of victories as well as laughs that year.  Many fond memories have followed, and I hope for more to come.  Happy 40th!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Carolyn ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[While the drafts at Yiannis & fine glasses of wine are all part of the picture, it is the fountain Coke runs & conversations that sit at the foundation of this friendship.  I count you as a blessing in this life & wish for many Big Gulp moments over the next 40. Love u!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Appleby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kat - my Southern sister, kindred spirit, party girl with a killer smile. Who else rocks a crock-pot by day and a mantle by night? Love every moment we spend together. The proof is in the pics. Happiest of birthdays on your 40th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura W.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember when Margaret,Katherine's mom told us she was expecting.  I was so excited about becoming an aunt. I saw her for the first time when she was 2 weeks old.  I held her for a long time. She was and still is beautiful inside and out.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah Drane Chapman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My goodness gracious!  One moment I am holding my beautiful baby girl and the next moment she is turning 40.  You have grown into a lovely woman whom I admire, respect and value not just as a daughter but as my friend.  I love you, Katherine]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Kat!! We are so excited to be a part of your special day.  I'm so glad we met when Hudson and Ella were little  and and I was able to convince you to lead  our crazy Girl Scout troop! Looking forward to many more fun years together with the girls! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Tee & Bobby Colangelo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kat you have been so welcoming and loving to both me and Gabriella. I am so happy to have a special friend like you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[DeGasperis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Drew and I were playing in the Half Moon...Dawn was nervous about the dinner, as she really didn't know many people...Even though they just met, Kat treated her like a sister and best friend that night, as she does whenever we see her...Truly a wonderful person!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Eric and Dawn Lebenson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are so many moments that have been special but it makes me laugh to think of the time the four of us were at the bar at Amelia Island and the guys left us because we just had to smoke a cigarette.  That was a good cigarette.  Totally worth it.  Happy 40th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Retha]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always makes me smile remembering our lunches with Eileen and Sharon. As Eileen once told me, "Your life begins at 40!"/R/RHappy Birthday!/RMeg and Pete]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Megan and Peter Ward]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kat, you are one of the most adorable girls that I know.  You are the definition of Southern grace.  You make everyone around you happy, because your happiness is infectious.  I love you to death!  Happy, happy birthday beautiful girl!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pam Bringsjord]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So many good times, many silly & some simple but become special. Karaoke in our basement, yoga poses during a dinner party, being pregnant together (your 1st, my last!) and the special greeting bestowed upon me by your girls when I visited after the Van was born!! XO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ann Marie Cooleen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Katherine was like an older sister to Alison. She always played with Alison when we visited. Katherine was a cheerleader and Alison wanted to be one. During one visit, they practiced cheers in another room. They returned and put on a "Cheers Show". Thank you Katherine. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Don]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Kat! I think it is safe to say we know what are most treasured memory might be!!! (LOL) We have had many good times together through the years and we look forward to many many more!! xoxo/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Beth & Andrew]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kat , the forever trooper, comes to a Giant game with all the guys not long after Van comes into the world, agrees to a dinner stop on Mclean Avenue even though it means using her pump in the car in the parking lot !!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you , Dave Cleary ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There is nothing better than Kat dancing in the Ricciardi Base...  The memory always puts a smile on my face.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[XOXOX Stephanie and Chris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have done amazing things in your 40 years!  But I do get a grin when I come across my copy of the newspaper headline after the high school food fight--"Kat Hase Expelled From School" I love you very much. Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kat~/RWhen you walk into a room, it's your smile and warmth that is the first thing noticed./RThat is only surpassed by your wit, charm, and fabulous sense of humor which makes any gathering a party!!! /RWishing you the happiest of birthdays and cheers to 40!/RLove]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Scott & Erica ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Curing hangovers before they start and then going to my new crash pad in the middle of your formal living room!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Zander]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[After an evening of gaiety at Sleepy Hollow, Drew, Katherine and I were feeling famished. As I was the designated driver, I asked for dinner suggestions. Katherine said, "I want some muthaf$@kin Chalupas." I drove to Taco Bell in Elmsford. We laughed the whole way home.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gavin Flickinger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Katherine,/RYou are amazingly kind, warm and generous and have always been a huge style inspiration to me. You're also incredibly selfless, I'll never forget when Pepe was a puppy and you called your Dad on his behalf and quickly eased my concern.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heidi Taylor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Who knew you would come into my life and continue the southern charm gene. I have loved watching you navigate from the diamond district in NYC to conquering Westchester. You are a special woman, wife, mother and I wish you a very happy 40th birthday.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sharon aka Nana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To a woman that has it all- Beauty, intelligence, compassion, style and class./R It seems you are getting better with age.../RI am so glad to have you as my friend./R  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrea Benza]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kat~ to know you is to love you!!  You are one of the most driven and authentic people I've ever known.  Always up for a good time and the life of the party!  So happy that we've been connecting more lately & share a love of all things Southern! Many rose' cheers to you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday!  Love, Macon ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>