<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2425-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/1/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[neil goodman]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[4115 MENLO DR]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[TUCKER]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[GA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[30084-2226]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sand]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Ann!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Ann Goodman Bignault]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love Neil, Amy & Emma]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Throughout my childhood, Miss Ann never failed to be a kind hearted and positive "second mama".  Whether she was driving us around or giving me all the apple juice I wanted, when I was under her supervision, she made me feel like an honorary Bignault for the day. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Josh Monis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, you are a always there/RTo turn to when i’m blue./RA friend who is beside me,/RIn everything I do./RThough words are never quite enough/RIt's this message that i send,/RI feel so very blessed to have you /RAs a sister and my friend!/RHappy Birthday Ann!/RYou are THE BEST!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your loving brother, Neil]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The thing I like most about Ann Bignault is that she always loves her  daughters.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrew Adkins]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have the best and craziest family and I love being  part of it ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrew Adkins ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, over all the years,tears,kids,walks in the neighborhood,and parties in the driveways..I am so happy to call you my friend! While we may not talk  every day I know if we need each other we are there in a minutes notice.. I know I can always count on you to be there!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you girl! Happy Birthday! Beth]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whenever I see you, Ann, you light up my world!!!! You are a beautiful ray of light. It would be impossible to leave your presence without feeling lifted and loved, no matter how much time has passed!!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tamra Koger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite thing... sharing a pregnancy!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cara Hoffman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My Aunt Annie exudes joy. Her heart is in celebration whenever the family is together, and her excitement is contagious. She's always the first to welcome any newbie into our fold with open arms, and no matter what, you know she genuinely cares. /RI love her dearly.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stephanie Bignault ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Having known Ann since she was in High School, I am in awe of her positive attitude and caring personality.  She remains a example to me of the good in the world.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Bignault]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember one of our first conversations, you told me a friend of yours said you were a yellow because you bring sunshine wherever you go. I always feel that way around you. You are always so sweet, kind, and positive. Like the sun, being around you brightens my day:)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Valerie Bignault]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann has always been the sweetest and most positive person! Tall and skinny which for me... short and stocky was always jealous of! LOL Love you Ann! Happy Birthday!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura (Hickman) George]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is one of the most genuine people I have every known. Nothing fake or pretentious about this lady. If Ann is your friend, she is a true friend, one you can call on anytime. Although we haven't spoken in many years , Ann is a great friend  one i will always remember]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Lance]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There's more than one thing that I like most about Ann. But the one that comes to mind first is the way she is as a Mother.  What a wonderful role model she is! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alice Smith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Annie, /RThank you for always showing me the love, even when I have not been so lovable.  You are the perfect balance of intelligence, a fun personality and a caring heart.  You are a rainbow in my life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Bignault]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Beautiful person inside and out.  Always smiling, friendly, and a joy to be around.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vicki Wampler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann,/R/RHappy Birthday to a dear friend with a contagious joie de vivre!  You are one bubbly, brilliant, benevolent, beautiful  Bignault. All that wrapped up in those amazing curls! I am honored to call you friend.   Have a wonderful birthday!/RLove,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christa Gaddy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Beautiful, fun,kind and thoughtful sister in law,happy birthday.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[lizzette.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Beautiful sweet friend, who loves her family and friends! Lives life to the fullest! She is as Beautiful on the outside as she is on the inside! Happy Birthday! Love you!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Terri Honeycutt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you, Ann, for being a dear supportive friend and confidante all these years. I'll never forget our med school days!  Then marriages, then kids! Blessings to you for all your days. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lisa Hospodar Rawlings, M.D.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann,/RYou are the kind of friend who I want to be friends with for life!  Your beautiful smile and infectious good humor make you always a joy to be with!  I love you my dear friend and hope your birthday is as fabulous as you are!  Much love from all us Stephenses!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Curly hair announcing a bouncy loving personality]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bret sleight]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday! We have been friends through babies, parties in the driveway, moving, and trips to the beach. I have loved every minute and even though we don't see or talk to each other every day- I love that we pick up just like we are together all the time.. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you girl! Happy Birthday! Beth]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is one of those rare people who is as beautiful on the inside as she is on the outside.  Ann brightens up anyone's day just by her presence, a rare quality.  Happy birthday Ann...thanks for being so awesome!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[lisa cohen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Annie/R/RYou are my love and my life.  I am grateful everyday for the blessing of you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jon Bignault ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your joy, excitement, and compassion for our family has always been a bright inspiration to my life as long as I can remember.  The way you express your love so emphatically and without restraint is a most cherished gift and a blessing to us all.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aaron Bignault]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Great role model--courteous, friendly, responsible, high achiever,  wonderful mom and wife, pleasant, competent, and so much more.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Georges and Gloria]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are beautiful on the inside and out! Your smile is contagious! I am blessed beyond measure to call you my friend!! Enjoy your special day!! Love and Hugs to you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kristi Smith ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann has the most beautiful smile and warm heart.  She puts you at ease and makes you feel like you have known her for many years.  She is kind and thoughtful in a graceful way.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cynthia, Sean and Caitlin Kelly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[This Yankee met Ann during our residency at UNC and we have been close ever since. I cherish my time with Ann at the ACC basketball tournament each year when we pick up right where we left off. Ann is the total package. I wish I could see more of her and her family!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellen Bahtiarian (Greg too!)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The thing I love most about Ann is her ability to always find something positive or good or funny in a bleak situation. Ann always finds a way to be happy and to make other people happy. I love her. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jill Thompson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are always so sweet and have such a generous nature. We love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[christina Sikes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's all about the smile! From the first introduction forward, you always made me feel so welcome. Whether you were managing introductions at Amy and Neil's wedding, or dancing with all the girls in the kitchen doing the Thanksgiving dishes, your warmth shines through!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are beautiful inside and out! I have seen you be caring and compassionate with our patients and I love that about you! Sharing about our families with each other has been fun and comforting. You have picked up my spirits on more occasions than I can remember! Love U]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Donna Harris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From the first time I met Ann she has embraced me like family.  She has a way of making everyone feel included, important and loved.  I'm blessed to call her "sis"!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sweet, kind, smart and fun! Genuine inside and out. A true friend to the end!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday My Friend! Debra]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about you, Ann, is your uncanny way of getting all of us (Bignaults) playing games together. The most remarkable event to date was when you miraculously organized a huge family Pictionary game that included both of the Grandmothers! You're awesome!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday! Love you, Michelle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are always so kind and never in a bad mood]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Spencer Wellons]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am in awe of the wonderful mom, and person you are. You are kind, compassionate, beautiful and smart. Your love, and support shows  in everything you say and do. You make this world a better place. Wishing you blessings today and always. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cousin Mia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the best things about my mom is how much she cares. She always worries about me and my sisters and helps us keep track of our lives. She takes care of the little things that people don't always notice or appreciate, but in the end, we are so grateful for her.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah Bignault]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about my mom is how she puts her family and friends' needs before her own.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sophie Bignault]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I love most about my Aunt Ann is that she is very exciting. She also lets me play in her hot tub. I love when she cuddles me and Samantha.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Emma]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Annie!/R/RNo matter what your age, you're always young, active, fun, smart and gorgeous! If it were not for you, Jon would be more like Jim and me... It is always a pleasure to spend time with you and I look forward to seeing you in Mexico Beach. Love YOU!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stephen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always a word of kindness, you bring the fun to any place you are. You have always been family to me and a sister I truly feel blessed to have??]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Another year as passed and you grow more lovely each year~your smile, your charm, your beauty, your winsome ways. Our precious daughter,we are so thankful for all the cherished memories of the past,the sweet moments of the present,and the hope and promise of the future.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ Loving you always, Mommy and Daddy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>