<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2426-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/1/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Jennifer Chung]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[222 East 39th Street]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[14B]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[New York]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[NY]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[10016]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_60]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[SM 2015]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Sobin]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY -]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[June 7 2007/R/RKoo. First time you had sushi.  First time you drank in years. Thanks for asking me out to celebrate my OpHedge anniversary. Best first date ever :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember when you dropped me on my head.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Agravats]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Sobin!! Aside from my parents, you are quite possibly the only other person to call me by my real name and I know how much you enjoy seeing me in a huffy puff. HA!  I especially miss Sunday Footballs at your house and enjoying Jen's home cooked meals!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brittany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Warrior Dash. Beating Sobin by at least 2 mins. and then sending the times to John D. who never lets him live it down.  I am and will always be the champion.  All the late nights hanging in the first Ophedge office were also a lot of fun.  I love you man. Happy Birthday]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[TC]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Best Bet Ever!/R/RDec-14-2014/Rour special moment]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Qi Wang]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Old Man!/Rp.s. you are not getting a check now becuase you got this lovely gift instead.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jared]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember casino night up in Rye Brook and how you were so angry that the IS couldn't catch my Buick?  Weren't you so relieved to see me at the party?  haha good times.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Lin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Swift Du]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Lin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember that time you turned my desk into a house or sent an email to the entire company looking for my watch from my parents for being a good son.  Those were good times.  Enjoy your birthday buddy.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jacob]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[remember when you broke tubie?  it was one of my favorite memories of our wedding, even if tubie was sacrificed for a few laughs and squeals.  thanks for always being a good sport and thinking of amusing things to pass our time! rip little tubie, you are missed! :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[jeannie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[That time we got drunk and you went to get me pajamas, but found me passed out naked in your guest bedroom.../R/R/R...totally didn't happen!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Swong]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We've jumped through fire, swam through ice, jumped from planes, and raged all night. I couldn't think of a better person to have done these with!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Swong]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[- every time we play MJ, and we need a certain tile, mad footsie action under the table <3]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[SteNzo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[- when Sobin and Jen got engaged, Sobin came over to the VPL section and everyone congratulated Sobin, but he quickly corrected them and said they should be congratulating Jen]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ChEnZo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[- the time when Sobin was nice to Alvin, oh wait, that never happened]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[An0nYm0uS (^_~)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[John Lin]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Swift Du]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember that time we were plqying hoops at Suny Purchase and I drove down the lane and dunked on your head?.. I am getting old but that is what I remember.. LOL. Serioulsy though I have still only been to Citi Field once the time you and Jen took Jen and I.. Good Times]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gil]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The representations of Toblerone Island are still intact, if you know what I mean, but much less Enrique and Taylor Swift, unfortunately. Ok, maybe none. Keep workin out hard to be the next Wall St Decathlete so we can celebrate with the best burger in NY, Umami Burger!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Fu]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Every Holiday Party where you make bad decisions with Stefan, because of tequila, and then let me take pictures of it.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leung]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for being there at my 27th birthday (8-13-11)!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leung]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Basketball at Ardsley.  As usual, Sobin got mad at some call and went ballistic!  Usually it's amusing except this time I was the victim of his wrath. He threatened to kill me and I ran for it! He chased me like a mad man around the entire park until he got tired. ;)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joji Varughese]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember constantly beating Sobin over and over in pool./R/R"If I beat you it means nothing, if you beat me your famous"/R/RHappy Birthday Bud!/R/RYour favorite friend,/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Saj]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sobin facts/R/RSobin was bitten by a cobra and after five days of excruciating pain... the cobra died/R/RSobin can kill two stones with one bird./R/RSobin once kicked a horse in the chin. Its descendants today are known as giraffes. /R/RSobin does not sleep; he waits. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Fink family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sobin's calendar goes straight from March 31st to April 2. No one fools Sobin. /R/RIf Sobin was a Spartan in the movie 300, the movie would be called 1./R/RIf Sobin's shoe collection was  Spartan in the movie 300, the movie would be called 32,468 pairs./R/RHappy birthdya bud]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Fink Family 2]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[BAR TACO/RNeed I say more?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Liz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have shared a ton of fun times together but my fav was Miami!  From the Foutainableau pool to eating crabs to dim sum (thanks jen) to LIV, we had an awesome time like we always do with you guys.  Hope you have an amazing birthday & hope we share many more memories!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Raquel Gozzi aka "Rocky"]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[That time we cruised through SF - top down, heat on! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steffi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[That time you made me crawl through mud after enduring the crossfit pit of shame...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steffi ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[That time I beat you in MJ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steffi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are my brother from another mother and I knew you when you were just a super skinny little kid - I'll never forget the day I got you in trouble for skipping school with Fahad and your mom called the house - LOL! Love you tons. Have a great bday! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Arsh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sobin, you inspire me.../Rto work out.../Rwell, in person.../Rand only when Jen's with me. /R/R#DRpersonaltraining/R#imissyourface/R#toasttoanotheryearwiser ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joyce]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From not drinking alcohol 2 handing out shots like theres no tmrw...I will always rmbr when you.... Haha!! Did you think I was gonna say the first time you told me u loved Jen?! No that's not it its when you shaved finks hair into a Mohawk in the men's bathroom!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tess]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thankful to have Sobin be a part of Fahads life for such a long time it's the meaning of a true friendship. We also got to meet wonderful Jen.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amirah and Emaan Sultan ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We are always grateful that your diet is 90% protein shakes. There is more for us when Jen cooks!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rich and Del]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're so great at your job! Keep at it - as long as it keeps Jen close by. =)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Del]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday SOBIN. I have known you now 7 years and you're still smiling wtf. JK.  All the best on your special day.  You're definitely special...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Skates]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Sobinsss.../R/RI am very lucky for over the last 10 years to have such an AMAZING great friend. I don't have one special memory; I have many and hope for another 10 years of great memories. Us Cancers have to stick together. Have a GREAT birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Tinasss... xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Las Vegas September 2007/R/ROur very first trip together. Mandalay Bay wave pool. Grand Canyon helicopter champagne picnic. Jet skiing in Hoover Dam. Cirque du Soleil Ka. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JCM]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jamaica August 2008/R/RSurprise trip for my birthday. RIU Ocho Rios. Pit stop in Charlotte (hurricane). Jamaican beef patties & pina coladas. Friendly locals on the beach...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Thank you!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Vermont February 2008/R/RKillington Grand Resort Hotel. The best crispy waffles with choc syrup from Waffle Cabin. Beginners ski class (thanks for the help when I fell into the snow, NOT!) Heated outdoor pool. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JCM]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maui December 2008/R/RSeattle Space Needle. Westin Maui Resort & Spa. Watching whales at breakfast. Chocolate creme brulee. Huge water slide. Scary foggy rainy Maui Downhill sunrise bike tour. Snorkeling on the Gemini. Parasailing. "Anniversary" dinner at Lahaina Grill.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JCM]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thursday june 25th. I will always remember that day.  You are the master at bringing everyone closer and enjoying life. Glad i met you buddy. Enjoy your bday.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[K jackson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The first time I really got to know Sobin was at #DRinDR. We literally had to take an "Ice Cold Plunge" to get to know one another. Our spouses were first worried about how it would all turn out, but nowadays they make fun of the bromance! Happy Birthday Sobin!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelvin Wong]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I think about the laughs we had together at "The Nash". You and Jen are ridiculously good at reading one another's minds in Cards Against Humanity - so much so that it's almost as if you're cheating.../RHappy Birthday, Sobin!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura Wong]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[San Francisco June 2008/R/RLe Meridien. The longest bike ride EVER. Segways. Dinner in Sausalito watching SF disappear behind the fog. Losing sideview mirror (good job). Alcatraz. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JCM]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[DisneyWorld December 2009/R/RContemporary Resort. Parades every day and fireworks every night. Waiting in line with all the little kids to take pictures with the Up! characters. 3D glasses for almost every ride. Tower of Terror! Next time, Harry Potter Land!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JCM]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[May 2010/R/RWill you marry me?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[wubs]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aruba August 2011/R/RHoneymoon!! /RWestin Resort & Casino]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JCM]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[September 2012/R/RMy surprise 30th birthday party at Bowlmor Lanes. Moments like these remind me how lucky I am. Thanks for this amazing memory I will never forget.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[EUROTRIP April 2014/R/ROur first of many (hopefully) trips to Europe!  London, Paris, Amsterdam, Dublin. Remember to check our ATM card expiration date next time...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JCM]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[2013/R/RAruba back again cant get enough/R#DRinDR mamajuanas!/RTurks & Caicos - tubie video]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JCM]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Charlotte June 2015/R/RSkydive! Carolina. Can't believe we jumped out of an airplane at 14,000 ft! Unforgettable...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JCM]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[October 2012/R/RSensation White. When we're old and responsible.  Look back on this and remember we used to party like rockstars.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JCM]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[2007/R/RYou can stand under my umbrella/RNights out in Doral and White Plains/RBig Apple smoothie & car wash bets/RThanks for always ordering me lunch when I came to work late/RRoses and Rhymes]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[All grown up and quite the smarty/R35 years young and still the life of the party/RTake a look back at where you've been/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sobin, do you remember when...]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Two dozen doughnuts./R/ROne for me, one for Jen,/Rone for Janet.../Rand 21 for Sobin. :) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kalen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When it was 65 degrees at a Panthers game... /Rin December./R/R(Plus one for Charlotte)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kalen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>