<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2438-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/1/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Leigh Ann Klee]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[1301 Carolina Street]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Greensboro]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[NC]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[27401]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_60]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sand]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[We LOVE Bonnie]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Bonnie McElveen-Hunter]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[from a few admirers]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The past (almost) 18 years have been filled with the most amazing learning opportunities and experiences which have far surpassed any of my dreams.  I am so thankful to be part of your life and part of the Pace family!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leigh Ann ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Perfection is unattainable, /Rbut in the pursuit of perfection, /Ryou will Catch Excellence!"/R(NOTE:  Addendum 23.5b:  The above does not apply to one/RMary B. (Bonnie) McElveen-Hunter who in /RALL pursuits...achieves "perfection" as well as "catches excellence")]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday!!    Kristi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aside from the gratitude I feel toward you and the pleasure I take from my experience at Pace as a member of your leadership team, I am grateful for the inspiration and example you provide as a woman business leader for my teen daughters.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dana Adams]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One VERY special moment was underneath a most brillian star filled night in the desert of Chad where Bonnie led the elderly French-only speaking President of the Chadian Red Cross through multiple dances to the music of Bob Marley and The Beach Boys.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Meltzer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the woman whose exercise, diet, drive and beauty defy Mother Nature.  Here's to that box in Bozeman City!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Meltzer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Madame Chair:  Serving on your kitchen cabinet were some of the best times I have had in my 25+ years of volunteering with the American Red Cross. The ARC is blessed to have you serving as our Chairman.  Many more happy and healthy birthdays./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Fearless Pereles]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There's not enough room for a top ten, but here are the top 5 things you've taught me:/R1. Be kind to and treat everyone with respect./R2. Take time to do things you don't have time for./R3. Always be early./R4. Choose a glass of wine over a cookie./R5. Eat your veggies!/Rxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer Hawkins]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love the example Bonnie has set for so many, I watched from afar and feel great to be part of what she built -- and, its also cool that I remembered meeting her mom when I was a kid. I think Bonnie is quick to the punch, gets things fast and love her taste and style!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gordon Locke]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I know, from your actions, that this must be one of your favorite quotes from one of your favorite people: "We make a living by what we get, but we make a life by what we give"./RWinston Churchill/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Craig]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When you walk into a room, light emanates from your smile, style and grace./RYou enrich the lives of all who are blessed to know you./RThe world is truly a better place because of you!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tami Longaberger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bonnie flew to Geneva on literally an hour's notice, demonstrating to me that honor, commitment and sacrifice for the right cause, not to mention a loyal friendship, help guide her actions everyday. Happy Birthday to an exemplary leader and to an awfully big heart. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Carr]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have been a special person in my life, through the good times/R& the bad , you were always there with help & encouragement, &/RI will never forget those times. May you have a wounderful Birthday & many more to come my best to you. Chairman of the /RBoard At PACE ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[DAVIS Dixon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bonnie's grace and kindness are special gifts that enrich the lives of everyone she touches.  Her optimism, humor, generous nature, and spirituality have taught me to be a better person.  I feel deeply blessed to have Bonnie in my life; I wish her a very happy Birthday.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gail McGovern]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When in need of inspiration or encouragement we all turn to Bonnie. There is no other person in this world with her unique combination of intelligenge, faith and energy. Her love, so generously, shared, and her great sense of humour, never fails to lift our spirits.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Titta, Maria and Sarah Brunow]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite:  When you surprised us at our wedding.  Any time I need to explain what kind of person you are I always tell that story.  Huge responsibilities but still time for people in your life.  And our guests at your table still remember you by name 16 years later!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There is not a single thing I like most about Bonnie, there are many that operate together to make her a rare gem.  She is kind, funny, generous, culturally and business savy, and full of wisdom.  A rare find in one person.  Grateful to be among her friends.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cathy and Scott Stanley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I feel it is one of my most precious gifts to call you "friend". You have the most positive attitude and willingly take on a challenge with class. Your deep faith shows in your every movement. I wish you much happiness and look forward to working with you in the future.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[You are the best!-      Jim Melvin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Bonnie! Thank you for all your support over the years, both for me professionally and personally for my family. You have made Pace and Greensboro a wonderful, welcoming, experience for all of us. It means the world.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin, Kathy and the Briody Girls]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you Bonnie for the kindness and friendship you have shown my family over the years ...  and for allowing us to be "adopted" members of your family.  Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Mitchell Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Beautiful, brilliant, kind and generous!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda Amos Smith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I love about Bonnie is her modesty about all her accomplishments she is highly intelligent generous gracious beautiful inside and out she embraces love and a true gift from God she took wonderful care of her mother and of Bynum we are so blessed to know her]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marty Walter Michael frances]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You bring sunshine wherever you go. You are/Rthe most wonderful, adorable friend. Thank you for all the happy times we have shared--the trips,the laughs, and such exciting and memorable festive moments. Wishing you many, many more Happy Birthdays.  Hugs]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lucky Roosevelt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Fond memories exist of the fabulous Hong Kong birthday celebration and so many other special times together. One of the many blessings of our friendship is being "other mother" to Bynum Jr.  Thank you for being such a loving, generous and inspiring 'adopted sister'! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Barbara ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[" When you are full of Joy, you move faster & want to go about doing good to everyone".  /RThis explains your blazing speed!  You do so much for everyone & I'm profoundly thankful to have been part of your "pit crew" at Pace.  Wishing you much continued happiness & JOY!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday!  Monica ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A hail Mary meeting in Detroit almost 6 years ago, to try to save the troubled ACG business. We met our clients at a restaurant where Bonnie re-arranged tables, went into the kitchen to order broccoli for everyone and won their hearts and a second chance with a new team]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leslie Dunne Ketner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have empowered women to become anything they want to be in life!! I for one can attest to this!! You have been my mentor, my dear friend and the sister I never had./R  (...continued on next card)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Melanie Sabelhaus]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am blessed you entered my life and inspired me to shoot for the stars and make a big and bold difference in this world.  For this I am forever grateful!!/RWith great love and appreciation!/RHappy Birthday beautiful lady.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[BFF's forever, Melanie Sabelhaus]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have been with Pace for almost 20 years -starting with EW and then upstairs. There have been lots of changes but I've enjoyed every minute and feel priviliged to work here.It's a wonderful company thanks to your devotion and leadership. Thank you. Happy Birthday !!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Martha Leonard]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bear Bonnie:/RIt has been a good while since I called you a "rookie." I have enjoyed the time we have spent working together, the trips, and especially the down time. But, most of all, I cherish our friendship! I would not trade it for anything!!!!! Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Buzz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I came to Greensboro 8 years ago looking for a place where I could build a career and be part of a community. You have made both possible, and for that I will always be grateful. Thank you for leading by example and inspiring me to reach my full potential. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah Allen Nabors]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Quite simply you are a gift from God to His people and your success is His gift to you to help with that work.  Your friendship is a joy to me.  Happy birthday dear Bonnie.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shirley Spears]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have a most unique gift in tackling tough issues and bringing opposing sides together in harmony and love. It is amazing to watch. You lift people up. And there is always something interesting going on in your life. I cherish our friendship.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elaine Lyerly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bonnie - 270 characters is not enough space to share all we have experienced over the past 16 years. You are a great and true friend. You are abundantly blessed and you bless abundantly. Happy Birthday. May your best be yet to come! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stewart McLaurin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a true inspiration and have a heart of gold. Thank you for all you do for my family and I. You make me strive to be a better person each day. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dean Nickles]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Bonnie.  We are still in France, but wanted to let you know that our thoughts are with you on this special day. You have made a difference in the lives of many and continue to do so in your own very special way.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John, Christa, Madeline,John Thomas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember vividly an EMF concert in summer 2014 when you delivered a lovely speech about your mother, and said at the end “… and call your mother.” I called my mother later to tell her I loved her and thank you for your reminder to honor and cherish those we love.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathleen Kelley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always inspire me to reach higher!  I am forever grateful for your encouragement and leadership, during both good and challenging times. /RYou set an amazing personal example of service to others, demonstrating the joy—and the significance—of giving back!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jaci Ponzoni]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Bonnie - Thank you for always, always, always finding ways to empower women. Not only do you"lean in," you "lift up" and bring others with you on the journey. /R/RHappiest of Happy Birthdays! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Loads of love, Wendi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have great compassion for people! You are always willing to give back to the community and promote education. You have inspired me with your generosity to others. I hope you have a very Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[LaDonna Greeson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ w There is nothing like sharing your faith wit ha faithful friend - in prayer and song. In moments of sheer delight we often find ourselves breaking into song- a constant and beautiful reminder that "all is well with my soul." That is the tie that binds us.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eric L. Motley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Two pieces of advice I will take with me forever: we need to reach out and care for the least, the last, and the lost. The other: don't settle for being a thermometer. Be a thermostat.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dan Dooley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When people ask me about working for Pace, inevitably I tell them about working for you. It's rare that a company and personality are so intertwined--and it's your compassion, drive and encouragement that make this such a wonderful place to work.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gordon Bass]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Objective #1 in developing the new Pace Creative Presentation, /Rdefine “What Differentiates Us.” /R/RBonnie, you do. /RYou are the reason Pace is better and it’s an honor having the opportunity to learn from and work with you…]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Thank You, Happy Birthday, Jaimey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I cannot count the ways that Bonnie has enriched my life.  Her brilliance, beauty and kindness enchants kings and orphans alike.  Those of us in the middle stand in awe of the woman and the privilege of being recipients of her generosity of spirit.  I love you Bonnie!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Mochary]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[And of course, /Rit a great pleasure knowing /Rwe both have a connection /Rto Brown’s BBQ…]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Jaimey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your hair]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bynum Hunter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Little did I know on the road to ancient Skillidou and Hydra that I would be travelling with an ambassador and the Chairman of the American Red Cross or I would not have #@$!#edwhen she was late,even though I was with amazin Grace,and she was with that other guy]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Honorable W Eugene Johnston III]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Bonnie.../RWe have shared laughter and tears...everything from blizzards in DC to the heat of Haiti..but the best thing we share is the most amazing friendship that I will cherish always....HAPPY BIRTHDAY to my Soul Sister!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Keyes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chapter 65!!! - 19 yrs have given me  memories of the generosity, kindness, forgiveness of others, leadership & your incredible business savvy that is majic!  You have impacted many lives, especially mine. I thank you for believing in me & the adventures we have shared.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With Love, Gail Casper]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bonnie returned from the kitchen, cappuccino in hand, wearing bell-bottoms. She was unaware of the ruckus left in her wake. "Are those jeans?" they gasped. I inquired about her #OOTD (Outfit of the Day). She said, "Of course I wear jeans. These are by Seven!" #TrueStory]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[HBD! From Heather]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I didn't need to hunt after my Bonnie came into my life, a mutual friend did that for me.  From the moment we met, we hopped from one city to another.  It did not matter whether it was London, Moscow, Monaco, Paris or LA, anywhere with Bonnie is a heavenly experience!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[(continued...)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm blessed to hop with my Bonnie in any terrain!/R                                 /R/RLovingly,/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Madeleine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love Bonnie for MANY reasons and here are but a few: /R- she is devoted to her family as evidenced by the way she cared for her aging mother for many years /R- her faith inspires others to follow her example]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[(continued...)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My Sister, my Best Friend,  /RYou are Joy without End./RMay your birthday be/Rthe best it's ever been./RAnd may you feel the Love/Rcoming down from Above.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Tweed]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[- her business acumen is self evident and much admired/R- her devotion to the USA makes us proud to know her/R- and, finally, because of space limitation, we love her for remembering her friends - in our case for helping us sell our business during difficult times./RLove,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David & Joann Grimes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[SISTER/RSophisticated/RIntelligent/RSpirited/RTerrific/RElegant/RRare]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday!  Tweed]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[With the "can't" obstacle removed, Madeline stepped forward with challenge after challenge, and you never flinched.  Yes, you had further encouragement by your quiet, decorated pilot Dad who had a wing totally surprising our Cold War opposition.  Warmest wishes!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With much admiration    Buren & Tom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the things that I admire most about Bonnie is how she finds true joy in giving to others.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen Johnson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>