<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2440-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/2/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Chandler LoCascio]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[5404 West 149th Place]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[#2]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Hawthorne]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[CA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[90250]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[scarlet]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[For when you need a reminder]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Renee LoCascio]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Chandler]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom, you inspire me every day, and have helped me become the person I will be today and into the future. I can only hope to be as caring, patient, and loving as you are. I'll love you forever; I'll like you for always; as long as I'm living my mommy you'll be. xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chandler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are an enjoyable person to be around.  Time spent with you is priceless.  Even though we met by a special circumstance, I am happy to have you in my life.  Happy Birthday my dear friend! Be always healthy, happy and of course wealthy!  I hug you and kiss you!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anna Haroutunian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have always loved that Renee is a TRUE Friend and I can always count on her positive, can do attitude...I truly enjoy her company and I am a better person because of her friendship. Happy Birthday my long-time friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robbie Ruiz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Renee is that she always has a smile on her face and she always says....."Its ALL good".  She's been a blessing to have in my life and I consider her a wonderful friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With Love, Dee Dee Turpin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you style, independence and friendship.  Happy Birthday.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Holly Dutton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I Love Renee!  She is so thoughtful and a really good friend about staying in touch.   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy Vicars]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the many things I like about Renee is... Her positivity. I'm always more peaceful after our conversations. I love how, in any situation, whether it's frustrating, scary, or sad, Renee helps me see the bigger picture and how I will grow from it.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christine Rawson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Her shoes! /RHer handbags!/RI love Renee's taste /Rand sense of style. /R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rebecca Rawson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Renee is witty, charming, kind, supportive and a dear friend to me and many others.  In short, I love her and cherish our friendship.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Beautiful inside and out, smart but not arrogant, a wonderful friend! You are loved and respected by all who know you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paddy Reynolds]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It would be imposable to say only ONE thing.  There is so much I love about this Woman.  Her kindness, understanding, work ethic, family values, sense of humor, loyalty are just a few. She is however quite selfish! She won't give me my cat!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer Hews]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[P. Renee/R/RPositive/RResponsible/REnergetic/RNegotiator/RExtraordinary/RExtra Special/R/RMy Sister ! My Mentor !/RI Love You !/RBeckie ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Beckie ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What an amazing role model you have been for our daughter....and a loving and caring wife/friend to me for all of these years.     /R/RHappy Birthday Renee!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I love most about you is they way you make me smile when I've had a bad day.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chandler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I love most about you is your amazing ability to come up with creative dinners every night ;)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chandler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your relentless pursuit of a healthy lifestyle inspires us.  Your big heart inspires concern for all you encounter.  You are devoted to your loving daughter as well as those two feisty felines who rule the household.  Surely happiness will follow you in the future.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael Russell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whew, were does one begin when writing about one of the most dear and influential people in your life.  Your strength has always been top of the list (even above style & smarts) of what I admire about you.     Proud to be your friend. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[love you always, Gina Harpur ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(Card #2) /RSpeaking of style... you looked way hotter than me in Dittos!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[your jealous friend, Gina Harpur]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You challenge me to be my best self everyday, and you are always there to support me when I need it. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo Chandler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are there to pick me up when I fall, as well as when I succeed. You support me unconditionally, and that inspires me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chandler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No matter how much I hate to say it, you have taught me that "This too, shall pass." This has been one of the most important reminders to myself on a day to day basis.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chandler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Renee, Happy Birthday to a beautiful lady who has charm, grace, intelligence, drive and is a pleasure to be with. I hope this is your best year yet and that you enjoy your birthday with all your loved ones. I am honored to be your friend,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Adrienne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Renee is a kind and generous friend.  She is always there to listen without judgment.  I treasure our friendship and what a beautiful person she is, inside and out.  Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carrie Rognlien]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[  The one thing I like most about Renee is everything. As a young girl you knew what you wanted and you went for it and I think the results are amazing. You have very high standards and keep them. The daughter you raised is fantastic! The life you live says it all. Dad]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Hembree]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You can make me laugh even when we are 3,000 miles apart. xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chandler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The Renee Cocktail:/R3 cups of Sweetness/R1 tsp of Kindness/R2 Tsp Elegance & Good Taste/R1 cup of Intellect/R2 cups of Playfulness/R1 1/2 of Flirtation/R1 tsp Boldness/R6 oz. of Courage/RAdd a heaping of Laughter/RBlend with ice and sip slowly on the beach..(smile)/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[A Mixologist]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Renee understands the power of a good question:/R/R"Do you want me to listen, or do you want my advice?"/R/R"Do you want to be happy, or do you want to be right?"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Keith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You allow everything in life to take place and be a part of life but not get hung up on things and let them clog your heart.  You have chosen to be happy, and have enriched the lives of those of us fortunate enough to know you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[A Casual Observer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're awed by nature and some of your best days are those spent outdoors.  You can see the best in things and appreciate the details in nature; from a changing sunset, to the color of the sea, to the fragrance of a flower. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Winnedumah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Although sometimes you forget this is my house, you always sit with me on the stairs to purr and make me feel like the queen I deserve to be. In the mornings we always purr, which is my favorite purr of the day. You are loving and you care that my water glass stays full]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[M]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love the times when I get to sit in your lap and sneak my paws in between your thighs when you nap. I love that you make me feel safe when I am scared. I love that you feed me mountains of tuna. And I especially love it when you feed me before 6pm. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Q]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["You is kind. You is smart. You is important." - The Help/RYou are all of these in their truest form./RI love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chandler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The Renee Cake/R1.5 cups unconditional love/R2 cups sweetness/R4 Tbsp laughs/R1 tsp sass/R2 Tbsp determination/RFrost with buckets of chocolate frosting./RSit back. Cut a piece. Smile.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chandler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>