<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2443-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/3/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[RENEE GOSIK]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[302 ST ANDREWS PL]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[BLUE BELL]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19422]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_60]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Live - Laugh - Love]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Walter and Marie]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[We Are Family]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I loved going to West Point Park every summer. The best part was riding the train past our picnic tables and waving to you both - wondering why the heck all the grownups were just hanging around the picnic tables all day instead of riding the rides with us!  Now I know.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Renee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember coming home from getting my engagement ring, mom and dad were in the kitchen and dad turned and said it would never last, 22 years later.....love you dad and mom]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have learned from Mom and Dad that making MEMORIES is the most important thing in life.  The Gosik's do this best by keeping TRADITIONS.  Thanksgiving and Christmas Eve are most treasured.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I was nervous to meet the entire family at Brandon's graduation party.  Upon being introduced to the two of you, I was instantly put at ease.  You treated me like family from day one, and I am so lucky to have you in my life!  You are an inspiration, I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Flip Cup Partner, Katie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Loved our family vacations in wildwood.  Remember the Dolphin restaurant, and going by ourselves to buy penny candy at corner store.  Shucking crabs on the rooftop, and meeting the Canadians.  We have continued that tradition with our family in the outer banks.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Donna]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love that Mondays  are my family prayer day.  I will never forget to stop and smell the roses!  Congratulations on 60years of being together!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Donna]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Over the years I've learned that friends may come and go but family is forever, even a family full of goobers!  I believe my love of tradition comes from both of you. Focusing on a strong marriage and family are just one of your many traditions that I will carry on!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Debi (ha! I spelled it the old way)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Christmas Eve & Day, Memorial Day Parades, Lion's Lake, Wildwood (the Dolphin restaurant) Willow Grove park, Easter dresses, Thanksgiving. Eaton Yale & Town softball games, the Pigeon races.... All Because Two People Fell In Love~  PTL for putting you two together. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All my love! Debbie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks Mom and Dad for being there for us every step of the way.  You always had our back and would be there for us no matter what. The love that you two have for each other reminds me every day of just how lucky I am to have your both as my parents.  Love you both!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Renee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wow, what did I learn from you guys in the 34 years I've  known you? 'The cabbage patch' is actually the Acme parking lot...porch swings are awesome...porcelain cats can live a long time on the roof..I can kick everyone's *^*# at horseshoes...and that you are inspiring!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your favorite, Dave]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Resilience! A lot of water has passed under the bridge! Good times, tough times, family brings you through!  You guys are great,&God has blessed you greatly!! Congrats on 60 years of wedded bliss!! (hey, I didn't know meatballs could be used as a currency...just sayin')]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your favorite, Dave, again!!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you both for that you have done for my family, hope we can be as half as good parents to our two boys as you are to us. /R/RLOVE YOU BOTH]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memories are of when Luke and I were little, and our routine when we would come over would be breakfast, food shopping, poker, lunch, then TV. Every day for the whole summer and made many memories doing so! Love you guys!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have so many memories together, but one thing I will always carry with me is that we all get together for every holiday as a family, where most families don't, and it all started because of you guys, and that is something all of us can remember. The "Gosik" holidays.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I've been lucky enough to spend over 25 years with you guys.  I even had time to smash into Walt's car. We've had a lot of laughs with more to come. Walt and Marie. 60 years together and still like kids with each other.  You've made a great life for so/R many. Thanks]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wheels aka the other Chris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Pop-pop & Grandmom - /R/RHappy Anniversary! I can't imagine being together with a boy as long as you two have been together haha. The love you two show for each other is inspiring & I pray one day I will find someone to make me as happy as you two make each other! LOVE U!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathryn ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite memories of you two (and the family) is all of us together at the mountain houses... the love and fun times shared during those years was priceless! I always enjoyed making up dances to songs to impress all the grownups (especially you two!) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathryn ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You taught us that family is paramount & a happy marriage = a happy family unit. We are eternally grateful for your love lessons that we've absorbed over the years from catching you lovingly gaze into each other's eyes to stealing kisses between rolling meatballs! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love The Swindells Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary Pops & Gigi! Rylan said he loves when Gigi "mints" (knits/crochets) him his slippers & Aiden said he loves swinging on your back porch swing! I think you can safely say we all have our own love story with that porch swing!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Ace & Duce Swindells ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for sharing your recipe for a delicious marriage through the years! Here's to 60 more years!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love The Swindells Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ "Learn a little laugh a lot" ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Luke ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memory is when nick and I would come over in the summer and weven would all watch The Price is Right and then we would all play cards made so many memories playing cards love you guys ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Luke ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Pop-Pop and Grandmom, Congratulations on 60 wonderful years of marriage! I don't think there is a better family in the area that compares to us Gosik's, and it is all because of you two! Thank you for believing in us and loving us like no other! You truly are the best!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matthew ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memory with Pop-Pop was when my parents were in Paris and you took me to my confirmation and then baseball game after. I hit 2 home runs that game with you there. I look back on that all the time and still haven't had a game I have been more proud to play in]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matthew ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So many memories so I will share a few.  /R/RWhen going to college I remember and greatly appreciated Mom making those famous meatballs for me and my roommates. This was an example of the family values, of caring for each other, that you taught me as I grew to a man]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laird]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My (not so clear) but favorite memory with Grandmom is when we were up at the mountain house and we would help you make your famous meatballs. I don't remember it, but I watched the home videos and I would challenge anyone to find a happier kid in the world at the time!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matthew ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One other memory was at sky top in the poconoes when that judge and family "crashed" our New Year's Eve dinner. As a family we all pulled it off causing the Judge to remark what a wonderful family.  I thought later that the truly rich man at that table was dad. Thx dad]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laird ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memory of spending time with you guys is from when I was a little girl and we were in the Poconoes. I used to wake up early and the three of us would play cards:) love you guys! Thanks for the memories!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lauren]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[GG & Pops,/RWe cherish the memory when we visited you at your house. You gave us a piece of your treasured volcano. Thank you!! We love you so much!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Austin & Tyler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Without your love, I would have never been able to accomplish the things in my life that I have.  No matter how tough the situation is, I am comforted by knowing that I can always wiggle my way in between you as I did on our wrap around couch wearing my GREEN HOUSE COAT]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Memory lane:  watching together moon landing, Iran Hostage Crisis, Chitty Chitty Bang Bang, Happy Days, Vietnam Vets come home, All in the Family, Andy Griffith,Rowan&Martis laugh In,World at War,Sundays Eagles games, March Madness("gotta move-whoo that was tough"),Lucy]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Ramblers/Pigeon Club & race day w/ grand pop, ND/Penn State/ChristmasEves/GrandMom Yancer/Uncle Nick Pool parties/ Breakfast for Bensalem friends/WildWood & the happy drives down(Nixon resigning) sad drives home/Waiting dads return from SuperBowls/MOM'S amazing meals!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ "Mom and Dad, I fell in love with a girl that is originally from Harrisburg." "Oh, her parents still live there? Do they drive?Son, marry that girl, I'll have someone to drive my pigeons west for training." *The conspiracy theory behind why Mark was allowed to marry me]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Donna Jean]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my fondest memories was a Sunday at your house when you told me I could call you mom and dad...it was a day I will never forget. You two have shown all of us, by example, what true love and commitment are all about. Cheers to both of you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Donna Jean]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A Saturday morning October, 1987. Dad in the living room, Mom in kitchen: Dad>/R"So you met a girl last night and your not taking her out tonight?" If you don't, you have one month to move out. Me>" You're not serious, right?" Dad>"I'm not kidding boy!"/RAnd so it began..]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark and Donna Jean   est 3/11/1989]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's the Circle of Life/RAnd it moves us all/RThrough despair and hope/RThrough faith and love/RTill we find our place/ROn the path unwinding/RIn the Circle/RThe Circle of Life/R   You, Walt and Marie, without any and all doubt, are our Mufasas!!/R           /R  /R  /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Donna  Mark Chris Kathryn Matt ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have been in the company of many wealthy people in my life and I have come to realize that you, mom and dad, are by far the wealthiest of them all! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark   ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I still remember to this day asking "Paintin' Pop-Pop" to throw me pitches in the backyard and you telling me you couldn't because "you have a bone in your knee." Hopefully over the years I havent asked you to many questions like the day I did down our basement...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christopher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Grandmom, the one memory that I have that will always stick with me is helping you make meatballs at the mountains. And then getting home from a long day of skiing and wearing "Paintin Grandmom's" slippers to keep our feet warm at night.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christopher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 60th Anniversary! There aren't enough cards in here to write down how many memories I have from growing up. From holidays, vacations, parties, and games of cards, the memories I have with you will last a lifetime. I love you so much!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christopher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember showing Mom my first pair of  slippers that I crocheted for Mark. They were so big they could have fit the Jolly Green Giant. Mom just laughed, and showed me how to properly size them. Now, every new friend gets Mom's slippers, she is our Goodwill Ambassador.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Donna Jean ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["The roots of a family tree begins with the love of two hearts." I have always been so grateful to have this big, goober, Gosik family. We are a very special bunch and we are SO blessed. Thank you for starting it all. Congrats on 60 years. Here's to many, many more!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brittany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Meatballs, horseshoes,  "woman!", slippers, whirl pools, Easter, pigeons, Christmas Eve & more! You have taught me EVERYTHING about the true meaning of tradition and family. Your love is so inspiring! "I have found the one whom my soul loves." Song of Soloman 3:4]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brittany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tradition is a practiced art that you have mastered in this family. By your example, we have learned the importance of family and how our traditions have strengthened the bond that is our family. No words can describe how much you've done for us and generations to come!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ashley ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite memories growing up will always be how loving and affectionate my grandparents always were- it never mattered who was watching, their love is pure!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ashley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Some of the best memories I have are of all of us sitting around in the sun room on Easter Sunday talking and laughing and eating a ton of kielbasi and deviled eggs. I also loved playing in the pool, jumping on the trampoline, and going to see the exotic pigeons. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Brandon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You two are seriously an inspiration to us all. It takes a special kind of love to last for 60 years together. It is amazing to see all that you have built over the years. One can only wish to have all the successes that you two have enjoyed. I love you both!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brandon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Grandmom and Grandpop-/R/RCongratulations on 60 years! so many fond old memories of parades, whirl/wave pools, Christmases and Easters. Lots of new ones too- hayrides and drinking games and visiting our mountain home. Been a blast, keep it coming! Love you both!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Brian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dad some of my best memories was hanging out with you and Chicken grandpop going to the pigeon club, and on race day, and being called "shadow" by grandpop./R/RMom I can still remember playing rummy and having tea with you and grandmom Yancer, also doing whirlpools.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jay - your favorite son]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Life Isn't About Waiting For The Storm To Pass - /RIt's About Learning To Dance In The Rain]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Here's to Making More Memories]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>