<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2452-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/6/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Rachel Rabinowitz]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[35 East 35th Street]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[Apt 12E]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[New York]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[NY]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[10016]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[scarlet]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Mom's Birthday Gift]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Janis Rabinowitz]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Rachel and Steph]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I don't even know where to begin because you have been there for every important moment in my life. Thank you for always being there to talk to on all of my walks around the city and for being the best mom in the world. I love you soooooo much!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rachel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We feel so lucky to have you as part of our lives... golf,canasta, food and holidays...You are a friend who feels like family. You are honest and loyal..you understand what it is to be a true friend. Happy Special Birthday to a VERY Special Friend. Much Love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marc and Debbie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am so happy that we became so close this year.  Your friendship means alot to me and you truly are a warm and loving person who always sees the best in everyone.  I wish for you the happiest of birthdays and hope to share many more wonderful moments with your family!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellen Kushel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our friendship started in Casa de Campo over 20 years ago!! from there its been a beautiful ride...every moment shared with you is a special one.  You are a wonderful friend and confidant.  Wishing you the Happiest of Birthdays and everything wonderful in Life./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gail Kelsey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[First time playing golf with The Birthday Girl and she wedged a 90 yard shot straight into the hole. We jumped up and down and celebrated like we had known each other forever - and we still do!!!! So glad I could share this special occasion with you!!  Much Love, Terri]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Terri Katz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The four of us in Capri touring the blue grotto.  15 years of unmeasurable  laughs. We jumped in for a swim. Joel's  blood curdling screams came fast and furious. Medusa bite. Janis and I got out if that water so fast.  Joel had a nice bite but we still had a great day ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Didi and howie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[55+ years of friendship, one moment? /RSo many moments lots of laughing, some tears and wonderful memories...as kids;  day camp (hotshots at the Y), teen camp, your father in the middle of 75th; adulthood; families sunrises&sunsets. /RLots of history and lots of love/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anita]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[How do I begin to tell the story of Janis Rabinowitz. It started it in Club Med a long long time ago. We've shared so many good times sad times and created so many memories together. Everything she does will All her heart. A great friend, better cook, and SPECIAL person]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Debbie Klein]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[   1 OF 3/RSUNG TO THE MELODY OF NY, NY/R/RWe really miss you/RSince you’ve moved away/RYou’re blessed with many visitors/RJanis ……..Janis/R/RYou’re one of a kind/RSay what’s on your mind/RI’m to blessed to have you as my friend/RJanis ……..Janis]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[SUSAN MACK]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[2 of 3/RYou like to wake up in a city where you can play golf/RYou’ve found so many new friends (none like Susan and Ralph)/R/RThis song is to say/RHave a Happy Birthday/RIts great to have you here for the /RMonth of July/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Part 2 of 3]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[3 of 3/RYou’ll make time to  fit in cards, golf , tennis /RAnd friends galore/R/RHAPPY BIRTHDAY JANIS /RA special  friend I adore!!!/R/RWITH LOVE AND HUGS/R/R(PS find NY NY on YOUTUBE and sing along!)/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[SUSAN MACK]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 55th Birthday Mom ;)! Love you to the moon and I hope you have the most amazing birthday! Thanks for always being there to catch me in the hall when I would sprint to your room during a thunder storm. Now lets celebrate with some Malbec since im "Your" daughter XO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steph]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have had so many fun times on the golf course, hanging out relaxing or enjoying a cocktail & good food.  Winters at Woodfield are the best with a great friend.  Wishing you a wonderful birthday! xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan Kasindorf ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There is not a day that goes by these past 29 years that I don't feel blessed to have you in my life  the love you have shown the girls and I and the devotion you have for us is truly the greatest gift we could ask for I love you so much ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks to the Macks, the Rabinowitz family met the Saks. Holidays and Seder by the sea is what you do, you're a perfect hostess for a large crew. When I got sick you were always there, and I know that you care.  May your birthday be filled with love, health & happiness!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lots of love,  Amy Saks]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I knew we'd be friends when she walked into Accent on You, 22 years ago looked around and said "I love this pantsuit" but I really can't afford it but one day I'm going to come back and be your best client!  Not only was she my best client but we became great friends?????]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellen Kramer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Janis,/RWe are so fortunate that you're our friend! We have shared many wonderful moments! You're warm, kind & generous & we love playing golf & spending time with you & Joel! Wishing you a very happy & healthy birthday! /RAll our love, /RMichelle & Jeff]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Any time spent with Janis is special. Spending time together in Colorado, enjoying our hikes together and our long talks along the way are definitely up there on my list. And I'll always remember that "what happens in Colorado stays in Colorado!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan (and brookie man, too)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As Janis said in regard to last years high holidays, we created a new tradition. We haven't know each other long but in a short time have become close and created many memories.  Janis has opened her home and her heart and is a very special person and friend ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maxine and the Hochhauser family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my most special friend, Janis, I can best express what Janis has meant to me  from something i found written about friendship: "sometimes in life you find a special friend.  Someone  who changes your life just by being part of it.  Someone who makes"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Terry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[you believe that there really is good in the world and that there really is an unlocked door waiting to be opened.  This is forever friendship .  When you are down and the world seems dark and empty , your forever friend lifts you up in spirit and makes that dark and ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Terry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[empty world suddenly seem bright and full.   Your forever friend gets you through the hard times, the sad times, and the confused times.  If you turn and walk away, your forever friend follows.  If you lose your way, your forever friend guides you and cheers you on.   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Terry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your forever friend holds your hand and tells you that everything is going to be okay.  And if you find such a friend you feel happy and complete because you need not worry.  You have a forever friend, and forever has no end."Janis, thanks for being my forever friend"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Terry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have shared many happy times together and look forward to many more.  . And i will always be there for you as you have been for me./RBest wishes for a wonderful birthday , i love u,/RTerry/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One day Janis walked into Accent on You and saw a pantsuit she loved.She told me it was too expensive but one day she would  be my "best customer". Not only did that come true but for 22 years I've had alot more than that, I've had a great friend and confidant!! XoX]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellen Kramer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Janis,in this special day, I wish you all the very best, wish you all the joy you can ever have and I wish you happiness now and forever!!!/RI Wish we can continue being good friends and I am looking forward to share many more happy memories together in the future.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Olga Henick and Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[wishing you the best on your birthday--we love visiting and making brookies, yodle pies, white trash and cocktails--always fun when we're all together.  So thankful you called that day to tell me you saw Samantha at camp--the start of a great friendship & memories xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jody Berger-Wenig]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday! Always great to spend time with you...from Florida to New York. Enjoy your day! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Evan Wien]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No matter the location (Boca, Miami, the Hamptons, Westchester, the Elevator), i've enjoyed every experience I've shared with you. Heres to 20,00 Fitbit steps and a lifetime of technical support./R/RHappy Birthday Janis! /RMany More!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Adam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Over the past 40 years Janis and I have shared SO many special moments. She is one of my oldest friends and has been a constant in my life. I love her so much and hope she has the most wonderful and special birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Niki Gregory]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Many years ago a trip up the Pacific Coast Hwy stopping to eat & shop every chance we got was a memorable bonding experience. There was another memorable moment when we added up our charge receipts. The ivory & black vase in the family room reminds me of a great time. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sister Sue]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>