<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2457-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/7/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Katherine Thompson]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[2604 Bala Lane]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Ardmore]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19003]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_60]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[The Scott Thompson]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[THE Scott Thompson]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[All your people]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am SO thankful you stopped to tie your shoe....can't imagine this journey without you.  Happy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Katie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Scott had good manners, a quick wit and impeccable taste, and could really get us some offensive boards when we needed them./R/RWait, this is a birthday thing?  Uh, change to present tense.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike Carey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The night we realized that he had an alter ego: Tom Scottson! What has THAT guy been up to lately? Happy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charlotte]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Scott turned a Disney trip that could have been full of line waiting and cranky kids into a wonderful time. He transformed into a kid with a law degree and got the slow moving McMahon's going. It was a great time - no line waiting! FAST PASS BABY!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Colorado McMahons]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So many great memories.  Late night steak and cheese calzones, trying to see how much we could cram into Scott's tiny mouth, fireworks on the White House lawn, diabolically crude insults using the insultanator, Olympics gold medal game...need more characters!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Josh Rubin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Here's to another 40 years of brilliantly planned and executed April Fool's Day jokes!  /RHAPPY BIRTHDAY!!!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Terresa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[2003, Powelton Apartment. We hate you, Aaron Boone. Talking Red Sox, talking Celtics. We love you, Pedro and Paul. Picking strawberries, eating cider donuts. We love you, Kara and Annie. Putting up a hoop. Colin loves you, Scott. Eat slow, show up, good man, THE Scott.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[KGT, LT and CT, love you, too. ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey Scott, remember when you threw up all over me?  Soooo, we've got that going for us./R/RHappy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Barbara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'll ever forget that moment of admiration & overflowing joy I experienced when you showed up in that Col. Sanders outfit. You are a true friend, loving dad to your girls and the perfect yin to KT's yang! We love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Clowes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One more thing that didn't fit in my other section. Thank you for letting me steal your "TheScott" for my "thelizmcneil" gmail address all those years ago! I always credit you with the idea when people tell me I'm clever!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Liz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tom Scottson, there are so many great times we've shared, it's hard to pick a favorite. Top contenders would have to include Bad Basketball League, Colonel Sanders Halloween, and oh so many Ultimate games. Glad to have you as a friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian Girard]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's not the holiday season until I've dressed in some sort of crazy sweater, composed some kind of ridiculous song, shopped for a gift I'm embarrassed to bring to the register, and offended 3 friends in angling to take it home w/ me! The Scott does a Xmas party right! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maureen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The kindest earnestest guy in the room. Mix that with a prodigious intellect & you have the rarest dude who can both empathize and rationalize around any problem.  Also, his strength is amazing, his girth is enormous, and his height unequalled.  Loves butterscotch.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Costellos in Medford, MA]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tony Robbins giving me a pep talk at Lisa & Clapper's wedding, The stupid intervention for Nae, Colonel Sanders.... and countless other times. It all adds up to you being a genuinely great guy and friend. I wish you a happy 40th and I hope it's Scottie's choice all day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eileen (aka Das Boot, aka Bird).]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Building a girl out of boxes for Scott to practice hugging? Driving cross-country and Scott clogging the toilet in New Orleans? Convincing a cop to let us add our own plaque to a Tufts bench? Creating our own fraternity, Beta Mu Pi -- BUTT? How I do choose just one?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Count Tobin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Seriously, though, Scott has been a friend to the end for many years, as kind and loyal and hilarious and just as great a guy as you could ever hope to meet. Even if his French Daddy character is deeply insulting to Les Québécois.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cold Mountain (and its inaccurate depiction of Cold War weaponry), Colonel Sanders, Christmas Party Extravaganza's, Scottie's Choice, WaWa safe baby drops...all fabulous memories.  But, better is your genuine laugh, quick wit and love for your beautiful family! HBD:)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Corinne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 40th , Scott! We have been thinking of the easy days of ultimate, happy hour and playing bridge.  We hope the next 40 are an amazing journey and, seriously, bring us back to bridge.  And golf.  And other old people games.  But at least they are games!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bonny and Colly et al.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[While I will always treasure my time spent with Tony Robbins and of course my autographed copy of his book! It pales in comparison to time spent with The Scott. You are a kind, thoughtful and hilarious gentleman, husband and dad. You deserve a spin at the Whiskey Wheel!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We met you as the Colonel at the Greeks and knew you were a winner. Thanks for serving up drinks and your witty humor every Christmas. Happy 40th birthday - have a spin on the whiskey wheel and wish for a scottys choice]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom & Christine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm feeling like the cript keeper. Your not aloud to be 40. But how could you be the you that you are without time. Wishing you and your beautiful, wonderful family a terrific day.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Cumberland Martins]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Scott, Happy 40th birthday to an all around great guy with lots of "visual interest!" Enjoy your day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susie and Dan Clune]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Eagles games, Halloween trick or treating, the teal bar, pinochle, bridge, skiing, Dork Den, making snow cones, Supper Club, driveway basketball, frisbee catches, 4th of July, Settlers of Catan.../RThanks for making everyday moments so memorable.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Bobbitt Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's shocking to me that I owe a lifetime friendship with someone as loyal, creative, funny, and brilliant as The Scott Thompson to some random administrator at a huge law firm in D.C. Officemates for life!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rick Swedloff]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 40th!  You are one of the smartest, cleverest, kindest, most hilarious people I know.  Thanks for the big laughs (Go, Cookie!) and the snickers (dang dab dibbidy do!).  Feel lucky to have been there for moments big (Halloween 2000) and small.  Here's to many more!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Ann Marie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Scott!! We wish you all the best for the coming year. We love your open nature, warm smile, and gentleness. Where you are, there is kindness. Have a wonderful celebration! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Liz & Ethan Goldberg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Memory from Christmas 2007/RLet's set the stage: You, Katie, & Annie came to our home for dinner. Likely, the first time to Merwood Park & to our home. Annie found our Christmas tree & broke the leg off Zwarte Piet. Scott, you were so concerned. Happy 40th, Scott!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alison & Brandon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So many memorable moments with the best roommate I could have asked for and a hell of a friend... the Carpool, the Vault, the Bad Frogs, the Blair Witch, the "Original" Colonel, the Snow Couch, the Hurricane Party and bandana Taboo among others.  Happy 40th Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Doug Benson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have so many memories...dinner at Pod, Zwarte Piet, BBQs, soft top slit, mustard chicken, finding Bala house, dinner swaps, Supper Club, Bar Master, Gadget Guy, The Great American Camp Out, riding bikes on your driveway, playing in the snow, Eagles games. Happy 40th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Yezes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I don't know what it says about me that so many of my fond memories of Scott involve him mocking me. For having a big head (I don't), for losing my car at the airport parking lot. 15 years later, I still mock myself on Scott's behalf. So I say, happy birthday, meanie. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jill Dash]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There have been so many good times, but you know what we appreciate most? We love how THE Scott is always THE (same) Scott! A rare find, consistent people like you represent all that is good in the world!  100% GENUINE in every single way, we celebrate YOU! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sean & Tara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[While I cannot possibly be expected to document the full list of disappointments over the past 25 years, I can say that you're one of my closest friends and I wish you every happiness in your senior citizenship.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt Stowe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[His first family vacation when we drove from San Fran to Yosemite after Megan's wedding.  Without hesitation we made him drive the car with full crew, Gma and a weeks worth of groceries in tow.  His patience, thoughtfulness and wit have always shined through then & now.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelly & Molly McMahon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Scott, happy birthday to a wonderful dad and a great nephew. Happy 39th you can celebrate over and over and over again]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The lamannos]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Scott  I remember  vividly you  flying to Kansas City  with me picking you up @ the airport and driving to Weston Missouri where you asked for Katie's hand in marriage We were already impressed with you so saying yes was easy/R We have been blessed  ever by your presence]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Papa Mike ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Scott!  I am so glad you married into our family!  See you soon...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom and Mary Hastings ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Scott!!! I always enjoy talking to you at family get togethers! Hope you have a wonderful day full of family, laughter, and fun! (Which I know will not be hard haha) /RLove, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Erin Hastings ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'll never forget making cinnamon rolls in the morning with you.  You are always smiling and you are the best dad EVER!  You are caring, kind, funny and generous.  My favorite memory is when we went to the Taylor Swift concert together.  I LOVE YOU -xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Annie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best thing I like about my dad is that he's funny, kind and nice.  When we go to Maine, I love playing in the water with him, especially when it RAINS!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lucy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love my dad because he gives me hugs AND because he is SO happy AND he is so funny.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Claire]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What do we love about Scott?/RChase: He does "rock-a-bye baby" on the swings./RBeckett: That he loves to play with me./RElizabeth: When he made that mix tape with his own guitar acoustic solos/RJeff: That he is the best brother in the world/RHappy 40th, we love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff, Elizabeth, Chase and Beckett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[By the time you were 3, we knew you were going to be a lawyer because you couldn't stop asking questions and it wasn't too long before you figured out our answers were BS...but that still didn't stop you from asking even harder questions.  Lool where it got you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom and Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Spring break in Virgina Beach in March. What could possibly go wrong? Besides the freezing cold weather, nothing. From three days of bacon-filled meals to a visit to the Stonewall Jackson Shrine in a Volvo from Connecticut pumping out Roxette, it was all right.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian Ostrer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dad and I are sitting here at the cottage remembering celebrating your birthday at Backstreet Landing.  /R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom and Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Scott, Happy 40th! So many fun, special memories with you! In particular your handy-work as bartender (especially the wheel with "Scotty's choice") and your acknowledgment of my stupid convention in LBI! Good times...and many more ahead my friend! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Renae&Kevin ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Of course, Catie remembers the original Colonel Sanders moment, as well as the dozens (and dozens!) of re-tellings/re-enactments. All great things start with a great story - and you, TSC, have been nothing but the best from the very moment you entered Katie's circle.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Catie Chris Abby & Hannah Wolfgang]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to a great friend and classmate.  Survivor of road trips to London, the Bahamas and the ballparks of the Midwest.  Starting left fielder for Benson's Bad Frogs. It's great to see someone so thoughtful be so successful.  May you enjoy this one & many more.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Justin Sullivan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The "fun" trip of taking you all to the airport for Disney world when I couldn't make it out of the car fast enough on the highway. /R/RDrunken trick or treating.. Enough said. /R/RLast but not least having the best roommates in Philly! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Hastings ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So many to choose from--Of course I do remember that first time we tried to diaper Annie.  I was a rusty grandma and you first time dad. But I think you caught on quicker than I did! You always seem to know just the right thing to say to encourage!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Patty-mother -in-law]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One more – your kind and loving invitation when we went to Damarascotta with the grandmas and all shared lobster together!  Happy 40th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Patty ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The beginning was magical... Chaucer's, Brigid's, Kelly Drive, the Greeks, & the West Wing (aka first kiss).  The middle epic... Okemo, Bermuda, California, Maine, London, DISNEY....  Looking forward to every moment as our love story lives on...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Katie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>