<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2463-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/8/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Mary Magner]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[1801 Ridgeview CT]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Cedar Rapids]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[IA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[52403]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_60]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Here's to the first 60 years!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Steve Carpenter]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[From your many fans]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Here are some of our "lighter" moments: The blue moon over the Grand Canyon, the lightening storm at the Cinque Terre, the lightening bugs at the camp ground, and the Eiffel Tower.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are my voice - you take my rambling thoughts and make them whole.  You have a special skill set that sets you apart from the rest and I appreciate that very much.  :)   Enjoy your special day and special BD number.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Steve has an uncanny gift at describing people using everyday kitchen measurements. A typical description: the person is 3/4 cup of a selected other person, with a dash and pinch of of yet another person. Weird? Yes. Accurate? Oh, yeah!/RHappy 60th, my friend : )]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy Kaiser]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A clever, caring, sensitive man, that Steven! He bled Kirkwood blue; he told the many stories.  He felt the music of KCCK as he feels the music of life.  Words from the heart...that be Scarpen!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joyce and Carl Sefl]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember early in getting to know Steve - listening to him on the radio with Grandma Magner - then later having discussions with him on history, books, music, and current events - always interesting and engaging.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cheyl Magner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Steve:/RI recall your great story about leaning against the lamp pole in Atlanta and getting yelled at by some southern lady about how you had no respect for those brave souls who fought and died for the glory of Dixie.  /RHave a wonderful birthday!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pete Balik]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Steve,/RToday, is a day to celebrate what an incredible person you are. I do not believe the word no, or I am to busy is part of your vocabulary. We are so blessed to have you in our family./RHappy Birthday, wishing you many more happy and healthy ones./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shirley and Ken]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When it comes to toasts, no one says it more cleverly or poignantly than Steve. He touches us with his words and his humor lightens our spirits.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Carmen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Steve you still talk about time Bob and I helped you with your plumbing. However you have been a great asset to our family. Thanks for all you do. Top Tom and Peggy ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom and Peggy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Hi Steve,/RHope you have a great birthday~ We want you to know that we appreciate what a good friend you are to our family.  Everything from singing in Church together, to Council meetings, to helping mentor the boys, and waving around town./REnjoy your special day~]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tony, Steph, Zach, Matt and Brad ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bumpa, you have always been my favorite thing in my outdoors and science part of my life. I had fun when we looked under the microscope at several objects. I have fun hiking with you along trails and your street. Thank you for being my number one  Bumpa!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Isaac Scott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like doing science with my Steve, and looking at Isaac's germs and hair. I also enjoyed bird watching with you.????????I loved going on trips with you and Nana.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Trevor Scott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Twin Sons of Different Mothers!  Hard to believe it has been 40 years since you and I started debating politics, the cosmos, people and most importantly, the merits of certain rock 'n rollers.  You've always been there for me/us.  Love you, brother.  Get your hot dogs!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dell and Jan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Steve's knowledge and talents are so wide-ranging--music, art, history, literature, gardening, cooking--that he would be downright intimidating, if not for his problems shuffling cards! Even that minor weakness he handles with class and good humor. Happy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rhonda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[For all the times you helped me./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sheila Gatewood]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Recall with pleasure strolling and chatting with Steve in Savannah. Also a couple of joyous happy hours there. Finally, very pleased that Steve could "inherit" my square-foot garden boxes and soil when we moved. Steve's the ideal person to have it and put it to good use]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ken Kekke]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy BIG 60!Patti and I send our best wishes for you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your fellow famers!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When it comes to words no one says it better than Bumpa!  It is always a creative treat to hear how you put words together.  A memory is of you enjoying your jazz music sitting in the living room on Bever with Lunch snuggled close by.  Happy wonderful 60!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sara Scott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I've always called you a Renaissance man. Your knowledge and appreciation of art and music gave me a fresh pair of insightful eyes on many projects. You are patient, kind, caring, encouraging, forever positive…a real class act and the kind of person I try to be.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kit]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Bumpa,/R   Happy 60th birthday! I love you so much. Even though I haven't gotten the privilege to spend all 60 years of your life with you the time I have spent with you will last me a life time. Enjoy your birthday!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Olivia Scott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The trip to DesMoines when Christy and Jeff were little to the Science Center. It was a great day and the time spent with you for the kids and I was very special. Fun and Educational for all!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Teresa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The Amish Auction in Lamoni each Spring has been fun together and something I look forward to doing with you for many more years to come.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Teresa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[YOU NEVER CHOOSE YOUR FAMILY BUT YOU DO CHOOSE WHO TO KEEP IN YOUR LIFE! YOU ARE AN AWESOME BROTHER AND I AM SO PROUD TO CALL YOU FRIEND. /RHAPPY BIRTHDAY BIG BROTHER!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[TERESA]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You may not know how much it really meant to us that you where a part of our ceremony. It gave me a real feeling of unity! Tony and I thank you from the bottom of our hearts. It truly meant the world to us! Until next time, take care! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[We love you! Heather&Tony]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember getting cards in the mail from my uncle Steve! Thanks for taking the time! It was one of the only ways I could get to know my family! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your niece Heather ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite things about you are, your love of education and impeccable taste in music! A+]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Daleske's]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your eloquence and personality are enlightening, Steve. I can always count on the smile on your face. Most importantly though, you have a heart that believes in kids and the common good. Whether it's a kickball game or fundraising you make an impact every day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Myers]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Steve! Jesus has called you to be His hands and feet at this time and place...I am thankful to serve with you as a council person and as a Bertramite ... Praying Psalm 91:4 " He will cover you with his feathers..." Praising Jesus for you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Penny Kula]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We are always pleased to know someone/Relse is aging to perfection... along with us!/R/RWe wish you many more birthdays!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John & Joan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Steve, Great travel memories. Nat'l Park hopping in Utah, where you were my cohort in acrophobia (TYOB!)  Then, Yellowstone and Italy! On a more serious note: you helped in so many ways after David's death & I remain eternally grateful.  We will toast you on your 60th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy Challed]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Happy Birthday, Steve.  I loved the most recent email recommending a book!  I had just finished All the Light We Cannot See and your encapsulation was perfect.  Book recommendations and watching you speak at Toastmasters. A priceless education thanks to you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allison York]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 21st anniversary of your 39th birthday.  I have enjoyed knowing you through the club all of these years and appreciate your commitment to the community through your good work.  I must say that it is remarkable what can eminate from Missouri, you and Harry Truman.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Scott Overland]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Staying at your house in Cedar Rapids and visiting Palisades Park, Fiftieth B-day party,/Rwalking my country road while you identify birds and their calls, and I identify wild flowers, Iowa Skippers, Living History Farm trip, YOU cooking in MY kitchen,many these favorite]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your little sis, Twila]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Every moment is a special moment with Bumpa. He has always been so supportive of us and his enthusiasm is inspiring. I can't say I've met a more passionate person in my life. We love you all so much! Have a wonderful birthday bumps! ??]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Megan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Steve--You are such an awesome volunteer! It was a pleasure to work with you and Jeremy for 2 years of your match. Jeremy often told me you were a great person he could talk to, and coming from a teenage boy, that's pretty amazing! Thanks for all you do!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christina Clements, BBBS]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Steve!  You've always got a smile to share,  kind word to say,  or words of encouragement for our family.  May you have a blessed anand wonderful birthday! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Denise,  Nick, and Julia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ I remember when I graduated from high school and was feeling a little unsure about my journey ahead.  You talked  about my next step being filled with so many opportunities and turned it into such a positive moment for me.  Your positive perspective is so contagious!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Annie (Magner) Johnson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So many fun times! Especially when beating him @ Monopoly & him trying figure how I did it! :) I really remember much fun we had when he came to KC. Even the liquor store visit was fun! I really enjoyed spending the afternoon @ The Truman Library. Love you!! ToAnother60]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Steve! /RYou are such a special person and offer such wisdom. Mike and I love visiting with you about politics, education, family, travel - you always offer strong insight. We feel lucky to be able to call you family! Happy travels this year!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Panochs ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Uncle Steve! I will always remember the day we shared last year when you came to visit me in Ottumwa. Beautiful conversation just you and I. I hope to spend more time with you soon. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Katrina Briggs]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Its hard to pick one special moment with an amazing individual. I appreciate and get excited with every moment.  Whether its the trips to KC during the summer or the family dinners, I always enjoy each moment and become excited for more.  Happy Birthday Steve! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff and Carrie Carpenter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my first memories with Uncle Steve was when we were driving to Bethany one night.  He looks up at the sky and tells me to look at the stars. I say " I can't see them that well"  You then turn off the lights to the car as we cruised down the road.   How bout now? ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff Carpenter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey BIG Brother, I didn't want to read the other notes to you until I wrote mine, so I didn't realize we could write more than 1!!/RMy first was really crowded, so I will write another! I LOVE having you for my BIG Brother!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[from your little sis' Twila]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You were always fun to have around! Remember playing Scrabble with Mary and my grandkids! All of us (except Christy) had a great time! The night playing Life with the kids was a memorable time, too: Wyatt wanted to stay up with us big kids and was such a "pill"!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Twila]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Loved buddying up w you in Italy!  Kindred spirit in gustatory derring-do w Ligurian squid and raw anchovies.  On the same page about Galileo's middle finger in Firenze.  Your encyclopedic knowledge + zest for adventure = cherished travel companion.  Happy 60, Bro! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Winitzky]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday!!!!!!!!! Remember when you would feed the birds that was always a good time. Loved watching you provide food to the inhabitants of your backyard and the walks down the block we would take afterwords.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allison K Clements]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My 1st memory of Steve was when I was ten and everyone was at our house for Christmas.  He always made an effort to talk to us and listen. To make a long story short, I remember dragging out my 5-inch binder of baseball cards or show him. We sifted through them all. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Molly Magner Hong]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Another memory I have of Steve was when he schooled me on Vanguard, the Star Fund, and Windsor II. He sat with me, emailed me years later to answer questions, and was a wealth of knowledge. So much of investing is confusing. I appreciated Steve's help.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Molly Magner Hong]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It is always entertaining and enlightening to hear the "Steveisms" added to any conversations or speeches!/RAlways witty and willing to help anyone. Wishing you many more years of stories young man!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sue Murphy ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi-Ho Steverino!/R  And Happy Birthday!/RWe have a fresh memory of you & Mary sharing Bill's birthday celebration with us just last month and then surprising us by making it your treat.  That was  nice and so you.  We hope to be able to properly celebrate your day soon./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy & Bill Kilbourn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being "Bumpa" for the Clements family. Your love and devotion to the our family is an inspiration. Have a wonderful birthday and many many more to come.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrew]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for your patience with drawing princesses, especially the shoes... Happiest of Birthdays to you. We love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Annette]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you so much for always taking us to cool places and being my Bumpa. I hope you have a wonderful day! Happy Birthday!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mitchell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Bumpa,/R  I love it when I get to come over to your house and bark at the birds and squirrels. I also like it when you take me on long walks! I hope you are able to bark at animals and take long walks on your birthday./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Bo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have always enjoyed our insightful conversations on a variety of worldly topics.  Your passion for continuous learning is an inspiration for all of us.  You help me appreciate all of the great gifts that we have been given.  You have been a fantastic father-in-law!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rob Scott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You made KCCK such a fun place to work. You’d burst out of your office & say something newsworthy, exciting, or hilarious. I loved your stories of your childhood.  I can never look at a rounded sofa arm & not think of a miniature Steve riding the open plains of Missouri]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy York]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeremy described Steve as "smart." He said that Steve listens to him and has good ideas about how to solve any problem that he may have. When asked who a "special adult" in his life is, Jeremy replied that it was Steve. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeremy/Big Brothers Big Sisters]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Steve, You have been a pleasure to work with from the start. Your caring nature and dedication to your match is remarkable and we thoroughly enjoy having you involved in our program. Thank you for all your hard work.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sara Nightingale]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>