<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2464-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/8/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Blake Kron]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[3541 Hazen Circle]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Anchorage]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[AK]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[99515]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 80th Birthday]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Judy Kron (aka Grandma)]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Friends & Family of Judy Kron]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love how you are always there for each of us no matter whats going on. We can always count on your love and support and warm hugs.  We love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Blake, Abigale, Kenzie, and Camdyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We always enjoyed coming over to her house for birthdays and celebrations.  The hospitality and food is always great. Happy Birthday. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris & Sue and family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have so many wonderful memories of you. You are so special and loved.  Do you remember sharing a room in ft Benton?  What fun!  You and Bob were always so good to me and the girls, there isn't room to list all the things you did for us.  We love you.  Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Don and Vida and family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We many fond memories but the one that stands out the most for us is watching Judy   Polk dancing with her handsome handlebar mustache husband, Robert.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dawn & Rodney Kinney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom,/RI learned to truly value my family the one that God blessed me to born into and the one that I would have of my own.  It was your faith in us that lead me to find my faith in God and want to a part of His family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paul]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Many days I talked with you most of the way home from work in Washington.  You made me feel like I was already home.  Your the very best Mom.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paul]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being the rock of the family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[-]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom-/RI have a special place in my heart for you for the period in my life when you were working at ATU full time and raising 3 teenage sons while dad worked on the slope. You spent quality time with us, took us to church and took us to our sporting events. LOVE YOU]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rob Kron]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I feel so blessed each and every moment that I spend with you. It makes my heart smile to share all the wonderful-ness that is Arloe with you. And I have and will always admire you for the strong woman that you are. We are blessed to be a part of your life. We love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Zsivon, Jamie and Arloe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Judy, when I think of you I think of the warmth of sunshine,/Rthe happiness of smiles,/Rthe sounds of laughter,/Rthe feeling of love,/Rand the sharing of good cheer.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stacie, Tino, & Tristan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I loved all the "projects" we did that Bob had to help us finish.  Some of them worked and some of them didn't, but we always had a lot of laughs over them.  Now we run errands, have coffee and lunch and never lack for things to talk about.  You are a special person.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your BFF Sister, Love, Bobbie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It seems like a lifetime has past since I worked with Judy at ATU so I cannot remember any specific moment but the one thing I have always remembered is the love she had for her family, her pleasant smile and easy going personality. She was a pleasure to work with!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Donnie Mays]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love most that you love us all with everything you have. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tabby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hello Aunt Judy! /RI love you so much! You are such a positive constant in my life, always taking time to visit with me. I love hanging out with you and playing cards with you! You are awesome! You make me smile and laugh:)  Thank you for teaching me to crochet:) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Melissa Knapp]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember Grandma came to pick me up from high school in Grandpas truck and I was so embarrassed of the truck that I dove in and a hid. I told Grandma to drive very fast. She was just laughing away thinking it was so funny.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kameron ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember having a slumber party with all the cousins at Grandmas and she would let us girls sit on her lap and put on makeup with her. She would show us where to put what and always told us we looked beautiful when really I'm sure we looked like clowns. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kameron]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memory of Grandma was when all the grandkids would stay the night at her place and she would let us make forts with her couch cushions and dress up in her pretty night gowns. She would sleep in her chair with us so we wouldn't get scared at night. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kameron]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am most grateful for my Grandma because she has always believed in me even when I didn't believe in myself. She is the positivity I always run to when I need to be lifted up. She is my rock and I am forever grateful for her.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kameron]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being a truly classy and fabulously fashionable woman. Thank you for teaching me broken cookies have no calories, a grandma hug can fix any mood  and pies taste best when made with love. I love you so very much!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Zsoelle ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[All my life I have looked up to you as a role model.  Your beauty, strength, love, intelligence, talents, and spirituality illuminate every aspect of your life. What a blessing you are to me, big sister!  With love and admiration forever,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gonda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I still remember how you tried to stifle your laughter as you drove me, in the middle of the night, to the emergency room  in Lawrence to get a fly removed from my ear!  You've always been a wonderful sister-in-law.  Love and best wishes,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dale]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I was young I felt like you were always surrounded by the most beautiful things. There was something extra fancy about you and the gifts you shared. As a woman, I still feel that way. However, the most exquisite gift you've blessed our family is your beautiful soul]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer Romine & family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Making Jell-O always consisted of an ice-cube cool down so I could eat it as soon as possible!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Briana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Intelligent, loving, and giving.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Briana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love being able to share our faith, it is so special.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Briana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Judy, I appreciate how special you make everyone feel!  A great memory I have is of going to Alaska when I was in middle school.  Such beautiful country, both you and Bob seemed so happy to share it with us.  Fishing in Homer is still one of my favorite trips! Love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Lilly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a GREAT great aunt and we love you very much!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stevie, Tris, Maisyn, Ty, and Jake]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for making me A LOT of peanut butter and jelly sandwiches.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Blake]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love coloring, making dots, and your hugs.  I love you so much grandma.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mackenzie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember all the fun times we ate at Red Robin and watched the balloons float away in the sky.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Blake]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for always making me smile]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Camdyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Judy, what a great way to wish you a special birthday, I am so blessed to have you for a sister. We had so much fun together, sharing a room, our friends, our families, our hopes and dreams and working together. I have always been so proud of you. Stay happy and healthy]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Sylvia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The thing I love most about Grandma is that she is incredibly accepting of everyone and loves you for who you are. /RShe also spoils her grand kids and great grand kids rotten! :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Abigale-]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Judy, one memory that I cherish is our trip with Rob to Lake Powell AZ. We took off from Pheonix and created many memories on that trip. We played Western Music, stopped at a 50's restaurant in Kingman and had homemade rootbeer that delicious. Love you and Happy 80th.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laurie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>