<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2467-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/8/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Kirsten Bray]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[362 Front Street S]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Issaquah]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[WA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[98027]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 50th Birthday Tracy!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Tracy Webster]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[With Love, From Your Friends]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Crudites and bathtubs...nobody knows how to party quite as well as you!  Thanks for always kicking it up a notch!!!  The memories keep me laughing & smiling always.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kisses and cocktails, Kirsten]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tracy- First words that come to mind - beautiful, generous, intelligent, hostess, devoted mom and friend/R/RFavorite memory - Rodeo in Arizona!  Paul Green heels, silk shirt and all. We are still going to ride the bull one day!/R/RLove you T! Happy 50th!!/R/RLove,  Cari/R/R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[XOXO]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tracy, your generous and loving spirit, your strength and kindness of heart and  how you love well and true./ROne of my best memories (and there are many) is the day you gave birth to Megan and I was so privileged and thrilled to be in the room!/RHappy Birthday ! Love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sherrye]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tracy, /RNaming one thing I like most about you or one special moment is impossible, as there have been so many! I cherish the years we spent as neighbors with little kids, and the many lunches we've talked non-stop. Every moment with you has been the one I like most! :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much love, Karin Allen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tracy, /RI love how loyal and protective you are of your family and friends. I know if I ever need help I can call you at any time and you will be there for me with no questions asked. You love and play with all your heart. Thank you for being my friend! XOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allison]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tracy you are inspirational. Not only do you cherish and care for your family and friends, you devote time and attention to the community around you. Your unselfish hard work makes me the people around you want  to do more. So lucky, and happy, we are friends! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joni ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tracy is the one of the most generous people I know....whether she's inspiring others to give or if she's quietly giving behind the scenes to someone in need, she is the true definition of compassion.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen Carlton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I first met Tracy last year on a trip to Mexico./RWe had a fabulous time together and I learned then, that Tracy is a very caring and compassionate person./RI feel blessed that I can call Tracy my friend!/RHAPPY BIRTHDAY !!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo Linda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Miss Tracy, fifty never looked so good. Even though we've been *sisters* for years, I feel like our friendship has really blossomed--better late than never--in a really great way these last few years. Happy Birthday to a wonderful mother, wife, sister and friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jill Boltmann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[“This is my wish for you: peace in your heart, prosperity through the year, happiness that multiplies, fun around every corner, energy to chase your dreams and much joy to fill your world"   /R/R"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Warfield]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your commitment and dedication to your family is truly a special gift that you continue to bless them with.  They are so very lucky to have such a wonderful mother and wife in their lives.  You are also a blessing to so many people and God has truly blessed them too.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Denise]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always the hostess, electricity or not! A gas range, a wind up radio, a dozen candles with a few great friends and you still turn what should have been a bust into one of the most memorable dinner parties ever! Your creativity and hospitality always amazes me!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[XOXO Kirsten]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, my friend.  I will never forget our escapades in Mira Verde and The Ranch.  Of course, Europe had a multitude of fun and interesting memories.  We must continue our long weekend trips together.  Love you, Ellie]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellen Geminder]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I know about my dear friend Trac.../RYou have a heart of gold,very loyal/RYou are a protector, a beauty, and a wonderful mama./RYou talk about Brian like you are a teenager in love./ROh and you are a master at laundering the whitest of athletic pants!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy 50 my girl, I love ya! Melisy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So many years of great memories growing up together...friends and sisters!  Wishing you an amazing 50th and wishing I could be there to celebrate with you!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lots of love, Brooke]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[T - My wish for you is to see in the mirror what all your family and friends see-beauty, compassion, loyalty, a lil craziness & party planner supreme!  You've hit 50-relax and enjoy the ride-don't sweat the little stuff and surround yourself with those that choose YOU! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love,  Suz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite things about Tracy is no matter where she is or how busy she may be, I know that she would be there for me in an instant.  She cherishes good friends, and truly knows how to be one in return.  She gives freely of her heart, her time and her love. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Always, Caryn ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tracy, I think of our bond as a golden thread woven throughout both of our lives. As friends and Pi Phi sisters, we have supported each other during both high school and college, in Europe, at reunions and many visits since graduation. It's a unique and dear bond.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy 50th! Love you, Steph]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love your tenacity. You are timeless and hilarious. LOL when you think about the big pink bath robe in Chicago for the Seahawks game and many tiny bubbles.  I love how you inspire me to do more for my community and our world. Jeremiah 29:11 Happy 50th! Love you always]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marcia ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Tracy,  You are a wonderful friend filled with extraordinary amounts of love, laughter and generosity.   From "Lanz" pajamas to "Phoebe," birthday parties to Christmas parties, I have cherished them all...  You are a gift from God and a true blessing in my life.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All my love, Sarah ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mommy, you teach me how to love unconditionally everyday through the way you are there for us kids, your family and friends. Thank you so much! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Car]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 50th to my gorgeous friend! Your generosity, style and grace are gifts to us all. So grateful to be able to call you my friend for the last 30+ years.  Wishing you health, joy, love and laughter and loads of fun!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With love, Heather ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tracy, /RYou are a kind, giving, generous, faithful, fun and beautiful friend! I am so glad that our kids brought us together and we now share these stages of Life! Blessings and Happy 50th! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[XO, Christy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tracy you are bright, compassionate, reliable, beautiful, generous, caring,  and a great travel companion! /RBut what I admire the most is your Love and Devotion for your beautiful family. /RCheers to you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rosie VC]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday! I remember how thrilled I was to get *YOU* as my big sister. You're woven through all my freshman year memories. Whenever I get the chance to see you (not often enough) you are still the same beautiful friend you've always been. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Kira]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Poised, Beautiful, Strong Willed, Intelligent, Encouraging and so Thoughtful.  Those are all words that immediately immediately come to mind when I think of my "big sis" Tracy.  Happy Birthday Girlfriend!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cindy Funes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[How can I describe the most awesome woman in my life in such a short script?  Big Sister? Hardly... You are so much more than that!  My best friend, my confidant, the one I can count on for EVERYTHING!  You are my rock, my inspiration, and my true source of comfort.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim (1 of 2)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the one who always goes out of your way for others, especially your little sister! I can only aspire to be the Mom you are, and thank you every day for being the friend that you are to me.  I love you Sissy!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim (2 of 2)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Momma, you are the most caring and selfless person I know. Thank you for your unconditional love and support through every step of my life. No matter what I am going through I can always count on you. I hope to be half the mom that you are someday. I love you so much!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our friendship of 30 years means more to me than you know.  I have spent some of the most important times of my life with you Thank you for always being there for me unconditionally and for always making me laugh. You’re my best friend and I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy 50th! Laura]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To my beautiful First Born, My Pride, My Joy! You're the AMAZING woman I knew you would become. From Romper Room, to Song Smiths, to Pi Phi's and beyond, you've made many amazing friends along the way. You're an AMAZING daughter, sister, wife, Mom and friend. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom (1 of 2)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You give so much to others sharing your time and talents and love and you are an inspiration for your children.  I am so proud of you honey!/RHappy 50th Birthday to my beautiful daughter./RI love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom (2 of 2)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Girlfriend! Wishing you a wonderful birthday and many more!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love ya, Robyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I value the friend who for me finds time on his calendar, but I cherish the friend who for me does not consult his calendar.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[As Quoted by Robert Brault]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Be courteous to all, but intimate with few, and let those few be well tried before you give them your confidence.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[As Quoted by George Washington]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[True friends are like diamonds - bright, beautiful, valuable, and always in style! You are all of those things & more. Thank you for being an inspiration, amazing role model, trusted confidant, enthusiastic cheerleader, and most importantly an irreplaceable best friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With Love & Gratitude, Kirsten]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Be slow to fall into friendship, but when you are in, continue firm and constant.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[As Quoted by Socrates]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When a woman becomes her own best friend life is easier.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[As Quoted by Diane Von Furstenberg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A true friend freely, advises justly, assists readily, adventures boldly, takes all patiently, defends courageously, and continues a friend unchangeably.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[As Quoted by William Penn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There is nothing like puking with somebody to make you into old friends.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[As Quoted by Sylvia Plath]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Anybody can sympathize with the sufferings of a friend, but it requires a very fine nature to sympathize with a friends success.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[As Quoted by Oscar Wilde]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A friend is one that knows who you are, understands where you have been, accepts what you have become, and still, gently allows you to grow.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[As Quoted by William Shakespeare]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Friendship is the hardest thing in the world to explain. It's not something you learn in school.  But if you haven't learned the meaning of friendship, you really haven't learned anything.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[As Quoted by Muhammad Ali]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Don't walk behind me; I may not lead. Don't walk in front of me; I may not follow.  Just walk beside me and be my friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[As Quoted by Albert Camus]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I would rather walk with a friend in the dark, than alone in the light.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[As Quoted by Helen Keller]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No friendship is an accident.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[As Quoted by O. Henry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The truth is, everyone is going to hurt you.  You just got to find the ones worth suffering for.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[As Quoted by Bob Marley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A friend is someone who knows all about you and still loves you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[As Quoted by Elbert Hubbard]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Friendship is always a sweet responsibility, never an opportunity.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[As Quoted by Khalil Gibran]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[True friendship multiplies the good in life and divides its evils. Strive to have friends, for life without friends is like life on a desert island...to find one real friend in a lifetime is good fortune; to keep him is a blessing.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[As Quote by Baltasar Gracian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>