<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2468-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/8/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Carolyn Walker]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[431 Churchill Drive]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Berwyn]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19312]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Andrew's 50th Birthday]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Andrew]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Evan, Liam, Patrick, and Carolyn]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our favorite friend from Paw Paw Mi!  You always make everyone feel so special.  Enjoy the next 50 it's a great ride!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo  Nan, David, Will and Luke ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I wish you the very best day! So happy I know you. You have made me mad, laugh hysterically, annoyed but I always know I will snort if I talk to you!! Thanks for always brighten my day!!! Love]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gloria]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the most knowledgeable NFL talent evaluator. I will never question your savant abilities again. I admire your kind and giving spirit. Congratulations on reaching this significant milestone and thank you for being my friend. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paul Kovarick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Andrew, /RGreat memories of your boys and their time at New Eagle. The Walkers are super parents, super kids and super neighbors. Happy 50th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Theresa Booz ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ "SSSSSSSSSSS", that means Happy 50th Birthday from the three crazy blonde girls you love. Hope its a great one, enjoy all our fun talks around the kitchen counter and your always positive, happy attitude.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Major's]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Andrew, welcome to the over 50 club!  Hope to see you soon.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Thomas Schauerman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andrew is the most caring person we have ever met.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gossow Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always have something so kind and encouraging to say about my kids. I am very grateful for the laughs and sincerity of our friendship. I believe I also owe you rent for the amount of time Erik's bike has spent in your garage :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leslie Elken]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In 1979 after an exhausting day touring Washington, DC, we returned to our campground. Andrew and I then went to Manassas and did our own re-enactment of the Battle of Bull Run. So glad he is a history nut like me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for making us smile and laugh ("it's a no-smiling day!") whenever we see you.  We couldn't have chosen a better neighbor!  It doesn't hurt that you're still a Cubs fan either.  Well, maybe one of us disagrees with that ;)  We hope you have a fun, memorable b-day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Johnson Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 50th Birthday!!  I met you when you were 25 Years Old!!  (That is weird)  Lots of more adventures to come!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Carolyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I feel like we really bonded while sitting on the Broadhurst's couch listening to Father Zloch talk about the future at St. Monica while we were trying to mentally will the food on the kitchen table to come to us!  Well, that and our mutual admiration for Mr. CJ Spiller]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I've always enjoyed about you is that you always make for enjoyable conversation ... especially when we make that Boston connection (even though Brian tells me that you're a Steelers fan)!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Patti]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The first day we met was certainly memorable. Not just because our side mirrors tapped on narrow Contention Ln but because I got to meet one of the most wonderful guys out there.  You have a huge smile and even bigger heart./R/RHappy Birthday, Andrew!  You are awesome.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cristina]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Have not seen Andrew in some time...but will always remember his happy, smiling face and wonderful disposition. /RSincerest wishes for a memorable 50th/Rbirthday HAPPY DAY!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Irene Joyce]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andrew, you are a genuine person even when you make fun of my Philly accent! SO happy we have the Walker Famly in our lives!  Seriously, you are a good friend and YEAH! I wish you a very HAPPY BIRTHDAY! Don't ever stop teasing me!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michele Ippolti]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the biggest blessing to our family! Every time we see Dunkin Donuts, we think "Andrew"! Every time we look @ Isabella, we think "Andrew". The love we have for you and your family is exactly that "FAMILY"! We love you and are wishing you the happiest B-day ever!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Moraja Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andrew, I love how you always make Elizabeth feel like she is one of the boys... Have a fantastic birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With much love, Tricia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Crab claws, Kit Kats, laughing little kids, bbq's, blow up pools, bull dogs, antlers and let's not forget karaoke:) will forever remind me of you!  New Years Eve has never been the same and I cherish the memories.   Happy Birthday adorable Andrew!!  Love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jill & Fam:)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To Penn State's number 1 fan: Happy 50th!! I will never forget when Liam stopped by Mrs Troys class to "check" on Mollie. That is a true sign of a great kid with a great male role model. You guys have always been so kind to us. Cheers to many more!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary and Mollie Saylor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mr. Walker always makes me feel special and like I'm the prettiest girl in the room. I know he only has sons so I feel like his adopted daughter because he is definitely like a second father to me. He even criticizes my shorts length ;) I love you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah Mullen ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A dear son-in-law. So happy to have you as part of the family.  You bring so much fun to all of our events.  Always smiling and always there when you are needed.  It is a joy and pleasure to see how much you love your family and how it is reflected in everything you do.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Maureen and Jim McElderry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[H/RHappy Birthday Drew, really your 50.I thought you wer much older than that. Have a great day my friend. JT]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jerry Taylor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andrew is one of the nicest guys you'll ever meet....unless you forget his name on the golf course!   He will remember a special time when the corporate VP of Human Resources referred to him as "boy" because he forgot his first name.  My ears are still burning...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gary Novak]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To the ultimate Steeler fan.... from your semi-Steeler, semi- Bills fan./RHappy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gary Novak]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Oh Andrew......Happy 50th Birthday!!/RMy funny memory of you is when we discovered we shared the same B-day...we were at "The Top of The Hub" in Boston.  It was one of our many fun nights out with you and Carolyn!!/R/RWishing you a wonderful Birthday!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kerri Finnegan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our flatter fluttered its way into your mailbox]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anonymous]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite thing about Uncle Andrew is how he always tells my mom that I must be the prettiest girl in the school.....have a great birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[MaryKate :)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Andrew!  Too many fun memories to pick just one - but our Cubs games were always the best day ever!  HB!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Phil and Kathleen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the nicest and most awesome guy, turning 50, we know!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark, Sonia, DJ Peterson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It is really hard to wish a Cubs fan a Happy Birthday! :) Hope all your wishes come true - except if that wish is a Cubs win. Enjoy your day and thank you for being such a great friend to my dad!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hana Olliges]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday you old man! come back to the farm and see us, we miss you. Hope all is well and that you enjoy your day! Oh, and the Cubs are terrible, duh:)/R/R-With love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gayla]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 50th /Rto an all-around great guy!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andy & Kristina Haines]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I think of you, I smile! /RYou are like a big bear hug that is always there to give comfort. /RI am so very grateful that we met back at 2555 and hoping for some dark & stormy nights in the future.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Deb "The Nooker" Raines]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 50th Andrew!  Will never forget refusing your Red color choice on the Magnum because of the extra cost and then ordering it for others (Carl).  I will never hear the end of it! Also you telling Darla we once dated and then she called me on it! Priceless!  Go Cards]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Forever Friend, Michelle Hire]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We met on adjacent treadmills in a chicago apartment.  I knew I like him when he joked that  he stays focused on the treadmill by gazing into the mirror and "running toward the fat guy."/RClassic Andy.  immediate connection.  one of my best friends.  miss you buddy]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rob Raines]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember one time when you used to live in Chicago, we were watching tv with Evan. Evan and I were sitting in the red Cars tiny couch. Then you started to tickle us! We were laughing, giggling, and having fun. Happy birthday Uncle Andrew!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Bizzy ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my fondest memories is bringing my little brother home when he joined our family. He had such fat little cheeks, big brown eyes, an adorable smile, and a huge heart. Come to think of it, he still does! Welcome to the top of the hill! Happy 50th!!! /RLove, Allison]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allison Walker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ahndy saved my father's life in more ways than one.  Ahndy kept my dad connected to friends at Ferro, and by checking on him at his apartment.  Ahndy spreads genuine joy wherever he goes, and we are all the luckier for knowing him.  Happy 50th to one very great man ! ????]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan and Casey in Montana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There isn't a nicer man in this neighborhood.  Seriously!  Your kindness and generosity were evident from the moment I met you and it's never faded!  You deserve every nice thing people say about you and then some.  Happy 50th Andrew! Enjoy every minute of it.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leslie Kemm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the nicest person turning 50 we know!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peterson Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andrew,/R     Wishing you a very happy 50th birthday!  We love you and your family...even though you're not EAGLES fans!  Cheers to another 50 years!  Happy Birthdsy!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, The Ostroff Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We schauermans always thought the world of Andrew. But the funniest thing was that when we all had children as they would come east to meet our cousins, the one every single one remembered was always Andrew! He has a gift. Happy birthday from the West!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anne Schauerman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best salesman in the company. Brags about being an expert fisherman - I can still hear his screams on Silver Lake when he tried to put the wiggly worm on the hook.  We were tied 5 fish to 5 fish, when he cut my line bringing in the tiebreaker so he wouldn't lose!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larry Bauer (LRB)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andrew,/RI have met you only a couple of times. I saw good humor and joy of life and deep compassion  for your family. Great qualities. Enjoy the next 50 years with the same great attitude./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cathy Haviland]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember when you were young and you thought you couldn't pet a bull? You were very timid about approaching the 2500 pound animal roaming free in the field. But you went into the field carrying young Evan and pet the bull.  The bull even tried to lick you! Happy 50th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love ya, Dean and Peggy Field]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memory of Andrew is on his and Carolyn's wedding day. Andrew made my sister the happiest person in the world on that day. He has always put Carolyn first and that is my favorite aspect of Andrew. Happy Birthday!!!!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim McElderry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 50th Birthday, Andrew!  It has been a real trip over the years, lots of laughs.  Quick review: Turkeyville, tropical paradise, and short innuendos.  Enjoy your day, my friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sherrie Plummer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ah, Andrew; you're getting older! Seems like just last year when we yelled "Hey, Andrew, get over here" to save you from the whining of your sisters. Over the years, you've become a valued friend and neighbor, and I'll miss the adventures as the era of Walloon ends.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom Shifrin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kostner Ave. is not the same without you. Andrew, you made everyday SPECIAL- the best neighbor anybody can wish for.Enjoy your big day & wish you all the best in the years to come .]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mathew & Sally]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/RThanks for always being there to cheer me up!  /RAnd for my regular supply of milk shakes, Timbits and Coppola wine!  You are an amazing guy who makes everyone feel like family! /RHappy 50th! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mrs. Troy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love our awesome memories of Chicago, nights at our kitchen table and dinners with the Walkers!  We will always have enough Bacardi and diet Pepsi whenever you stop by during your next 50 years!  /RHappy Birthday Old Man!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike and Ali]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Mr. Walker!/RThanks for always making me feel like one of your boys! /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jack Troy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[SSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS!/R(That's Happy Birthday in snake language!)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maggie and Ashley Troy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To my fellow gym rat, who supports his family and friends.  The Steeler's stink, but your Cubs are due.  Thank you for your service in the military.  Your boys have a great role model.  Happy 50th, the Ipp's love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Ippoliti's]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andrew, we love how genuinely excited you are to visit with Grace & Liam. Always smiling and always with a big, warm, heart-felt greeting.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim, Jim, Grace & Liam McElderry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We were in the car with the Walker boys singing "Call me Maybe" together really loudly. Mr Walker was so embarrassed, he wanted to keep the windows up and music down, but Evan kept turning it up. It was really fun!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alina Swaney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love our shared appreciation for the motherland, God's country, Michigan /Rand that you know how it feels to parent a wrestler (or 3)./R/RYou & Carolyn remind us to laugh, smile, appreciate our blessings and look for joy in all circumstances.  /RCongrats on your first 50]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kirk and Debbie Elken]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[RCIA classes at Queen of All Saints - interesting discussions, Fr Trout, Purgatory presentation by Ray!?! We'll never forget that. I think you'll be going to heaven....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ann O'Neill]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We miss you in Chicago! You will always hold a special place in our hearts. We wish you a very special 50th birthday celebration. Looking forward to the next time we see you and the family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shawn, Ann, Kelsey & Conor O'Neill]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Andrew!/R/RYou are one of the most positive, giving men that I know.  It is a honor to call you our friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randy & Krista]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Drew... I will never forget the 9 holes of golf we played in the rain and you were at even par after the first 4 holes. Happy 50th !! Just wait!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tucker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andrew is one of the best hires I've ever made; great salesman, technically strong, connects well with people, strong moral character, never cheats in golf & will always be a very dear friend....if you believe any of this I have a bridge to sell you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Doug Harty]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ One of my favorite times with Andrew was the night before his wedding.  I didn't really know him, but ended up being with Andrew and one of his buddies late into the night.  After that I knew he would be welcome into the family.  Other than his Michigan blind spots....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Johnny Schauerman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andrew has a special spot with my kids.  For some reason they all like him - I can't figure it out.  He is very lucky to have Caroline put up with him.  Now that he is old I hope we get to see him more.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Johnny and Claudia Schauerman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[And there was the time we had dinner at Lakeside Charlies after a successful day selling to foundry customers in Michigan. Their we sat with a beer in hand, admiring a wondrous sunset and enjoying another successful day's end. Ahh to be a dirt peddler!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Logsdon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday, Andrew! We look forward to seeing you every year, you have a way of making us all feel special. Missing you is not acceptable, we'll just find another venue for a thousand marshmallows and Dark and Stormys! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Swaneys]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Warm wishes for a very happy 50th birthday./RSo many fun memories - tennis in Florida, Taylor Dane on the radio, Chuck's Steakhouse and days at the beach watching your boys ride in the waves!/R ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maureen, Eileen, Anne and Sarah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Andrew! WOW 50! How long ago were the Boston days? Remember diet coke in the freezer? SO funny! Have a fantastic day with your amazing wife and beautiful boys!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen and Angelo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Happy 50th Andy!  Lots and lots of memories in all these years we have been friends.  Get your paperwork in - you're late!  I seem to say that a lot!  Here's to good friends --CHEERS!  And go Cubs!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jody (Larson) Anderson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 50th, Andy!  Here's hoping that you don't wait another 50 years for your Cubbies!  Have a wonderful day with your family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cindy Waters  - STL Forever!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Drew --  happy birthday from the Left Coast. /RCome on out and visit me I have a room at a local hotel for you.  They miss you.   Same bed and sheets that you remember !  /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Don]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andrew, I enjoy our banter about who's the best team that season.  You love the Steelers and I divide my admiration between my hometown Giants and adopted Chargers.  I love that we share our passion of football. It's great being your friend and neighbor.  Welcome to 50!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marian(and all the Nalitts)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andy (a.k.a. "boy") used to come to the Champaign office when he was living in Chicago and we miss those visits now that he lives in PA.  He's a genuinely good guy and a true friend.  Happy 50th boy!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chad Beukema]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the original flatterbox. You make everyone you meet feel special and appreciated. Thank you for being our friend  through many ups and downs over the last eight years. Whenever we need a good laugh, we think of the fish in the disposal!  We love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt & Bridget]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 50th Birthday to one of the nicest guys I know!  You always make me laugh (lots of Catholic girl jokes but I forgive you)  I have learned to always check the gas in my car and that you are POSITIVE about your month end numbers!  Enjoy your day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pattie (PK)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The popcorn machine on the couch in the Chicago house with pretend ^!*@er and salt. Happy Birthday!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah Peltier]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One summer I woke up early and you and Patrick were already awake. Patrick was a baby and you took us to the little bayside breakfast place in lavallette. I had so much fun laughing and feeding Patrick. That memory always comes to mind when I think of you.happy birthday]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anne (anniepants) Peltier]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[50 years of stories and I've heard every one]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your pride and joy Evan Walker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are always smiling, Don't stop, not even when you turn 100!!/RThe best for you. Happy Happy Birthday!!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Guillen-Perez Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Andrew from Larry and Joanne in the Bronx ... "For each petal on the Shamrock this brings a wish your way. Good health,  good luck and happiness for today and every day."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larry and Joanne Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Where to start - teddy bear, test tube, duker renting rooms by the hour... definitely you out running the gator on all fours was my favorite.  Still can't believe you knew you were quicker by jumping on all fours!..  Cheers to the slowest gator in the world!  Happy 50th]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Curtis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[40 years ago we met.  Since then I have had a brick fall on my head from the top of your house, a hammer test my not so hard hat, walnuts throwen at me, and camping at the land.  Most of all 40 years ago I found a true brother.  One that I will alway love and admire.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ryan Hamilton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Lots of memories from watching youtube at 11pm at Walloon to the Christmas tree falling and you shaking with anger.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your favorite son, Liam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Loved our trip to Rhode Island and the Lobster Mac and Cheese at Brick Alley Pub!  Thanks Dad for having lunch with me and all my friends at New Eagle!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your beautiful son Patrick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hammer to Ryan's head. Pita Pocket Bread Frplace hotdogs/ice skating. Night fishing. Ski to Old Mill Golf Course. B'day pancakes w/smile. Reserved front seats at play. Torn pants w/$in pocket for graduation. Detroit game/hole in car floor. Only Ryan has $$. Squirt (pop)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill/Elizabeth Hamilton/321 W. Cass]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey Andy, Wow! 50 yrs old! AARP is now officially in your "Go To Cards Collection".... I want to wish you a Happy Birthday and I hope you have many more to come Pal "I just Love hearing those Old Navy Stories of you protecting Bermuda on the USS Miller" Happy Birthday ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Hallahan ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Uncle Andrew! Hope I get to see you sometime this summer, if not, looking forward to Christmas. /RLOVE YOU! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eileen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>