<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2475-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/10/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[shannon komen]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[1746 89th Pl NE]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Clyde Hill]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[WA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[98004]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sand]]></cardcolor>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[3 tips for happiness.../R--Marry your best friend; they're proud of you at your best and 'have your back' when you need help. /R--Laugh together! Laugh at yourself; (no one is perfect : )/R--You'll feel better when you've been kind than you will when being right/Rlove you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[-Aunt Shannon ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I like about both Jacquelyn and Josh is that they are probably the two most "easy" people in our family. Both of them are such easy-going, positive people, and it makes them so fun to be around. I'm so proud of you both, and so glad that you found each other!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kyle Komen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jacquelyn- you were always a happy, even tempered baby and have grown into a truly lovely woman.  You have found your wonderful match in Josh and we couldn't be more thrilled for you both!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All our love, Aunt Linda & family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jac & Josh,/RWe are so happy for you two! Who would have thought the older baseball guy and the Gatorade girl would be getting married! Married life is the good life! Josh always remember:/R"happy wife =happy life". /RLove you guys!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Lentz's]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Like a flower ???? i have watched your relationship grow and blossom since you two met.  As a parent I could not be happier to know your future will be together. Respect each other, listen to each other, share your dreams together.  ???? With love and Congratulations ! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura aka Proud! Mamma and MOB]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jacquelyn and Josh, your kindness and compassion towards others and each other is a gift and should be used as a model for all. Thank you for your everlasting friendship and all the great memories. Cheers to many more!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maddy & Pepe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It is impossible to not feel like you are best friends with Team Skomen whenever you are around them. I love how welcoming and lovable of people they truly are; amazing individuals but even better as a team. Feel blessed to be a part of their lives.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sierra West]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We can't imagine a more perfect couple. The love you have for eachother is contagious. Scott and I are so lucky to have you both in our lives and can't wait for all the many adventures to come!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Scott & Claire]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jacquelyn and Josh, We are so incredibly happy for you! I knew from the first time I met Josh and saw you two together, that you had something truly special. Always cherish that and remember to continue having as much fun together as you already do. We love you both!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brittany and Kelly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are two AWESOME people, thus your marriage will be equally AWESOME. /RWhen the time comes when it doesn’t seem so terrific; whether that time lasts an hour, a day, a week or longer, try to work hard to make it feel the way it feels today. It will always be worth it. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Greg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Josh and Jacquelyn    My best wishes for the bright future you deserve. What a perfect union.Two bright and especially thoughtful,considerate people. Also Jacquelyn sends really cute [and insulting] birthday cards.  /R                             ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rich Komen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It would be hard to find a cuter, more positive or fun couple. We've loved getting to know Josh these past several years; everyone adored him right from the start./RJosh- you are the perfect compliment to Jacquelyn, who we love- and a great addition to the family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Greg/Shan, Kyle/Christina, Bo&Quinn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Josh and Jack,/R/RYou are both always so full of energy and tremendously uplifting to be around. Thank you for being two of my best friends. The future is bright.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Burgher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Find in each other for that thing that makes you have that feeling that is better than being just happy.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Janet Komen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jacquelyn and Josh,/RI am so happy for you two! Your love for each other is so inspiring and I can't wait to see where it takes you. Congratulations!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellie Komen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[J&J! The love you have for one another and for friends&family is beyond admirable. You are each other's best friends, confidants, &PICs and your smiles&wits lighten a room! I am lucky to have watched your relationship evolve and can't wait for many memories yet to come.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lots of love, Liv]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love the way you look at each other with such joy-you bring out the best in each other in such a loving, fun-filled way! We know you will enjoy a lifetime of happiness together! (We're also secretly pleased you now have your own supply of wine)...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larry and Anne ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jacquelyn,/RWe are so happy for you two! We knew from the first time seeing you together, that you had a great friendship. We see the happiness and joy you bring each other. May your life together be filled with wonderful adventures. Take time to have some fun each day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[William & Tiffany Jolly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jacquelyn and Josh, you guys will have an amazing life together! You are both such positive and fun-loving people. Congrats again and here's to many great memories ahead!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Riley Komen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Take time to enjoy each other, plan date nights often, laugh together, cry together but most importantly keep saying, "I love you" every day. Sometimes the little things like a note or a hug add up and keep the fire alive.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kristin and Greg Metcalf]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You both make it look easy!/R/RThank you, Jacquelyn, for being a positive force in our family. For your kindness, thoughtfulness, and always seeking the good in others. /R/RAnd for finding Josh!/R/RSo much love!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Keep the humor levels up and the toilet seat down. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sally Bergesen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A great marriage can last without ever trying to assign blame for anything. Also BJs are way overrated versus sex with the lights on.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob and Sarah Lesko ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jacquelyn and Josh, /R/RI can't even begin to tell you how happy I am to have met you both this year. You are such an incredible couple and every time I'm around you, I can't help but smile knowing that you both found your best friend to spend the rest of your life with.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heather ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jack and Josh, You two bring fun and joy to every situation, and together are such a bright couple. Keep shining my friends!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Jackie ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Never take yourself too seriously. Laugh and let the little things go. /R/RBut always take your love seriously. Work for it, protect it, cherish it, respect it./R/RLaugh and love. The rest will figure itself out. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[mac]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I was so excited when Josh came and told me he was going to propose to Jacquelyn on their vacation in Hawaii./RWe are so blessed to have a beautiful, smart, fun to be around daughter in our family./RThank-you, Lord./RI love you both so much!/RLots of love Mom/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jan Scofield  {Josh's Mom}]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The marriage adventure will bring both difficult and amazing times, so don't forget about your communication. Your dependence is as important as your independence, so  don't loose either and stay supportive of aspirations.  Work hard, play hard, always bring the Love!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Carruthers']]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jack & Josh,/RYou continue to inspire me with your love for each other and everyone around you. I can't wait to celebrate your big day - you deserve nothing but the best. Love you both.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hannah Maserjian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You guys have a happiness and easy going attitude that is contagious to the people around you. You are both such fun and caring people and I know you'll have an amazing, life-lasting marriage!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Quinn Komen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always enjoy the moment, and never take any day for granted. You two have a bright future ahead of you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo, Julie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember - boys are stupid and girls are crazy. Though these are not words I would use to describe you, this is simply a fact of life and applies respectively to every man and woman on earth. Please remember this, and please be patient when the other acts as such.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bo Komen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Josh & Jack,/R/RTo keep a healthy relationship you must keep the sandy burgers cooking and early bed time camping trips rolling! Cheers and may your love flow like wine!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Willy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[* Spend time together on a regular basis; don't let your busy life get in the way of this!/R* Share your dreams and support each others./R* Regular, open, honest communication is essential.  Don't keep secrets!!/R* Play / have fun together!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brad Komen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Dog Equals Happy Life]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Pupos]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the most kind and genuine couple we know and we are lucky to have you as friends.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Pupos]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have never met a pair of people as genuinely sincere and interested in the people around them as you two.  You both truly make the company around you better. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joey Dunn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happiest congratulations to the sweetest pair I know! Always remember the goofy kids you each fell in love with, for they could not have predicted a future this bright. Wishing you more days as happy as this one and more occasions for celebration!/RXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[J&J - /R/RDo stuff together. /RTake that however you want to. /R/RWe love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Scotty and Jess Nelson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>