<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2479-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/13/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Lilli Ouyang]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[352 Pacheco Street]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[San Francisco]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[CA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[94116]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDEX_PRIORITYOVERNIGHT]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy birthday Phil!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Philip Ouyang]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Your partner-in-crime]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I met Phil in a dorm room in Dobbs Ferry, New York.  He and I were unloading the many bags of our daughters, roommates at CityTerm for the fall 2009 semester.  I saw a man of purpose.  He followed Lilli's orders and made sure Chloe was comfortable. A guy you could trust]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Cohen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how Phil is composed and in charge but let's Lilli think she is in charge! I love how much Phil loves his family and would do anything for them! He is a good friend to so many people, too. I feel lucky to be his friend! Happy happy birthday! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda Nathan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Philip knows the best wines ever!  I remember it was my birthday and I was debating if I drink ...and since Philip always knows how to order the best of everything he ordered a killer bottle and I had a great birthday with his wonderful family!  Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Marcia and Drennon ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remembered vividly that I was standing in the kitchen, with my mom busy preparing dinner one night in '84. Out of no where, she asked whether the man I had been dating actually talked! Yes, that would be Phil- a man of few words, wise, honest & strong. He is my rock.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lilli ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday to a man who enjoys good food and fine wines and generously hosts fabulous meals.  (Let's forget Greens and stick to meat!!)  All the best for a magnificent birthday with great food, superb wine and company of loving family and friends! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Deborah ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Philip! Happy Birthday! Thank you for always taking me to the best restaurants all around the world! You are so generous!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Drennon Kimpton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[THE gentleman for all seasons & reasons who loves the best = Lilli, Brittany & Chloe.  Know you also love an autobahn-tested navy blue babe Porsche.  Know so as we waited while you watched valet park car in primo spot @ Gary Danko's.  All blessings, many happy returns.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barry & Vickie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to you Philip, on this special day! You have a family that I admire, always travelling to exotic places with your girls and wife, always generous to your friends! I especially enjoyed our trip to Napa where you told stories about the mud bath you took!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cynthia and Claude]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are too many special moments to name just one: eating only french fries for a week, learning to drive, blasting the Beatles on the way to school, father-daughter dinner dances. I have loved them all.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brittany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Missing our flight to San Francisco and staying the night in the very luxurious JFK airport hotel.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brittany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Scuba trips in remote locations (and not knowing how to set up our own gear).]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brittany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Philip, you are one of the nicest guys I know!/RHappy,happy birthday!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy Kefalas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday dear Philip. We are grateful to have shared so many wonderful moments with you and your beautiful family over the past 22 years. Your good humor and generosity always make you the most welcome company. We look forward to creating more memories together!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With love from Bob, Katy and kids]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When Philip looks at 'modern art' at museums, he wonders why artists would name their paintings "Untitled". Having played artist himself, Philip created a 5" mosaic square for my garden table and aptly named it "Moldy Ham". An artist with few words--just the right ones."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michele]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite memories with Dad is going to Game 1 of the World Series in 2010. Every Giants game with Dad is special but this one was the best. I was stressed out from applying to colleges but Dad always knows how to keep me grounded and I'll never forget this.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chloé]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[At the end of my sophomore year at Vassar, Dad flew out to help me pack and store my stuff. Though this may seem insignificant, I loved the time we spent together just the two of us - having meals, and enjoying each other's company. I'm always grateful for all he does. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chloé]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dad is one of the silliest people I know. When people tell me that they like my sense of humor or that I'm also silly, I know that I get it from Dad. I am so lucky to have someone so goofy as a father - he reminds me to always laugh and to not take myself so seriously.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chloé]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I appreciate that whenever the family gets together for meals there's always the danger of Philip and the brothers making table sport out of the most random, inappropriate, juvenile, disgusting, and taboo topics./R/RHappy Birthday and Stay Cool!!  Cheers!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bro-in-law Fred]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for your guidance and support all these years.  Happy Birthday!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jonathan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Phil is known to be a fabulous and devoted dad and husband. I witnessed Phil loading the largest musical instrument, the harp into his car.  /RPhil just does it with a smile!/RDidn't you ever wish they had chosen to play the flute or the harmonica instead? /RHappy Birthday]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alice Mark]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday to a wonderful person and a great boss./REnjoy your day./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Yvonne Yu]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Phil & I meet monthly for lunch, usually at Tadich Grill./ROur standard lunch menu:/RBombay Sapphire Martini straight up w/ olive. /RA bottle of white wine/ROyster Rockefeller/RWienerschnitzel/Rfollowed by final glass of martini/RYes, we live dangerously & /Rthank god for Uber!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[On a trip to Paris, Philip suggested that we use the limo service of the Georges V. To our surprise, a rep of the hotel met us at CDG, escorted us through immigration, assisted with luggage and whisked us off. Philip has been the go-to person for travel tips since.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vicky O.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[On one of Philip’s travels to see his parents in HK, he brought them so much joy. He had plans to golf with friends in China but family circumstances arose that required a decision on his part. He chose family. They were moved by his act and were proud of him.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vicky & Giannina]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Now that I've read everyone else's comments, I feel compelled to be more sentimental. Happy birthday Philip, wishing you the best of days. Not to be shared with others but share this with Lilli: Our bathroom arrangement at the lodge at Pebble Beach.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sammy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Many years ago, four of us went to Scottsdale. We were so cheap that we all shared a room. Everyone was snoring. Philip had a high-pitched snore; Albert had a low-pitched snore; Teddy had random spurts of snores. All together they drove me crazy.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sammy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Compliments to your judgment when you agreed to a daring mountain bike ride with me at the steep and beautiful Long Ridge Open Space Preserve on the back of my tandem...what a great way to build a trusting relationship.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rickson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Phillip, you represent the values and character of a loving husband, caring father, faithful friend and cherish those moments with family celebrating life. You understand that balance in life is needed but includes huge amounts of Love. /RHappy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mrs. Coleman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always know the best restaurants (and bars) in any city, its always a fun time when Phillip is in town!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Audrey Snyder]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always remember our drive and breakfast with the Porsche. Great spending time with just Philip]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A favorite Philip moment was at a smart Paris restaurant, L'Arome. When the bill was presented, it was clear the restaurant was taking advantage. Negotiations ensued, the owner was adamant; I went ballistic. Philip, the adult, remained calm and resolved the issue.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael Wilson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Some of my fondest memories of Philip are from our time on the MA Wine Committee. It was a terrific, creative group and Philip could always be counted on for good humor and good sense. He donated lovely wine and connected us to generous sources for wine and sake!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frances Wilson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have nothing but good memories of Philip. He is always the best dresser in the crowd with not a hair out of place. Philip has the best temperament of anybody I know. Nothing upsets him....the ideal golf partner. Happy Birthday and many more!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Kwok]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Just one moment? When I think of Philip, I think of so many Special moments! Each is a moment of such kindness towards others and such generosity of spirit. Philip has the warmest heart and ready smile, and always lifts my spirits! Happy, Happy Birthday! :-)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pam, Will & Mollie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Philip-/Rhappy birthday!/RYou are one of the nicest guys I know!/RI don't have anything else more special, you are the special one!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy Kefalas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Philip,/RLiz and I have many moments to remember. We have both thoroughly enjoyed the chance to have wonderful dinners with you and Lilli. Your insight and kind nature have meant the world to us!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Travis Brownley and Liz Katz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you /Rfor always laughing at my stale jokes/Rfor loving me even when I'm insuffersble/Rfor standing by me when the world is against me/Rfor taking care of me when I break down/RMost of all, thank you/Rfor coming into my life and stayed./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lilli ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Honey-/RI'll never forget how I decided erroneously that it would be fun to run towards you and leapt into your arms, never doubting that you could catch me.   /RThe hard fall to the picnic ground did not hurt nearly as much as the hysterical laughters from our friends!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lilli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Philip! One of the great joys of having a child is meeting her wonderful friends and their wonderful parents. Philip, you are a super dedicated father to Chloe and Brittany! Thank you for your generosity in sharing good times with our family!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Cathy + Greg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Philip! I can't recall one specific special moment (but I do recall those early dating years as you pursued my dear friend Lilli!). For some strange reason, I remember you always wore an IZOD sweater to school! Now you are too cool for that! Cheers!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sheila & family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The most fun thing one can do with Philip is go out and eat. He has a bigger and more inventive appetite than anyone I have ever met. Nice to break bread with someone who love food as much as we do. Here's to many more chances to do so.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Greg and Cathy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best "Phil" moment I remember was a few years back when Phil reserved a TRX fitness class for his family. Lilli's brother works hard for the first 30 minutes and runs out to throw up. Phil, who was taking his sweet ass time says "Whats his problem?!" Classic.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christopher Tozzi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wanting to join me in the frigid waters off of Stinson Beach, the only wet suit available was the 20 year old black wet suit donated by my wife's ex high school boyfriend. Philip was game, put it on, holes everywhere in the suit from age, and jumped in! That's Philip!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wes Moore]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I think of Philip, no one particular moment comes to mind.  What does come to mind is 20 years of working together, loyalty and, above all, friendship. I can think of no client or colleague whom I hold in higher regard or for whom I have greater admiration.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peter Aitelli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[With Philip's creative problem solving we turned the little School camping trip (cold tents, campfire food, sleeping bags) into a sleepover for Chloe and Isabel at the beach house starting after the s'mores. Philip and I see eye to eye and he is a great friend! Congrats]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate Moore]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>