<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2481-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/13/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[April Williams]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[125 Warwick Road]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Northfield]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[MA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[01360]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_60]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Retirement]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Jim Conlon]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Time for a new adventure!]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I first started in commercial sales at HNE you agreed to spend time with me and give me advice. I started with a traditional sales rep opening. You stopped me and said build the relationship first and the business will come. Best business advice ever. Good luck Jim]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Josh Nadeau]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your retirement is bittersweet for me; you will be greatly missed.  There's not enough room to say all I have to say, but I'm sure you know the sentiment. You're an excellent coach & a wonderful friend. You only live once, but if you work it right once is enough. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[April Williams]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim, you had the best collection of 45 rpm records I've ever seen, and Mark and I were rarely able to beat you in 2 on 1! On the professional level, I have always appreciated your advice and assistance. We'll miss you at the office. Best wishes for the future!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peter and Megin Ziomek]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for building a business that so highly values relationships.  /R/RWhen I phoned your office from a puddle of tears on the floor of the elevator lobby outside my dad's hospital room at the Lahey Clinic, I was so glad you were on the other end of the line.  /R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cinda Jones, W.D. Cowls, Inc.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[While we strongly object to your retiring, we are grateful that you've trained a first rate team, and found a buyer of your business who shares your values and focus on personal customer service.  /R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cinda Jones, W.D. Cowls, Inc.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim ha sbeen a friend, neighbor, insurance agent, and business associate, but I will never forget the way he helped me when I was contemplating getting into this financial services business. He pulled out all the stops, and I can never thank him enough. Good luck Jim!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allen Davis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim is the consummate gentleman to deal with from the carrier side... always had his clients needs first.  Congratulations Jim on an extraordinary career... Many years of happiness to you and your family./RThank you for everything these past years.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peter Graham- Security Mutual Life]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim,/RI will always remember/Ryour constant smile, /R talks of travels taken and/Rtrips yet to come./RThanks for the years of /Rfriendship and support./REnjoy each and every /Rmoment of the days ahead!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Trish Vassallo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Retirement only means that it is time for new adventures!  Cherish every moment and have fun!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wendy Ann Papko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We are going to miss your local restaurant reviews and vacation destination advice.  Each year we looked forward to our meeting with you even when we knew you were bringing us news of a rate increase!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill and Kay Daugherty]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim has been such a joy to work with!! Vast knowledge about the insurance industry, very professional, always has the best interests of his clients at heart. Jim's more than a broker; he's been invaluable to our business and I count him as a friend! Thanks so much, Jim!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ron Heald (W.D. Cowls)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memories of Jim are all about the golf tournament. From the beginning, Jim and I worked together to make it happen. Jim is special because he is so real. We have shared lots of personal and professional things and I treasure his friendship.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joan Temkin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There was a time that Jim would call me Trish and Trish he would call Denise - one day we both were name tags!!  I have enjoyed our talks as I travel between his office and the real estate office.  His encouragement and friendship I will never forget!  You miss you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Denise Sawicki]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim came to every meeting we had together well prepared.  He always had our best interest, and helped many individuals who were in difficult situations over the years.  Thank you for your care and management of our benefits package.  You will be missed!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob Logan, Palmer Foundry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim, /R/RYour are a gentleman, a professional across the board and a friend. Well done on all fronts./R/RBest regards,/R/RPat ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat Hughes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will never forget how Jim treats his parents and what a special relationship they share. I believe you can learn a great deal about a person based on how they treat their parents. They share mutual respect and admiration and that is truly a gift.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rick and Donna Doleva]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memories: Playing my first round of golf at The Ranch and you were so encouraging. Great restaurant recommendations for Mystic and Ogunquit. Always challenging me to be the best Account Exec I can be, I love "Norms per K" reporting! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Warm Regards, Sandy Stankiewicz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I assume that you have copyrighted the "horizontal handshake" ?! I hope that hasn't influenced your golf swing. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Coull]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim I will miss you. I will miss our little talks in the office and in the lunch room. We are both survivors of cancer in the same year and as I always ask you how you are you always say *I'm Well* Tagging each other with our fist. Enjoy your retirement. XOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christine Ryan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Jim, Thank you for always being a great person to work with over the past 8 years. I always enjoyed our industry conversations and how we both agreed on a lot of topics. Enjoy your retirement! You deserve it! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gregory Spero ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Jim -/ROne of the greatest pleasures of my career in the Hospitality Industry was the pleasure of working with you. Thank you for your knowledge, your patience, and your sense of humor. You will be missed!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Debbie McNaney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim,/R/RIt has been a distinct pleasure in getting to know you in my capacity as Executive Director of the Amherst Area Chamber.  Thank you for your years of dedication and support to the organization.  Best wishes in your retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Don Courtemanche]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Jim,/RThe Amherst Area Business Community is better, stronger and more vibrant because of you. Thank you for you many contributions, most especially to the Golf Tournament. Wishing you health and happiness in your well-deserved retirement. With warmest regards,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie Marcus]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim and I got really close after "buying" season tickets together for UMASS basketball. This is where we discovered we have so much in common. We share similar health issues, similar sardonic attitudes and of course a similar sense of humor(much to our wives chagrin). ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[We love you, Steven and Michele]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I enjoy every interaction with Jim. His knowledge, strategic thinking and integrity is what drives him and I find that very inspiring and motivating. I wish him a great retirement and health and happiness.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian Kivel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It is about time you caught up to me and retired.  Enjoy it because you deserve it.  Congrats to a great man, great friend with a great smile.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dan Maloney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["I'm just a phone call away..."  and indeed you were  always there for us!  /R/RThanks Jim!/REnjoy Retirement to the fullest!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Silverscape Designs]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Jim,/R/RIt has been a great experience working with you and you will be truly missed.  Your attention to detail and going the extra mile to help others will not be forgotten. You are truly the BEST....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cheryl Sweetman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What started with business quickly evolved into a friendship full of laughs and great times!!!/R/RWishing you all the best!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff Krawczyk]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Irish Blessing/R/RFor each petal on the shamrock/RThis brings a wish your way/RGood health, good luck, and happiness/RFor today and every day]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Georgia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim at my first golf committee meeting:/RNo self-respecting golfer would play with a logo ball/RI’m thinking: Who is this guy? Way too serious/R But since then I have learned to admire and respect his passion and attention to detail/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your friend Youssef]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim’s greetings are always like a wonderful sunny morning: warm, very pleasant, and so genuine! I’ll miss your greetings! I’ll miss our laughs and gripes about the weather. I’ll miss seeing you and working with you. And I wish you great weather, always!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan Dorais]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey Jim, now you will have time to get that jump shot back again.  Always enjoyed working together. /REnjoy your time on the links.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob Kieras]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have truly been one of my strongest mentors for the past 14 years, I appreciate your investment in my abilities, you will be missed!!!!Enjoy retirement, you deserve it!/R     Jill G.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jill Goulet]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'll never forget your impact on me personally and professionally, Jim. Very early in my career you always gave me the time even if you were busy and I always learned something from you. Congratulations on an outstanding career - wishing you a happy and healthy back 9!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Justin Jude Slattery]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memory of Jim is a simple one.  I was in a car accident and I received one card in the mail.  It was from Jim and April.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Connole]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Despite his insistence that beer tastes better with ice cubes, Jim Conlon is one of my favorite people ever. He can get $20 bucks for a good cause, run a meeting as efficiently as anyone alive, and he's a great sounding board, mentor, and friend. Happy golfing, Jim!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tony Maroulis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ I've been working with many 'volunteer' groups - personal and professional - for over 40 years. Jim is, by far, the most able 'volunteer LEADER' I've had the honor to work with. He excels in every way as he successfully manages the "Herd Of Cats" he leads. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Fred Smith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim,/R/RI have enjoyed our many years working together under one roof!  I'll especially miss our conversations comparing travel notes.  Hope you stop by from time to time so we can continue these!  Wishing you and Carol many years of sharing life's joys together.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sue Henry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim/RIt was great working with you /RI wish you the very best]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Beth Heath]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim,/RYour kindness, good humor, love of people and support for the Chamber over all these years truly reflects the quality person and friend you are./R/RNow, your golfing is a discussion for another day!/R/RI wish you the very best.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larry Archey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ohy: a few weeks after I started at JFC we had a broker breakfast.  I had to ask you for cash to get out of the garage, you were pulled over, and then I accidentally called 911.  You just laughed.  And I…completely embarrassed, the beginning of a wonderful relationship.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michelle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim never steered us wrong & helped guide us through the health insurance process to make sure that we have the best available especially when one our own really needs it. He put us at ease by sharing his own experiences with us.  We thank him for many years!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Judie, Dave and Katie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always enjoyed talking with Jim about golf, UMass hoops and how the industry was changing.  Congrats Jim on you retirement.  Enjoy every day of it.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Johnson - BCBSMA]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim, where has the time gone? As I reflect back, I think the thing that stands out the most is your friendship and the consideration that you have for people. You are well liked and for good reason. I wish you good health and hope that you have a wonderful retirement.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anthony and Pamela DeSimone]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You introduced me to ice cubes in beer after a sun filled day on the golf course.  During the day you were patient, had encouraging words to say and you are a lot of fun to be around!  I will always value your insight and willingness to share your experience.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Beth Helenius]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on your retirement Jim!!! Now you can really start living!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Broll and Sharon Povinelli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It may seem trite to say you are a great guy, but it is truly rare in life to meet someone of your quality, let alone work with him and be considered a friend. We've come a long way since having a beer at Rafters' last September. I raise my glass to you: cheers!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt Hollister, Hollister Insurance]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim, you have a contagious passion for servicing clients that I admire, and I know others do as well.  Your thoughtfulness and personal touch in how you work with people will be sorely missed.  I wish you all the best in your retirement.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer Lavigne-Fallon Health]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memory of Jim is sitting in his office at the small table talking about health care and the ever changing world it was.  The unique part was the conversation always finished with a few moments catching up on golf, family, travel and lovely island St. Maartin]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karrie Soltys]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A special note of appreciation to Jim for always encouraging me to pursue my passions in the health care industry, and timely words of wisdom he shared with me. Your support and kindness have touched many, and remain strong reminders to continue our journeys.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karrie Soltys]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am grateful to have had you in my life as a mentor, life coach & friend.  You took a chance on me,  believed in me & showed me all the ropes. I hold you & Carol in such high regards; you both deserve nothing but the best. Enjoy; never stop living life to its fullest!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rebecca Eckert]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>