<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2483-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/13/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Stefanie Haines]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[9 Basin Front Drive]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Newbury]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[MA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[01951]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Made with love for Stef & Dave]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Stef & Dave Kurtz]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Share all your joys, sorrows, blessing with each other daily....Do not let the Sun go down on your anger....A wife's smile and happiness are better than Sunshine....Take the Marriage Vows to heart, they will guide your love for one another....She's generally right! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ed Tonkin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations and warm good wishes.  Marriage is a grand adventure!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Moorhead (loving Wendy)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As my grandmother always said "take chances, Columbus did!"  I am so happy for you both and that you are taking a chance with each other.  With the right expectations and attitude I know your marriage will be a long and loving one.   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Romar & Andy Knapp]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Say "I love you" every day.  Say it often, mean it and most importantly ... show it. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Rode]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marriage is really not a daily 50/50 partnership. Some days it might be 60/40, or 70/30, or even 90/10. If you keep score, you'll always have a winner and a looser. The only way to succeed in your marriage, is not to keep score. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Rode]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Best marriage advice anyone ever gave us: Never stop dating and always be best friends. /R/RCongratulations, you two! Dave, we knew you were "The One" for Stef from the moment that we met you. Enjoy every moment of your lives together!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff and Laura Wheeler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Try new things together, compromise, and love the little things about eachother!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Zeebens]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Stef and Dave,/R/RMarriage is a partnership.   Honor that and respect each other.  /R/RHug each other every day!! /R/RCompliment your spouse often.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Michelle and Peter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Stef and Dave,/R/RYou two have had many adventures thus far in your relationship.  You are soon to begin a journey together that will challenge and enrich your lives.  You know an Ironman is tough but a successful marriage is even more difficult.  Give it your all!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Michelle and Peter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Stef and Dave,/Rwishing you both days filled with kindness, laughter, love and blessings.  /Rmay you both enjoy your amazing journey!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Auntie Lynn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My suggestion to the happy couple is to go outside on a clear night and spend some quiet time together under the stars and planets.  Catch a meteor, listen for a distant whip-poor-will or bull frog, and simply to enjoy the peace and calming influence of the night sky.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael McQuaide]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Just to wake up each morning, just to have you by my side./RJust to know that you're never really far away./RJust a reason for living, just to say I adore. Just to know that you're here in my heart to stay./RFor you, all the rest of my life, for you."/RJohn Denver]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Our love song to you both: Mom&Jim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always kiss each other goodnight and never go to bed mad at each other.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Lemay's]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kiss, touch and say “I love you” every day.  Don’t take a day together for granted, they go by too quickly.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Congratulations – Steve and Mariell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Trip over love, you can get up.  Fall in love and you fall forever.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Author Unknown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Since marriage is God's idea (Genesis 2:24), it makes sense that His design and purpose ought to be considered and followed.  There will be many challenges along the way but if we are on His road we can go to Him for His help.  Otherwise we are on our own!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ken, Pat and Esther Thomas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wedding Wishes: "May all your ups and downs be between the sheets!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anonymous]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[After 30 years of marriage we have found, It's the little things that matter....a compliment, a small kindness to show you care, overlooking mistakes/mishaps. Someone to listen, not judge and knowing you have a safe place to land when the outside world feels cruel.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jamie & Dee Benvie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love, patience and lots of wine are the keys to a happy marriage. Wishing you much happiness!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alison and Keith Kellerman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[LIVE your life to the fullest LAUGH at life's small things /RLOVE your life together /R/RWe're so happy for you guys! Can't wait to celebrate your special day neighb style! Love you guys! :) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Danielle and Kevin ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember my sentimental friend, a heart is not measured by how much you love, but by how much you are loved by others./R- the wizard of Oz ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leah Schaake and boys]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Yes, Dear."/R/R(It took me 10 years /Rto figure that out. - Ken)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Holli & Ken]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I was right- /R"Every kiss begins with Kurtz!"/R/RSo happy for you guys! xoxo/R/R/R/R/RWith love from your niece,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aunt Stef - When Dave proposed to you, I bet you found it very "engaging!!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Sam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Stefanie and Dave, /RWhen two wonderful people find each other and decide to share the rest of their lives, there's nothing better. You are those wonderful people and I couldn't be happier for you. Advice? Find and love newness in each other as you grow together. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gail Page]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Be patient with each other, share fun times, and respect each other's imperfections.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad & Charity]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To Stef and Dave, with love from Charity. This comes from a poem by Christina Rossetti titled, /R"What Good Shall My Life do Me?"/R/RLead lives of Love, that others who/RBehold your lives may kindle too/RWith Love and cast their lots with you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[“When you realize you want to spend the rest of your life with somebody, you want the rest of your life to start as soon as possible.”]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[When Harry Met Sally]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always laugh and drink wine]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[James and Cheryl]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[“Life’s better with company. Everybody needs a copilot.”]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Up In The Air]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hopefully you two still have the little corn man I gave you to take on your travels.  He can watch over your marriage and bring you all the happiness!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ally Lawson (Niece)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In life, actions speak louder than words. /RIn a marriage, words and actions go hand-in-hand.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ken & Holli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[God brought you two together and has blessed your beautiful marriage.  Be the first one to forgive and say I'm sorry, keep your promises, listen to each other with your heart, be sweet and kind to each other, have fun, laugh a lot, and say I love you everyday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sue Kurtz (Mother)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["You should be kissed, and often, and by someone who knows how."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gone with the Wind]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[LAUGH!/R/RLooks and physical activity will change as time goes on.  Your personalities and outlooks will change but if you can continue to laugh together it will get you through the toughest times.  /R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jason and Rose MacKenzie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember two things and everything will be fantastic!/R-Stef always gets the last slice of pizza/R-Dave always get to sleep in]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Sweebens]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A happy marriage is a long conversation that always seems too short.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[André Maurois (French author)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Stef, I've watched you grow up from a small child to a confident woman. I wish you and Dave the joy of sharing ideas, hopes and dreams, celebrating life's pleasures and facing life's ups and downs hand in hand.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Judy Eliasberg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember to always carve out time to date./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karl and Corey Strohmeyer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I wish you both a happy, healthy adventurous life. Staying friends and respecting your differences will make the journey even more pleasurable. I'm so happy for you both.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Donna]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We'll always remember that Thanksgiving where you brought along your 'friend,' and we first met Dave./R/RWelcome to the family, /R"Uncle Dave!" /R(it's just official now)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kristina, Andrew, Sam & Alex (KASA)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Do not question your love. Take your lover by the hand. Release the power within yourself. Tame the wild cosmos with a whisper. That's right, don't be shy. Whip out everything you got and do it in the butt.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leon Phelps]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carry on being active together and continue to contribute to your relationship. Keep on communicating and always be mindful of how you make each other feel. :-)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan Morehouse]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We share what Nunu said to us on our wedding day..."Be good to each other."  It can be as simple as that.  XOX]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shannon and Tom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Eat well, travel, be good to each other, and come to Portsmouth often! :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael Richards]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We wish you lots of love and happiness!  And, always eat ice cream!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Muah, muah - Maureen & Chad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(From Shan) Keep her well fed after long runs and you'll be just fine. /R/R(From Ben) Go for the litre of beer.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shannon & Ben]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Inside this box, you will find greetings from your friends & family, near and far. Maybe a funny memory or a tip (or two!) for a successful marriage. Either way, we all wish you years and years of happiness together! /REnjoy your Flatterbox!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love from the Haines family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>