<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2489-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/13/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Kendall Fay]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[410 Silvergrove Dr]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Cary]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[NC]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[27513]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Birthday!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Wil Fay]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[40 Years of Wil]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ASU, El Diablo; Wil loved Filibertos, singing its praises all the time as one of his favorites. I wouldn't eat there because it tasted suspect. Later they found dead cats in 16 locations one of which he frequented. Wil's response...."Dead cat is pretty good".]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aaron & ALL The Stelzers in NYC!!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Halloween, 31-Oct, 1996 @ The Tammaron Apts, back patio ~3am drinking hot tea and "laughing laughing falling apart,"...../R/R"What are you and I going to do to change the world? I don't know what but we are going to do something together."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aaron & ALL The Stelzers in NYC!!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Visiting Wil in September, 2013. I visited Wil and his family in Raleigh-Durham, NC. We stayed up on Friday night, late, drank and laughed our tails off. My gut hurt the next day. Laughing is always my fondest memories of hang'n with Wil.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aaron & ALL The Stelzers in NYC!!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wanna play another hand?  Let's say, I don't know...queens are wild.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff K and Charles]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wil- Hard to believe these memories were more than 1/2 your life ago, but there are many: from the "Jump Around" video @ Six Flags to road trips to Indiana to the "last supper" at Uncle Bills before the impending slaughter...many great times, old friend. Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chops & Michelle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Doing Tai Bo in heels, in your upstairs apartment in U City at 2:00am.  I still wonder what your downstairs neighbors thought...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amy most popular girl at HHS]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Friday night Happy Hours (on Thursdays) and Galaxy Quest.  Best. Movie. Ever. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pollocks]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a smart, genuine and compassionate person with a great sense of humor. I respect you professionally and like you personally because of it. Happy Birthday to a great boss and friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Phillip (and Venus and Violet)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wil ( Sha-La-La)..   I would not even know where to start with a favorite memory... To many to choose from after all these years.  I am proud to have helped shape you into who you are today.  I am looking forward to all the memories we have yet to make.     Gonzadabunya]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelcey (Sha-la-lee)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Wil-Billy!   "My potato is orange..."  ;o) Love you bunches & lucky to call you family!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ash & Scott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 40th Birthday!/RHard to believe you are so old. Seems like just yesterday you were throwing "trash the neighborhood" parties at the House by LHSN. Hope you are doing well!! Remember to take it easy, you can't get your AARP card for a few years. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nate and Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I just want you to know how much of an impact you have made on me. I have learned more from you in the past 5 years than most people learn in their entire career. You are a great boss, a great attorney, and a great human being. Happy Birthday!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jon Warrick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wil, how can I ever forget your sharp wit and probing questions about everything! Thank you for being a great Dad to Eli,Hallie &Karys.  Also, appreciate your compassion for others-you made sure that Zach was included in activities at our family gathering.  Happy 40th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Pete and Brenda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My notes for "The Devil Wears a Piggly Wiggly Shirt" tell-all book: Someone called and Wil couldn't put them on hold./REnd of List. You are such a wonderful person/boss/lawyer, that you are ruining my chances at fame and a Lifetime Movie starring Tori Spelling as me! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maria ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It lets me write more of these? /RHappy Birthday Wil!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maria]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Wil/RI love you. You are one of the special people in my life. You make me laugh so hard milk comes out of my nose. More like orange juice cause I don't like milk.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, H-Bear]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Roses are red, violets are blue. All dads are great, but not as great as you./RHappy bday my old man????????????????]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ Love, Eli????]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To the best dad: thank you for being a really nice dad to me. I love you and I hope you love me. If I didn't have you I wouldn't have the best family. Happy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Karys]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Wil...it's your Aunt Sally in Winter Park.../RI saw the deep joy in your parents' eyes as they welcomed you into their lives... you brought so much happiness :) My family loves you dearly! We are all so proud of you and your family... /RHappy Birthday and Love, Sally ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Sally]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have infused a lot of fun and madness into our family. One of my favorite memories is the spontaneous game of "Duck, Duck, Goose" - and then there is that classic line, "does someone have something they would like to say?"  Have a great birthday!  You deserve it!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dottie (aka MIL)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You'll always be Neck-Ed man to me. Stop aging. You're making me an old geezer. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember one time when will and Jimmy schooled me on the basketball court at Sunland. It was that day I reali I remember one time when Wil and Jimmy schooled me on the basketball court at Sunland.  It was that day I realized sports ball was not for me. ????]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brahm Fay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Cousin Wil:  /RWow, let's stop the clock!  If you are 40, what does that make me??  We are very proud of all your successes .... from Lucent to Lawyer!  Wishing you and Kendall many more years of happiness and success !!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ed Wynne & John Payne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wil, happy birthday and many, many more.   We are glad you are part of our "strange" family!    /R    ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Warren and Marie ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wil,/R/RWhether it is an "orange" potato or how to connect gutter drains, you always have an opinion based on sound logic.  I am happy that 'we' are part of your family.  It is pleasing to know how much you truly love Kendall and Eli/Hallie/Karys.     /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bobby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Uncle Wil! You're pretty awesome to be birthday buddies with. I'll always remember our Pirates of the Caribbean birthday. I'm excited to have many more fun shared birthdays with you in the future! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elizabeth]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Having not seen him in many years it was a great surprise to run into Wil at the airport in NC a few years back.   I remember sharing lots of good times and laughs in college with him and am psyched that our families are able to do the same now. Happy 40th, Wiggidiwil!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dail Holderness]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You've added character & and depth this family would be lost without.  We're grateful for the love you have for Kendall, Eli, Hallie, & Karys & would be forever ignorant had you not clarified chocolate milk all those years ago..  Happy birthday!  Cheers to many more!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[love, Brett, Erin, Natalie & Avery ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Uncle Wil! Thanks for all the great tummy time!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carter and Abby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Wil! Thanks for trusting me as your partner at the firm and always reminding me to find a balance between the office and my family. And seriously thanks for taking Abby when she tried to embarrass me at SAS. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bekki]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What's this pop up message about an NDA?! Happy Birthday to a guy who could probably win connect 4 in 3 moves, if only we'd agree to play.  You've added so much to our family- The Fay Way, the Art of the Fay and Fay-cations, and we're the better for it. Happy 40th, Wil!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Monica]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I don't get to see you often, but when I do you always make it special. I'll never forget when you came across the country just to surprise me for my birthday. I hope your birthday is just as fun!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Syr]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We wish we were there to celebrate w/ wine flights, gradually upgrade to wine bottles, frantically shove Flinstone vitamins in our faces, while Ron wonders around & passes out in the first bed he finds. Hanging out w/ your babies & doing sober things is also acceptable.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday - Ron and Nora ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're a lot of things to a lot of people, but to me, you're everything. Happy 40 years! To be honest, the past 17 are MY favorite, but I'm even more excited for the next 40.;) I love you much!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kendall]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>