<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2495-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/14/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Lauren Sefton]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[242 Park Street]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Little River]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[SC]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[29566]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Dave & Nancy's 65th Birthdays]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Dave and Nancy Blalock]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Collected by Lauren and Eric]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dave following the wrong car, thinking it was us, "stalked" a woman with three screaming kids about 2 miles down a dead end road, only to find a terrified lady thinking he was chasing her down to get her. "We had a lively conversation that night at dinner."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kay and Brent Hensley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dave and Nancy, following a car they thought was us, "stalked" the car for about 2 miles when it finally stopped.  Dave discovered the mistake when he walked up to the car to find a lady with 3 terrified kids screaming that the man was going to get them. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brent and Kay Hensley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite memories of Dad is thinking about him when he saw me outside the Hacienda in Santa Fe to walk me through the house and down the aisle. His smile and him walking me on his arm are memories I'll always cherish!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you heaps! Lauren]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom - I loved our Girls' Weekend in Ohio!  Thinking of chili dogs, upside-down roller coasters and sharing the Honeymoon Suite always cheers me up! Love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lauren]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lauren and Eric’s wedding weekend was so very special – the beautiful surroundings and wedding flowers, the delicious breakfasts, the bus trips, the laughter, our many conversations, and Larry’s mother and Nana chatting together as if they’d known each other forever.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie and Larry Sefton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The summer evening together at Pat O’Brien’s on Beale Street is another very special memory.  We loved sharing the music, the laughter, the ongoing antics of Joe and Jeremy, seeing Joan and Nana together again, and enjoying that glorious fire in the patio fountain.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie and Larry Sefton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Trip to Fire Island with Dave at 22 yrs old, no place to stay except above a bar with a band and ran out of money. Captiva Island with Dave and Nancy, all of us had food poisoning except Dave who was drinking beer. Trip did solidify our friendship with  them. Holt]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Holt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Fond remembrances of the house in Crescent. Breakfast at noon, lunch at 5, dinner at 10, then go out about 11 pm. Grandma was always in the kitchen, Dave's mom at the house, and Raggy coming over to visit. Boiled peanuts and Dave never sitting down at the beach. Holt]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Holt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Is great living in NMB and so much appreciate Dave and Nancy encouraging me to move down here. Nancy is such a sweet blessing in every way and I always enjoy golf with Dave and eating out them. They are true lifelong friends and I love and appreciate them. Holt]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Holt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Weekend at grandmother's beach house. We had been out, and return to find our dog, Johnny Dollar, had broken through the screened porch. The next day Andy & Dave "fixing" the screened porch!/RAlso, summer at the beach!! Martha-"is there a boy in there!" FUN TIMES!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[We love you!! Andy & Betty Hensley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dave and Nancy & darling daughter Lauren "Snow White",  wrapped our family in good will and fun. Best was Dave "kidnapping" A&Z's pumpkin; ransom notes; "drop off" points; returning a tiny pumpkin, then a larger, larger, till the real pumpkin sat back on the stoop. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Monika, Chris, Anna & Zac with LOVE]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I fondly remember the Colonel and his bride touring the grounds of Gamble Road, & waxing poetic with his soothing southern drawl. "You know, if you had told me ten years ago that you could make money selling bottled water, I would have said you were out of your mind!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Chapman with love]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I could not have survived my time living in NYC without Uncle Dave and Aunt Nancy! I will always cherish that time I had with them. My fellow flight attendants and I loved stopping by Dave's office for a visit and staying at their house made me feel like I was home! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenny ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Dave and Nancy.  We will always be greatful of your friendship and neighborly bond when we lived next store to one another in Scotch Plains. You are still very much missed.....Craig especially misses his favorite golf partner!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Craig and Cheryl Lynch ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will never forget telling Dave that I cant wait for Bailey to grow up and calm down. After you "googled" wheaton terriers you were laughing hsterically telling me that they were known as the "peter pan" of dogs. They never grow up. 11 years later and still crazy. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Craig Lynch]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As a child, I remember us all going to a Yankee's game on "Bobby Mercer Day" and they played the Detroit Tigers.  It was interesting parking in the Bronx.  We had awesome seats in right field.  Thanks Uncle Dave and Aunt Nancy for treating me to a special memory!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rob Roakes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One special memory was taking a dinner ferry to watch the Macy's Fourth of July fireworks in the New York Harbor.  Hundreds of yachts and boats of all sizes and one had a butler serving dinner to a couple before the fireworks started.  It was a spectacular evening!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob and Mary]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always love seeing Dave and Nancy when we visit the beach.  Taking a boat ride or crabbing at Little River is such a treat!  Thank you for making me always feel welcome as part of your family!  Happy Birthday!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Suzanne Roakes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When Dave married Nancy I felt like I was losing her.  Little did I know I was gaining a wonderful uncle.  We always have fun together but my favorite memory is the many times we "closed the beach".  Happy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Spending time with Aunt Nancy has always been a blast! As a child we'd watch scary movies, ride roller coasters & look for Boo Radley.  As I grew up the fun continued: riding taxis in NYC, photo bombing before photo bombing was cool & chasing ambulances. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nancy,/RI'm so thankful to have you in my life.  You have ways been there for me and I am grateful to have someone who is like a second mother to me. Happy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love going crabbing with you and sitting by the dock watching the boats go by.  The beach towels you gave us were the best!!  Happy Birthday!  We love you!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah and Regan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You've got all my love!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mama]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ We have shared some epic family adventures! From eating all the ice cream in Germany to hiking up volcanoes in Hawaii...from exploring the Grand Canyon to bunking down with Margi...I love all the memories and meals we have shared. Thanks for giving me a love of travel!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lauren]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One memory? No way. Lets see, there's our wedding, Hawaii, Alaska, Nova Scotia, Crater Lake, the Grand Canyon, and Yosemite. Plus all the Thanksgiving trips, summers in Paradise, and every Christmas in Wadesboro. I can't pick just one!/R/RHappy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eric]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I should have known there were going to be lots of Blalock Family DIY projects in my future after I helped y'all paint and customize Lauren's dorm room! I'll always remember Dave's negotiating for the fridge at Home Depot. Always happy to help out!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eric]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>