<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2501-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/15/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Jamee Rivers]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[900 East 8th Avenue]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[Suite 300]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[King of Prussia]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19406]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sunshine]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 25th Anniversary]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Bryan Cunningham]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Your Family at Imagefirst]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I feel lucky to have had the opportunity to learn about ImageFIRST from you. I mean you have been around so long it's like learning about the bible from Moses.  To put it in a context you are more familiar with, working with you has been like a "breath of fresh air"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Travis Margo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan,/RCongrats on achieving an incredible milestone of 25 years at Imagefirst.  You embody the Imagefirst Culture and are widely regarded as an expert in the field of everything Imagefirst!  Kudos to you reaching 50! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Kennedy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan /RCongratulations on your milestone at ImageFirst. Always with a positive attitude and open mind.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gladys Santos]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan,/RIt's been an absolute pleasure to have worked with you over the past 25 years.  I've watched you develop into one of our best leaders.  I want thank you for all that you have contributed to Image First and the manner in which you have done so./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff Berstein]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan, your reputation as the embodiment of the IF Way preceded you.  Now that I gotten to know you, I can also call you friend.  Here's to many more years!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Filomena]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Not only does Bryan bring wisdom to our conversations, but his untamable positivity  makes our interactions fun.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chuck DelCamp]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan, you are "one of a kind" and I am so fortunate to have met you.  Here is a listing of a bunch of "C's" that characterize who you are as a person and a leader of this business - Caring, Creative, Competent, Conscientious, Committed and down right Crazy!  Congrats!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan,/R/RCongratulations on 25 Years! What an awesome milestone! Thank you for all you do for ImageFirst and all the things we know you will do for us in the future. We truly enjoy working with you and I'm sure there will be many more years to come! Congrats!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Chorn and The Atlanta Team]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You set  a great example for us newbies, that hard work, commitment, & fun, will take you on a great adventure with this company.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heather Archuleta]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan Happy Anniverserary !  It is amazing to see how many people you have influenced in this company.  It is an honor to work with you.  I wish you all of the best in your years to come! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gino]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan, I am always impressed with the well of knowledge and new ideas you possess. It is a great pleasure to have the opportunity to work with someone so creative and passionate. Congrats on 25!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Scott Majewski & Team Chicago]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan,/RYou are an amazing person.  Thank you for all that you have helped me to learn and helped me to feel like part of the team here at ImageFIRST.  You embody the meaning of our values and I appreciate your leading the way by example.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michelle Kelly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Oh Bry, where do I begin?  It has been a pleasure to work for you and with you for so many years.  It sure has been fun watching us and ImageFIRST grow.  We've seen each other through good and bad times.  I'm happy I have an amazing co-worker and friend in YOU!/R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much Love, Herbie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan their are a lot of interesting stories others can share about you but only one person fit to tell it.  You are a legend and I am Thankful to be part of your story!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charlie C]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your inspiration and Coaching has allowed me to be a better person and leader. Thank you for believing in me when I didn't believe in myself. Happy 25th Anniversary SIR!!!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Louis Gallardo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan, Thank you for everything you have done for not only me but the entire organization as well. You must  be proud to see what you personally had a hand in building. Remarkable is not used enough and what you have done, truly is. Good luck with the next 25 years.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex Greenman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan, it is an honor to be a member of the ImageFIRST family with you.  You are a powerful example of who a servant leader should be. Thank you for sharing your work ethic, values, creativity, and knowledge with me. May you success continue.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Darrell Boyles]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on your 25th anniversary. Thank you for sharing your knowledge and wisdom. It is something I will always hold dear]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan/RCongratulations on 25 successful years with ImageFirst.  You have been a joy to work and have always been willing to share your knowledge with others.  Thank you and I wish you continued success.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Ann McGowan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have been through so much together!  Remember all those times in Clay St. and driving to help out in Long Island City? Good times!  /RBryan, you have invaluable to me and I truly appreciate your experience and knowledge, but i am most proud to call you my friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Will Brown ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[WOW, Congrats! What a milestone! I admire Bryan 's creativity, seems like he is always thinking and the wheels are turning.  Just goes to show that he is dedicated and passionate about his job with ImageFIRST.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lady Di at ImageFIRST Lancaster ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lancaster's loss, South LA's gain. We enjoy his visits back here to Lancaster County when he is here. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lady Di at ImageFIRST Lancaster]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Spalding, You have shown what a true leader is by the way you teach and lead everyday. Your passion for success and compassion for people truly speaks volumes of the person you are. Thank you for giving me the chance to be apart of your amazing family here at LA south. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael Hoddick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm proud of you B!  It is amazing how far the skinny kid from the quarry has come.  Yet, you have kept your core strengths: Loyalty, dedication, effectiveness &, of course, creativity!  You have become a professional who makes those around him better..you are a leader!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Geraghty]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 25th Anniversary with ImageFirst. I don't have any great stories to share like Joe or Jeff but I truely see the passion you have for Imagefirst and the purpose. Your the reason why I love this job. REALLY!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Noda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan. As a native of the Lancaster area your reputation precedes you. Your leadership and knowledge has led the LA team to be one of the best. Thank you for being one of our Image First leaders leading the way and developing world class leaders.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frank Gundrum]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan congratulations on 25 years with ImageFIRST that is a great accomplishment. Your creativity and passion for what you do is truly REMARKABLE and an inspiration.  I look forward to working with you for many more years!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Roberts]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan,/RMost of us have worked for many managers and it is extremely rare to find a manager who has such an immense passion for what they do, all the while, truly caring about each of their associates. Thank you for truly caring and congratulations on 25 years with IF. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Bryan. Five years ago you gave me the opportunity to be part of the Image First family and I will forever be grateful. I have been able to learn the companies values through you and have seen you live those values everyday. Wishing you another 25 years.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Ruiz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[OK here's my quote/RBryan, Thank you for believing in me....for always letting me know to be humble. No matter how high or how far u go in this great company never forget where u came from. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Miguel Mora]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan,  Congrats on 25 years! It  has been amazing working for such a dedicated and knowledgeable GM.  You are a wonderful “out of the box” thinker and I look forward to learning more from you and getting to work with for your next 25! ?/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Emma Wendt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan,  Congratulations on 25 years of service with Imagefirst.  Your leadership, creativity and ability to see the future is truly remarkable.  I look forward to working with for the next 25 years.  Continue to be an inspiration to others.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jamee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Bryan,/R/RHappy 25th!/RI have enjoyed working with you for these past 6 years and I look forward to the next 20./RWishing you 25 more wonderful years./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cathy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for everything you have done for ImageFIRST.  We wish you health and happiness and another 25 years!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sylvia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan,/RHappy 25th! Thank you for everything you have done for ImageFIRST!  I wish you all of the best.  /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joanna]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan,/RHappy 25th anniversary,/RIt’s a pleasure knowing a remarkable man and I am grateful and honored to call you my boss ./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vicky Machai]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan,/RCongrats for 25 years.  Thank you for giving me this job.  I like working hard and have a lot of respect for you./RHappy 25 years!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Enrique]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 25th anniversary Bryan,  hope your time at ImageFIRST has been fun.  I have enjoyed working with you for the last two years./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carlos A]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan, /RHappy 25th anniversary!/RThank you for giving me the opportunity to work here and for pushing me along.  For sharing your knowledge and for being one of the best bosses I have.  Thank you!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maribel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan,/RThank you for being the best boss I have ever had.  You’ve worked so hard these past 25 years and I hope these messages encourage you to stay another quarter century!/RWith love,/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenn Alba!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan,/RThank you for the opportunity of working in this company.  Happy 25th and god bless you every day!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Araseli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan,/R/RHappy 25th!  You are a great manager!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Regina]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan, Happy anniversary/R/RIt is a pleasure working with you!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marisol]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan,/RCheers to your 25 Anniversary /RHope you stay another 25 years.  Congrats!  /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jose M.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sunshine]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>