<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2505-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/16/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Cara Maresca]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[44 Blueberry Lane]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Hopkinton]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[MA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[01748]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Birthday!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Bob Maresca]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love, your friends and family]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite memories is our weekend ritual of playing tennis then going to Hopkinton Gourmet when I was little. At first, I was only in it for the cookies at the Gourm, but it soon became my favorite part of the week because we got to hang out just us. Love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bob is enthusiastic about all his endeavors like his golf swing invention which almost got him on the Do Not Fly List or adding the excitement of fireworks to liven up a party or eating New York Bagels or Stromboli!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Redi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that Bob will drive 4 hours to Huntington on Christmas Day, greet everyone with enthusiasm and then pitch right in and carve the fillet without complaint!  No wonder we all love you!  The party begins when Uncle Bobby arrives!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Redi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sixty may seem a little old but look at all you have. By now you should have a nice big pension to keep you going.  You get senior discounts.  You can brag about your kids. At 60 you are not old, you are in the prime of your life!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Hassett, Age 10]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have always been a role model for me both personally and professionally. Will never forget the homemade rocket in the driveway that almost took off Donnas head and landed nicely in a bag of charcoal in the garage. Almost lost your wife and house in one shot. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Hassett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Best coach I ever had!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ben]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So many great moments! I remember a moustachioed Uncle Space Face (where did that nickname come from?) bringing loud musical toys to all the grandkids at Christmas, and the competitive juices flowing as he flew down the snow tube run at Woodloch. Good times!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jason]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When you told Dr. Bose you had to leave a meeting to go trick or treating with Cara and Mike...& then were just as excited about getting the candy as they were! You always put family first, and make everything fun with your enthusiasm and that twinkle in your eye!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you xo Donna (your first wife)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for all of your business over the years. We never knew it was possible to light a lawn on fire with gasoline. /R/RSincerely,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ Hopkinton Fire Department ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Laura and I went to Florida with Bob down to his condo at Marco Island. Donna was already there. We pulled up to his garage and Bob is furious it won't open. He tried everything. Turns out we were in front of the wrong garage!! His 1st senior moment. Happy Birthday Bob ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lou and Laura Papadellis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday! You have been,& continue to be, a role model in so many ways.I have always respected your humble nature & find it refreshing that someone as smart, accomplished & dynamic is so incredibly balanced & real.  You always put family first -we love you for it!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Suzanne ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love Bob's passion for a homemade zamboni & ice rink, creative retaliation on the pumpkin smasher, always great with the kids (Ellie insisting you take a nap on the dining room floor),pulling the kids around the pool in Marco (against the rules!).We love you !]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Howe Family ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for re-building GIDDYUP!  Thanks to you, my childhood rocking horse has been restored for my own children...  and if it survives Drew, possibly even their children.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Suzanne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I admire your enthusiasm for life! I remember going to visit the two of you in your new home.  We thought we were lost and then we heard explosions! We followed the noise and sure enough, you were practicing blowing up boulders in your yard to entertain our boys! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dotsy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I think we can all attribute your brains, character, personality, and success to a certain babysitter you had when you were about 10 years old!  Who knew you would wind up being my brother-in-law?  /RThanks for all you've done for the MZ kids.  We love Uncle Bobby!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Exciting Easter moment as Bob launched a rocket in his  front yard which went in the wrong direction heading down and sideways at supersonic speed, missing Donna's and others heads by inches to then crash land and hours later start a fire in charcoal inside the garage.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Flip Zuckerman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always love hearing your stories and advice. When the boys were younger, you told me how it is much harder to raise a child's confidence than it is to tame their ego a bit. You were referring to sports but it helps me in many parenting situations. Happy Birthday!!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Merdith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's been great having a brother to call when I don't know what I'm doing. Like getting a generator going during Sandy. Not enough room to list the many far more important things. Thanks for always being there. I am glad I'm so much younger only being in my 50's.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gene]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bob is one of the most generous people I know. He is a great listener. He is genuinely interested in others. He is quick with a laugh, and quick to offer a helping hand. He is great with kids. He makes any gathering more fun. I feel lucky to know him & call him family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kerry Burke]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Uncle Bobby,/RI love visiting you in Florida! We wish you a happy birthday!/RWe love you so much. /R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Molly and Finn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A "special moment" I shared with Bob involved him playfully throwing me up in the air on the way to the beach but somehow ending up landing on my head.  According to Bob it knocked some sense into me - unfortunately years later it was knocked out again by our dog, Daisy]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Terrianne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My special bonding moment had to be when Bob had me run back and forth in the backyard so he could use me as a target for darts. He was a better shot than he thought because he got me in the thigh!! He's made up for it many times over by being a great friend & brother.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have a memory of walking with you on fifth avenue with your legs as straight as a robot. I asked you what was wrong. You said "I don't want to bend my feet and get creases in my new shoes."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We still don't believe that was a golf swing trainer. It looked like a bomb and smelled like explosives. We've got our eye on you, Maresca. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Boston Logan TSA/Anti-Terrorism Div]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So many things come to mind: your diabolical affinity for scaring me with hanging bodies from my light string or hiding beneath my bed then reaching up and grabbing my neck. Spilled milk at every meal, eating candy off the street, the charming nicknames you invented!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gastank, Tubs, Load]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have short term memory, so I'll go with the most recent impressive "Winter escapade"- the Propane Flamer Thrower melting the Ice Dams on the roof!  Fortunately, Bob escaped with his hat listed the only fatality!/RThe Hopkinton FD is now on Speed dial!/RHappy 60th Bob!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[George and Cathy Murphy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dad and I are so proud at the man you've become. You're not only thoughtful and generous with us but with everyone you meet. We treasure the letters you send us. I know you don't like saving things, but I keep them all because I often reread them. We are truly blessed.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom and Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your obsession with fire is genetic. Do you remember the fires in the barrel Nana used to make? She'd be proud of your expertise and creativity with your fireworks antics and flame-throwing ice dam melter. You seem to have inherited her pyromania.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom and Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[His interesting first few cars and his many run-ins with the police in regard to them./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Years of summer memories at Long Beach. Lots of surf and turf, unstable chowda, visits to Lobstah Land, trips to the ice cream store, awesome firework displays, at least 50 pounds of Nichols candies and tons of laughs. Thanks for the memories.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Teaching me the pretzel!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The mounds of shrimp you consumed at Zaberers!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bob/RYour two favorite words/RSunset Grill]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lou]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dad,so many sports practices/games stick out in my mind,especially baseball--dodging tennis balls hurled at your head truly is a great way to build a batter's confidence! And I'll never forget all the fun rides home with pre-dinner appetizers (snickers) & crazy driving!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Timmy was always disappointed when Ted showed up to help Bob coach their YMCA basketball team. Timmy begged to go home in Bob's car even though Ted was there. Mystery was solved when we realized  Bob always bought candy for the boys (and himself) on the way home.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ted and Kathy Dlugolecki]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The "last" July 4th fireworks display at Bob's house was quite memorable. We all felt like we survived the Battle of Gettsyburg as the fireworks shot sideways into the house causing mass hysteria. Luckily, Donna found bags of frozen peas for the wounded survivors. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ted and Kathy Dlugolecki]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks, Bob, for keeping Ted out of the Miami prison system in June, 2010!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy Dlugolecki]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Following Little League practice at Reed Park Bob's players followed him to the trunk of his old white Camry trunk where he displayed two large coolers of ice cream. It was a Norman Rockwell moment, with Bob wearing a big generous smile as a favored baseball coach!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vinnie and Lisa Lawler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nobody mixes a "Super Terrific" quite like you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lisa Lawler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One special moment I often recall was our "late night" trip to the bose headquaters building for a quick tour after dinner one night circa 1994 on a trip up to see you Maresca's.  It was very informal in nature and it really left a lasting impression on me to this day.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tim Rooney Jr.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Also, favorite invention ever was the remote control boat with the water gun fitted to it.  I remember you taking an interest in my remote control hobby at the time, listening to some of my input an 2 weeks later you created that monster, quite the engineering feat!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tim Rooney Jr.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my first memories of you is thinking you were my dad &grabbing your hand while walking. When I realized it,everyone laughed and I was so embarrassed(I was prob 4)! But how lucky I am to have an uncle that not only looks like my father but cares about me like one!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chrissy ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I do not immediately warm up to everyone I meet, but when I met you I was comfortable and able to be my silly self! Lucky to have you as a great-uncle!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lilyana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We admire you for how hard you work and how successful you are, but also for your kindness towards everyone, especially welcoming Dom into our extended family. You are a great uncle and Godfather and a great role model to all of us, we love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chrissy, Dominick, & Lily]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I met you I'd been hearing about you from a brother that idolized you.But I thought you were just a normal guy wearing a silly hippie shirt.As the years went on I realized he was right. I am honored to be your sis-in-law.He was right-you've lived up to that & more!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[i remember all those years ago, when we were little and traveling to Florida every year, the time spent in the pool getting away from the shark and laughing hysterically when caught.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Connor MZ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's impossible to sum up Uncle Bobby in one memory when his generous spirit and kindness lives in much we find around us: DD's munchkins, a horse racing ticket, Surfside Softie, or show of fireworks. No matter how old we may grow, there are some things we never forget!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hannah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bob, we love the times when you've shown your McGyver-ness, such as figuring out how to soundproof part of our basement for the boys' band. Your creativity is always awesome!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chuck and Cathy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Looking forward to a birthday dinner at Wed Wobstah with you, I'll even sing you the song!!!  Happy Birthday Bob!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rob & the Pdub Hassetts]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Bob!  How can anyone pick one favorite story? Of course, the ever-expanding fireworks experiments (not enough room for a JPP joke) are all winners. But the one that might summarize you best is the homemade zamboni: brilliant, fun, and never boring. -Matt]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt Murphy ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bob you continue to do life the right way, and we are all better for having you in our's.  Thank you for both the direct guidance you've given me over the years but also the indirect guidance by just serving as such a good example to follow.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rob Hassett, +49 Handicap]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Mr. Maresca! Feels like only yesterday we were stopping by Lucky Farms, followed by you throwing us around in the legendary Camry after our "Cheese and Crackers" basketball practice at the YMCA. Hope you have a great 60th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Timmy Dlugolecki]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Little Brother (I am the only one who can call you that), I always envied how you never seemed to be afraid of anything - except Daddy-long-legs. I remember you running screaming out of the tent in Nana's backyard in Mastic because one almost touched you.  Love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your big sister, Mary Frances]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember you buying the loudest mechanical toys ever made for Jason as Christmas and birthday presents - I think just so you could play with them :).  Tried to return the favor when you had kids but couldn't find anything that came close.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[MF]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey Bob,/RHappy 60th to a terrific friend and to one of the funniest people I know. It seems like only yesterday we were celebrating your 50th  - hey, by the way, have you ever finished paying off the bill for all the ice cream my kids ate at your club that weekend? xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love ya, Sue Fisher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Even though I'm not officially your niece, you've always made me feel like it! And the warmth and love I feel from you has extended to Eric, from day one!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allison & Eric]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[How can you limit me to sharing just one special moment with my lifelong friend?  I'm an English teacher dammit!  I'll try, but this new technology is cramping my verbose style.  In any event, it's the summer of 1980 and Bob, JB, and I are staying in a no tell-motel ..]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Fisher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[... in Omaha and I am having a leisurely cup of joe and reading the local rag when Bob, in a somewhat hurried manner, tells me to shank the coffee and meet him in the parking lot.  Reading the stunned reaction on my face (I do enjoy my coffee), Bob informs me that...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Fisher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If there's one thing I've learned from you, it's "keep your eye on the ball, keep your eye on the ball, keep your eye on the ball." Oh, and sixty-five twenty. Don't you forget it.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always thought you wrote the Van Morrison song "Brown-Eyed Girl" for me. I will never forget the day Sarah Lawler told me that that was HER dad's song for her--I refused to believe her for years! I think I know where I got my occasional stubbornness from. :)/R#farmade]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember the time you drank more pina coladas than any man I have ever seen. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex from Punta Canta]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[he took down the shower curtain in our room to use as a protective cover for our luggage, which was tied to the top of his legendary VW Beetle and thus subject to the elements.  I selected this brief moment in our "On the Road" trip because it is quintessential Bob.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Fisher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[On one hand, there is the inventive, always thinking, problem-solving Bob.  On the other, there is Bob the rebel, the adventurer, the let's-try-it-my-way guy that no doubt contributed to his success. As I recall, we paid for the hotel on my credit card, but the fast...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Fisher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[exit with the shower curtain on the top of the Beetle remains priceless.  Priceless too is our friendship.  All the best to a terrific 60th Birthday! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Fisher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have always admired Bob's energy and enthusiasm for life. I remember our trips to Marco growing up: whether it be tennis, basketball, or just playing in the pool, he was not only always passionate about engaging in activities with us, but he made them much more fun!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Rooney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dad, I remember you always coaching our soccer/baseball/basketball/football teams growing up, and showing up to every game in high school. I appreciate that even more now that I'm working--you've always, always made time for us. /RLove you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>