<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2512-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/17/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[tiffany cavallaro]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[33330 Pacific Coast Highway]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[malibu]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[CA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[90265]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_60]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[You are loved by all...]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Mike Keriakos]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Happy 40th!]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I fell in love with your head, your heart and your ability to make me a better person. There is no one else in the world that could make me happier and I cannot imagine my life without you...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lovey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always love how Mike sees the best in situations and always has an optimistic view on things. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rami Abdel-Misih]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[After the fight Mike lost the decision and became the object of Duke's derision.  Duke you had one fight now here's another.  You didn't know that Mike's got a brother.  This family sticks together like glue.  You hear that Duke?  I'M COMIN' FOR YOU!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrew Steuter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The thing I like most about Mike besides what an amazing life partner he is to Tiffany, is that from the first day I met him to every single time we've spent together after, he has always, always let me know and made me feel that I'm truly family. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Rachel Berman ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that the only thing bigger than Mikey's head, is his heart.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Despite Mike's many professional and personal successes (look at his apt, gorgeous wife and amazing son), Mike has an unbelievable way of coming down to your level to present himself mostly as a caring friend, a caring friend who just so happens to be incredibly capable]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Vance]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mike can accomplish anything. True story: after learning meditation Mike set his mind to growing taller. We were skeptical and measured him shoeless against the door jamb. Mike grew taller and the markings remained for years afterwards in the old bungalow on Ezra Street]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jason and Tina Fleming]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["No is the second best answer you can get".  Not for mike.  For mike there is only one answer and that is YES. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We are so fortunate to have you as our son-in-law. You are kind, considerate,and so generous with your friends and family. Most of all, you are a great father and husband. The love you share with our daughter is apparent. Just know that you are loved and appreciated.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tony & Cyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[your humility.  your heart.  your willingness to make this world a better place.  i can go on and on, but you have changed my life and the lives of so many.  thank you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mira Riad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Funny ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ashraf & Dalia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kind]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ashraf & Dalia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The one think I love most about you is your imagination and ability to dream!  Helping us all not only to leave the house and go into the field, but chase our dream.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Duke McKenzie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Mike is the endless love and support he gives to those closest to him. Love him like a brother! Happy birthday Mikey!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sophie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite story is where Mike would go on about how mom & dad loved me more since there happened to be a few more photos of me during our childhood..from which Mike concluded he was loved less & also surmised he was adopted! Happy 40th - to my fave storyteller ever :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marian, Andrew, Vicky & Matthew]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom & dad would ask Mike 'what do you want to be when you grow up?' He would say 'a garbage man'. At 4, Vicky suggested that her career path be a clown & a gas attendant..she thought it best to 'clown' on weekends & pump gas on weekdays..greatness runs in this family :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marian, Andrew, Vicky & Matthew]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I think that Mike's drive to be among the best came from my dad telling Mike & I at a young age, "You have two hands & two feet..you're like everybody else, so why can't you be the best at whatever it is you choose to do?" Words that I'm sure Mike continues to live by!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marian, Andrew, Vicky & Matthew]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mike's generosity: buying my wedding dress for me as a wedding gift while he was living in his 200 sq ft Soho apartment with his BFF, Duke; sending me beautiful flowers on my birthday, making me fresh bread from his homemade bread making machine...& the list goes on :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Just one thing about Michael? /RHe's always right :) /RI can say that now with confidence, hindsight being 20/20. Had I had the courage to change my career path when good advice was imparted, I've no doubt it would have been the soundest route. Wisdom and perspective! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Thérèse, a.k.a. T-Bone]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[While I probably have fewer experiences with Mike than others sharing similar sentiments, I can say with assurance that optimism, élan, inclusiveness, grit, panache and kindness aside, Mike is bold.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nick Slavin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There's much to love about Mike but, for me, its that he is still a kid at heart.  His infectious enthusiasm & belief that anything is possible plus his effortless offering of love is what makes him so awesome.  Most of us sadly lose that but Mike still has it aplenty!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sujay, Margo and Noah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I LOVE about MIKE is how every expression or sentiment or thought that comes out of his mouth is a byproduct of the amount of love he has in his heart. This is one of many character traits he possesses. A lesson I learned from him years ago.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Fr. Gregory S.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Remind yourself, nobody built like you, you design yourself" /R- Jay Z  /R/RThank you for always being a rock in our family and an amazing, loving friend. /RHappy 40th Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cathy Piedra-McKenzie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mike’s Words of Wisdom/Rcirca 1999:/R"You don’t have to be perfect to get the deal -just better than your competition."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[email from Mike to Steve McPhee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mike’s Words of Wisdom/Rcirca 1999:/R"I am on great terms with the people at iVil.  /RThey love me.  They treat me like the Dalai Lama."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[email from Mike to Steve McPhee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mike’s Words of Wisdom/Rcirca 1999/R"We're not exactly pioneers - rather guys who know when it's time to show up at the party a bit too late to nab the prom queen, but early enough that there are still women left!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[email from Mike to Steve McPhee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We are so fortunate to have Mike as a son. The space is not enough to document our pouring love to him. Mike has a heart of pure gold that is rare to find a second to it. He goes out of his way to make life beautiful for his family, friends and others. Happiness, fun an]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom and Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[and joy are manifested in his personality. He is a man of principle even if he sacrifices what he has. He is a wise leader who can respond to each challenge with a fresh eye. He influences, guides and supports. He is stubborn but wise, firm but kind, determined but hone]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom and Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[honest, sometimes seems unreal but because he is resourceful./RThe last but not least; he is the luckiest to find Tiffany as a wife and is the happiest as a father to Kai. Happy 40th birthday “Mikey boya nice”/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom and Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love your speed and pursuit of meaning.  You prove that real opportunity is always, always, just a conversation away.  /RKeep up the good fight!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin Ryan and family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/RMike is a man of many talents, and while he manages to keep most of those talents hidden from the world, one he can't hide is his amazing taste in friends. /R/RObviously.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mick Riad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mike is true and Mike makes me laugh.  Mike is perhaps the most truth-telling person I know.  Mike makes  me laugh, really laugh.   I laugh more with (truly with, not at) Mike than with anyone in my life. Mike is a gift.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Tauber]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that every time we have a conversation, you inspire and motivate me. You always make me feel important, valued and that you believe in me. I feel extremely blessed to have had you come into my life!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paula Lemass-Ibrahim ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I like most about Mike is that he listens to Mother Hen ;)  JK! We love him for the fun, smart and wonderful person that he is! Happy 40! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Neetu and Sumeet]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mike is the best friend a person can have. Once you make the bond, he is loyal, caring, and creatively fun...and brings truth with him always. I love being able to ask Mikie a question and know I will get an authentic response. I treasure our friendship.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Batstone]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Michael's loyalty and deep love for his family and friends. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leathers]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[For Mike, his success in life is tied to his love of helping others. He helps them grow, he helps them reach their true potential. For me, well, I don't know where I'd be without him.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pete]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Mikey!/RYou are a great dad, you take good care of Kai./RHave a good birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Layla]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have been a guru and someone that I've learned much from.  You march to your own beat and I admire that.  I would be a different person had you not become a part of my life so many years ago!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bernie & Chelsea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mike  is the younger brother I never had. Mike has the unique quality of only seeing the best in everyone. I am blessed to have him in my life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Medhat Ibrahim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Dude, are on this planet?"/RI love you and all the fun times and your brilliant creative mind. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peter Barsoom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Mike is his how he respects everyone around him and values the opinions of people of different ages and backgrounds. He doesn't pretend to be something he's not nor does he try to make you feel that he's big shot, even though he really is!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marc Mikhael]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I admire your firmness in faith and your commitment to those you love as well as to those who need your assistance./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love       Mal]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He's got a big heart, an open mind, and he calls it like he sees it. And for those reasons I have a tremendous amount of love and respect for him and I'm proud to call him my brother. Makes a pretty good pickle too...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ben]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your warmth, compassion and sincere love for others are your greatest attributes. They are at the core of what makes you a great cousin, father, husband and entrepreneur. Love you  Cuz! Happy 40th Birthday!!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mina Sarofeim ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We are so thankful to call Michael family, he is genuinely committed to those he holds close. He is a true pleasure to be around and his antics have us giggling constantly. The love he showers on his nephews warms our hearts. /R/RPeace & Light,/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris & Randi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The one thing I like most about Mike is his ability to inspire.  Mike's belief in himself, his belief in others, and the passion he brings to all his endeavors is an inspiration to us all.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dad, you are someone I will always look up to no matter how tall I grow. Thanks for being my hero...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kai]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that Mike is a relentless dreamer and does not let past failures or wins color his appetite to pursue big dreams in the future. I also love that every time I see mike and tell him how fit he looks, he tells me it's bc he just got a haircut ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Emily ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Good listener, trust worthy,&respect differences. Punctual always; you have perfected the art of timing: time for silence, time to allow your friends to hurl themselves into their own destiny & time to help them pick up the pieces. You are an inspiration & role model XO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sousou, Ron, Coli,Dan,Kris Salazar]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>