<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2523-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/20/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Lisa Charleston]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[616 Trephanny Lane]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Wayne]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19087]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy thoughts & love notes]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Colleen Charleston]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Family and Friends who ADORE YOU!!]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I loved spending Election Day with Aunt Colleen.  We both had Cheese steaks for breakfast at the King of Prussia Mall.  It was the best! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lily Gianna Thompson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My wish for you is to be at peace in your new home. Your army of big and little bubs is right behind you and we can't wait for many home-cooked meals of meatballs, tuna casserole, and whatever sweet baked concoction I force us to eat in our new kitchen. We're with you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Manf]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Looking forward to sharing many cups of tea as we sit, savor and solve the problems the world. OK - giggle and piggy snort about all those we love. Adore you!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lisa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[May your new home be a place where you continue to collect warm and happy memories with all who love you. Sending much love. Let me know when you're ready for a visit. XOXO ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cousin Bonnie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[May your new home fill with joyous and loving memories. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cousin Amy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remembering your Wedding Day ...you were gorgeous floating down the path. All beauty and love! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Rose and Uncle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wishing you peace, joy, contentment and adventures in your new home. We love you Colleen. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cindy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom,/RWe cannot wait for your new home to become Chase's favorite hang out. Going to Grandma's is always the best, and we know Chase will feel that way when he comes over to visit. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chase, Katie, and Matt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Around here, we don't look backwards for very long... We keep moving forward, opening up new doors and doing new things because we're curious... And curiosity keeps leading us down new paths." /R~ Walt Disney ~t/RLove, /RMikaila Thompson ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Growth is painful. Change is painful. But nothing is as painful as staying stuck somewhere you don't belong."/R~unknown~/R"The great thing in the world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving."/R~Oliver Wendell Homes~/RLove,/RMikaila Thompson ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[(www.funlava.com/www.dailymayo.com)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Good luck in this new phase in your life and don't forget to reach out to your family and friends if you need a hand.  They all love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle G]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have always been an inspiration to me artistically. I am in awe of your ability to take ordinary items and turn them into "Aunt Colleen Vignettes."  Our favorite things in our home are the two pieces you made- the clock and the dresser.  Keep shining your light!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[April and Chris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love,/Ralways]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe, Lynne, Jared & Leah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mommies- Although we have had a lifetime of unforgettable memories on Kent Road, I look forward to all the new ones we will create on Brynwood Manor.  I am so proud of all your hard work.  Daddy is surely smiling down.  Pioneer women for life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tootie Bell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There is a Wonder Woman inside each of us. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[A secret admirer ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are people in your life whom you unknowingly inspire simply be being you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Adore you!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A bird siting on a tree is never afraid of the branch breaking because her trust is not on the branch but on it's own wings. Always believe in yourself. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[All you need is love....and a tiara./R/RAnd maybe a cookie. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[:-)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear One/R    Do not be afraid to sparkle and shine.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you bunches!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The words you speak become the house you live in.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hafiz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nothing can dim the light which shines from within.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maya Angelou]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You alone are enough. You have nothing to prove to anybody.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maya Angelou]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He said, "There are only two days in the year that nothing can be done. One is called yesterday and the other is called tomorrow,  so today is the right day to love, believe, do and mostly live."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dalai Lama]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No one in this life has has a more profound impact on me and my family than Robert.  He was an extraordinary person and cousin and friend and i fear i will feel his loss the rest of my life.  My comfort is that the best of him lives on in his children and granchildren.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frank Gerolamo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for telling me the other day that I'm your favorite child.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[boy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[2nd floor apartment on cottman ave where I had lunch with you and Robert was the place  where I first thought how lucky my nephew had become./REver after when I was in your company my judgement was confirmed.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[uncle don]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If you ever feel like giving up, just remember there's a little (or big) girl watching who wants to be just like you./RDon't disappoint her/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If you ever feel like giving up, just remember there's a little (or big) girl watching who wants to be just like you./RDon't disappoint her]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["There is a sacredness in tears. They are not the mark of weakness, but of power. They speak more eloquently than ten thousand tongues. They are messengers of overwhelming grief...and unspeakable love."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Washington Irving]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No beauty shines brighter than that of a good heart]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Yours is the BEST heart too!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are people in your life whom you unknowingly inspire simply by being you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Truth!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Look forward with hope, not backwards with regret.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Embrace the glorious mess that you are!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elizabeth Gilbert]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Art has the role in education of helping children become like themselves instead of more like everyone else." Sydney Clemens./RTHANK YOU for inspiring ART in our lives!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Adore you!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Be your authentic, awesome, amazing self! The world needs YOU and your beautiful light. Shine bright, Dear One"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Adore you!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Worrying does not empty tomorrow of its troubles. It empties today of its strength. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Truth!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She was afraid. She did it anyway, and it felt SO GOOD!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A Mother's LOVE for her child is like noting else in the world. It knows no law, no pity, it dares all things, and crushes down remorselessly all that that stand in its path. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Agatha Christie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Stop thinking too much, it's alright not to know the answers. They will come to you wen you least expect it.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much love]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Everything in moderation./RExcept Awesome./RYou ca never have too much Awesome!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Everything in moderation./RExcept Awesome./RYou ca never have too much Awesome!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There is nothing more beautiful than believing in youserlf. Thank you for helping us to believe in ourselves~]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mikaila and Lily]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are never as alone as you feel at times. We carry with us the love of those that can't be with us, the hope of what can be and the connection to something bigger than we can imagine.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxoxoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I hope you still feel small when you stand beside the ocean whenever one door closes I hope one more opens, and promise me that you'll give faith a fighting chance. When you get the choice to sit it our or dance, I HOPE YOU DANCE]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you bunches!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happiness starts with you - not your relationships, not your job, not your money, but with you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have chosen to be HAPPY because it is good for my health.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Voltaire]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If your compassion does not include yourself, it is incomplete]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Buddha]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Eventually all things fall into place. Until then, laugh at the confusion, live for the moments and know everything happens for a reason. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Albert Schweitzer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Eventually all things fall into place. Until then, laugh at the confusion, live for the moments and know everything happens for a reason. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Albert Schweitzer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are far, far better things ahead than any we leave behind.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[C. S. Lewis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>