<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2536-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/22/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Nicole Hill]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[9728 Middleton Ridge Road]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Vienna]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[VA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[22182]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sand]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 40th Birthday Jackie! ]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Jackie Vandermeersch]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Nicole Hill]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jackie is fiercely loyal and loves her people no matter what.  She loves me even though I dislocated her broken toe./ROh and she trusts her people too- she let me dislocate her toe because I told her I knew what I was doing.../RLove you Jackie.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jordan (in case it wasn't obvious)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Easy to rile her up. Forgives quickly.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Readyhough]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Over the past 9 years, Jackie has been my boss, teammate, mentor, biggest supporter, first to humiliate, key advisor, shopping partner, source for gossip, rumbikub teacher, best beach buddy, loyal listener.../R/RBut what I love most, she is a forever friend. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What you see is what you get. Thanks for being you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jackie is amazing to have at work because of her awesome sense of humor and the fact that she is normal, which means a lot at our place of business.  She is also very skilled in putting flag poles together.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kitty Veith ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that Jackie and I have been friends since puberty! Back in middle school we jointly signed our names as "2/5" because we were part of a group of girls who named ourselves "The Fabulous 5". Beyond barfy! That being said, 2/5 Forever! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo, Nicole ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that Jackie is: 1) A loyal friend and family member 2) As honest as the day is long 3) Incredibly hardworking 4) Even more stubborn than I am 5) Secretly addicted to trashy and mindless reality TV shows/R6) My forever friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo, Nicole ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Jackie, How can all you kids be turning 40 when your Moms are only 50 ??  It's a mystery. Today is Johnny's B-Day too. How could I have not known,after all these years, that you guy's were born on the same day./RCelebrate today and everyday./RYour the best.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eileen Tramonte]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jackie's energy and love for others has no limits!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jon, Amanda, Kyla and Wyatt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She is my Soul Sister.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sully]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are my Sunshine!!! Hope you have a wonderful Birthday and a Fantastic year!!!  You are now old like me.  Love you lotso.  XOXOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Hubby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite memories of you is watching you swing dance at your wedding! You were stunning!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stephanie Nicolaides]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jackie, you are such a beautiful person, on both the outside and inside. Although I don't see you nearly enough, I truly value the times we have spent together. A lot of time could pass, but I always know when I see you, you will be authentically you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stephanie Nicolaides]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Quack, I cherish our memories: naked sit n spin, OC summers, Greece and "I want your sex!", church, pool parties, searching for husbands in the Greek Islands, picking up cab money, inhaling pizza, kicking coolers, NYEs, my wedding, your wedding, and our walks & talks. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[HBD, my sister friend. Love u! Tini]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are so many things that I love about you: the way you care so deeply for your family and friends, your loyalty, sense of humor, your laugh, your cookie parties, and dancing moves. You are fun, caring, generous, smart and I am SO very lucky to call you my friend. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wishing you a very HBD! Christina]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I like most about Jackie is her candid and transparent approach to any situation, any conversation and any person lucky enough to be in her company. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[James ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[wait..its asking me for just one thing.  That's tough! I LOVE (not like) Jackie's ability to listen and make you feel like you are the only on in the room.  She always has touched me this way and I leave a conversation with her feeling better for it. I love you Jackie!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[McGovern ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I just figured out how to add more...YES!  Soooo I also LOVE her laugh!!!  When I can make her laugh, I am so proud of myself! If she tears up laughing even better!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[-McGovern]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Yes there is more....she doesn't know this either but she is one of those few that when I see she is coming to an event, I am much more excited to go and look forward to it even more (and will ensure I don't cancel:)...ha! LOVE YOU!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[-McGovern]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that Jackie is such a morning person. I've never been around anyone who can just get up and go like that. It's truly amazing! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[George Alafoginis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Her big heart]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marty Alafoginis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Her sense of humor]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marty Alafoginis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Her imaginary friends Petey and Yogi]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marty Alafoginis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Her loyalty]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marty Alafoginis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Her love of family]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marty Alafoginis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love her wit and sense of humor!  She makes me laugh out loud.  I also love her loyalty and passion for family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Al]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are my sunshine my only sunshine, you make me happy when skies are grey. You'll never know dear, how much I love you and even though you've tried, you can't take my sunshine away:) Couldn't have asked for a better best friend for the past 27 years! I heart you mucho]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kristin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Although she thinks she's funnier than me, she's the best sister-in-law a girl could ask for! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bets]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Jackie is how little she is. Even though she is my big sister technically speaking she has been my "little" sister since I was 11. Seriously though Jay and I haven't always gotten along, but as adults she is one of my best friends. Love you J]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[George Alafoginis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One more thing that is really important. Most people don't know this, but Jackie likes to eat Pigs Feet and Sleep in meat. That is all. Love you much]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[George Alafoginis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love everything about my amazing sister so it is hard to pick just one thing...but one of my favorites is her sense of humor. She is hilarious and makes everyone around her laugh and feel great about themselves. /R/RI LOVE MY ANKARA!!!!!!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[the other Ankara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that Jackie has inspired an Alafoginis family song that has been sung for over 30 years!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kristina (and George)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I love about Jackie is that she is my niece, we share  a blood line, we are connected through generations of relatives so  her divine sense of humor, her earthy, practical view of life are qualities that I admire and respect and which she inherited from me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I will love her always, Dodiej]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love everything about Jackie; your internal and external beauty, you devotion to family, your thoughtfulness, your laugh and hilarious sense of humor, your stunning curls,  your supportive husband, and your insightfulness that you will never be a morning person. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[XOXO, Elena and Jacques]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[that is just too hard, there are a bazillion things I love about you- like your family, especially your godparents. I love that You always make me laugh about the real things in life and Iknow that you are always there for me and any other member of our crazy family!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joanne aka JoJo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love my bestie for so many reasons. She is loyal, honest and is always there for her family and friends. I am forever grateful for the day back in college when she walked up to me at a party and said she thought we would make great friends! 20 years later she is my ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Very best friend. Luv Fulton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She has such LOVE for her family...and, her family dearly LOVES her..!/RHappy Birthday, Jackie! /R35 is the BEST! ;-)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tina Jones]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maybe She's Born With It. /RMaybe It's Maybelline./RLove Jackie's Stunning Eyes!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo, Nicole ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love that Jackie is the BEST JELL-O shot maker of all time. Or maybe Mark makes the JELL-O shots and Jackie just passes them out and takes credit for their deliciousness.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo, Nicole ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love that Jackie married such a kind man...who also happens to be handy, considerate, (annoyingly) neat, and hot. If anyone deserved to hit the hubby lotto it was Jackie! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo, Nicole ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love that right before I was about to meet Mark for the first time at Fight Night, Jackie looked at me and said, "I like him. A lot. So DO NOT SPEAK. Do not fuck it up". Thankfully, I managed to keep my mouth shut. Truly, a miracle. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo, Nicole ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I loved going to Pizza Mart with Jackie and Christina after trying to 'Whoop It Up' at some crazy ass bar I can't (nor want) to remember and having them make fun of me for devouring the piping hot pizza like it was my very last meal.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo, Nicole ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that Jackie has come to my boys' irritatingly loud birthday parties over the years despite her hangovers, migraines, in-laws in town, and the fact that there were probably 1,000+ other places she would rather be...glad she was by my side. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo, Nicole ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that on my wedding day Jackie looked at me and said, "You really need to get your ass in the shower"...because I was running a little behind. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo, Nicole ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that Jackie can be the scariest and kindest person on the planet. Totally depends on the stars! Or the time of day! LOL! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo, Nicole ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Forever grateful that Jackie introduced me to Christina Loukas Murphy! It was like Jackie handed me a winning ticket to the friend lottery! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo, Nicole ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Loved watching Jackie run around 'Fight Night' with her headset and clipboard, calmly handling all of the chaos and nonsense. I was in awe of her awesomeness...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo, Nicole ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our family has so many stories and memories that we share. I scared you with the whipper snapper but look how you turned out. Successful and happily married to a wonderful guy. The Loukas family loves you as their own and thank you 4 being an important part of our lives]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, Paul and Linda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>