<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2537-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/22/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Susanne Winton]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[8720 Escabaso Drive]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Austin]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[TX]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[78748]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[pink]]></cardcolor>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are one of the loveliest people we know.  You are kind and loving. Our lives are enriched because we know you!/RHave a truly special birthday! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie and Terry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[you raised the wonderful man I married.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Suzanne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[you are a terrific mother-in-law to me.  I've been so lucky to have you in my life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Suzanne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have met all the challenges life has given you with such admirable grace and strength. Your laughter is the finest music I ever hope to hear and your wisdom is always a work of art. My favorite quote from you- "Happiness is a choice. "/RLove you always,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have had, and will always have great conversations!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[G.G., /RYou're the most caring person I have ever met. Thank you for all of the words of encouragement and love over the years. Those words will be with me forever. "We may not get to see a lot of each other...but it's really nice to know you're out there!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Becka]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you have raised wonderful children, taught them about love, and one of them helped to bring the man I love into this world. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[your smile is so genuine.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Roseanna]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[G.G ~/RYou are very genuine./RI remember when you first met Becka as a baby, it was the most special moment, you lit up the room with a glow that is irreplaceable.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[April~]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[G.G./RI hope you have a great birthday. Enjoy many days to follow/R<3]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Logun Winton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you make me feel loved with your home-made birthday cards.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Broday ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In celebration of your birthday, I love you because you have always been the kindest and most thoughtful person I have ever known. My memories of you have always been filled with laughter and the generous nature that is you. Hope you have a wonderful birthday.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love always, Rick and Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In celebration of your birthday, I love you because your wonderful warm smile and sweetness. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy Winton Wilkerson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[you are my mother and as my mother you have my unconditional love. You have always been loving, supportive, and nonjudgmental toward me, therefore I have learned to be the same.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Son]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You make me so happy. Making you smile is one of the best things I've ever done in my life. I love you dearly and we're all so incredibly fortunate to have you in our lives and hearts. /R/RYour wisdom and joy will always be with me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite memories of us is how you used to make me cinnamon toast for breakfast at the house in Mineral Wells. All the fancy food in the world can't compare to how wonderful that toast was. Sitting in that kitchen and knowing I was loved... how lucky I am.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have been my treasured mother for 68 years!  /RWhere would I be without you?/RLove,/RSuzy]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Suzy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/R/RIn celebration of your birthday, I love you because of your wonderful sweet smile.  That smile has always been welcoming, forgiving, and loving.  It has always been reassuring to see that smile.  Thank you for sharing that smile with me over all of these years.  Love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jane Winton Gage]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like your hugs because they are soft]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrew Winton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[GG, I hope your day is wonderful because you deserve it. You are one of the most sweetest, kindest souls I have ever met and I enjoy every moment spent with you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amy Winton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul, Katy and I have always enjoyed sharing our lives with you and basking in the sunshine of your beautiful smile.  You've always made me feel special by calling me one of your "other daughters."  May your birthday bring you much joy and happiness.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Janelle ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In celebration of your birthday, I love you because of your sweet and caring nature. What a beautiful person you are!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Linda   ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love you for your kind and gentle ways...for your strength and courage...for that hearty humor that results in a contagious laugh.  We respect you for your clam reserved way in the midst of all that is happening around you!  Looking forward to our next call!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ken & Gaila]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aunt Sue!  We celebrate the very special occasion of this birthday with you and want you to know we love you because your smile is absolutely contagious!!  My mother, Joy and I always commented on how we don't remember a time when you weren't smiling!  We miss you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joy and Jerry Bostick, Jana Blewett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[...because you always loved me, because you set examples of patience, loyalty, courage, forgiveness, because your laughter is genuine and full of joy, and it is impossible NOT to laugh with you.  I love you, Aunt Sue, just because.  Happy Birthday!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John and Jo Murphy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have been so kind and generous to all, so caring & accepting, so patient and forgiving; such a model of true Christian virtue./RWith love & admiration,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Craig]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have always made me a part of the Tibbs family; always made me feel loved; always made me feel comfortable; and always made me laugh. You were very comforting over the years in the loss of my parents...just like an aunt would be. You are very special to me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gaila Raiden Davis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[GG,/RI know we do not get to see alot of each other but I wanted you to know "I love You"..The memories I have of us will be cherished, Your beautiful grace,smile and wisdom will be close to my heart always. Wishing you a blessed Birthday and many more to follow.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shannon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are such a sweet Grandmother.  I have such wonderful memories throughout my childhood of visiting you in Mineral Wells.  I will also always cherish the letters you wrote me while I was in Germany.  I love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Trey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[GG - I love you because you make the best cards. Some people buy cheap cards and throw some money in it. You make your cards homemade and from the heart. The way you cut out letters in magazines and use foam letters and cool pictures is so neat. I love you, GG./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Will]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mother, It has been my blessing to have wonderful memories of you in my younger years, and to get to know you in my adult years. You have been an inspiration in my life and a role model./RI love you and will cherish the times we have had together. /RLove Always, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[GG - I love how warm and friendly you are. You always welcome everybody with a smile. You always have nice things to say and witty comments, too. You give out love like baskets of flowers, and your hugs and kisses make me know that I am loved. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Will]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will especially cherish those trips from Austin to Mineral Wells while I was getting my degree at Mid Western.  /R"We were just two gals on the road", and it was special ! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Anne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Grandma - I love you because you have always been there for me, taking care of me in all ways possible, from Sprite floats and fried catfish to words of encouragement and honest advice. I see your smile in the moon and hear your voice in bird songs.  I love you always.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kem]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[GG - I love you and your family that has accepted me as their own.  Your wisdom of "family is where you find them" has helped me to better understand my life and choices.  Thank you for sharing with me and loving me.  Very truly yours always.  Love & Peace]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Greg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you for your wisdom, humor, wit and smile. But above all, for your caring./R/RBest wishes on your Birthday and always./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Lange]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aunt Sue,/RI love you because you have always been the sweetest person that was full of love for all of us. When I think of you, I can hear your sweet, calm voice giving us assurance. My childhood was blessed because of you being part of our family. Happy 95th Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wanda Winton West]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love you to the moon and back GG, have a super great birthday.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Taylor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>