<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2538-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/22/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Thomas Evans]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[561 Coldstream Drive]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Berwyn]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19312]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 30th Amy!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Amy Evans]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love, T, L, C, & E]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I admire your heart for children, passion for others, and sense of adventure.  I am so proud of the woman you have become.  You are an amazing sister, aunt, and friend - Love you sis!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Big Bro]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amy, one thing i like most about you is your inquisitive spirit and curiosity!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt Thanabalan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[something i like more than your curiosity, is your desire to understand/know people so different from you. Like myself. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt Thanabalan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Amy is a bright, talented and kind young woman who is never afraid to reach out to help others when needed. She has a strong Christian Character and expresses her convictions freely and without hesitation or apology. I am blessed to call her my niece and friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Marie (DiAmore)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Amy!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Marie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amy is not only my little cousin, she is also my friend. I adore her sense of humor, and her ability to be helpful, kind, and loving. As we've gotten older and spent more time together I've realized that I would have picked her as a friend if God hadn't done it for me. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christi (DiAmore) Serra]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amy, two words that describe you come to mind right away: genuine and purposeful. The first night I met you, you invited me to go to Prague and then you followed through :). I treasure your friendship. Thank you for the many ways you have been so intentional in my life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Megan Goodoien ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amy is a gracious young woman.  She is always truly thankful for even the little things done for her.  We are so proud that even though she is very well accomplished, she is still the sweet girl we have always known and loved.  She will always seek God's best for her!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Arlene & Uncle George]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Not only is Amy BEAUTIFUL, she has one of the best senses of humor I've ever come across. I have lots of memories in where my stomach is in great pains from laughing so much, so-much-so that just thinking of Amy makes me smile. :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Melissa DiFelice]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Amy is that she  is always learning new things and shares about her experiences with her friends! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elisabeth C.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how you can seem so put-together, responsible, and like such a little lady--and then in the next moment you can crack yourself (and everyone else) up with a loud burp, or punny joke, etc. You are this amazing balance of maturity and complete silliness!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[carolyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how no matter how many years, miles, and circumstances come between us--we can fall back into place, enjoying our friendship like it was that first Harrisonburg summer. I wish I got to enjoy your presence even more often! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[carolyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Amy is her refusal to give John the satisfaction of a high five!/R/RChinatown soon? Bubble tea on me!/R/RHappiest birthday friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rachel Easlea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amy has always been a sweet young woman who loves the Lord and her family.  I'm proud to be related to her. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Joanne.  ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love that you are adventurous, visiting your friends all over the world! You are a beautiful woman! We love you! Happy Birthday, sweet cousin!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Beth & Sam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love your disarming honesty./RThe way you practice being quick to listen and slow to speak. /RYour kind friendship./RYour hospitality style /Rand your humor -/R both of which foster ease./RAnd the fact that we can go anywhere in the world together /Rif only we have a map.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mekenzie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always notice the little things around you; you don't let moments go by fleetingly. I love that about you - you're kind, observant, and makes things beautiful. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stella]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amy!/RI am so thankful to have had you as a friend for the past 7 (!!!!) years!/RYou are so thoughtful and intentional, I really admire both of those things about you. /RAnd you are super creative and stylish!/RSo glad God brought you to West Philly! Love you friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meredith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that you clap like a seal when you laugh really hard. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Megamy ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love your fun and playful nature. I love how faithful and loyal of a friend you are. I love when you braid my hair b/c I can't return the favor. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meggie ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that we have shared multiple addresses in multiple cities (and states)! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mega-neighbor ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Colorado, Rhode Island, California, New York, Connecticut, Massachusetts, New Jersey, Virginia...all places we have traveled to together. What fun we have had!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amy's snuggle bunny ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are truly called; called to teach, serve and bless; called to seek and to wait. Your passion for instilling learning in children will reach far into generations. The Lord has blessed you and us, through you. I love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Amy, Poopsie, Tulip, Amy-Gal, Sweet Daughter, Beautiful Woman after God's heart. I wish everything wonderful for you on your 30th birthday.  I have been so blessed and I love you so very much!  You are the best daughter anyone could ever wish for.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I love you, Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am so very proud of the woman you are.  You are adventurous and excited to travel to new places. You are also always willing to take on new challenges where God leads you.  I am truly amazed at all that you've already accomplished in just three decades of life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your proud Mama]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a wise woman, a thoughtful and deep person who is a loving friend and daughter.  You always look for the best in others, and have a heart for the underprivileged.  God has richly blessed you. You are a joy in my life & I thank God for blessing me with YOU.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Amy! I love you, Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It is hard to narrow down my favorite thing about Amy Evans, but I have to say it is her sense of humor. The way we laugh together brings me so much joy and comfort. It is just one of the ways I feel understood, cared for and loved by Amy.  And for that I am thankful!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heidi Zeman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love the way Amy lives out her faith. Her gentle spirit and caring nature  are the fragrance of Christ. It's always a joy to be with her :-) Happy 30th Amy!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carl and Linda Teets]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kind and Gracious Heart]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meg Kimble]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Now when people ask, I can honestly say that I have indeed taken a shower with my socks on.../RThere's so much freedom in not having to lie anymore.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Samson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amy was an instantly warm and welcoming friend to me when I came to Philadelphia.  She is so incredibly selfless and kind.  I so appreciated her support and friendship especially in our jobs together.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anne Smith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amy is a great friend to hang out with. As long as there is at least one buffer friend. More buffers are always better. Also, cough medicine makes hangouts much more tolerable. /RHave a wonderful birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jaime Dlubac - duh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aunt Mimi,/R/RI love that you are already looking out for me and making sure that I don't have to endure too much baseball.  I know we will have lots of fun adventures together.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Emmy, age 8 months]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Aunt T!/R/RWe love doing coolio things with you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Franklin and Harriet Turtle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aunt Mimi and I like to play: Kitties/RI like it when Aunt Mimi is: Silly/RIf Aunt Mimi was an animal she would be a: Tiger/RIf Aunt Mimi was something you could drive she would be a: Motorcycle/RIf Aunt Mimi was a food, she would be a: Pea/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charlie, age 3]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that you are a loyal, thoughtful, and caring friend. My life is richer with you in it! Happy 30th Birthday, Amy! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Catharine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that we are friends. I love that you live a life full of compassion for others. I love your loyalty to family and friends. I love the way you play with C and E. I love your adventurous spirit.  I love learning from you. Most of all: I love laughing with you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So happy to know that you've committed your life to the Lord and are willing to share His love with the young people you come in contact with everyday. May God's blessings always be with you! Happy Birthday!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Sam & Aunt Marie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[On our regular visits to Provolones, I appreciated how you kept my leash loose enough to enjoy the experience, but secure enough that I didn't accidentally run into oncoming traffic.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Harvey (the hunting cat-dog)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amy, you are lovely. My favorite thing about you is your intentionality. You love people well through your kindness, humor, and sincerity. I'm so glad I know you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marilyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your loving heart and carefree spirit are a gift to all those around you.  Our kiddos wish they had a "Cool Aunt Amy" too!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Clark Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday!  I hope you get a new pair of sunglasses so we can trade again!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gracie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Æ's heart for Jesus and her willingness to turn to him for wisdom and understanding. She points me toward's God's delight in us over and over. I couldn't ask for a better quality in a friend. Love you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jamie ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Everybody's talkin' bout my tight pants. I got my tight pants. I got my tight pants on.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jimmy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Duke Dog]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>