<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2554-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/26/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Catherine Miller]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[7053 Marymount Way]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Goleta]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[CA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[93117]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Birthday ACC]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Ann Catherine Cady Cooper]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Catherine]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I'll never forget is the epic college road trip we took back east. Finding all those great BBQ joints, eating hush puppies, driving through beautiful campuses -  Chesapeake Bay crabs, boat rides - it was all amazing! Thanks for planning such a great trip. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Catherine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are too many special moments we spent with Ann but for sure our road trip to Napa Valley with our beloved three Entlebuchers Greta, Heidi and Willi will remain one special time. Driving in the VW Bus up north and visiting other Entle lovers was the best time ever.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bettina, Heidi and Willi & Ralph]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[How fondly we remember our trip to Hawaii for your birthday month a few years ago. Such fun to explore the island, put our toes in the soft sand and swim every day. There is nothing like the beach in summer!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Catherine, Victoria & Caroline]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Noni, I remember you teaching me art when I was younger and I found my passion in it through you. Remember the art show? Painting in the art studio? I do and it was great. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Caroline]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can't select one moment, but I do know that meeting Ann brought a lot of fun and joy to my life through our early duplicate bridge days to balancing check books to tennis, both playing and critiquing, and to wonderful talks about whatever.   Love her!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[gretchen gleason]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Probably our road trip to Phenoix stand out the most. The winds were so bad the CHP closed HI10 so we had to stay another night at Frank Lloyd Wright's Biltmore. Since Ann is Miss Personality we soon knew everyone around us while we sat in the bar for light supper. FUN]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[toni (gump)amorteguy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Staying at the Bird Cage or in the Gypsy Wagon is always a party.  On way back to the desert from Phenoix we were thrilled to see the mountains  covered with snow...in places down to the highway.  Ann's warmth and generosity is limitless.  She can melt  snow.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[antoinette gump amorteguy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What a precious jewel are in my life, my dear friend.  For over 25 years you/Rhave been my mentor, my guide, my counselor and my friend.  Such wisdom you possess!  I am blessed beyond/Rmeasure to know you!  Live, love, and laugh on for many years! Stop by to potty anytime]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pam Reaume]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Memories of - Blue Dodge, visiting with your wonderful parents, Neighborhood discussions about topics on the ballot, Joey and Catherine, P.R. and Heather,/RSo many visits to the desert.  Amber, seeing your choices as you built Quail Cove, Peter in the MG, skunks in front]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pam Reaume]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jobs as  candy distributor, advertising rep, my divorce on McFarlane, evenings of wine and whine (mine), Penny.  Easter at the Bird Cage, kitchen rebuild al la Pat, cruising the RV with V&C on 111. Pink patio furniture, Coldwater, C's bday at Clonards, beautiful Bella. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[love our memories! Pam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann Cooper is a very special friend.  She was one of my tennis partners.  I used to hit the ball very hard and my serve was as fast as Roscoe Tanner but I didn't know where it was going.  But Ann went toe to toe with me and often beat me.  We had a lot of fun. Happy BD!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt Bryant]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[On a typical gray Seattle day, I laid out how overwhelmed college made me feel & got an invitation to relax in the desert.  Crystal ball? or inherent wisdom? It was the perfect tonic for my worried soul.  I credit you (& Greta) for my Magna C Laude success. Thank you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Scott Cooper]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[This is when life becomes a dream: sitting with you on a beach, a bench or a balcony somewhere in California, having a drink, a laugh and a chat about people, a book or life itself. You`re a distant, but sincerely cherished friend who makes our days more precious!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bea, Camilla, Carlotta and Thomas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We met Ann on a Baltic Cruise. We got on very well. I was robbed in Estonia and Ann insisted on giving me money, she was paying in advance for my husband's cheese, which we duly sent as soon as we got home. Ann is a very lovely character.  We send our love]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Margaret and John Knox]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite Christmases as a kid were spent with you and the family at the Aptos house. It was a wonderful mix of cousins, candy, presents, and playing. Those holidays were so carefree and happy! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christina Cooper O'Donnell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I had the best time with Ann last fall at her desert get-away! Great food, great art, laughs, and of course our wonderful Entlebuchers!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Becky Christiansen & Bow]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A lifelong sisterhood friendship/Rbegan in 1958 when we both pledged/RDelta Gamma at UCSB!/Ritb,/RMary Jane]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Jane Fuerst Salcido]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One?  Heck--a hundred and one.  Jazz on top of the building in Pasadena and at the S.B. Bowl,  red wine/great food,   gypsy wagon in the avocados/ in the desert, walks through the palms, architecture,  visiting you from summer place to summer place, ad infinitum.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Monica Pizura]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What a joy you've been to me for decades.  How fortunate for us that our mothers were friends. I love your company and wish we were able to see one another more often. I hope your 75 is special just like you! I'm right behind you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love and miss you Rosemary]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, remember how we met?  It was Swiss Dog Day 2011 in San Francisco and our smart Entles Greta and Emi brought us together.  Seems we've known each other longer--we always have good, comfortable times in your company.  Here's wishing you many more birthdays.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elaine Fohr ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Ann,  One of the best things that happened to me when we moved to Tradtion was renewing our friendship. After all this time we still have good laughs together especially being bridge partners.  It is wonderful seeing you with your family and how much you love them.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love to you on your Birthday, Patt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jim joins me in wishing you the best year yet! Filled with family, good times, good health, and good cards. We will be thinking of you on your special day knowing you will be with your loved ones/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Jim and Patt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Reconnecting with Ann in the desert has been such a special gift. So I will have to say our first lunch at Daily Grill after many years was the beginning of renewed friendship. Who cannot love this beautiful woman! Happy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lucy Perricone ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have a lot of great memories with Ann, and can't possibly consolidate to one:   I remember our wonderful bridge games, our tennis tournaments, going over her checkbook in San Marino EONS ago, tennis bets for breakfasts, and just sharing our shots on email.   Love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gretchen Gleason]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are my second favorite mom.  Ever.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Neal]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann Cady Cooper, you are a shooting star who makes our lives happier with your irrepressible smile, laughter and adventures./R30 years of friendship at UCSB, San Marino, Glendale, Germany, Palm Desert and L.A., every one of those times has an Ann Story. We love YOU!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marilyn Lee and Harvey Schneider]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Ann Cooper has been a mighty blessing in my life. She is a wonderful, joyous, loving person.   /ROne spring,  Ann gave me a wonderful birthday party. This was an occasion I will never forget. The most special gift was a prayer Ann had written for me./RHappy Birthday Ann!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sue Branson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Happy Birthday Auntie! Wishing you a spectacular celebration! Cheers to continuing a beautiful life. I always remember your warm, fun, inclusive spirit and all the marketing/sales calls you had us do as kids to teach gumption and tenacity :) Love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Cady]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[THE DAY WE DECIDED ON OUR "ENTLE" WAS THE DAY THAT DREW US TO ANN.  SHE WELCOMED US WITH OPEN ARMS INTO HER HOUSE TO INTRODUCE US TO HER "GRETTA".  WHEN "EMMA" ARRIVED, ANN WAS ALWAYS THERE WITH ANSWERS TO OUR QUESTIONS AND OPEN DOORS FOR OUR GIRLS TO GET TOGETHER. XOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[TAYLOR'S, RON, MIMI, TJ & EMMA]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Entles, who knew they could create such a beautiful friendship. We wish you the most fabulous birthday and hope to get to see you more often this year. /RWith Love/RMerry, Cliff, Jason, Jared and Madison]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Chewning Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Auntie, What fun energy you have always had! I have such good memories of Lacy Park, camping, Germany & Switzerland, and of course Amber and the desert! I still think about your Mercedes and the fun times at your house in San Marino! Love and Happy Birthday fellow Leo!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Jocie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Ann, we will never forget when you, Catherine and your wonderful granddaughters visited us in Berlin! We had such a nice day with you and many good cocktails Sebastian was mixing for us! We were laughing and enjoying ourselves and had a great time with you!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nina, Sebastian, Moritz und Marie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I fondly remember when we first met in a cafe near the Teltow canal in August 1994 just after a dear mutual friend had passed away. We spent many happy days together when Ann lived in Berlin and whenever we visited each other ever after. We are friends forever.      ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wolf]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Too many fun times to narrow it down to just one.  Down at the desert, hanging out on the patio, cooking on the BBQ for everyone as the kids play games inside, and just talking with my Mom.  Always planning the next trip or project./RHappy Birthday!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember getting the overpriced ice cream and cappuchino while gazing at Notre Dame? Sleeping in the turret on Il de City? Amusement park and art? Shopping, cab rides past Arc d'Triumph? Versailles? Ah we'll always have Paris! What a wonderful trip 2007]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Catherine, Victoria & Caroline]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I had the good fortune of meeting and gaining a life-long confidant and loya friend when Ann and I met at UCSB some 58 yars ago.  Since those days, we have shared experiences on the UCSB Alumni Board, Reunion committees, Alumni House project, medical experiences, and ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gil Romoff]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[many social events.  Ann is a very positive, intelligent, and caring person--I am very grateful for her valuable frienship.  Ann:  I hoe you have many more healthy and successful years.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gil Romoff]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memory of Ann was close to when we first met her and she had us for dinner plus a lecture on dates. She sat at a table and gave a legitimate tutorial about raising dates, propagating and harvesting them. Jack and I fell in love with her that night. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sally and Jack Danforth]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She is has the most inquiring mind, the greatest sense of humor and a joyful disposition. Ann is an original, we are proud to call her friend. Happy Birthday]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sally and Jack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When Ann Catherine and I were young children, our parents loved Death Valley.  Our Dad took the back seat out of his 41 Ford convertible and made little beds for my sister and I.  We got up at 4 am and when we arrived at Death Valley, we could ride horses Tom & Socks! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Love, Jocelyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, you are more fun than anyone I know. I won't make this public, but your response (at the ice cream social the day we brought Joey and Alec to UCSB to start their freshmen year) when I was bemoaning my empty nest status was one for the ages! /RHave a great birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With much affection and love, Paula]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann brought so much happiness into my life by helping me find my wonderful dog Fritz.  She is such a positive, caring and fun friend, Mother and Grandmother.  I cannot think of a time we've spent together that did not involve laughter.  We just love her.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat and Fritz Mitchell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Some people have that special gift that keeps them close at heart. They listen, love, advise at times weather near or far apart. Dear Ann for over 50 years your friendship has meant so much. By phone, email or post we've always stayed in touch.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandy #1]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[College years brought us together, memories by the score. My learning to drive in the big blue Merc while you must have hit the floor! So much fun from dorm life trauma to loving UCSB. Sorority time for both of us Pi Phi for me and for you DG.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandy #2]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The years flew by our kids have grown and parenting gives way to new horizons always there, we learn more each day. What I love so much about you Ann you live life to the fullest. Happy 75th I am blessed to live near you to share time with you and always learn from you ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much Love, Sandy (#3)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann embodies joie de vivre; a dynamic, adventurous, optimistic, cheerful, funny and fun-loving woman who is a joy to be around. I'm so thankful Ralph and Bettina introduced us. We don't yet have that many "times" behind us, but look forward to many more!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[LOVE you!! Ellen Considine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann has great St. Patty's parties/RAnn is ready to sit and talk with me - /RI remember our summer gatherings and visits when she is here for the University/RShe gives me presents and presents/RShe is generous and kind/RThank you, Ann, for being Santa and a good friend/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Helen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I first met Ann at UCSB where we both pledged DG. We became roommates and have been good friends ever since! We all love Ann and the good times we have shared; either at her home or ours! She is loves people and life! She is the Aunte Mame of our generation!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Don and Linda Linck & family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann was our first neighbor to introduce herself when we moved to Cahuilla Hills. She has become a treasured friend & neighbor,......even though she doesn't stick around for the 155 degree heat that come in the summer months./R/RHappy Birthday Ann.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rick & Sue]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I meant 115 degrees]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rick & Sue]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear AC,/RWishes for this birthday year to be filled with adventures, good health and cheer. Remember 30 years ago playing bridge with the girls. Then in 2000 hooking up again in the desert. We sure kicked up a duststorm or two!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Norine #1]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our great trip to Mamouth and spending time with Jane & Tom - horses & dogs. Later watching you become a dog lover and I adopted Maci Graci. So many wonderful times filled with laughter - may there be many more to come my dear friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lots of Love, Norine (#2)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love going with you on vacation adventures! Santa Barbara is a HUGE favorite that we all - including Greta - love. We have such fun relaxing and trying out new card games and ways to entertain ourselves. It's always afternoon in Santa Barbara! We love it here!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Catherine, Victoria, Caroline Greta]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann, it was at the DG House during Rush that I first met you.  Ann you knocked my socks off.  I loved how friendly, smart and classy you were and are still to this day.  I left the house thinking I sure hope I get invited to DG because I want Ann as my Big Sister!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eloise Reyes Preiss]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are so many great memories both in San Marino and the Desert! You've always made us all feel so welcome in your homes. Spending time with you there is sure to be laughter and lively conversation!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Trish]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I Remember the times we spent together in the "birdcage", at night, with a glass of wine looking at the glitter of the stars and laughing, always laughing about something. Ann has the most infectious laugh! By day we would visit Bruce and Clonard in their artful Aerie.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie Masterson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wishing you the best of birthdays! A reconnection has to be in the cards! As single ladies we could have some more wild times for sure! How about skinny dipping in the ocean on a moonless night?? Love and a big bear hug from a fellow San Marino teacher and desert rat! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie Masterson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for raising a kind, gentle, and selfless man. /RHappy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gisela]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA['ve been most fortunate to have spent lots of time with Ann over the years.  There are so many wonderful, positive experiences both here in the U.S and also visiting her in Germany.  I recall her driving on the highways with great skill and precision.  So gifted.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ray Rath]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Let's play golf today! O.K. off to Brookside golf Course.  we tee off...hmm where's the hole?   there it is over there-18 of those, a few were way to long...seeing the same people over and over? Now that I play with the structured golf groups, I laugh at the fun we had!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Janet Shannon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday!!  our 60 years of friendship has never dwindled..your wonderful joie de vivre and great sense of humor keeps us all coming back!  Love u, thanks for the memories!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Janet Shannon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One doesn’t choose one’s sister-in-law, so I just got lucky. Summing up nearly 60 years of friendship requires a whole bucket full of complimentary adjectives. So much positive energy flows from Ann that people feel younger …she can’t be LXXV. Happiest Birthday to you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tommy & Alison Cooper]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Ann! I hope you have a wonderful birthday! I miss you! Wish you could come over and drink wine with me or go to your backyard and drink wine! We had so much fun with Catherine and the girls! And our cul-de-sac parties! Hope we can have wine soon! Cheers!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lots of Love, Kathy Bayle xo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ SINCE THE DAY I MET "AC" OUR PERSONALITIES CLICKED. WE HAVE HAD FUN!/RREMEMBER SHOPPING FOR MY FIRST VOLVO, STORING MY NORMAN ROCKWELL, PLAYING THE PONIES, BEING IN YOUR WEDDING?/RAC IS A SPARK IN EVERYONES' LIFE. THAKS FOR BEING A 56 YEAR SPARK IN MINE!/RLOVE YOU, STEVE ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[NORWOOD]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Ann, we have been wonderful friends for decades! /R/R2001: we had fun when the three of us were preparing Kaese-spaetzle in the burning desert. /R2009: we celebrated at MUC airport with beer and pretzels. /R2015:  we shared past memories in Old Pasadena - u r  great!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All the best, Addie and Christoph]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember sharing a Baltic cruise in 2008 aboard the Azamara Journey with the one and only Ann Cooper.  A warm, joyful and wonderful woman...keep smiling :)  /RHappy Birthday Ann!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Margie & Lonnie Boutté ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Some of my favorite moments were when you drove me to school for two years and we talked and listened to the BeeGees. /R/RThank you for funding my Ancestry obsession, I just love it as you know. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Victoria]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have a tremendous sense of business. From selling candy to movie theaters, to representing artists and photographers you could do it all! Renting out your houses to meet people & make $, now the palms are your latest venture. You are the epitome of an entrepreneur!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Catherine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for taking such good care of me as a puppy, and introducing me to new places and people. I love hanging out with you and going for walks. Thank you especially for my bionic legs, now I know I will soon be recovered enough to chase the ball! I am devoted to you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Greta]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I like & admire most is your commitment to V&C. They are who they are because of you. Exposing them to new cultures & ways of thinking - they have greater knowledge & admiration for people & the arts. You can cook as well as any on Food Network! Adventure on!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday - Robert]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann is also a terrific driver and doesn't mind doing it on our various trips together including to Napa and driving around the surrounding countryside and to Santa Cruz via the Big Sur coastline and all the other fun places we went together]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Toni Amorteguy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Catherine,/R/RI sent you already short text a while ago but here are some photos you can add to it. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bettina, Heidi and Willi & Ralph]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann Cady Cooper save my life more than once, out of the boredom that most live their timid lives out of.  She brought me out of the shadows living in some Pasadena hell apartment to a castle.  She is the best!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Neal Florine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Ann,/RI remember coming to your house and sharing time with you and the girls. We ate Italian that night, I think. You are one of the few true "ladies" that I have known. Surely the girls have grown up into sweet ladies like you and Catherine. My love to all.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mrs. Laurie Klimowicz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Ann:Every single time I have had the pleasure to see you, you always have a smile. /RLove Russ and Jo Ann]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Russell W. Phinder]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cousin Ann 's visit with grandaughter Victoria was memorable Nice to see and be with the Califorina clan .Wish it happened more often .happy Birthday Ann .]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[john cady]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann and her daughter and I, Doris, had lunch on Friday! We had a great time and I am getting to know Ann more and more! She is a great person with great people skills and she is so much fun to be with!/RI hope for a lasting friendship!/RHappy Birthday Ann!!!!!!!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Doris Webb]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember fondly your living in the birdcage. Your desert property is so lovely and I was glad to be able to visit. Looking further back, I loved seeing you in Ojai when Catherine was there with the babies. All the best for a very Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen Fay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What fun to have you visit us this summer. You look terrific! We have a card and book for you but no address, so this will have to do for now. Continue enjoying those golden years ..you do it better than anyone we know! Happy, happy birthday.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Marcia and Maurie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday!/RWe Love You!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Marion & Juliana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom - /RI hope you have a fantastic birthday with many many more to come. You are my best friend and my dear sweet mother and I am truly blessed to have you in my life. I hope you know just how many people love and cherish you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Catherine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ann Catherine Cady Cooper/R/RHappy 75th Birthday/R/RAugust 6, 2015]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lots of Love to you!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>