<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2555-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/26/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[david mills]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[1040 evergreen pt rd]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[medina]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[WA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[98039]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDEX_FEDEX2DAY]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sand]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 90th Birthday Sally!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Sally Mills]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Much love from all of us]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Sally, /R"She walks in beauty, like the night/R  Of cloudless climes and starry skies;/RAnd all that's best of dark and bright/R  Meet in her aspect and her eyes;/RThus mellowed to that tender light/R  Which heaven to gaudy day denies."/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dick & June]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Gram, Happy Birthday! We love you more than you will ever know. I feel so blessed to have you as my Grammie. You have taught me so much and you are an inspiration to all us women. /RLove you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jujubee, Joel, Addison and Zachary]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 90th Birthday Sally!   That is a long time.   I wish I could be there to celebrate with you but I am in Arizona!  Thanks for over 60 years of being my sister-in-law and all the special times we have shared /Rthrough the years, especially family and cooking!    ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat Mills]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["She walks in beauty like the night" certainly describes our dear friend Sally Mills!/RFrom the day we met we felt  your friendship was a gift and we have cherished that gift for many years. /RNow we know the date of your birthday & we send our Love & best wishes to you  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Doris and Buck Coppess]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Sally, Happy 90th Birthday!!  I count you as one of my treasured blessings...I love spending quiet mornings with you knitting or serving at the Altar.  May you have a lovely family gathering with many more to come! XOXOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pam and Dave Griffith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As a Halloween prank you once "soaped" a neighbor's window.  Unfortunately for you, at the time the only thing you knew how to spell was your name..../RThat's one of the many stories about you I remember.  It's one of my favorites.  I love you.  So does Jesus!/R ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paul Richardson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sally...how many women get to be SOOO lucky to have a Mother in Law like you in their life? You inspire me to be a better person in all that you do, and all that you are.  Thank you for your love, friendship, and for being an absolute dream "Grammy" to our girls....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much love, Jilly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Sally. We are so grateful for your gracious kindness to us and your wonderful sense of humor. We're not sure, however, that we're capable of putting up a good Spite & Malice defense ...but willing to try. Blessings for the year ahead!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris & Rick Jillard]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sally is the grandmother I never had.  The kindest and sweetest lady I know (after my mother).  I still remember the first time she visited the Gaither family in Jamestown, RI.  She not only brought with her her positive, cheerful disposition but a sense of happy calm.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Masha Gaither]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sallers, I love you. Thank you for a lifetime of wonderful, fun filled memories as mom's - Betty McKenzie's - very best friendzie... and for always caring about and supporting  me and Jim. I am so grateful for you, and wish you the very best birthday ever!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 90th Sallers! I am so blessed to have had 55 years of your love & support, your unwavering belief in me, your kindness & compassion, your unconditional acceptance, your spiritual guidance, your strength during tough times & your infectious joy during happy times. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With much love, Jimmers xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Sally, /RHappy 90th Birthday! We really miss your visits on the  east coast but are really excited that we have come to visit you. We love your visits because of the baking,  games of Spite and Malice but mostly your lovely companionship./RWith much love,/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rowan, Masha, Natasha and Nina]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From back tickles, to finding the name of a flower, to the best hugs in the world, you are always the first one I go to! Your love and support is something I wouldn't trade for the world. Happiest of birthdays, Gram! Love you more than words can explain.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hayden]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sally, you have been a gift to your family, friends and parish over the years and it's time for you to receive gifts instead of giving!  You have been and always will be special and we wish you many more years of good healh and happiness.  Blessings and love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ Bill & Helen Tygret]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Sally,/RBirthday Blessings to an amazing lady.  You are so special and dear to me. Your gentle spirit radiates all around you, may this very special day be blessed with /Rlove. Hugs to you My Very /RDear Friend,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Della]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I think of you; I think about how lucky I am to be a Mills, I think about how someday I hope to be just like you, I think about how much I admire you. You are the most spectacular Grandma a girl could ever dream of having. When I think about you, I feel blessed.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Taylor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 90th Birthday Sally!  The girls and I are so happy to be a part of your celebration.  You have such a special place in our hearts.  Your kind, and gentle loving spirit, warmth, delightful wit, and countless angel food cakes have brought such joy to all of us!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nan, Courtney, and Conley xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The most immediate feeling I have when I think of you, Sally, is inclusion. When our families connected, you embraced me, and made feel like one of yours right away. It is such a treat to be one of your granddaughters. Happy Birthday! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chelsea LeRoy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank  for always being such a loving presence in my life. Gracious, kind, patient and generous. Even when my own life turned difficult you never missed a beat. I love so much and cannot imagine my life without you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lisa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sally has been a good friend and supporter for many years. She had confidence in her daughter's choice and for that I am eternally grateful. Sally is a great reader and a marvelous example of a life-long learner. She walks in love.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charlie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To my elegant and classy friend, I wish you a wonderful celebration and a year of joy and blessings. Working together on Intercessory Prayer has been a blessing. You have a countenance, Sally that is so beautiful and knowing you is such a privilege. Love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Judy Englund (and Dick too)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the closest person to a 2nd Mom for me, pretty sure I am #1 son to that other guy...who else would take pride in rolling Sally at age 87 through the lobby while she stood on a hand truck...I expect 10 more years of peach pie coming my way...god bless this lady..]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rick Nemyre]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Sally, We can't believe you are already 90 years old! We send our very best wishes for a wonderful birthday and for many more to come for our very favorite "cousin". Happy Birthday from Jim, Susan and all the West Coast Gaithers]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim, Susan, and all the Gaithers]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are my role model, inspiration and mentor. I'm still working on patience, keeping it simple and not making myself crazy. But the most important things have 'stuck'....family, making every penny count, and remembering what is really important. /RI love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Sally, You are such a special person to me, and I've so enjoyed all the fun times we've shared together. Sharing our children together is one of the very best times. Truely best wishes, and love to come, Sally. May God bless and keep you in his care.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barbara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 90th Birthday, Sally! /RI can't tell you now much it's meant to me to have you as a cousin and wonderful friend. I'm forever grateful (as are all the members my little petting zoo - you and Dad certainly taught me quite a love of animals, much to Mom's chagrin!)./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With all my love, Julie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Gram,/RI am so grateful that I have a "second" grandma like you. You have the heart and compassion of an angel and that's truly what you are. Lavender reminds me of you, whenever I come upon it. Happy Birthday, wish I could be there.  Love you lots,/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Courtney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm having 'Sally's guacamole' withdrawals.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ty]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am always admire for your elegant heart, elegant sense of all.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Katsuaki Demura]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lovely Sally,/RHappy Birthday. I still think about how beautiful you looked when you tried on the Japanese kimono for the first time, years ago.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Baba]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday to one of the most caring, beautiful, generous, kind and thoughtful person I know. The friendship you had with Nammy is truly remarkable... and I am so grateful that you are in my life! Love you Sallers.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aunt Sally is my best aunt ever, the Cherrio sandwiches she made when I came over for sleepovers were world famous.  /REverything she does is with class and grace!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael Mills]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sally always remembers my birthday and I get a phone call./RSally never knew quite how to take it when people said she looked just like her brother./RSally always has kind words for everyone./RSally is my one and only Aunt.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[M C Tevis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am the luckiest person in the world, I have you as my Mom./RMose/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Mills]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What a joy you are in my life.  You shine like the light of Jesus everywhere you go./RYour love for everyone is so evident, your gift of hospitality is so gracious, your generosity of your spirit and hard work behind the scenes is truely such a gift to all.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jo Moore]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Neil and I are so happy to be celebrating this very special birthday with you!! What a perfect occasion for our families to get together – I know we’ll love this time together. Happy Birthday!!/RMuch love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charlotte and Neil]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sally, you are a blessing to all who know you. Your kindness, grace and love for others is inspiring. You are beautiful, inside and out and I smile when I think of all the ways you have impacted my life. I love you and wish you a wonderful 90th birthday./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>