<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2557-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/27/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Kimberly Force]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[521 Sherman Ave]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Hawthorne]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[NY]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[10532]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_200]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[scarlet]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 70th Birthday, Georgia!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Georgia]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[with love from us]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am very happy that we remained friends after we retired.  Also I am glad we go to the gym together or I am sure I would be 20 pounds heavier!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barbara Montagna]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We remember fondly toasting to old friends with full glasses of red wine at Teresa's wedding in Italy! It was so great to spend time with you there! Happy 70th and many more happy and healthy ones! Cheers to you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meri & Margie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You offered your home to us when we came to New York for Jessica's wedding.  You gave your entire house to our family to use for the days we were there, while you and Uncle Larry stayed at Craig's. Yet another example of your selflessness!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kellie Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Throughout college Aunt Georgia would send the most thoughtful cards and care packages! Her thoughtfulness is something that I still talk about to this day and hope to pass along to my nieces and nephews when they are in school.   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Witenko Lukasiewicz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In my early teens, I recall traveling to NYC from Florida to spend time with Aunt Georgia and Kim in NYC.  I still remember wearing matching t-shirts and hitting up fun sights in the city! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Witenko Lukasiewicz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I still have fond memories of Christmas with all of the Witenko/Armstrong family.  I feel like it was yesterday that we were sitting in the basement, talking, laughing and watching old videos of Aunt Georgia, Black Barbara, Uncle George and my dad!   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Witenko Lukasiewicz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It is difficult to pinpoint one reason that Aunt Georgia is so special because she is kind, genuine, caring, loving, and fun.  Aunt Georgia is one of a kind! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Witenko Lukasiewicz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She and I would stuff ourselves with sweets brought in for someone's birthday at BOCES, and then convince ourselves that we had to eat some real food to balance it out./R/RSad part is...I still do that!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Tietjen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[For the longest time, your mom sent me a Luke dollar in every card. She even bought me a special wooden box in which to keep my Luke dollars. I thought it was so kind and really made me feel like a part of the family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kellie Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I also remember being envious of the amazing care packages she would send to Jon when we were in college. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kellie Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She's definitely a gift-giver at heart. My kids have gotten gifts for seeing her when she came to visit in Florida, as well as when they went to see her in New York!/R/RAunt Georgia is a one-of-a-kind, awesome person!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kellie Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite memories of Georgia was from my wedding.  She & Larry were both so genuinely happy to be there and so appreciative to be a part of it all and it really made my heart happy because of course I consider them part of my extended family!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Teresa Perretta]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When she had family dinners she would put lottery tickets under everybody's plates!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She always made sure we had a good time - even when Brian was getting stitched up in the hospital she was making balloons out of the rubber gloves & sticking biohazard stickers on him.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin O'Hea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[And it is the girls' turn to throw the party!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin O'Hea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am so grateful that my grandchildren have such a loving nanny close by!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christine Force]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We think she's afraid to assume that I actually know who she is, so every time we see her and she says hello, she always adds that she's Kim's mom, just in case! One of the last times we saw her we actually joked with her about it, so now she just says hello! Love her! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andy Serra]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Even though we don't see each other often, I treasure you as a friend. So glad our paths crossed & all because we volunteered for a committee (even forgot what it was for). You are a special person & deserve all the best life has to offer.  So happy you are in my life!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peggy Salierno]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Have lots of happy memories!  I remember our Wednesday lunches and the stir they caused in building A.  I looked forward to them every week. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peggy Salierno]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always had such a knack for picking just the right gift! I still cherish my Peggy’s treats candy dish.  Love the little boxes the chocolates came in (the candies were amazing). Don't know if you know this but I use the little boxes every year on my Christmas tree. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peggy Salierno]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best thing about Aunt Georgia is her strong sense of family first and always staying connected no matter where we all are!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michele Witenko Duncan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Luke dollars and boxes of treats she sent while away at college are great memories. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michele Witenko Duncan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Every year, you would take Corey & me out for a day of birthday shopping, lunch and dessert since we are all August babies. I especially remember you buying me the jeans I really wanted but my parents wouldn't buy because they never went on sale. :) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michele Witenko Duncan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember how diligent you were in adding each of Kim & Craig's school pictures on that yellow bus picture frame that hung outside of her bedroom. We barely had the pictures back and they were already framed in that yellow bus on the wall!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aimee Salvatore Adams]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I also remember Georgia teaching me how to make perogies. Even though she taught us how to make them the real Ukrainian way, we would make them with wonder white bread & mash popcorn inside!  She would laugh & roll her eyes at us!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aimee Salvatore Adams]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how Nanny loves me. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tycho]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love when Nanny makes dirt cake AND THEN I EAT IT!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tycho]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Nanny's house because it is very beautiful.  I like helping Nanny water her plants.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Duncan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We like when Nanny takes us to Game Stop.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tycho & Duncan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for re-doing our rooms!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tycho & Duncan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A favorite memory is sitting on the couch with you when I was little, watching All My Children and eating my lunch of balogna on toast with mustard.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how you sewed a patch of my pink blanket into the hem of my wedding dress.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You awe me with your kindness and generosity; your love, humor, compassion & warmth. You inspire me with your selflessness & love of family. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the sun of our family's solar system. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When Craig was getting married she asked me if I would do her hair for her. I went over to her house early in the morning and she was so pleased with the way it turned out.  She had a lot of confidence and trust in me as I’m not even a hairdresser!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carol DiBattista]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like you today and every day.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When we were young and small, too young to go out far alone, Georgia used to take us to Linden Boulevard to the candy store and buy us stuff to eat.  It was a real treat and I still remember her kindness letting us tag along.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She would get on her bike & ride for miles & miles to White Castle to buy us burgers. The trip was long & treacherous since she rode alone and across major roads. She did this out of her kind heart & never asked for anything in return. Boy, we loved those burgers.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I wish to thank you for our wonderful years together. I believe it was a group like no other. We had respect for one another, were very hard workers and as friends will do, could talk about anything with each other. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Carney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You taught me much, dear Georgia - about patience, kindness and always treatment of others done with much grace. I thank you for that. You are a very special person! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Carney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have many memories of Georgia. We came to BOCES in the same year probably a month apart. When she came to the Business Office she was the photographer for our parties and would make poster boards with the pictures she took.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy Mazza]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Georgia and Larry helped me immensely with raising my youngest son, Warren. I knew that they would be wonderful grandparents. They spent a lot of time taking my son to the Zoo, movies and other fun things. He has all good memories of these times.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy Mazza]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Georgia let us descend upon her house from the city and eat buckets full of her beautiful cherry tomatoes. She was always a gracious hostess to a bunch of loud twenty-somethings from New York.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alicia Hutchison Steffann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Georgia, Peggy and I formed a "lunch" bond many years ago while working at BOCES.  We met every Wednesday and shared lunch and conversation.  It always seemed that an hour was never enough because we always had a lot to catch up on. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sheila Campbell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are one of the kindest people I know - always thoughtful & considerate of everyone's feelings. In fact, I wish I could be more like you in that you always seem to see the positive side of situations and I don't think I have ever seen you really angry! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sheila Campbell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have always been a good friend to me and I value that friendship more than you know. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sheila Campbell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[40+ years of most memorable times shared with Georgia began as next-door neighbors for 2 1/2 years on Relda Street, Plainview.  Chats over the fence where the watermelons took over, nights swimming in the pool followed by breakfast jack sandwiches from Jack in the Box.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat & Frank O'Hea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Trips to the Greenport house & KOA…hanging out on the beach, fishing off the dock, sitting on the porch w/binoculars to watch sailboats, playing cards @ the kitchen table, kids drawing in the dark & the parties - girls’ turn & boys’ turn - shopping trips to Arcade.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat & Frank O'Hea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sharing celebrations of our June wedding anniversaries in NYC: Tavern on the Green, Broadway show & staying at the Hilton…Norwegian cruise to the Caribbean & Bermuda.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat & Frank O'Hea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Weekends in NYC @ Kim's Greystone apt.: eating our way through street fairs or fancy "foo foo" restaurants….Rhinebeck craft festival where Georgia put a sample soap in Frank's shirt pocket for safe keeping & he took a bite out of it because he thought it was chocolate.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat & Frank O'Hea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sharing meals: one favorite was Carbonara & winner winner chicken dinner...as well as Christmas sleepovers at Gay Ridge Road & meeting at the tree in NYC: these are just a sampling of all the great adventures we shared over the years.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat & Frank O'Hea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What is special about Georgia is her wonderful quirky sense of humor & wild curiosity. She is sincere, genuine, & encouraging - making you feel comfortable & at ease. To sum her up is she is fun to be with and to know her is to love her.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat & Frank O'Hea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A recent visit from our daughter Laurie prompted us to recall memories of our folk group days. Oh, the fun we had! Remember the time we decided to levitate somebody in a chair? We laughed then & continue to laugh today just thinking about it.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary & Dan Proulx]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We thank Him for His gift of YOU to our lives. You have been a loyal and committed friend. May the joy you bring to others come back to you today and always. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary & Dan Proulx]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I enjoyed working with you for so many years. I always appreciated your helpful, calm and efficient way you did your job. No matter what problem or urgency I came to you with, you solved. Thanks for all your help for all those years!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Margaret Koch]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Enjoy your birthday with you husband and thoughtful family. Oh yes, one more thing, I was always jealous of you every Tuesday when I saw your husband bringing you flowers. I always thought what a nice guy, Georgia is so lucky. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Margaret Koch]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the best shopping partner - you leave no stone unturned until we find the perfect item! Going wedding dress shopping with you, I was in capable hands - and you helped me choose the perfect dress.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Woof woof bark bark /R(we love to jump on you!)/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Edgar and Aquinnah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love when we have fun because that’s what being a grandma is about. All fun and no stress.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Isabel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I was little you used to make up kids' lyrics to songs in church - my favorite was all the Sesame Street characters during communion hymns!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I wonder how many dollars of change made it to our knees during church homilies??]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Monday night dinners and Easter and Christmas mornings are always the best when you are there.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Isabel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always make me laugh when you try to memorize songs and sing them to us.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Isabel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I loved it when I was really young and you told me the story about how you gave me gum at a wedding. And then how I stuck it on a statue of Mary.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Isabel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It’s so much fun when you wear your birthday crown everywhere on the Vineyard. It makes me laugh my head off. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Isabel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My first Christmas with you was overwhelming - my pile of presents was to the ceiling.  Every present was picked with such care.  I was overwhelmed with your kindness.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wendy Armstrong]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Making pierogi with you is such a special family tradition.  I love that now all of the grandchildren help too!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wendy Armstrong]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[DIP ITS!  /Rand a KC meatball.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wendy Armstrong]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When Sam was just born Craig needed to go away over night.  You offered to keep me company, so we rented the horror movie “The Ring.”  You stayed with me until late at night and helped me walk Mullin because I was too scared after the movie.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wendy Armstrong]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I became Georgia’s husband on June 22, 1968 and she made me the happiest man in the world. I still adore her and always will.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larry Armstrong]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Georgia gave birth to our son, Craig, on May 5, 1970 and we started a family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larry Armstrong]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Georgia gave birth to our daughter, Kim, on June 19, 1973, and our family was complete.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larry Armstrong]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The things I like most about Georgia are that she is beautiful, kind, gracious and sexy, and accepts me for who I am, without condition.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larry Armstrong]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Georgia was the mom that we all wanted to have – kind & funny, she made me feel like I was a part of the family & she always had time to play with us. I can't even count the number of impromptu pools parties, sleepovers & games of Spit we played over the years.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Debbie Sinnott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember going to Hawaii and taking hula lessons - no one rocked a lei and grass skirt like Georgia.  Mostly I remember how much fun Georgia was and is and how much fun it always was to be around her.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Debbie Sinnott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Georgia had been out to a restaurant & had spaghetti carbonara - she loved it so much that she was excited to make it and invite my family over to dinner at your house. I remember eating it in your dining room & loving it.  (STRANGE the things that stick with us!!)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandy Sinnott Wetzel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We remember Georgia & Larry coming over to play cards and for New Year's Eve parties.  Mostly we remember your bubbly personality and how much you loved your family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Helen & George Sinnott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Two of Georgia’s strongest attributes are her ability to give & listen. Through the years she has taken the time to listen to your woes, never setting judgment but always consoling.  She has always been a giver ...from the smallest to the biggest present!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carol DiBattista]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mother Teresa said, 'Spread Love Everywhere You Go, Let No One Ever Come to You Without Leaving Happier!' Georgia is a perfect example of what Mother Teresa said and believed in!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carol DiBattista]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I worked with Georgia the one thing that comes to mind is how sweet and caring she was.  We had some good laughs, but always got our work done.  And remember, 70 is only a number, you are still young at heart!  It is always great to see you at the luncheons.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Louise Giacomini]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Georgia and I didn't work together at BOCES but since retirement we have found a common ground: Facebook games! We started with Words With Friends & she beat me all the time. Then came Candy Crush - she was always ahead…now in Soda Crush she is already in outer space!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marylou Nesbit]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aunt Georgia would send all of us a massive box of candy for each holiday while in college.  All of my roommates wanted to meet this awesome Aunt.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Corey Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best thing about Aunt Georgia is her selfless dedication to her family and always being there during small or big life events for all of us.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Corey Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The annual August Birthday celebration will always be memorable.  /R/REvery year since I was maybe 6 or 7,  I got excited around June because it was time to plan our day with Aunt Georgia.  That's when Michele and I got our first Luke Dollars (which I still have today).  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Corey Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'll never forget going to Olive Garden for maybe 5 years in a row and getting full on alfredo, salad, and bread sticks.  When it came time for dessert, Aunt Georgia always ordered one of everything on the menu.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Corey Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I loved shopping for presents for our birthdays! Michele would be done in 10 minutes because she bought expensive things.  Then they would follow me around to every toy store in town as I got car sets, Nerf guns, and pretty much anything that was a few dollars. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Corey Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Georgia was so supportive of me when I sent my first born off to college - assuring me that each day would be better, and once I was hearing from Lauren regularly my tears would stop.  She was so right and her words of wisdom from her experience were so true.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lorraine Petruzzi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Georgia is so special & in her own quiet way could relay her care & concern when you were going through a rough time, like when my parents died and when my girls were going through treatment for breast cancer.  Her compassion was always from the heart and sincere.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lorraine Petruzzi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As we ate soup in our Jon & Kellie bowls recently, I was reminded how she gives our kids personalized gifts which means a lot to them, because their names are unique...  (And surely we wouldn't find items with their names on them in a store!)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kellie Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In the summer of ‘54, George & I went out on a raft. The waves started crashing on us but we were young & didn't swim very well. The raft flipped but Georgia swam out to us, maneuvered us to safety & had us hold on until we were in shallow water.  We owe you Georgia!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When my mom was so sick in the hospital I called her from the parking lot and cried and she just let me go on and listened until I felt better.  There are so many memories with Georgia – she is such a kind and warm hearted person. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She always puts everybody first and offers encouragement in times of need. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I was in a cast and couldn't get out she came to visit and brought me a sick present. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Georgia always makes me feel welcome and part of the family. She was the first person to come with me and I was so excited to show her my wedding dress. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My first thought of Georgia is Family First.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Denise Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Many great memories:"Luke" Dollars, confetti in greeting cards, dirt cake, venetian cookies & sausage bread. Traveling to Jon’s & Jess’ HS graduations. Welcoming all the Florida Witenkos when we invade Yorktown Hts. You always keeps in touch & ask how everyone is doing!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Denise Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I went off to college, Aunt Georgia would send me care packages loaded with candy every month.  The office staff got to know the BOCES boxes and would clamor around for me to open my loot and share with them.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jonathan Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We would receive a Luke dollar in our cards or Christmas presents. I continued to receive them in my college care packages. When I graduated HS, I received 100 Luke dollars in a box (quantity pushed Luke out of the Bible and into a special box).]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jonathan Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Luke dollars were always to be spent on fun stuff and had to be naturally acquired, not asked for at the bank...I had to restrain when  I worked at a bank!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jonathan Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My sister received $104.25 or some odd amount 4 years after my $100 gift to account for inflation because Aunt G was always equitable.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jonathan Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When Georgia was working her first job & still living at home, she paid room & board. Before Steve & I were allowed to eat, Georgia got fed first (her rule) since she paid rent. But Georgia also bought Steve & I presents every payday.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[George Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like about Georgia is how she takes care of family.  She always was generous with gifts to my kids & Steve's kids. Georgia always has a golden heart with people.  Georgia still is in contact with my kids.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[George Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I went 40 yrs believing my brother Steve was responsible for my pinkie injury until Georgia came forward with the truth.  She was the one who closed the door on me…She didn't want me to blame her!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[George Witenko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My Mother’s Love is stronger than a diaper pin stuck through a crying baby’s stomach.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Craig]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy memories of change on my knee at church, late night book deliveries to Westchester Book followed by a midnight breakfast and jellybean runs while Kim was at gymnastics.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Craig]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have not seen you in a while but I still remember your dedication and loyalty to your family & friends and your great smile.  Miss those group reunions we had at Noreen's.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary & Stan Suleski]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Really miss making beef barley soup for you and your husband, you were always my biggest fan. Hope you have a great birthday and many more to come.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leo Penzine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Even though you have held me by my ankles & shook me over the sink as a child to get the Diet Coke out, you’re still awesome. I have so much fun when you’re with us.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Samantha]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your mimmy-got-in-trouble stories late at night (after I’m supposed to be in bed…) are so much fun, and getting dinner and candy before a movie is always a great time. You’re an amazing grandma.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Samantha]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're a fabulous grandma and I'm so glad that you could help raise me and that I could grow up with you. Thank you so much for everything you've done, are doing, and will do for me. I love you so much.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Samantha]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have a vivid memory of the day I got into the jet ski accident. I was being wheeled around in the gurney and I looked up and Georgia was taking photos. Someone yelled at her to put the camera down and she replied, “What? It's just a few photos to remember this.”]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian O'Hea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Although I was not there for this one, it is on our wedding video. After my wedding, everyone went to the hotel bar. I think Wendy was filming and asked Georgia how many drinks she had and she held up 3 fingers and said “this many.”]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian O'Hea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember going over to Craig and Wendy's house for a BBQ when we lived in Katonah and Georgia asked if I could cut some of the vegetables for a salad and as I was chopping she came over to let me know how proud she was of me and the career I chose. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian O'Hea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I think the thing I most like about Georgia is her sense of adventure. /R/RI hope the O'Hea & Armstrong gangs can get together soon and create new memories! /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian O'Hea]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are sincere, warm, caring, giving, fun loving, just a lovely lady. We have shared secrets and stories like little girls do with their besties. It is overwhelming to me how many memories I have of you, and with you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Janice Taylor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We once had a (very rare) argument at work over an account switching hands. We went without speaking for about 2 days until you came into work one morning & said, “so are you ever going to talk to me again?” We laughed, hugged & I apologized and didn’t skip a beat.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Janice Taylor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In some ways we are so different, in others very similar. I treasure our friendship more then you will ever know. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Janice Taylor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have had hours of conversations, we have cried together, laughed together, just hung out together, and worked side by side together for all these years. I wouldn’t change a thing between us, except see you more these days.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Janice Taylor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When my son was very ill, you supported me so  at work. But the sweetest thing you did for me was to make one of your famous homemade ziti trays & come to my home to drop it off.  It meant the world to me; I lived on that yummy dish all week.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Janice Taylor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have always loved Georgia’s kind, caring and gentle personality.  She is truly a lovely lady.  I especially like her laugh - a low chuckle.  She always made me feel good when we would chat. I’m sending my love, Happy Birthday! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lois Schmidt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have fond memories of when you & Larry took me to the zoo when I was little.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Warren Patrinos]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You kindled my love of reading from a very young age, buying me Harry Potter books & anything else you thought I’d like. THANK YOU for that - reading is a still a passion of mine…and I still have the books that you gave me and am very thankful for them.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Warren Patrinos]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Many Greenport memories: We 6 kids shared many tube fights in the water & many fishing trips in your dad’s rowboat trying to catch blow fish. (I got to hate fishing!)  I also remember you in a white one-piece swim suit, and how it complemented your tan.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Comerford]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You were always easy going & fun to be around. We have not seen each other since your wedding; communication was lost for a while. But now we are back in touch & I can always count on an Xmas card from you with white snowflakes stuffed inside that go all over my carpet!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill & Pam Comerford]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Friends are hard to find - especially in your next-door neighbors. I was so happy and blessed to have had you for all those many years.  Can’t take that city out of the girls and indeed it was wonderful to meet someone who shared that Long Island quick accent.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maureen Geary]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I miss Gay Ridge Road so much & all the dinners that Craig & Eddie shared, naturally deciding which house had the best grub that night. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maureen Geary]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You were the funniest but probably didn’t even realize your quick wit….And remember calling me over in distress when flames were shooting out from the bottom of your stove?...I guess you thought I knew what to do?!?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maureen Geary]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When we lived in Jamaica and Larry was on leave, Georgia stopped on the way from work during a snow storm - we watched CREEPY MOVIES on TV and  Georgia had to sleep over until the next morning because the buses had stopped running.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[G'ma Marie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember that, when her mother was ill, Georgia stayed in Bellerose, cooking and caring for her parents. She was such a dedicated and loving daughter!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[G'ma Marie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Georgia LOVED White Castle hamburgers.  When she was expecting Craig, she would eat a whole bunch, maybe a dozen at a time.  I don't know where she put it all!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[G'ma Marie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I like most about Georgia is EVERYTHING - she is an excellent wife, mother and grandmother.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[G'ma Marie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm thankful that you raised Kim exactly how you did -- you made the person who would make my life complete, and I owe it all to you. (And Larry, I guess, but don't show him this.)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember the first Armstrong Christmas, and the shock and awe of the enormous present pile. Holy Christmas! This family knows how to celebrate a holiday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember, countless times, you having the patience and endurance of a saint while playing whatever make-believe games the boys wanted to play -- for hours!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I would come visit you in the Business Office in your cubicle to go over outstanding invoices & laugh about how things were changing. And oh the piles of paper waiting for me for auditing! When I came back the next day, we would laugh about what I couldn't find.   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barbara Skrapits]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Before Karen was born I “ran away” to you guys for the weekend. You & Larry got me at bus station to calm me down & bring me back to your new apt in Flushing. (Which I’m sure led to having you both for godparents for Karen.) I realize what a treasure you’ve always been!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat Zentner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My memory comes from the “Big Move” to your new house on Long Island. You were so organized & gave us a great lunch. By the end of day I was tired, but you just kept going like the energizer bunny.  Thanks for these memories that I’ll always have of my sister-in-law.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob Zentner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm lucky because my mom is my best friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>