<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2581-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/30/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Brendan Arnott]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[438 Prussian Lane]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Wayne]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19087]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[pink]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Jen's 50th Birthday]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Jennifer Arnott]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about my "Ernie" is that she LOVES me unconditionally- warts and all!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lou Lou ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We *** LOVE*** that Jen takes time to nurture her family and her friendships.  She's always got so much going on, but  intentionally carves out time to spend with each of us!  She makes us feel like we're the most important people in the world!   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura & Hannah Clark]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You make me a better person. Your love, good nature, and genorosity are virtues for which we should all aspire. /R/RI love you. Happy Birthday.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brendan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Who else can locate designer brands like Lilly Pulitzer, Louis Vuitton and Chanel at Goodwill or a thrift shop?  Jennifer not only appreciates the 'thrill of the hunt' & a 'good bargain', she loves the quality that comes from these designers. We LOVE that about Jen!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura & Hannah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Diet Coke, Chex Mix and a room at the Four Seasons in Beverly Hills. /R/RNeed I say more? ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen's first Chubb roommate]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jennifer Green Arnott is as beautiful inside as she is outside! She is the gal I would want in my foxhole!!  She is always there for those she loves.....AND Jen-Jen is always up for FUN!!!/RLOVE YOU and HAPPY BIRTHDAY XOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kristi and Doug DeCinces]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are always willing to help with a smile on your face, a kind word and open arms. Your enthusiasism for life, family and friends is beautiful. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Greg, Claire and Jackson xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jenny, you are a kind, beautiful, thoughtful friend, mother and wife, a true Christian woman.  Your kindness is boundless and your love is an inspiration.  I am so glad you were my "buddy family".  I love you!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[-Patty (aka Patellen)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jen Jen is the glue that holds our family together. She is the such a generous, caring and loving sister and aunt.We love you!/RHappy Birthday XOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Colorado Greens]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jennifer is kind, caring and thoughtful]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robyne & Warren Arnott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have to pick just ONE thing I love about Jen? Impossible! I'll start with her generosity, her commitment to helping others, her sense of humor, her love of her family, her sense of style, her smile, her forehand, and her friendship! The total package! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Annie Webb]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Perfection!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Husband ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My ride to the groomer, my walker, my feeder, and my belly scratcher. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pokey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I love most about Jen is her warmth and interest in others.  She is a true friend and I have witnessed and experienced her love and devotion to others.  She also is a lot of fun and is one to belly laugh with as well and shed a tear. She is a wonderful friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen Moon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jennifer, you are a warm and loving person, easy to talk to, genuinely interested in others, fun loving and funny!  You are beautiful both inside and out!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jane Dwyer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love that you are such a great Mum and that you make Brendan so happy. Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate, Gavin, Zac and Jake]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing that I like most about Jen is that no matter how long we may be apart, we can always pick up right where we left off.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marielena]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Honorable and extraordinary! My very special sister from another mother. Most generous and helpful spirit who is a gift of loving kindness. As you continue to age beautifully, may you find peace and joy always. Thank you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Xoxox, SueSue]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hard to choose one, but I have a soft spot for her amazing mothering skills. Seeing the children she has raised speaking a thousand words about the type of person she is. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pooper aka Sarah M]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["What is done in love, is done well" ~ so it isn't any wonder why everything Jen does is perfection.  You inspire me on every level my friend. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen Doble]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I LOVE the way Jennifer makes me feel in her home, always welcome, always loved and there are always delicious treats! I LOVE Jennifer's heart, the way she laughs and cries with me through all of life's moments. You are a special friend that I am blessed to know.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maureen Eggleton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have the most caring heart in the world! You are generous, loving and compassionate. I hope that the world will follow your example, because even when it is tough you are reliable, loving and overall just the best. I love you forever!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah Carroll]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jesus wept. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Sunday School Class]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I like most about Jen is that we can truly talk about ANYTHING without judgement. We are never at a loss for words when we are together. You are a true friend that I will continue to cherish forever. Thanks to SIJ preschool for bringing us together. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Coleen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ABCD! So grateful to have you as a friend, looking forward to all the good times ahead]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andy Doble]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jennifer is a loving, caring Mother,Wife,Daughter,and Friend.She is always available when you need a listening ear,a meal and loves to go junking!/RI thank her for the many times she has taken me shopping with her to warehouse sales and encouraged me to go for it Mom!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[love you Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[May you have a Wonderful Birthday and Many More Years of Happiness and Fun!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Mom!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Even when we haven't seen each other for several months, easy conversation just picks up where we last left off.  From hanging out on weekends in Sydney to the porch in NH, I always look forward to your fun stories and laughs, and for always being there to listen.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frank Anthony]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jennifer is caring, kind and loyal. She treats others with compassion and respect. And that is why I love her!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pam Anthony]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are so many things that I like about Jennifer!  She tells a great story, is open and interested in other people, and she is beautiful on the inside and out!  Happy Birthday!!  Enjoy your day and the year ahead! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jane Dwyer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[How do I love thee? Let me count the ways.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elizabeth Barrett Browning]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love is always patient and kind; love is never jealous; love is not boastful or conceited,it is never rude and never seeks its own advantage, it does not take offence or store up grievances./RLove does not rejoice at wrongdoing, but finds its joy in the truth.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[1 Corinthians 13 4-6]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Have I told you lately. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Van Morrison ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Admiring modern "art" on impromptu tourist days]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gordon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jen you are one of the most welcoming, kind and generous people I have met! Even though I don't see you as often as I'd like, when I do it feels like I never left and I am always sad to leave. I love you and look forward to when we will see each other again! I miss you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much love, hugs and prayers- Aileen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jennifer,/RYou are the most generous, kind and fun woman.  I have enjoyed knowing you for these past-is it 16 years?-and creating wonderful memories with you and your family.  You are one of the BEST!  Lots of love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cathy and Frank]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[...Jen is that she is probably the best example of what a friend should be.  She is loyal and understanding.  She's open and non judgmental.  She's the best listener I've ever met.  And I can't imagine that there is anyone sweeter than her in the whole wide world.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennie Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your ability to at a moments notice, drop off a case of beer at my back door. No questions asked with a smile on your face and a beep of your horn!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Irwin Fletcher (Phil)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jen,/ROne thing I like most about you is your gift of loyalty.  You have a genuine concern and kindness towards others.  You are always willing to give of yourself to help another without hesitation.  I feel truly blessed to have you as a close friend!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carolann Bertolotti ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jennifer - You are such a thoughtful person - always looking to make everything from a huge fundraising event to a simple, last minute drop-in lunch special ! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsay ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have a wonderful sense of playfulness - just think back to the birthday celebration at Stone Harbor that ended in a whip cream and cake food fight on the porch! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You were my wish!  After 2 brothers there was nothing more I wanted than a little sister ! So thankful to have you in my life !]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your big sis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jennifer- You are a compassionate, creative, intelligent, loving, fun, stylish, giving person and I am so proud of the woman you have become! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Lindsay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love the way you bring people together whether it is a family get together or  a school fundraiser ! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Mom,/RThis is another forced letter. I am having fun. I had 5 cookies and 10 cups of juice at the dance. /R/RReally I love that you help me all the time. I love that you sent me to Woodlynde and Agawam. I really love you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Declan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My mom is very caring and compassionate and always knows what to say, and for that, I'm grateful. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Cooper]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jennifer is a wonderful sister in law. She has been a great /RSupporter of Gordon and Sarah in Philadelphia.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob Carroll]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My Mom is very loving, loyal, courageous and brave. She always tries to make the good out of a bad situation, and always makes you feel loved. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Grace]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember when...You and Uncle B took my brothers and I to  take your child to work day at Chubb. You made the city so exciting to us, thank you for helping me find my home in Philadelphia! I dont know where I would be without you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah Carroll]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pink]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>