<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2584-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/31/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Gail Yosowitz]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[1131 Rexford Drive ]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Los Angeles ]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[CA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[90035]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 30th Birthday Cheryl ]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Cheryl Yosowitz]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love, Gail ]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have shared many special moments with Cher Bear and lover free spirit, her thoughtfulness, her ability to make everyone smile :) Happy birthday beautiful <3]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Denelle & Ryan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Happy 30th Birthday beautiful girl!  What a talented and beautiful young woman you have become.  We love you so much!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The McCausland's]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I think about our niece Cheryl, two things jump out. First, her nickname, "Special" or "Spech", which is perfectly fitting! Second, I always picture Cheryl sitting crossed legged, intently focused, and with great dexterity dressing her Barbi"s at lightening speed!/R"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Cookie, Uncle Bobby & cousins]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[HAPPY 30th CHERYL!!! The moment we met goes back...way back. I will never forget our classic picture at USA Pep & Cheer competition  sitting back to back 'as strangers' and now 10 yrs. later you are on of my best friends!Your energy and love for life is contagious. lv u]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amanda (Guzzy)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The most memorable moment, and there have been many, would be the Sunday morning while eating breakfast before Dena and Cheryl went to Hebrew School, when Cheryl, Dena and I composed THE Jewish Rap Song, the melody for Cheryl's RAP at Dena & David's Rehearsal Dinner.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alan Big Poppa Zell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Just a sample of my favorite Cheri moments: matching outfits, meeting at "the farm", CCP, shiny Airwalks & lip smackers, Troop Beverly Hills, our voices, countless "silent" laughs, my entire childhood, standing by my side at my wedding, my sister & best friend for life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All my love, Alli Hochberg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cheryl's nickname "Spesh" perfectly characterizes my beautiful niece.  She was “Spesh” from the moment she was born and is still “Spesh” today. As Cheryl approaches a new decade I send her all my love and my warmest good wishes for a lifetime filled with everything good]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Lisa ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Spesh always had a warm heart filled with love and affection.  When she was 2 years old she loved her older cousin, Jordan.  She would chase him around the house and when she caught him she would wrap her little arms around his legs and kiss him!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Lisa ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my very vivid memories of Cheryl is when she was 4 years old and came to Houston to celebrate her cousin Zac’s Bar Mitzvah.  She was dressed like a little princess and she stole the show as she danced the night away.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Lisa ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cheryl is gorgeous, friendly, sweet, intelligent, honest, kind, charming, hilarious, witty and ambitious...always has been and always will be...she makes everyone around her smile and want to become her best friend.../RHappy, Healthy Birthday & many many more]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I am her very proud 'Uncle John']]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cher-Bear, /RHappiest of birthdays to you! I am so grateful to call you my friend. Your enthusiasm for life and your amazing generosity makes an incredible friend and person. You make me laugh and are always there for me. Thank you for being YOU! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Roo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[How we shall never forget the infamous "hot-tub time machine" moments - Where it all began... ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JZ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite thing about Aunt Cheryl is her hair. Happy birthday! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shane Gordon ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like painting with Aunt Cheryl over thanksgiving.  I love her]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jesse Gordon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My earliest memories of Cheryl was when she was just turning 1 year old.  Morris, Jack and I went to visit the Yosowitz's family in /RArizona.  Cheryl was in her bouncy jumper, she did not sit still for a second. The cutest and baby ever!She still has that adorable smile]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Pam and family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[30 years ago... It seems like it was just a moment ago. But what a great moment it was. My beautiful Cheryl was born and my family was complete. Time has passed and your beauty just keeps getting better both inside and out.I'm honored to be your father. Love alwaysDad]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lee S Yosowitz, MD ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cher, I truly believe you were put on this earth to make people smile and feel special.  I will NEVER forget my surprise shower. Thank you for always making me feel like family. I know that you are a friend for life, and I feel very lucky for that. Happy 30th! Welcome:)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Arielle (Shmer)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cheryl,/RYou have always been one of the most beautiful people I have ever known inside and out. There have been so many little moments that you have offered the most inspiring advice, especially when I was feeling down on myself. You are an incredible friend, love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Renee XOXO]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[May favorite thing about you is your love of life, happiness you exude to all those around you and your infectious laugh.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Renee XOXO]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When you look up the word SPECIAL in the dictionary the definition is: remarkable, exceptional, outstanding and unique.  That is exactly what she was to us.  Her nickname was SPESH. She continues to be special in all of these ways. Happy Birthday Cheryl. We love you!!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[MOM- Janet]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your singing/RYour dancing/RYour hair/RYour jokes/RYour laugh/RYour wit/RI love it all!/R/RHappy 30th birthday Cher! Xoxox]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shai Shai]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cheryl is someone I hold very dear to my heart. The way she goes through life is inspiring and I find myself emulating so many of her qualities... her thoughtfulness is unparalleled, she's hilarious, has a huge heart, and a big bubbly personality that lights up a room.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jackie Griffin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cheryl has one of the best laughs I have ever heard! It is so infectious and I cannot help but smile while I'm around her! Her positivity is contagious and I am lucky to have a friend like her in my life. Love you Cher! Happy 30th! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Xo Kendra ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your smile, jawline, head tilt- dang you are photogenic! How I'd get so lucky to be your picture twin? And who knew stalking you in Rhetoric & Writing class would turn in to you being my fave chiller?! I love you little cub bear. xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[LJ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Within only one year we already have too many memories to count! From DubSmash day, to Park City shopping/ziplining, to tag-teaming meetings, to venting about almost everything (cough, Travis/Laura), and most of all supporting each other through just about everything!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michelle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm so proud of the woman you have become. Thanks for being such a wonderful sister & friend. You are an inspiration to me & so wise beyond your years! I can't wait to see what the next 30 years have in store for you! I love you & I hope you have a very happy bday! xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that when Jesse & Shane refer to our guest room, they call it "Aunt Gail & Aunt Cheryl's Room" even when you aren't in town because they love it when you come to visit! Thank you for being such a great Aunt & making memories with us! I promise to do the same ;)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'll always remember our sisters trip to Santa Barbara and how hard it was to find that green apple. Happy  30th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/RI love our talks and our laughs. You are one of the most loving and genuine people I know, feel so blessed to  have you in my life.  /R/RHappy Birthday Cheryl /RMuch health & happiness, always! /R/R/R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Natalie Cadoch :)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your laugh is infectious and always gets me laughing. I love when it's just the two of us and we can laugh about nothing for hours.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsey ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The name Cheryl was most popular in the 1940's, which to me makes perfect sense, you are an old soul.  The moment I met you I liked you; you felt familiar, comforting, honest and sincere.  Now back to that old soul, how about we pour a Manhattan and play an old record.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Caleb Nelson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[According to Urban Dictionary Cheryl's have trusting blue eyes and large bussoms. Whether or not that is entirely accurate I cannot say, but what I do know is you have a very beautiful heart, the kindest smile, and gosh darned the best hair since Farrah Fawcett.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Caleb Nelson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always enjoy my spontaneous moments with Cheryl. Her perspective & spirt are fresh, insightful and alive. One time that comes in mind is singing and practicing handstands in my living room while jamming out to our shared musical obsessions. Cheryl you are one of kind!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Justine ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cheryl I love our adventures together. There is never a plan, but we somehow always end up doing something fun, spontaneous and creative. /R/ROne of the many things that I admire about you is that you always remember others and things that are special to them. Love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Monica Bern]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Friends for 10+ years, reconnecting at Adele, and forever crying over wedding videos. I love your heart, soul, and spirit. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To Aunt Cheryl, /R/RYou have earned my love. And you are a lucky one.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Kingston]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are always the first one we call when we discover a good Asian restaurant. /RLove, the Wu's]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[aka the Zhangs]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cher bear, there are so many wonderful things I value about our friendship, but one of the most unique things about our relationship is your strange ability to remember everyone I've ever gone on a date with, even when I can't. You take "great listener" to a new level! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kayla]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The fact that you're one of the only people I would have as a house guest says it all! You're a beautiful person inside and out, which is why so many people call you their best friend. I miss u every day and love u with all my heart. Happiest of birthdays, u deserve it!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Rosenblum]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[P.S. You don't look a day over 23 ;) ;) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Rosenblum]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[How can I choose just one? Every memory I have with u is my favorite. Your ability to always be positive & optimistic is truly inspirational. Your constant support & wisdom have made me a better person. You are the light that people gather around for warmth & happiness]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Rosenblum ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In an era when first impressions are critical, Cheryl eclipses everyone.  To meet Cheryl is to instantly love, trust and respect her.  Knowing her just validates your first impressions.  She has every reason for her confidence and is a true inspiration.  Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JD]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cheryl/R(Noun)/RMy Best Friend, My Sister From Another Mister/R/RSynonyms- Cher, Yosogood, Shesh, Mary or Rhoda (depending on the occasion), Yos, CY, CherBear, Shesheyl, Sheshe ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dena/De/Denzel/DeDe/DeanBean]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's difficult 2 put in words how spesh our little Shesh is.  UR hands down the most creative, clever, empathetic person Ive ever met. Your ability 2 connect is unrivaled, U make people feel important. For these reasons, & countless more, Im so glad U "still know me"!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dena XOXOXOXOX]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cheers to 30 years of perfect ponytails, side salads w/ ranch dressing, snackpaks eaten with that trademark finger grip, to talking/texting at least 30 times/day, to RENT, to CLUELESS, I Love U to infinity & beyond, to a lifetime of amazing memories together!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dena XOXOXOX]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cheryl's beauty and energy captivates everyone she meets, but my favorite quality of Cheryl's is her disdain for talking behind peoples' backs. If she has something to say, she will say it to your face, and she will defend anyone who isn't present to defend themself. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[LOVE YOU CHER! Love, Boobin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cheryl, after about 18 years together I have lots of great memories but one that always makes me smile was the Ridin' Solo dance party. Your dance moves were and are so good.  And you're never afraid to be a total goof, which is a quality I really love about you. Xoxo  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Zoë Maas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Would it be the time I cried to you to be my little sis on pref night? Or when my Dad saw you naked? Would it be all those times we rocked out to Kelly C? Or our 2 months in Europe, or break-ups & break-ins? You can't decide on one moment with your very best friend. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I love you so much! <3, Meesh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have such a deep soul. Your appreciation for passion and profound longing for meaning and clarity in every aspect of your life is so beautiful. It's a huge part of what makes you so unique.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When we were in high school I was helping you set up for a stugo event. We found a bag of food from Jack in the Box and (of course) we ate it (without hesitation). Turns out it belonged to Trevor Shoush and he was less than pleased with us. Oops!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Taking pictures. We must have thousands together. Our standard pose at every dance, our long awaited "teeth brushing picture," and our joint senior portraits, just to name a few.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Along with the million memories that I could  describe that we have shared there are also memories that I wouldn't want to share with anyone but you because I hold them so close to my heart and they are only ours. Happy 30th to my best friend in the world. I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Camp. Beanies and Weenies. Getting pebbled. Fun life boards and scrapbooking. Everybody loves LC LC. Mexico trips. San Diego trips. Can I have a bite? The Lindsey and Cheryl show. Dance twins. Cafe au Clay (+De!). Cody and Jon. Our language. Horrific hangovers. Love.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The moment I met you outside of Sigma Pi, I remember thinking you were the absolute cutest and bubbliest #girlcrush. I knew you had to become my theta sister, voice twin and friend! Your drive, passion and heart continue to inspire me and I am blessed you are my friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lots of Love,  Jessica Barbier]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From the moment I met you outside of Sigma Pi, I thought you were the absolute cutest and bubbliest (#girlcrush). I knew you had to be my theta sister, friend and voice twin. Your drive, passion and heart inspire me daily and I am blessed to call you my friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you lots, Jessica Barbier]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You exemplify what a true friend is, Cher. No matter how much time elapses between getting together, we always seem to pick right back up & it's like we never skipped a beat. You're always there to lend a listening ear and to give the best advise. So thankful for you xo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chloe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have been able to share so many memorable moments with you it is really hard to pin down one favorite.  So I am just going to tell you that I am proud of you and look up to you.  Your Passion for life and love and family is inspirational.  I love you.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Adam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Never more than this immediate time in your life have I been more proud of you and seen such an amazing strength of character.  Like me, you are deep and not afraid to really go for what you want in life braving the unknown. You are such a courageous woman. I love]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[May you always love deeply, showcase your scrap booking skills, sing like you're performing on American Idol and stay away from the toilets in Mexico! Love you forever and always Cher-Bear! Xx]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Britters]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are too many moments to sum up in 270 characters so I will give a summation of my thoughts.  Pod is always, unapologetically herself, which makes every moment memorable.  She lights up every room, cares about every person she comes in contact with and just loves.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When Cheryl was 6 years old her Dad starting calling us "twins"!  What a compliment for me to look like Cheryl!  But, what I most appreciated, was the comparison to her inner beauty - her compassion & creativity, her exuberance and outlook, her engaging personality!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Lisa ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love all of my moments with Cher! Her energy and attitude are always so positive, and I just love being around it. She can make any situation fun. She truly is a special, beautiful soul!! Can't wait to see what 30 has in store for you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Kat]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To My Babygirl- Cheryl- on her 30th Birthday!  Wishing you the happiest birthday ever.  I love you dearly and forever.  So proud of you. Love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[30 years ago Mom and Dad gave the greatest gift I will ever receive... YOU! You are my sister, my real life doll, my weekend warrior, travel companion, therapist, chef, roommate, interior designer, crafting queen, but most of all you are MY best friend.  I am so proud ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gail ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Of the woman you have become.  I can only aspire to have the strength and courage that is innate in you. You bring joy and love to everyone you meet and brighten up a room just by walking into it.  Cheryl, never stop being you, because I love you just the way you are! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday xoxo, Gail ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cheers to the start of a new chapter.  May the the your next 30 years be even better than your last. We all love you so much and are so proud to call you our little sister! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer, Brian,  and Gail ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Those who don't believe in magic will never find it"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ronald Dahl ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Don't think it complicates things. Just feel, and if it feels like home, then follow its path]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[R. M Drake]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Being different is one of the most beautiful things on earth.. embrace your "YOU" NESS]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Don't ever let anyone dull your sparkle]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Life is short, break the rules, forgive quickly, kiss slowly, love truly, laugh uncontrollably, and never regret anything that made you smile. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xo ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In the end, only three things matter: how much you loved, how gently you lived, and how gracefully you let go of things not meant for you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Buddha]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Now and then it's good to pause in your pursuit of happiness and just be happy!:) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Guillaume Apollinaire]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I don't know where I am going from here but I promise it won't be boring! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Bowie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>