<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2591-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[7/31/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Jordana Popovich]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[100 Overhill Rd]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Bala Cynwyd]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19004]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sand]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[We love you because...]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Michele]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[The Rosen Family 2015]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you let me play with your backgammon pieces.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sydney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you give me cookies. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sydney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because of your tireless determination and effort to keep our family close. Spending Thanksgiving and the family trip together each year has enabled us to remain close despite our geographical distance from one another!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jordana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you can be dressed in Chanel and drinking a Heineken beer (out of a glass, of course)!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jordana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you have taught me, by example, how to be a person that I am proud to be and live a life that is dictated by strong values, honesty, and an appreciation of all things big and small. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jordana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because of your deep love and devotion to my father. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stewart]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because your devotion to family has rubbed off on me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andres]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because I like to tell people that I have a French grandmother ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andres]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because we share some of my earliest, fondest memories./R/RShepard's pie at your house for Thanksgiving... mmm]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andres]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because I like to chase frogs with Sydney.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stella]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because I like to play by your duck pond and pet your little "beebee" (baby) dog.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stella]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because /Ryou love me!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stella]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you bring my whole family together.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lucas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you're investing in me and my future educational endeavors.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lucas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you laugh and giggle at my sweet baby mannerisms and little chubby legs. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lucas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you have always made me feel beautiful.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elizabeth]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you and Grandad have always made sure to keep the family together. Whether it be at holidays or on magnificent trips we have all maintained a beautiful closeness with each other. Without you our Rosen bond would certainly not be as strong.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elizabeth]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you have always made me feel welcomed as part of the family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mitch]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you've been my lifelong role model as the epitome of grace and composure.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rebecca]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you for your voice and the sing-song way you greet me and say my name. Although I see you infrequently, your voice is always clear in my memory.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rebecca]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because being in awe of you, you've always inspired me to want to do my best in order to impress you. Your praise has always meant the very most to me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rebecca]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you are a significant part of what makes our family so close. Between the holidays, family trips or brunch at your house in Philly, you're the foundation for so much of the happiness and love this family gets to experience together./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because of how supportive you are with all of us. For the few times a year most of us get to see you, you're always making an active effort to find out what's going on in our lives and when appropriate, offering whatever support possible. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because of the kindness, interest and love you've shown Cali from the very first time you both met. I remember how nervous she was to meet you, wearing a dress she thought you might like and learning some French to try to impress you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you for our shared passion for all things french pastry. I will some day conqueror the croquembouche for you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cali]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you for welcoming me into your family with arms wide open. And even though we do not see each other that often, you always show me love.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cali]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because I appreciate everything you do for the family. You give me great inspiration for my future grandchildren. Thank you for being someone that I can look up to.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cali]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because the breakfasts on the family trip are delicious.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ira]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you are my standard of ‘class’.   I know not to stop at a New Jersey Rest Stop because you wouldn’t.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ira]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you are the only one in the family older than I am.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ira]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you really are an amazing person.  Tough yet warm, stunning yet humble,  smart yet gracious, and for the best reason of all, you make us a family and help keep us as 1.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cindy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you loved Dad so much, and completed and honored him like no one else.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cindy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because from the tips of your toes to the tweak of your nose, /RFrom the years you have lived to the gifts that you give,/ROur family is blessed though some of us jest/RFor the class that you bring of which we should sing.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cindy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You lift by your being, with grace we are seeing/R/RHow fine one can be, in your life, we do see.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cindy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because I so enjoy hearing about your earlier adventures, such as mountain climbing or living in Africa. You transport us to different times and places. Please keep telling us more!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Roberto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that as you & I are foreigners, I enjoy and appreciate our chatting about international issues, especially from France and Europe.  I am not only awed by your culture, wisdom, and social awareness but, most importantly, by your sensibility and kindness to others.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Roberto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you for your support of Robin and me over the years, and you have always shared your thoughts and advice on how to live a meaningful life. Thank you for teaching us, and by example, what is most important: Love and family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Roberto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because of your intelligence, charm, positive attitude, sense of humor, high energy level and generosity. And of course your sense of style.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stewart]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you for allowing me not to be that kid who never leaves the state. A main part of my life was going to Atlantic City every summer. Without those vacations, I wouldn't know how to swim today, and more importantly, how to build a chair-fort in a cabana.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ben]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have always loved how kind and caring you have been to others. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Haskell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you are an inspiration on how to live a full life with aplomb.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Beth]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you survived being brought into the Rosen family and ended up being ts matriarch. Quite an accomplishment!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Beth]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because I cannot say it enough: The family vacations have meant the world to Monica and Fernando, allowing them to experience what being part of a family is and what it means. Thank you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Beth]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because whenever I think of Grandma, I always think of her as a kind, caring and very wise with decisions.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Fernando]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you are the best grandmother I've had in 16 years seems crazy but true.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Fernando]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because having to spend time with each other is one of the most astonishing things to do. These times to be a family allow us to get together and to know each other and progressively become a part of the family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Fernando]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love you because of your commitment to being supportive and always believing in us as we pursue our unique ambitions and endeavors.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Derek & Kristen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love you because you continue being the "glue" that keeps the family together. The value you place on family will be forever remembered, and serves as a example for us to all  strive for.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Derek, Kristen & Peter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you for always being so organized and clean - it was always a much welcome break from the mess I grew up with at home (but don't tell my Mom I said that!)!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Derek]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because I believe that you embody the spirit of Granddad. You provide a source of inspiration for me as I strive to achieve my fullest potential, and to make the most of the opportunities I have been afforded. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Derek]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love you because you are central to defining the Rosen family identity, and your presence alone makes any occasion feel more special.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Derek, Kristen & Peter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you're the best Great Grandma anyone could ask you for, and as my favorite book says, "I love you more than mice love cheese"!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love you because your poise, generosity, and grace provide an example for us all to aspire to.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Derek, Kristen & Peter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because "the love of a grandmother is life's greatest blessing" - the role that you have played in my life is irreplaceable. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Derek]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love you for so graciously welcoming Kristen into the Rosen family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Derek & Kristen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you are the glue that holds the Rosen family together.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matthew and Jennifer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because some of my favorite and most important memories are of family holidays hosted at your house]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matthew and Jennifer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because of the unconditional love and support you have always shown me, and your acceptance of Jennifer into our family]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matthew and Jennifer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because/R"We are Rosen Gang"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matthew]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because both you and GrandDad helped shape me into the man I have become, and the father I will one day be]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matthew]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you are always the most fabulous person in the room!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because there's not a time we're together we don't laugh as if it's our last chance. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stevan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because having to spend time with each other is one of the most astonishing things to do. These times to be a family allow us to get together and to know each other and progressively become a part of the family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Fernando]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you for the way you and Jordana look at each other when you don't agree. And then the look she gives me, when you and I agree. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stevan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you never stop giving. Your time, your love, and your commitment to the family are unwavering, and we are all better for being a small reflection of you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stevan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because my love and gratitude for you run deeper than an ocean.  You are my role model and have shown me what it is to truly love life and live each day with boundless enthusiasm and passion. I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you for your role in some of my favorite memories ~ My wedding at your house, you & Dad with the kids when they were babies, Thanksgivings, AC, family trips, “talking” politics, playing cards, dinners together, watching you laugh when you are really moved.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because of how much love you inspire in all of us. One of the best things my father ever did was bring you into our lives.  I still thank him for that gift. Your mark on us is much greater than you know. Thank you, gracias, merci! Je t’aime beaucoup!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you make me smile.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Monica]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you have a joie de vivre that is contagious & inspiring! It's always fun to be with you - even when you're sick, you find something to smile and laugh about! It is a gift to us that you bring yourself so fully to each moment and with such exuberance.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sharon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you keep the family together.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Monica]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you always keep your spirits high and have a good sense of humor.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeremy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because of the effort you put into our family keeps the Rosen Gang strong.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amanda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you're such a positive energy, always spreading a smile or a laugh to those around you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amanda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you inspire me to grab life by the horns!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amanda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you are kind, loving and inspiring. You welcomed Fern and I into the family with open arms. Fern and I feel as if we were always part of the family. Thank you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Monica]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because I've benefitted from your genuine interest and concern in the affairs and matters of my life. You speak to me, give advice, and sometimes question my direction. You challenge me to become a better me. Thank you for being such a great grandmother!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Micah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because always you welcome each of us with enthusiasm & a genuine interest in whatever it is that lures us. Your caring support allows us to explore as we are uniquely drawn, & your questions prompt us to dig ever more deeply. You have an open mind and heart!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sharon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you for your and Dad's devotion to strengthening our family bonds. Year in and out, you bring together our expanding family for gourmet Thanksgiving extravagances, brunches, luncheons & dinners,& gorgeous vacations! We've so many memories!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sharon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because as I grow up and venture on my own path, I've been fortunate to be a part of our family vacations, where I've developed close relationships with my cousins, who've become my support network. Thank you for being the keeper of the Rosen family!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Micah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you for the joy you brought to my grandfather. I'll always remember the day I was with you & Granddad eating Hershey's kisses, & I asked if you loved Granddad. You laughed & said you did, & then I asked Granddad if he loved you, & he too laughed & said he did. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Micah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>