<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2596-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/3/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Linell Smith]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[2444 Eutaw Place]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Baltimore]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[MD]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[21217]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 60th Birthday, Mary]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Mary John Miller]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Assoc. of Mary J. Miller Admirers]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mary has taught me the simple value of being intellectually curious, straightforward and really good at a few things. She has a great analytical mind, and when combined with her knowledge of the financial markets, she is endlessly interesting. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Warnock]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I congratulate your many great works, but I feel obligated to remind you that the True Tragedy of our Time is the absence of a complete Weather Girls clothing line. And yes, I am available to consult. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Miranda Hall]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough." May this decade be filled with new adventures, new lessons, new memories and old friends. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Caitlin Brown Timson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have so much to give to the people of Baltimore at a very crucial time.  Please consider being part of efforts to move the City forward with healing and progress.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carla Hayden]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I hope you had a well-deserved rest after all the hard work you did for our country. You have the ability to make a difference in many different fields.  Take your time deciding what to do and be sure to leave a good cushion so that you can travel and do other things. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[George Roche]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[...Fast forward this scene to today./Our Mary is 60 – Hooray!/But there’s no rest, ole chap,/We’ve a leadership gap,/Let’s add “Mayor” to her long resumé...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat Dayton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mary, may you always go to others in peace and harmony.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Watters]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It has meant the world to share our 6-month-apart birthdays, 6-month-apart birthdays of our best-friend sons, and the companionship of the Miller clan over the last 28 years.  I will never forget your support of my Mom and me. Cheers to many more years of friendship.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bonnie Legro]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am a much better person because of Mary John Miller, who has remained that wonderful lady I met over 30 years ago. Her focus on the big picture down to the footnotes has not been matched. I am honored to be considered a friend, especially after I broke her nose.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vernon Reid]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You gave me one of the best pieces of advice ever: Underwear of any kind should always be completely covered. When asked to consider your next campaign, I immediately thought of ridding the world of exposed bra straps. I’m sure many would thank you for it!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aoibhinn Nyhan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Theater director Andre Gregory once wrote, "There is no such thing as talent, only lack of talent.  The rest is work." Your talents are formidable, and wherever your work takes you next, it will surely continue to be a paradigm of tenacity, ethics and excellence.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom Hall]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[With the Bolton Hill gang, not only did I gain a group of siblings, but a group of "second" mothers and fathers. Whenever I think of you, Mary, I think of the kindness and love you continually give to your Bolton Hill children. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrea Smillie Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mary has been the “glue” that has kept us all together. Many of her efforts center around food and celebrations: Labor Day gatherings, Christmas dinners, “girls’ weekends.”   But she also creates memories, including that famous water ballet, "It’s Raining Men.” "]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda Rose]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[First comes generosity: When Mary is given a gift, she seems to always share it with others (like the wonderful girls' slumber party at the Mandarin Oriental.) Second, there’s humility: Mary essentially ran the Treasury Dept., yet remained as sweet and humble as ever. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bonnie Copeland]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When it comes to organizing acts of kindness, you’re the champ. I will never forget the Marine Corps cheering section.  You routinely find a way to make difficult times more manageable, sad times more bearable, and happy times more joyous. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linell Smith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[During the past two years, you always found a way to say something inspiring and tangible that has made me a better teacher and member of the Baltimore community. It’s hard to give advice to a champion, but I would say JUST KEEP BEING YOU! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Travis Rodgers]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A person of great intellect and great heart, you are energized by leadership roles with meaningful impact, and you build engaged and committed teams. You have now begun a third career in organizational governance. I wonder what your fourth and fifth will be. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Smillie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Timothy Geithner said your “steady hand helped Treasury navigate critical domestic finance issues, earning deep respect from colleagues.”  You have also earned  utmost respect and gratitude from friends and family with your kindness and friendship. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[James Todaro]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You can create confidence and calm in what are often turbulent situations.  You possess that unique composite of intelligence, thoughtful judgment, common sense and the highest level of ethics. Those who work for you could not have had a better mentor or leader. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Timson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are sixty, looking like fifty/Running like half of that!/Now comes Act Two, be canny and careful/ Mary, you’re up at bat!...No one is as prepared as you/To face this lion’s den./Clever and quick and keen are you/to tackle all you can….]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Patrice Berchtenbreiter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It was a great idea to use "positive reinforcement" to encourage James and me to get involved with reading. One summer, with donuts and the arcade as incentives, we blew through 31 “great illustrated classics.” Thanks, Mary for sparking my interest in literary fiction. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Trevor Timson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite things is your look of extreme disapproval. The most public example of The Look  occurred  when you debated Larry Summers. He immediately queried, “Whadda I say?”  Geithner once asked if you could stand up to Larry. Well, you answered that question. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Miller]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our daughter is named Mary because it reflects someone whose intellect and steadiness are legendary  and who always strives to do good.  Mary Miller is the nicest person I have ever met. I hope you will now find the freedom to explore and the time to restore. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vicky Collins]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jackie and I agree that you would make a great advisor to leaders in both the public and private sectors.  Regardless of what you decide,  just keep being authentically you.   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Freeman and Jackie Hrabowski]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have admired and laughed with you for over 30 years. From the time we were both pregnant to proudly sharing news of our sons' marriages, we never miss a beat when we're together.  Welcome to the 60s! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cindy Conklin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I’ve been very proud and lucky to work for you, and with you, for all these years.  I wish that you can find as much enjoyment in relaxation as you’ve found in the productivity, generosity and kindness that you’ve shown others. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marcie Shriver]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am so proud of all the amazing things you have accomplished, and hope that you will return to full-time employment soon in order to accomplish more of them. I recommend you angle to succeed SRB, Larry Hogan, or Christine Lagarde.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ Tom Miller]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From having me “help” Marcie, to helping me as I try to transition into a new career, you have been instrumental in my personal growth. What would success look like when I’m your age? Being successful enough to be to someone what you have been to me.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Deanna Berchtenbreiter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You’ve managed to make it through the financial crisis at TRPA, the post-financial crisis at Treasury, and one of the more dysfunctional Congressional eras. You could write a book. You’ve set the example for staying cool under pressure and being well prepared! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Art Varnado]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Rather than take up a new sport, you become a political football coach. I can see you on C-Span, waving a clipboard and shouting into a headset as the American political system slouches towards destruction. Alternatively, you can become Bernie Sanders' financial adviser]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[James Miller]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mary understands business and finance on a global scale and generously shares that knowledge in a needy, local community she loves. For Mary, it is never about what but always about why – and always about others]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Doreen Bolger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It’s been said that our truest passions emerge in childhood only to be squelched by real life pressures. Those activities you loved long ago will still bring you joy. So if Nancy Drew mysteries appear on your coffee table, we'll understand! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda Moxley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Here are some Nyhan household suggestions for next steps. While some are of necessity exclusive, (#1 & #2) other combinations not necessarily so. Mary is more than qualified to undertake any of the following. For more, see Dan Nyhan II. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dan Nyhan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[1. Mayoress of Baltimore. She ticks many of the boxes. (UI, Finance, Government, etc. ) 2. Ambassador to Ireland. 3. Help next generation with short attention span. Create app addressing the basics of financial planning for 20-35 ages. For more, see Dan Nyhan III. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dan Nyhan II]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[4. Envision a path to heaven without visiting God's waiting room. (nursing home) 5.  In the event that The Donald doesn't blow up, an advisory role. He respects really bright people, including ladies, and advisor would promote inter-ideological rapprochement]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dan Nyhan III]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I find it helpful to think "What would Mary do/say/wear?" The answer always steers me in a good direction.  It’s safe to assume that Mary’s future will involve Bermuda, wine, and friends – and any combination will be well deserved. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessalyn Timson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In worlds where success is often given to the loudest and meanest, Mary remains one of the most genuine, classy, and kind people I know. I hope you continue to share your wisdom in the way you have with me. There’s an eager audience waiting to learn.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Adam Smillie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Forget the Greek debt crisis and which banks are too big to fail. Go hike the Camino Royale or fly to L.A. Take every chance to have lunch and dinner with your friends. One joy of this decade is that our friends know and care for us just as we are.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Neal Friedlander]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dedication to the people who work for her is one reason Mary has been so successful. Once as we drove back to Baltimore from a trip, Mary asked to be let out at an event at the ballpark to show the flag for senior management. Such a good role model!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy O'Neil]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whenever we think of you, we think of determination, can-do, mentorship and warmth. That’s why we know you will be successful as a downhill, all terrain mountain biking competitor and coach – trading a cushy seat on the board for a hard one on a bike.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nadine and Oliver Schein ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You helped make Baltimore feel like home for a young man from Lusaka, Zambia, by way of Columbia, MO. Because of you, the transition to classroom leadership was one hallmarked by the reminder of the importance of family. Thank you for allowing me to be a part of yours. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chitamawe Mulwanda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>