<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2600-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/4/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Lynn Dikolli]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[4101 Taylor Hall Place]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Chapel Hill]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[NC]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[27517]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_60]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[ Thoughts to inspire you....]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Samantha Dikolli]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[From people who love you]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Have fun and don't be afraid to make new friends! I know you'll miss me more than I'll miss you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Thomas ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Samantha Cleo, /R/RAlways have something /Rto look forward to. /R/RFor me, it's the next time /RI see you.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All my love, Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Samantha, /R/RMy heart bursts with pride when I think of how you have always tried your best in all of your amazing accomplishments. /R/RIt's all in the try. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All my love, Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Even though miles a part, I have still watched you grow into a beautiful young women./R/RMy tip in life is to always choose your attitude. Being nice, understanding and positive will get you far. Smile and love./R/RLike my dad told me, work hard and the rewards will come.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your loving cousin Candice x]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sometimes life might not always be the party we hoped for./R/RBut while we're here let's dance!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Candice]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Believe in yourself and follow your dreams!  It will be up to you to take action to achieve all that you want. And when in need of support, always know that you can call on family and friends who love you so much.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Mark]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Listen to your parents! Study hard and Please don't forget us when your famous! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Xha Xhi, Teta and Dylan xox]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When confronted with an important decision, it may be wise to ask, "what would uncle Dave do?".  Then do the opposite./RLove ya Sam,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Dave]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["The meaning of life is to find your gift -- the purpose of life is to give it away."/R /RMay your journey at UNC help you find your gift, Samantha.  Savor every experience, embrace every challenge, always be true to yourself.  We are so proud of you./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Mom, Dad & Thomas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember to take a nap now & then!  A good nap can fix most anything.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Duke]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hard work is very important, but make sure to set aside time to relax, pray, and hang out with friends. :) Stay close to Jesus and all the rest will work out fine! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your cousin Kate]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Follow your passion as you pursue your career. Let your passion guide you and the money will follow. It doesn't work the other way around.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, the Varelas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Buy lots of underwear....you won't need to do laundry as often!/RAlso, get involved.  If you're interested in doing something, go for it! Even if no one else you know is participating, you'll meet lots of new people :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michelle Gleason]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Party hard.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Grads often hear "follow your dreams" or "set your sights high."  Yes, consider tomorrow, but not at the expense of today. Be present and open to what today brings. Welcome what comes to you each day: every person, thought, situation, condition and feeling. Be here now.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Lea McAnally]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Starting college is like beginning an exciting new chapter in the book of your life.  What a wonderful opportunity to discover all that you can be, when you push yourself beyond your usual comfort zone.  Have fun exploring!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much love, Aunt Laura]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations, Samantha, and always/Rremember Grandma loves you and prays for you every day./R                     Love, Grandma]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Irene Serre]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Be proud of all your accomplishments!/RI am so proud of you and what you do.Be yourself and count the blessings you have received this far. Love, Gandma]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Irene Serre]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To our sweet Samantha, /Ryou're a wonderful, kind, brilliant person./RWe are so proud to have been part of your life since kindergarden./R/RMy only advice to you is :/RBe True To Yourself/RYou're perfect just the way you are!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian, Susan, Blake, and Davis ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Samantha congratulations....you rock at everything you do and we are so proud of you.  Keep in touch...often. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ML and V]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hope you enjoy college.  It will be a chance to meet new people and do new things.  Do it all :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ML and V]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hanging in Italy with your Mom...she is telling us all the great things you have been doing and are planning to do.  She is so proud of you....so in turn are we.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ML and V]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[1 Peter 5:7 - Give all your worries and cares to God, for he cares about you. /R/R/RAfter you sail through your undergrad, come to Toronto for your master's!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stephen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Set yourself a goal for each semester, unrelated to school. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt Gleason]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Some form of day planner / calendar system is critical for managing your time and priorities (deadlines, diet, sleep, exercise).  There will always be people who have spare time and want you to party. Go out and have fun, but learn when to say "No, I have to study!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Tony and Aunt Stephanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Keep your faith!  There will be many people telling you that science is real and God is not.  They are not smarter than God; they are wrong!  God created science and everything in the natural world.  He loves you and so do we!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Tony and Aunt Stephanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the sweetest, most giving person I know, Samantha.  Don't ever change your kind,/R positive outlook on the world.  It's one of the attributes that makes you special and makes people want to be around you.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Samantha, /RDon't forget to come and visit us in Australia. You always have a place to stay and a special place in our hearts. /RLots of love,/RXha Xhi Ossie, Teta Diora, Sophia, and Claudia]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Perth, Australia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Samantha,/RHard to believe the time has come for you to spread your wings and fly.  We wish you much success and are certain that you will fulfill your dreams.  You have all the knowledge, grace and power to do so.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Andrew and Billy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Don't forget to balance work and play as you move into the next phase of your life and continue to grow into the beautiful person that Michele, Billy and myself love so much and are so proud of.  /RMichele will always be an angel watching over you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Andrew]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Samantha,/RShare your sparkle wherever you are!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All my love, Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Follow your passion, stay true to yourself -- never follow someone else's path unless you're in the woods and lost and you see a path; then by all means you should follow that path. -:)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellen Degeneres]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We do not need magic to change the world, we carry all the power we need inside ourselves already: we have the power the imagine better.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[J.K. Rowling]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations!/RYou're off to Great Places, you're off and away!  You have brains in your head, you have feet in your shoes.  You can steer yourself in any direction you choose.  You're on your own & you know what you know.  You're the girl who will decide where to go.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dr. Seuss]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Explore. /R/RDream. /R/RDiscover.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your biggest fan, Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dedication and the will to never give up!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dikolli (Perth)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Study to learn something new - not just to make a grade!/RMeet as many people as you can!/RGet involved with organizations that focus on things you are passionate about./RPursue opportunities to serve others./RRemember God loves you and will never leave you!/RWe love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The McKiddys]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We've shared a lot of great snuggle time together, Samantha.  I will miss you . /R/RRemember,  play with the people who wag lots and bark very little.  /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[- Duke]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Samantha,/RLife is not about how fast you run, or how high you climb, but how well you bounce.  /RContinue to be dedicated to your craft, resilient to life's challenges and able to roll with the ups & downs.  Those attributes will take you far in life & keep you grounded.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lots & lots & lots of love, Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Don't worry about the world ending today -- it's already tomorrow in Australia.   -:)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[-Your favorite brother, Thomas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Life is not measured by the Breaths we take, but by the Moments that take our Breath away./RMay your life be filled with many such moments.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Mom, Dad and Thomas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Surround yourself with people who will encourage you and who share your passions.  Spend lots of time with these new friends (talking, laughing & hanging out), but don't be afraid to take some time for yourself now and again./R/RAlso: Go to the movies. :)/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrew Zettel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations, Samantha!  /R/RYou are gunna have a blast in college!  It will be a pile of fun, so enjoy every moment!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrew Zettel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Samantha as you enter the next stage of your life. /RExciting times!/REmbrace every opportunity that comes your way and keep being beautiful you always.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much love Miss Janine & Family x]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[University is a long old road. I find it's a lot less daunting to take it one semester at a time. Just focus on getting through this semester. Take you University career one semester at a time. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Zettel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have an awesome support system of friends and family. You can always fall back on us. Don't be afraid to reach out if ever things get tough.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Zettel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best decision I made in University was to seek out a good faith community on campus. Having young adults like me who shared my faith really helped me to persevere in the later years of my undergrad.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Zettel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sleep is the key. Don't sacrifice sleep for an extra couple hours spent on a paper or studying. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Zettel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Live every day like it's your last baseball game!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Luke Zettel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Country music washes away from the soul the dust of everyday life]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Luke Zettel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love learning for the sake of learning. It's not about marks and degrees. It's about learning how to learn, and doing it for the rest of your life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Tony and Aunt Stephanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Do the basic stuff well.  As Grandpa Zettel used to say, "bunts win more games than home runs"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Tony and Aunt Stephanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Samantha! When you go to school next year and you're studying really hard, try not to burn yourself out. I found that 50 min of study to 10 min of break was a good ratio. Also try to take some fun courses even if not related to your program. Enjoy Sam!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate Hundt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>