<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2605-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/4/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[RENEE GOSIK]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[302 ST ANDREWS PL]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[BLUE BELL]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19422]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_200]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Wheels]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Wheels]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Friends and Family]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From the day I set foot on the scene in Philly, you supported me being there.  I'll never forget that.  Thanks for being such a good friend. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leslie Gudel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I miss our date nights!  Our annual trip to Villa Gallace was something I always looked forward to.  We'll have to have a date night locally and maybe even invite Jamie and Renee :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leslie Gudel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for convincing Vuk I didn't belong in the kitchen!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leslie Gudel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can't believe that 25 years have passed by so quickly! I just couldn't imagine another life. You bring out the best in me. Looking forward to the next 25! Happy Birthday Muf!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dove]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From one proud Nittany Lion to another...there have been some good Phillies announcers but none better than "Wheels"! Insightful, humorous and entertaining. Met "wheel-man" and Renee on the street in State College a few years ago. An honor to know them both as friends!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike and Catherine Cappelletti]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 70th Wheels.  Wish I was there to help you celebrate your birthday.  The number of years you have been around is kind of ironic since your Nittany Lions will probably score 70 on the Illini this Fall.  Keep hittin 'em straight Wheels.  Take care. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andy Dixon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tough to pin down one, but my favorite moments with Wheels surround baseball and golf. First, I was so excited to see and name his dance "the Wheels" for the after the World Series. Secondly, golf at Pebble Beach was one of my highlights!! Great Friend and Grandfather!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom McCarthy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your qualities are too numerous to list on the space allowed. Your friendship means the world to me. I mean... Who puts up with all my idiosyncrasies better than you. Thank you for being who you are.                       ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tim McCarver]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My most memorable time with you (Big Wheels) was spring 2015, when I picked you to be on my Dream Team for the spring training golf tourney!! Going against all odds and taking tremendous heat in the draft room, Ha.  I really wanted to hear you and Bowa rip each other.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ryne Sandberg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nothing impressed me more during my 16 seasons working with you than the way you handled Harry's struggles on-the-air.  Always professional and helpful to him despite your personal differences.  That really said a lot to me about you as a person. Go Buckeyes!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff Halikman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nothing was funnier to me than riding from the airport to the hotel in Montreal on the bus at 1am and Francona yelling back asking you to do an inning of play-by-play so his wife could get the kids to fall asleep.  Good Times!!!   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff Halikman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I had the pleasure of working with Wheels on Phillies telecasts for over 2 decades.  He was a total professional, tireless worker and endless source of knowledge.  He taught me much about the game we both love.  I will always treasure the time we spent together.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jon Slobotkin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[During spring training years ago, Wheels was bugging me and Vuk for info on the team so we decided to teach him a lesson.  We tied him to a fence post at Jack Russell Stadium for an inning and hid his briefcase.  We couldn't stop laughing.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larry Bowa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I asked Wheels to drive down to spring training with me and it was a really small car.  I think it was an MG.  Once we got going, I wouldn't stop to sleep or switch seats so he was stuck in that seat for 18 hours and he was so pissed.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larry Bowa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Being able to walk into the press dining room after home games while Wheels was updating his notes and just talking baseball and life has been one of the best experiences of my career.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin Cooney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Wheels!/R/RMany years from now Ryan and I will still be watching the video from the Sept. 2013 game when you, T-Mac and Murph talked about our engagement on air. Thanks for creating such a special memory for us!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Todd and Ryan Zolecki]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Bday Wheels from all the Hurdle's tall and small. We've covered some distance together over the years. You've made a difference in the lives of many./RIn the words of Sinatra..."all I want for /Rmy birthday is another Birthday!"/RHead south!/RLove Clint]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Clint Hurdle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Yo Wheels, It's been over 40 yrs. and if you hadn't gone to have a beer with me that Spring night in Clearwater, I wouldn't have met my wife! Always loved K. Brett and I delivering you room service! You know what I mean! 70yrs old means one thing, I'm close./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tommy Hutton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chris,/RTough for me to site one moment we shared that was humorous, except maybe the World Series MVP presentation when only u and I were present, so I'll simply say that I cherish our friendship and the hundreds of moments we've shared from 1973 to the present. HBday.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael Jack Schmidt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday #70 to WHEELS! A pro's pro and a great friend!/R/RHave a great day!/RJoe Simpson]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Simpson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[How am I supposed to wish Happy Birthday to someone that doesn't seem to know when his birthday actually is?!?!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frank Coppenbarger ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Wheels - do you remember that time in SD you were writing an article for the Phila .Journel and you gave it to Chrissy to bring back to Phila.  You didn't trust me......she left it in the cab..]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Debbie xo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[More than one special moment.  Having  many conversations in the Press dining room with someone who truly loves baseball.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jack Scheuer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chris--I have enjoyed getting to know you better watching games in the Exec. box.  You are a class act and a good guy.  Happy 70th!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rick Strouse]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wheels happy birthday to you.  Never realized we were 15 years apart. /RAlways remember meeting at ND game in happy valley and seeing you at the ballpark./RHugs to Renee. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dr & Mrs Marone ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The Phillies Airport Homecoming Band wishes to serenade you with Happy Birthday!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Police & Fire Band]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[All the great times, airplane rides, golf, laughs, VUK etc.  Just way too many to possible capture on a small card like this.  Thanks for always being such a good sport and letting us have fun with you!  Happy Birthday to a great friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frank Coppenbarger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chris and I have had many memories from the first day we met-too many to remember. Tommy John can't get me out. LA was one great time. Happy 70th birthday!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Bull]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 70th Wheels! Cosmetic surgery sure has come a long way, huh? HA! Wishing you all the best on your special day. I can hear Harry and Skip toasting (or roasting) you now! Thanks for so many years of kindness...here's to 70 more seasons of fun and laughs!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chip Caray]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whenever I think of you, I recall my sports bloopers. DreamWeek: I was yanked from pitching for beaning Kent Tekulve. SoCal golf, my shoulder shattered by a ball. My 1st pitch into the Bucs dugout! No matter what though, you are always a great memory! Happy BDay Wheels!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Craig Shoemaker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Wheels!!  Because of you, I now have a new appreciation of "The Wave".  I know how much you enjoyed it, so I would make sure that I was right next to you participating in it!  Love you!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christine Connors]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're turning 70?!  That's about the number of times you stepped on my cable and tripped me!  I hope you have a fantastic 70th!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christine Connors]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's the everyday stuff that I miss.  Our discussions about the dinner menu, our dogs, NCIS, PSU.  Looking for your media guide that someone stole.  The Chinese firedrill of announcers, botched opens!  All that good stuff.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christine Connors]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[8 years together at the Phillies, including road trips, Judges' Chamber, divorces, ups and downs, World Series and many splendid memories have cemented a friendship that lasts forever.. And remember, "you really are an a$$@hole. Happy Birthday my good man."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tony Siegle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It was a 'hot' summer weekend in Cincinnati in the late '70's.  Waiting outside the team hotel, you and I along with the Tugger, searched for our ride.  The sound of a malfunctioning muffler and a late model sedan, produced The Craddock Sisters. What an adventure!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eddy Denny]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Wheels, I don't think I will ever forget how kind you were to rake a bunker for me several years ago. Unfortunately, you have never been able to forget it either! So sorry about all the teasing. Where has chivalry gone??/RLooking forward to many more rounds with you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday,  Lyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Not saying "goodnight/goodbye" is a no-no. Hence I watched Richard Deats pour out 2 water bottles @4.95 each, a rollout bed delivered to his room, ending up under it and S Rolen walking out and down the hallway wearing Wheels' sports coat, looking like Herman Munster]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larry Andersen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wheels:  From one Marple-Newtown grad to another, happy 70th birthday.  Since you share a birthday with my mom, I always remember yours.  Leigh and I hope you a wonderful birthday with many more to come! We Are...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leigh & Eric Tobin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[70 my a$$! My only regret in life is that I didn't whip the living $hit out of you back in the spring of '03. My hope is one of my boys will get that done for me one day to the delight of many future Phillies fans. As far as this occasion, I have underwear older than 70]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cecil A. Popodonovich, USPS]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I first met Chris thirty eight years ago. I would like to say it feels just like yesterday, but it actually feels pretty much like thirty eight years ago. Chris is one of the sweetest and most genuine people I've ever met. There should be a statue of him at the ballpark]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christopher Guest]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Because you were born my husband and then his wife listened to his beloved team and heard from your voice the triumphs and tribulations of being a lifelong Phillies fan. When I visited the booth you made me feel welcome and not a  Luddite. I'm so glad you were born.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jamie Lee Curtis Guest]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Yo Wheels! Happy 70th Birthday and special wishes to a good man, friend and important part of Phillies lore. We have great memories to share and you have been there every step of the way.  You also look a lot better than Bowa!  Sorry for all the "GOOSES"/RSincerely,  LC]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larry Christenson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chris & I shared many PSU moments. 05 PSU-OSU for the Big 10. We are with 109,839 rabid fans for a White Out, 2 top 10 teams. PSU leads 17-10 late, classic game, Troy Smith is driving OSU to tie and Tamba Hali, Tamba Hali forces a Smith fumble, we win & finish 11-1 # 3!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian Aungst]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I frequently texted Chris during telecasts to comment, my biggest complaints were when we were stuck watching opposing broadcasters who were awful compared to him, he was always gracious in his response. Those guys provided no real baseball info like Chris always did!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian Aungst]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chris. I have tried to get Rick Santorum to sit next to you in the PSU Skybox for the past four years. So far no luck but maybe as a favor for you birthday he would do you that "favor"!!  You are the best and Kip sends his regards as well (I just talked with him. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rich DiEugenio. We Are...]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Great to work with Wheels for 3 years on Prism/Sportschannel!  Love the memories he and Dad shared through the years.  Remember early in his career when the Phils players put Wheels in the tarp and rolled it on the field. You've come a long way buddy!  Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Todd Kalas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hard to believe that you're 70! I had so many great memories with you over the years and miss our talks. I have some over-the-air greetings for you that have accumulated, by the way. I'm also wondering...can I pull out the chair from under you one last time?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hugs and kisses, Rory McNeil]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I just hope that you have bought Renee a diamond ring with all that money you took from me on the golf course]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Giles]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Much as felicidades en tu dia y que este dia te encuentre lleno de salud,/RHappy birthday Ruedas.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Juan Samuel ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Wheels, I hope you have a great day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Benny Looper]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Too many wonderful Phillies moments to count!  Seeing you at the Nittany Lion Inn the night before a Penn State football game and trading old stories was a blast!  HAPPY BIRTHDAY!  See you around the ballpark for many years to come.  We love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dan & Cathy Baker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Replacing you in PR in 1983 was challenging enough, but stepping into the booth in San Diego a year later when you took ill was really asking a lot. Strange how you made a miraculous recovery once someone mentioned Wally Pipp and my radio career was over after one night]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Pal Vince (aka Vinay Debarg)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We go back so far that I still call you Chris.  Who would have thought that in July 1971 when you drove me to a Phils/Flyers usherette hockey game, that one month later we would be working together and friends through all these years.  We wish you a wonderful 70th b-day]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much love, Adele and Jack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[WHEELS TURNS 70/RDepartment of Confirmation and Denial confirms shocking announcement./R/RLong-time Phillies employee denies real birthdate is April 9 despite being published in his book. Memory and punctuation are weaknesses.  Signs of senior moments.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Baron, who else?]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lots of them, but that first dinner in LA on my first road trip was great!  Thanks for the advice and all of your fun stories! Even tho we are at odds during college football season, you're still my buddy. Cheers to You, Wheels! Happy Birthday!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christa Linzey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So many years and too many events to recall..not enough room..always glad for a drink or 2 we shared at sassafrass after Debbie's wedding. The rest is history..you have been a dear and loyal friend to me and I cherish our friendship! Hope this next decade is the best!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marianne "teen angel"]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chris,/RI am so grateful to have you in my life. You have taught me to believe in myself. Whether I was pretending to be your waitress and serve you dessert after thanksgiving, or asking you for career advice, you have always been a thoughtful, kind, and inspiring:).  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lauren ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chris,/RHappy Birthday to a wonderful man!  Thanks for opening your home and your heart to our family. Here's to making many more memories./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laird and Donna Kantruss]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'll always remember the fun we had during the late 70's ragging you about your hair and sneaking up behind you to give you a little 'goose'...hard to believe you've hit 70!..wish you many more happy healthy ones!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kitty]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wheels your gift for your 70th is a bigTHANKYOU, a late "call-up" to your world of friends I so enjoy the chats and visits we share. My best compliment to you is to say you are playing way "above the rim" and grossly over you head with your life partner Renee! lucky man]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael Kirschner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Fond memories which began in 1977 and remain fresh today.  Thanks for your mentoring, friendship and support.  With your help, a dream became a reality, an internship became a career and an usherette became my wife.  You're a true Phillie and a truer friend.  Cheers!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ed Wade]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Loved working with you Wheels!  Your love of the game is unparalleled.  I will never forget the night of October 29,2008 and being able to observe you perform "The Wheeler" and getting to high 5 you moments after the Phils won the title!  Happy birthday my friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Jackson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What a phenomenal ride you have had! You have come a long way the first 70 years from Egg Harbor-Marple Newtown-PSU-Phillies to having your own Wikipedia page... now you have the next 30 years to spend more time with the Gosiks and continuing your wonderful ride!  WeAre]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chris  Happy 70th You old thing! It's been great knowing you these 22 years. Lots of fun and laughs, especially at Jack Russell. Looking forward to many more years of friendship.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA["Mare" & Charles Marullo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wheels, as for this birthday, it's just a number!  I passed it several years ago and it's painless!  I'd tell a couple of stories but the Crescent Street one and the Downey's story are best kept to ourselves.  Happy Birthday my friend and many more healthy years!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dave Van Horne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wheels, miss talking baseball w/you in the booth. Rarely did I not learn something either in talking w/you beforehand or your commentary of the game. When you stopped in the booth & asked about Hamels' foul ball count the other Sunday, felt like old times. Happy B-day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carl Graber]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can't possibly share just one memory from our long history.  As a lifelong Phillies fan, I grew up listening to you.  Then working with the Phillies beginning in 1992, I got to know you.  Being able to call you my friend is the most special thing to me.  Love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cindy Webster]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Chris! Thank you for many years of support, advice, and guidance throughout my life. The favors you have done for me will never be repaid and I really do appreciate everything. You have provided me great memories that I will cherish forever! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christopher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Wheels,/RThanks for everything! You missed your true calling. You should have coached under Joe Paterno. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Best Always, Ruly ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Happy 70th Wheels!  Hard to believe how fast time flies bye.  Over 40 years of memorable seasons.  Go state!  Cheers from California!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brad Kalas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the biggest negatives of leaving the National League after 23 years was missing out on the relationships forged through the years with people like Wheels. I particularly miss the ^$%# you gave me when L.A. and I might show up at the yard a "little" hungover.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All the best, Swanee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday To my Uncle Wheels! You have blessed my childhood & adult yrs with countless memories treasuring the Phightin's! Christmas Eve is another treasured tradition! So glad to have you a part of the goober Gosik fam! Cheers to many more "phist" pumping years!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ashley Kantruss]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I joined "the team" in 2012, no one made me feel more welcomed, right away, than you Wheels. As a kid, and as a colleague,  I never had anything but the upmost respect for you as a broadcaster and a person. /RBest moment: playing golf at East Gate!/RHappy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Murph]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wheels never let us forget he was a star at Marple Newtown!He's such a good friend, that  he sent me a dollar for my fine when I was ejected by Joe West in N.Y. He second guessed my every move at fantasy camp , when HE drafted the team! Happy birthday from our family!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wine-o]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wheels, Great Memories, golf with Whitey and Harry.sidewalks and U turns across the medium from the golf course. Reminding me the "off" outfielder was too deep during your broadcast. That was BIG. My dew looked better than yours! Happy 70th Birthday. Vuk & Fregos say hi]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lee Elia and family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You will always be a special part of "Phillies" history. You will always have a unique friendship in my heart. Have a great day. Thanks for being Wheels.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Skipper Lee and family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mr. Wheeler - CW/R/RIf it wasn't for working with you on the Phillies Golf Tournament, I never would have gotten to know you and appreciate & enjoy baseball the way I do.  /R/RYou will never know how many people you have touched but you will always be part of BCC!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[M&M ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[  We were very fortunate to meet Chris,in 1978, at a Phillies speaking engagement. His knowledge of baseball is like none other. We truly miss his excellent commentary./R   We have always known Chris to think of others before himself./R   Happy 70th to Our Good Friend]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Diane and Bob Bacine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I grew up listening to Wheels!/RWhen we first met, I didn't want to bother him with more baseball talk, but then I got to know him, and I found he is as passionate about baseball off the clock, as he was while broadcasting.  He is genuine and a great guy!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Greg Swindells]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Chris, I remember the first time we met. I believe it was Thanksgiving & I must've been  Aidens age. I remember thinking- wow this guy must be really special for my Aunt Nay to bring around us Goobers! You're more than special to us & we're lucky to celebrate you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy birthday! Love, Amber]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's hard to believe that you and I have been part of the Gosik family for almost the same amount of time...we are the outlaws, you know...we have to stick together! You and I conspired a long time ago to surprise Renee for her birthday; we got her good! Happy 70th! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Donna Jean ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's been so fun sharing our football tailgates with you at Penn State. How lucky are Mark and I to have Kathryn and Matt spend their college years in the happiest of all valleys, one of your loves...Nittany Lion Inn, Seafood Buffets, JoePa,  THON, Blue & White, WE ARE]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark and Donna ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best things in life are the people we love, the places we’ve been and the memories we’ve made along the way.  Thank you for being part of our family and the memories we’ve made with a lot more to come! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, The Heath family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Pop Pop!/RWithout a doubt you are my favorite Nittany Lion!  Despite my background I respect your loyalty to your school.  I have thoroughly enjoyed talking football, among other things the 23 years I have known you.  Have a great day! Here's to many more!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Phil Sheridan- Sunshine ND'92]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite moment was when the Phillies won the 2008 World Series, when you came down to celebrate with us! Something I will never forget for the rest of my life!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wheels was one of the 1st people I met when I came to PHL in '94. I will never forget the kindness he showed me that 1st year. Since then he has become a great friend and mentor, a blessing in my life. Wheels is a great baseball man -- and an even better man. HBD, amigo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Salisbury]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[For my routine, in the clubhouse for the first 3 innings of each game, always listening and watching every pitch.  I remember our team and our players through your voice and knowledge.  When I listened or when we talked, always impressed, loved your take on the game!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[B Lidge]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Working with WHEELS were the best 25 years of my professional career. A fine person and a great broadcaster. I am saddened by his passing at 90. /RThe hall of fame is welcoming an ANGEL./RHugs and free ADAMS CLUBS./RJR]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Reynolds]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Uncle Chris! Happy Birthday!! I hope you enjoy it! I've loved watching you broadcast over the years but I think the most special moment was hearing you speak to the class at PSU... not only was it inspiring but made me very proud to call you my uncle! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathryn Gosik]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ambassador Wheeler,/RHaving fun honoring your  title throughout the country with Frank. He would do anything for one of his best friends (especially if it embarrasses you)! Wishing you many more years together of golf, good stories and him making you jump. Enjoy 70!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cathie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will never forget all the great memories made at Phillies games from the Vet, to the World Series in '08. Also going to the best dinner at the Nittany Lion Inn Friday night, then tailgating the game Saturday morning in Happy Valley! Thank you for everything!/RWE ARE!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matthew ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Back in the day I really enjoyed talking baseball, golf & PSU with you off the air in the Vet booth when I worked for 1210. Btw, you can blame me on the "Wheeler dance" video. It was my idea to shoot you guys in the booth. We loved the reaction. Happy Birthday. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Neil Hartman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What can I possibly say about you? Most of it would be in the "happened in Vegas" mode. I am definitely glad that I never had to witness Whitey paying off on the bet you made on that 3 break putt. You are a great friend and we always look forward to our time together.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ken Hamilton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I don't have a moment to share. Instead, I will talk about how you brought me in from day one and never big leagued me. Not once. More than you know, I value your friendship, support, advice and counsel. I miss our time together on the road but grateful to have had it.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Greg Casterioto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ The composure and patience that Wheels had while taking all the good natured kidding from us in the late 70's and early 80's, especially from Bowa, will always be one of my fondest memories of a good friend. Harry, Whitey, and Wheels were the best.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ron (Slinky) and Julie Reed]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wheels - Happy 70th birthday from your friends at the St. Louis Cardinals...we wish you many more!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian Bartow, St. Louis Cardinals]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wheels, I've truly enjoyed our 22 years of friendship. Happy Birthday!!! Looking forward to having you co-host more Baseball Insiders shows!! All the best!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Brazer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love having you in our family.  Like hearing your baseball stories. Thanks for having us all over for Christmas Eve.  We know how much you love our Pollyanna.  Please don't hit my car again.  Proud of you!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Walt and Marie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey Wheels, I hear you're turning 39 this year and I would love to take this opportunity to wish you a happy birthday. Every year for 20 years I look forward to spring training when I have the chance to sit and talk to you about baseball and life. All my best.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Luigi Gallace]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday my friend!! Seems like only yesterday we shared our tiny ST office space-the Quality Inn, then Jack Russell.  The stories and laughs are aplenty from checking the odometer on Tony's car to having your afternoon nap interrupted by the seagulls!!  Love ya~]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Suzie (Ingersoll)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Chris! Although we met later in life you always put a smile on my face with your big hello and warm hugs. I love seeing you from my seat in HOF when we exchange waves and smiles. I met my dear friend Renee due to you and I am blessed to be a part of your world. HBD!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jami Amaro and entire family! Xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We were going through some old pictures the other day and I came across your going away party at our house. You still go away every year to Clearwater but for some reason we decided that one particular year to throw you a party. Do you remember the goggles and speedo??]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eileen and Larry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I got cut off, anyway, we have so many wonderful memories on and off the course. Happy Birthday to a great guy!!??]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Eileen and Larry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There is nothing better than standing in for a Hall of Famer (in golf).  That's exactly what Chris did when MJS couldn't make our annual Caves Valley trip and wouldn't you know it, Chris stepped up and was an unbelievable Hall of Famer himself. Wishing you all the best.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin Beale]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can't comment on Wheels' golf game these days, but you haven't lived until you've seen grown men -- David Montgomery, Paul Callahan and Wheels -- arguing over strokes in miniature golf.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeannie Ashburn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, kiddo!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Ashburns]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always, from day one back in 1993, a gentleman./RI have never seen you be anything but open and gracious to anyone that steps foot in the booth.  Techs, stage manager, scribes, visiting media, and even fans.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robert Brooks "Brooksie"]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You took the high road so often that you made it look easy, and I know that it was not.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robert Brooks "Brooksie"]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Instigator in my friendly feud with Vuk (ALvsNL): "Vuko, Tip says George Bell had 4 hits in his 1st game with the Cubs"/R/RJolly Foil-T.F. steals his bag & puts it under bus tire. Driver finds & holds it up: "Anybody lose a bag?"  Throngs of laughter/RWheels-a good person]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ray G. Tipton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From Philly to LA to San Fran, San Diego and Houston -- even the Dominican Republic if you remember. It's been a wonderful journey and I'm happy to have shared so many treasured moments with you. Can't wait for you to make Belleair CC your home. Are you really 70?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hal and Pat Bodley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey Wheels,  All that I can says is, if it wasn't for you I would never have had a career.  I might still be tending bar at Downeys.  Then my only relationship with Larry Andersen would be as a person I would have to continuously flag.  Congrats, Wheels. Enjoy Life!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Video Dan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If I had a video from all the years of people goosing Wheels, (which was literally every day) it would be a bestseller! /R/RLove ya Wheels!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dutchy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 70th. The Andorra Christmas parties get trumped by Rendell fundraiser at the Green Tree party house. That night jump started Ed's political career and quite possibly changed relationships for a number of guests/RFor 44 years we are where we always dreamed to be./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David, son of Willy who admired you]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Nitany, I hope your dad treats you well now that he has gotten so old!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your friend, Dugout]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Wow Wheels-you are really getting closer to shooting your age!  You know we go back 43 years to the early 70's.  Lots of good times traveling, golfing @ BBCC, Phantasy Camps, and front office times.  /RMay advanced age not prevent Renee from putting up with you...Enjoy!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Del and Dale Unser]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From the time Ruben Sr was in the front office and I was a little pain in the !%# running around the Vet until now; what I admire the most is Wheels' work eithic, his thirst for knowledge of the game and his pure love for the Phillies. Love ya, Muff]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ruben Jr. ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Daddy - I wuv you so much! You always give me hugs and kisses and belly scratches. I love our naps together. Sorry I snore loud sometimes and you have to go to the guest bedroom but I really like your side of the bed. Love you to the moon and back! x x x o o o]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nittany ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have so many great memories with Wheels...his kindness to me in the broadcast booth...after-game visits to "Nicky Blair's on Sunset Blvd..and above all, the pleasure of hearing him call a Phillies game with his unerring expertise...one of the best!/R "]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JIMMY RITZ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Now this year we hopefully started a new tradition...dinners together with me & Suzanne during spring training...and maybe even another concert.  Happy Birthday, Wheels]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JIMMY RITZ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sharing an office with Wheels was always great fun - especially when his buddies John Vukovich and Bobby Wine would torture him by re-arranging the furniture or stealing his supplies while he wasn't there! It never took Wheels long to figure out who the culprits were!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Regina Castellani]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As the Community Relations Department grew, we added Karen Howard who was also a cat lover like me. We would find and rescue cats from the Vet and many times, Wheels would come back from a road trip and find a cat or two living in our office. He was a great sport!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Regina Castellani]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Of all the great memories, the best one is that I always enjoyed Wheels' sense of humor and outlook on life. I learned a lot from him in regards to dealing with people and MLB players. Those years together will always be special! Thank you, Chris and Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Regina Castellani]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My early memories are when we were young.  We worked hard and played hard like children, in the early years of the Vet. My later memories have are about how loving you were to Blackie.  She loved you and so do I.  Have a great birthday!  How did we get this old???  Love]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jodie Lehman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wheels...so you are turning 70! Wow I can't believe it. The best thing I can say about you is how much I miss you. I always appreciated your friendship while I was with the Phillies and hope you have a Phantastic celebration! Let's go to Ribit! Here is to another 70!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Raymond (The other old guy)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So many memories...so much fun! We are blessed! Enjoy your day, and know that Bob and I love you, and wish you the best, today and always!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob & Sue Boone]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One "celebrity" moment I remember about working with Wheels was that he knew a lot of people. Imagine my surprise when I found Jamie Lee Curtis and Christopher Guest in our tiny office during a game! Wow!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Regina Castellani]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wheels,/R/RHappy Birthday to you!!/RMiss seeing you on the road and around the park! Always will remember the banter between you and Vuke!!! Some of the funniest times ever!!/RAll the best!!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dan O'Rourke]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I've know you as long as I can remember! Whether it was my dad torturing you, telling Wheels stories, or just listening to your voice on TV, you have always been a part of my life! Wishing you the happiest birthday and to many more! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nikki Stolarick and Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I've known Chris for over 45 years and we've known Chris as a great Phillies and Penn State fan. I recall a moment when he played left field on the WPVI-FIL softball team and making a Willie Mays type catch to save the game. Happy 70th Chris!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Werndl]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Chris,/RHappy 70th Birthday. Enjoy and embrace this milestone./RI think you are one of the most kind and genuine people I have ever met. You always take time to talk and listen. You are a great role model for the kids. I'm so glad to have you in our family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Karen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wheels,  Apparently you think any month starting with "A" is your birthday month. You're either smart & working the system or you've lost it.  Since you're friends with Frank, I'll go with the latter and keep leaving cakes in April. At 70, celebrate any time you want!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cathie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The "@sshole everyone told me about" turned out to be a trusted resource and a valuable friend. I only wish he hadn't gotten me started playing golf. With that in mind, I guess it turns out he is an @sshole after all. We miss you, but you'll always be in our schtick!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Scott Franzke]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Im so glad we got to play so many rounds of golf. I most enjoyed you being our 4th with Ellie, Eileen & me that one Fall season when we played just about every day. We never did get to see you wear your speedo going away gift. /RHoping to play many more years with you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[XOXO-Ann Blasko]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chris: HAPPY BIRTHDAY, AND BEST WISHES. I have enjoyed our friendship over the years, and I hope you continue to make Clearwater, FL. and the Belleair CC your winter home.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Conway OP (Old Pro)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Seems like yesterday, we were both in our 20s playing softball @WCAU.  I'm sure you remember when I told Coppenbarger and Vuk how Jack Downey flew you in from Penn State for a big game. This resulted in them putting you on trial in a Kangaroo Court. Happy 70th Wheels!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ed]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Wheels!!/RMy favorite moment was talking with you after your 1st lesson with Jon Estilow. You had the biggest smile along with a giggle that wouldn't stop. You knew you hit a solid golf shot. TY for bringing the smiles and giggles out in millions of people]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Henry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[BOBBY V. TOLD ME HE HAS A CAR COMING FOR YOU. ALL THE BEST. I WILL FOLLOW IN AUGUST.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jay Horwitz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Vuk, Pope and I didn't have much to work with, but you turned out to be a pretty good baseball guy and like all of us old farts with big mouths are either dead, retired or useless to the game we love, but our memories and that love of the game still make us special.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dallas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Chris - glad you're part of the family...we are a little off but you got use to us.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jay]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Yo Chris -  I said before - You can jump in my foxhole any time. You are a man's man. Luv always,  "VC" - "Poe"  Dad - haha]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Walt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chris, of all your great qualities I think I most appreciate your consistent generosity on the golf course. Happy Birthday to you buddy!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Roger Cohn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>