<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2616-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/6/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Carolyn Guyet]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[5240 N. Lake Drive]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Milwaukee]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[WI]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[53217]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Loved for a Lifetime]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Maureen Manning]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom, you are my role model, my guardian angel, and a best friend. Thank you for all you have done to make my life easier and happier. You are a ray of sunshine to so many. You always put God and your family first. You are such an inspiration and I love you very much.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Carolyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a beautiful mother with so much love for your family. I wish you a wonderful happy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Emily Hauer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are many things I admire about Maureen, but the one trait that I admire so much is her dedication to her family.  She has an obvious interest in all her children and grandchildren, and she seems to have boundless energy.  Happy Birthday, Maureen.  Peggy Harris/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peggy Harris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom pushed me to expect more from myself and to never settle.  This drives me as an adult to never quit and never stop trying to be better.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paul]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maureen, You have been such a big part of our lives always, but especially since we moved here so many years ago!  Thank you for all the help, generosity and thoughtfulness that you have shown us for the past 15 years! We love you and wish you a happy 75th birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Brenda Jack Peter Joseph & Ken]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Grandma, you have been so devoted to me since the day I was born. I have never known anything but love and laughter from you. Thank you for being so wonderful, kind, and caring. You are my only grandmother, but you are the only one I need. I love you very much.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Madeleine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Grandma,/RThank you for always giving me belly rubs and for sneaking me pieces of fish and chicken when no one was looking. I need lots of love and attention and you are always happy to oblige.  Now, if you would only let me sleep in the bed...Still love you, though.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Louie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maureen's sense of loyalty is very admirable.  Her fierce loyalty of her family, faith and mission of the Ronald McDonald House guides her decisions and actions every day.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ann Petrie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I've always appreciated that Mrs Manning made me feel welcomed & loved in her home since I was 8 years old. That kindness exists still today & I see it mirrored through her daughter who has been such a dear friend to me. You've built a house on love. Thanks for sharing ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carrie Chimenti ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Grandma,/RI hope that you have a wonderful birthday! You are the sweetest Grandma in the world! I love your fashionable clothes and how you kept Daddy's toys so we can play with them! I love you and thank you for being the most wonderful Grandma ever!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sally]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Grandma,/RI love how we go to the store and get donuts. I always enjoy staying with you. I love you Grandma.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Liam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Grandma,/RI love how friendly you are and that you always give me big hugs. I hope you have a great birthday. I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Grandma. I like eating fruit snacks and drinking chocolate milk  with you in your kitchen. I love your cake. I love you Grandma.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Maureen! I wish for you many years of excitement & blessings./R"The Lord your God is with you. He is mighty to save. He will take great delight in you, He will rejoice over you with singing" -Zephaniah 3:17/RYou are a special lady & I am thankful for you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Molly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maureen is a person who will listen, takes the time to truly understand what is being said and stands by her friends during good and bad times.  Happy 75th Birthday Maureen.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joan Abdoo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations, Maureen. /RFor 50 years, you have been a special Sister-in-law and Friend. We remember all your gourmet dinners and enjoyable get-togethers on Prairie Road. Have a wonderful birthday.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Ellen and John]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[How blessed I was 30+ years ago when you were by my side to forge our way into the unknown world of Milwaukee in the "80's".  Who would have ever thought we'd still be here but even more so, that we now have children & grandchildren also here.  /RWarm wishes on your 75th]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Gail Chimenti]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maureen is beautiful and graceful. She has gifted the world with six wonderful and capable children. We, Darbandi family, are so lucky, to have  Elise, one of her beautiful daughters as our daughter in law./RZohreh]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Zohreh Darbandi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maureen-/RWishing you the happiest of birthdays!/RThank you for your many years of time and dedication to the Ronald McDonald House. Your support is immeasurable.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heather Egerer (RMHC)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maureen, while I have only known you a short time, I admire your young at heart attitude and enthusiasm, and your wardrobe!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandi Evans]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It is hard to limit to one thing what I like most about Maureen.  I feel most fortunate to have her friendship and I enjoy HUGELY the memories that began after Jim and I found Maureen, Ken and Kenneth at an M&I football game event very soon after they moved to Milwaukee]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joan Urdan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for all those years you raised me, for your guidance, your warmth and your love.  I am so lucky to have you!  You are the most fabulous, beautiful, greatest and most dazzling woman in the world!  Wishing you the best and happiest Birthday!  I love you a lot!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elise]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aside from your generosity you are the Queen of appetizers.  I have many wonderful memeories of Christmas with multi generations of family and delicious appetizers, including the year we were so busy eating them that the oven forgot to be turned on.  Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cheri ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Like all big sisters, Maureen loved to tease. I remember driving to Florida in 1951 with no AC & the windows shut. She was 11 & I was 6. Cowboy’s & Indians dominated the TV & she told me there were Indians behind the trees along the road waiting to shoot arrows at me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wonderful memories of your parties in the Little House on The Prairie (Road). You are a great friend. I miss you. Happy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ann Rosen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Many happy memories of the days in Huntington and our visits with you in WI. You are a beautiful, kind and generous lady!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jerry Rosen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maureen is a caring and thoughtful person.  There have been many times when she helped Elise and I, like when Sam was born.  She thinks about others, as she dedicated herself to charity.  Last but not least, we love the wonderful dishes she makes like Shepard's Pie!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Many Darbandi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From beginning as a pleasant across the back fence neighborly chat, we have developed a wonderful friendship.  We have shared happy times and we have shared  sadnesses and I am grateful.  My wish for you is years of health and happiness and, for us years of friendship.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Joyce]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are an incredibly generous & thoughtful person.  It shows in the way you welcomed me into your family; you have treated me as one of your own, you have been like a mom to me, we can talk about the tough things in life. Thank you for a always been here for us.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Allan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memory is you being forced to take me out on a lot of your dates.  Too bad I was so young, I think I fell in love with all of your rejects! I guess I was a good chaperone, because you wound up with the best, Ken. Thank you for being a wonderful big sister.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Gayle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maureen is a wonderful volunteer and mentor. She's generous with time and advice! She has taught me a lot about events: 1. the bread basket must have height 2. serve beer in glasses so bottles don't junk up photos 3. self-cancel stamps at USPS. Happy Birthday, Maureen!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jacquelyn, Ronald McDonald House]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Grandma~/R/RYou are the greatest Grandma ever!  I love how you take care of me and give me love, hugs and kisses(and cookies!)!  You are always thinking about me and always know how to make me happy.  I hope that you have the best birthday ever!  I love you lots XOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maureen's dedication to the Ronald McDonald House has been an inspiration to me.  She is our leader, but she leads by example - pitching in wherever she sees a need.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dan & Kim Geigler]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I admire Maureen's keen devotion to Ronald McDonald House and its mission. She so obviously cares about the families who stay here. Her basic humanity shines through as she interacts with staff, sharing experiences and listening with concern to their stories and needs.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jerry Ryack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The One thing I love the most about my mother is she has always been completely herself.  I never knew any other mothers (or grandmas) who could pull off 5 inch stilettos, while holding a crying baby, cooking a 5 course meal, all while being uniquely, beautifully her.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jacqueline Harris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maureen, one of the things I have learned about you while working at the Ronald McDonald House is that you care deeply and you are not afraid to ask the tough questions.  Thank you and Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marlene Bruno]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A very Happy Birthday to you, Maureen. You have been a wonderful mother to all your children, and a good friend to me. Thank you for your many kindnesses over the years, and I wish God's blessings upon you and yours.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Monsignor Maury Voity]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maureen,/RI couldn't ask for a better mother-in-law. You are one my favorite people in the world. I think the greatest accomplishment one can achieve is being a successful parent. All you have to do is look at your family to see that you have succeeded there in spades.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Carl]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>