<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2629-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/11/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Jennifer Locke]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[2036 ERIE ST]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[GRAFTON]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[WI]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[53024-9681]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sand]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 50th Wedding Anniversary]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Ron and LouAnn Meyer]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[With love, Jeff, Jenni & Janelle]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your marriage is a living, Christian example of what God intended for a blessed union. Thank you for blessing us with this example to follow./R  /RWith all of our love and appreciation, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andy, Jenni, Mikayla and Baden]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[God has blessed you with each other and used the two of you to be a blessing to many.  We are blessed to have been a small feature of those who are blessed./RHappy Anniversary!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gail and Jock Ficken]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being an incredible reflection of Jesus Christ's love for His Bride, the Church!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ed & Nancy Blonski]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like many of Jeff and Jenni's friends over the years have been welcomed into your home with unconditional love and understanding. Thanks for everything.  Ginger would be proud of "my family".  Congrats on 50 years together and all of God's blessings along the way!!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matthew Thies ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations and God's richest blessings to you both as you celebrate 50 years of marriage! /R/R"The Lord has done this, and it is marvelous in our eyes. This is the day the Lord has made; let us rejoice and be glad in it!"/R- Psalm 118:23-24]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bernie & Gretchen Huesmann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our one special memory is of Ron giving Theresa a ride to visit Concordia College and encouraging her to attend there.  We have been blessed immeasurably because of this!  In fact, we're writing this on our 24th anniversary.  Thank you both for your love and care.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark and Theresa Shaltanis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Grandma and Grandpa,/RHappy 50th! You two are such amazing people who I will always look up to. I couldn't ask for better grandparents.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mikayla]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wow!  You are beating us to the big 50!  Congratulations and blessings to you both!  What a lot of great times we've shared over the years.  (New Year's Eve parties, kids at MLHS and now grandkids' games etc.).  Celebrate!  it's a wonderful achievement!!  ????]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cami and Jim Juergensen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[At Camp Okoboji there was this pastor sporting a crew cut. He mixed it up with the campers on the basketball court. Over the years I would come to greatly respect him and would have the pleasure of getting to know his lovely supportive wife. Thank you for serving. Glory]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff and Laurie Prewitt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have been a wonderful example of a great marriage! Thank you for sharing that love with those around you! Love and blessings for the years to come :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Justin and Sarah Kumpfer and family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite Grandma and Grandpa moments is when Grandma took me to Chuck E. Cheese's.  Then I came home and snuggled with Grandpa.  I am so glad I have the best Grandparents anyone could ask for.  Happy 50th Anniversary!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Baden]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We will never forget our first visit to a bed and breakfast with you. It ended up being rooms in the back of a nursing home. We even had breakfast with the residents. We praise God with you for 50 golden years together!  CONGRATULATIONS and GOD BLESS YOU!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allen and Shirley Piepenbrink]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember being welcomed into the Meyer Family specifically Easter weekend of 1990. I was engaged to Jeffrey and instantly felt loved and was extended grace. I have always felt loved and encouraged by you both & thank God often for the gift of your son as my husband!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amy ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We appreciate the way you have both taken an interest in our children and shown them such love and support.  Thank you for making time to attend their different events and celebrate them. They are blessed to have faithful praying (great) Grandparents! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kyla, Jon, Bailey Kacie Abbey Alli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You've done this /R“...commit yourselves wholeheartedly to these commands that I am giving you today. Repeat them again and again to your children. Talk about them when you are at home and when you are on the road, when you are going to bed and when you are getting up." "]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeffrey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As far back as my memory will stretch when I think of Ron, LouAnn is always there adding stability, love and fun. Ask Lou to do Marilyn for you! Ron is always ready to draw a few laughs. Ask him to show you how the flash bulbs worked in the old cameras!  Living Eph.4:2]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rejoicing with you, Timm & Rosalie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Eph. 4:2 "Be completely humble and gentle; be patient, bearing with one another in love." This is what we have seen in your marriage for 50 years!  To God be the Glory! Congratulations!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Blessings, Timm & Rosalie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Over the years we have had many laughs and tears together.  So happy for you both and praise God for the example you have given to us. We look forward to our family times together. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John and Gerri]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember the summer we were all in Reedsburg and went to the Dells, beer and peanuts and then down to the ball park.....love you two!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gerri]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wishing two very special people a anniversary that will be treasured for years to come!!!  God Bless you both!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jean, Jim & Gretchen Fisher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["My purpose is that they may be encouraged in heart and united in love, so that they may have the full riches of complete understanding, in order that they may know the mystery of God, namely, Christ."/RColossians 2:2 /RThank you for showing me Jesus through your love. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kacie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["As for me and my house, we will serve the Lord." Thanks for living out this promise together for 50 years and for always being so gracious.  Congratulations and Special Blessings. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There is a young nurse in St. Louie, who used to live here on North Dewey.  She's my only sister and, oh, how I've missed her.  She went and got married, oh phooey! (limerick written 50 years ago)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randine and John Beth]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron and LouAnn:  Congratulations!  God has shown his love through you to many, many of his children./R/RI'm grateful to you, Ron, as one of the very first to give me your card so that we could test out the idea of PLI with your pastors.  Thanks for all the support for PLI]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Norb and Jackie Oesch]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[God bless you both for all you have given to His service, your family and friends. You have truly been 'blessed to be a blessing to others'!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chuck and Sharon Little]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations and God's Blessings as you celebrate your 50th Wedding Anniversary.  You have both been a blessing to many!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Roger, Ruth and Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron and Lou Ann have been our good friends for many years.  We have enjoyed traveling with them to Mich. and other places.  During Ron's Presidency I often asked Lou Ann to host a pastor's wives talk secession - she never refused and always did a great job.  God bless]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dawn and Bryan O'Connor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron is a churchman, caring pastor and friend. LouAnn is the smiling gal who brings joy to others, incl. skits for pastor's wives. Blessings for being God's gifts of love to each other for 50 years. Once they invited Cal to stay with them in their motel room-he did. Love]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cal and Karen Seban]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[16 years old when we first met. 1st Call - Manilla. As newest pastor in the circuit, Ron got saddled with the likes of us! Through Okoboji, Spencer, South Wisconsin! you have always been part of my family. I'm glad to be part of yours! I love you both very much! R-JWWYA]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alan & Jeynell Boeck- Han, Ben, Abi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["As for me and my house, we will serve the Lord" Joshua 24:15. The 2 of you have lived in the Lord as such an example of love. Thank you for leading our entire family in your 50 years of marriage. May God bless you with many more.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gloria & Bruce]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[May He who began a good work in your relationship 50 years ago continue to bring it to completion in the years to come,  thanks for your example of God's faithfulness.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John and Elaine Kieschnick ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[God's blessings to you on your special day.  May He bless you with many more years here on this earth and then into eternity with Him.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rick and Karen Fairbrother]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The smiles you give each other communicate a deep love and devotion, reflecting Christ's love in your lives! You are wonderful models for many.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Timothy and Sharon Maschke]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 50th Anniversary to two special people. God's Blessings for many more years!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cheryl and Mark Austin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on your 50th Anniversary! You both have always been special to our family and I want you to know how much we appreciate your support and care over the years, it means more than you know. Blessings to you on this special day and always,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dolores Goetsch]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you to Ron and LouAnn for sharing our wedding day with us.  We will always remember Ron participating in the wedding and being such a wonderful Godfather to Matt.  We love you and have a great day together!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matthew and Shelley Ehlke and girls]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron and I first met when we started at Concordia Senior College in Ft. Wayne.  I met his beautiful bride when we were privileged to be a part of their wedding.  Over those 50+ years, Ron and LouAnn have one of our greatest examples of Christian love.  God bless!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wayne and Bev Schroeder]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Grandma and Grandpa!  Happy Anniversary.  Thank you for always being the /Rbest grandparents and grandchild could ever ask for.  I love you very much /Rand hope you have a ton more years together!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jaedyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are great parents in law and I hope you have a wonderful wedding /Ranniversary!  I love you and thank you for always being YOU! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Donald]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[MOM & DAD, you are the best parents in the world /Rand I have endless love for the both of you!  Happy 50th Wedding /RAnniversary:)  You are a blessing to so many people including me and my /Rfamily.  Thank you for everything you do for us and so many more./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Janelle :)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What great encouragement you have been for us as you modeled ministry and marriage!  so many of us have been blessed by your example.  That marvelous example has been passed on to your children.  We have been particularly blessed by your Jeff and Amy!  Celebrate well!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Betty and Vern Gundermann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always was glad when Ron went home to visit LouAnn /Rwhile we were attending Senior College, because I could catch a ride with him /Rand go home, too.  Thanks, Ron!  God's blessings on your future years together.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paul Droegemueller]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary to a special couple!  I have always been proud to call you family . My memory is from our recent Meyer reunion. Your banter and smiles helped make my young granddaughters feel so special and set the tone for the entire afternoon . Thanks for caring. ?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jan & Jim Henke and Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron and Lou Ann, so many years, so many times to serve our Lord.  Paula and I remember your kindness and dedication to share the Good News.  Ron, in your many years as Pastor, Executive and President.  Lou Ann, your Bible studies at conferences. and conventions.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill and Paula Otto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[At seminary in St. Louis, you often invited me to join you in worship on Sundays, afterward inviting me to your apartment for lunch, consisting of delicious pancakes. I will never forget your hospitality and generosity, "Cuz" and your great pancakes, Lou Ann! God bless!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Duane and Evelyn Goetsch]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["And now these three remain: faith, hope and love.  But the greatest of these is love."/R    - 1 Corinthians 13:13]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[August 21, 1965]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations! 50 years of marriage is wonderful.  You two are an inspiration to all of us married couples.  You show such great Christian values and inspire us to be the best that we can be.  /R/RJeremiah 29:11.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brad & Tracey Bowers]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ I first met Ron at a golf outing to raise support for CUW. He was friendly and always smiling. /RLouAnn was kind and supportive of the pastor's wives. Margie appreciated many conversations woman to woman and mom to mom. You are both blessings to the Lord's people. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Don and Margie Stein]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We remember when Renee and Jenni became friends at a family reunion and then you let her stay with us for a few days when you were out of town./RWishing you God's richest blessings on your 50th Wedding Anniversary.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ella Mae and Lyle LeMoine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>