<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2633-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/11/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Terry Sue Bowman]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[204 Meade Drive, SW]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Leesburg]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[VA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[20175]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Hannah Bowman Class of 2015]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Hannah Bowman]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love, your many fans.]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I cannot believe you are graduating high school, you were just a baby visiting Oregon for the first time. Have a blast at Camp USC! College is awesome and I can't wait to visit you. You are going to have so much fun and have such a bright future ahead of you! Love you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Katie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I first met Hannah she called me short and after that moment I knew we were meant to be bffs. love you Hannah and I'm so proud of you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelsey Slack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dearest Hannah,/RCongratulations on this major milestone in life.  We are so proud and happy for you!  We will always treasure the fun times we had together with both of our families and look forward to many more.  Good luck in college and always dream big! xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Russell Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[.Christopher Robin to Winnie the Pooh, "Promise me you'll remember, you are braver than you believe, stronger than you seem, and smarter than you think." -A.A. Milne/RThis sums up what I used to tell you Hannah in 4th grade, the body can achieve what the mind believes.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bruce Blakeney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hannah, remember what Abraham Lincoln said, "In the end, it's not the years in your life that count.  It's the life in your years."  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bruce Blakeney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hannah, you're one cool lady.  I'm so happy I've gotten to know you this year (mostly due to you bothering me in the morning).  I know you're going to do crazy great things with your life.  I hope you love calculus forever.  Keep in touch!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ms. V]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hannah, I had such a wonderful time in high school with you, you are one of my favorite seniors and I am going to miss you so much next year, swim won't be the same. My favorite memories of being friends and high school is when you would say "Yeager, what did you do!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jake Yeager]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congrats girl! Thanks for so many childhood memories.  We're always laughing when we're together and continue to be our dorky selves. Love you so much Hannah! You'll always be a great friend. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ali ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hannah, you are a ray of sunshine! Seeing you always brightens my day! You have such a kind and giving heart. I know that you will continue to be an inspiration to others as you begin college this fall. Your bubbly personality and joyful spirit will serve you well.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love from Mrs. Rexroad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hannah {SC #3}/R/RCongratulations! I'm so proud and excited for you. I know you'll take everything that has made you so kind, smart and confident to your next adventure. I can't wait to see what comes next - HGB 2.0! /R /RFortune befriends the bold. (e.dickinson)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Auntie Mary Kay {SC #2}]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Woohoo! You did it! You have made the most of every minute of high school. We can't wait to see what your future holds. You will always be an honorary Hawkeye and Bobcat in our eyes. Visit soon!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Mattox Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hannah, Hannah, Hannah- Off to the real USC! You are going to have a great experience and I am sure you will excel as you have in all the others things you have done. We are all very proud of you. Can't wait to hear about your excellent adventure, hopefully in November!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Tucker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hannah- Good thing I can't post pictures here. I have a couple of good ones from my TV screen phone from where were visited a couple of years ago. That was a blast especially when Grandmommy said she wanted to go with us to shop at the National Mall! LOL!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Tucker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hannah Banana! Congrats on all of your tremendous achievements thus far! More importantly, congrats on who you are as a person - hard-working, compassionate, tenacious, and strong. I am so proud of you, and you should be to! Love you today & always! Now go conquer USC!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cousin Sarah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations Hannah!!  We are all so proud of you!!  I can't believe time has gone so fast.  I remember when you all were little and would come over to play in the snow. It has been nice to watch you grow into a wonderful young lady!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[We love you! The Rowells]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hannah is the absolute best swim coach/sitter/role model for our girls, Cece and Ivy... Among other Hannah-inspirations, their goal this summer is to swim the full length of the pool UNDER WATER! Hannah is fearless, energetic, and full of love and support!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Tomaszewskis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hannah,/R I know you will do great things at USC. I'm going to miss swimming with you next year. Love you so much!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessi ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Always listen t the still small voice inside you, its usually right! Know that your a beautiful young lady with a great future ahead of you. Go make your mark! And always remember your are loved by us.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[AuntieTammy and Uncle Virgil]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So proud of you sweet girl! /RYou are an amazing young woman with a brilliant future ahead. Hold true to who you are and who you want to be. Stay as beautiful on both the inside and out as you are today. Always know you have a friend in me. Love you so very very much!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Nancy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["If you can imagine it, you can achieve it. If you can dream it, you can become it."/R/R  - William Arthur Ward/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bessie Linkous ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hannah - /RI have such fond memories of you in third grade.  Your sweet, gentle nature was such a joy.  Your hugs and love of reading were the best!  I know you will achieve great things in life and can't wait to hear of all your continued accomplishments.  Way to go!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bessie Linkous ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Every great dream begins with a dreamer. Always remember you have within you the strength, the patience, and the passion to reach for the stars to change the world." /R Harriet Tubman]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bessie Linkous ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for being one of my best friends throughout the past four years! We have shared some wonderful memories that I definitely will not forget. Best of luck at the University of South Carolina!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sam Rexroad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congrats on graduating from high school! You are about to start an incredible adventure, so live it up!!! Join an intramural team, go to class, sign up for a new class, dress up for a theme party, have fun and tell your parents/sister you love them :)/R/RLove you Hannah!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Megan Atkins]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You were the quiet, book reading, don't need to always be with the group kid of our first playgroup and Myrtle Beach family.  Looks like that ability to not conform has paid off for you, and you have blossomed into a beautiful young lady.  Always be true to yourself!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve & Sheila Milonovich and Kids]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hannah, I always enjoy seeing what you wear to school. You have such a great sense of fashion, and are a style inspiration. I hope you have a great time in college! I'll miss seeing you around the neighborhood. <3]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kristen Martwinski]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite memories is baking with you.  I have a recipe for Chocolate Cake that you baked with me, and you crossed off each step as you finished it.  Whenever I make that cake, and see the steps crossed off on the recipe, it reminds me of you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Beth Martwinski]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have been my swim sister ever since I can remember and you will always be my swim sister. I love you Hannah and I wish you the best of luck at college! /RSNOW SISTERS FOREVER!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Kayla]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[May college bring you new challenges and horizons for the future./RYou have to have the stamina to meet obstacles and overcome them.    The influence you exert is through you own life and/Rwhat  you've become yourself.  You must do the thing which you cannot do. God Bless]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jane Cornell (Nana Jane)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I wish you the happiest college days anyone has ever had.  Just keep that beautiful smile sparkling for the world to see.  I love you and admire you.  I couldn't ask for anything more.  You are terrific!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, Grandmommy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We were entrusted with the privilege of looking after you your first sleepover away from your Mom and Dad.  From that day forward, you were family to us. You are a remarkable, beautiful young woman.  We watch with joy as you confidently follow your dreams and purpose.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cindy, Doug, Lily and Jaegar]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love your beautiful smile, giraffe hugs and easy way. We look forward to hearing your story, it will be amazing./R/RToday is your day! Your mountain is waiting. So... get on your way. ~ Dr. Seuss]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Miss Julie & Mike]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Don't sweat the petty things and don't pet the sweaty things.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[May May]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dream a dream../RMake a wish.. /RStep into the future/RAnd always be proud /RTo be YOU!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love , Auntie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My Sweet Hannah-belle, /RI love you for ALL that you are and ALL that you are yet to be.  /RMay you follow your dreams, always believe in yourself and keep hope in your heart.  /RI am so proud to be your Auntie and I am here for you whenever you need me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All my love,  Auntie Jeanne-Marie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hannah, well done! One step after the other...and now already you reached graduation. The next step will be equally exciting...I am sure you are looking forward to it and will enjoy. All the best! Let me always know if you need advise.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hubert]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It was an utmost pleasure and honor being your English teacher and swim coach. You brought an air of maturity, leadership, and benevolence to both the classroom and pool deck - please know that I wish for you nothing but the best in all of your future endeavors.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nick Grzeda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ One special gift that you take into the future:  you instinctively know and respond to the needs of others.  Like Maya Angelou said:   "People will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel."  /R ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love from Grandma Marty]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey Golddigger…not you can’t have more money!! You are worthless at explaining baseball, but you have been truly professional help when it was needed. I sought that advice. Thank you. Keep that excellence in all you do at USC and beyond. Final thought…tall is overrated!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Earl Eck and the whole Eck Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[hannah: /Rthank you for all the wonderful memories and fun we have shared together. thank you for everything you have done for me, you don't know how much i appreciate it. i hope college is an awesome experience and i will miss you so much! i love you han. #sistas4lyfe ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[izzy ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hannah the banana! From the "balloon head" in Richardson...to the beautiful young woman in Leesburg, I know you are ready to take on the world! I only hope the world is ready for you! I wish you nothing less than the best!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grandaddy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Don't let anyone...ever...dull your sparkle! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grandaddy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Han, I wish we could team-take college, because we're pretty good at that, but (even without your favorite soccer player) I know you'll do amazing things at USC.  You are beautiful, smart, funny and a great friend!  I can't wait to hear all about your adventures!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Emily, Allison & Lauren]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[HGB, you are truly an amazing young lady. You light up the world with your positive spirit. If we all believed in ourselves the way you do, there'd be no end to the good we could do in this world. I love you more than you can imagine & can't wait to see you shine at USC]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I love you, baby girl!  Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hannah, I saw this and thought of you... this is so you..../R"To her the world seemed like a grand and interesting place....and she could hardly wait to get out there!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hannah, there've been early mornings, late nights, a few fears & tears, lots of smiles, giggles, piles of books, successes and scraped knees...through it all, you've grown into a graceful & talented young woman. I'm so proud of you and can't wait to see what comes next!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ I love you! Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>