<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2637-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/12/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Patricia Marlies Lissack]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[803 Pennstone Road]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Bryn Mawr]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19010]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_60]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[185 Wonderful Years!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Carol and Rafe Lissack]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Your friends and family]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have been a superb role model in your marriage and amazing grandparents to my children.  We are all truly blessed by your presence in our lives. Thank you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marlies]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's really difficult to find just one thing that I like most about Carol and Rafe.  However, I'd have to say that it is their ability to take in people, turn them into friends, and if lucky, treat them like family.  I'm glad to say that I'm one of the lucky ones.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy Reavy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are so many memories growing up with two parents like you...but I do know how lucky I am to have the most caring, loving, supportive, generous and kind parents like I do. Words will never do justice to say how I feel, or express how much I love you both!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[6/20/13: I always love having you come to MIA for the Finals. As we secured our Gm. 7 victory & I made my way to the court to celebrate, I looked over at you to see your excitement. That was my favorite part of the Championship; to be able to share it with both of you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love your spontaneity. We always have wonderful adventures with continuous laughter. You can't ask for a better combination for friendship. May we continue to share all our milestones together./RWishing you Happy Birthday and Happy Anniversary,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barbara and Stephen ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[R&C/RWho knew? /RWhat a ride! /RGood. Fair. Fun and Crazy...and all that in between./R/ROur heartfelt thanks and love for always being there for us and our family./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jonathan and Mona]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[After a chance encounter watching a fire being put out on Chestnut Street on our way back from a 76ers game, we introduced ourselves to Rafe, who I instantly recognized as Carol's groom from the wedding pictures she shared at school. We became close friends. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gail & Mike]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have shared many memorable and wonderful experiences together,from the bowels of the President Hotel locker room in Atlantic City to the beach resorts of Cannes & St. Tropez.40 years later we still enjoy a special friendship celebrating our birthdays & anniversaries.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gail & Mike]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[GOOD FRIENDS like you are hard to find......./Rso, you are stuck with US./RNorth, East, South and West--- oh the places we have been!!!!!/RWishing everyday is a celebration./RLovingly, Beth and Jerry]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Beth and Jerry Frezel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[.....always a good time when we're together!/ROur dinners are adventurous and always filled with great conversation.  We wish you health, happiness, and lots of time to enjoy them together!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sheila & Larry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol and Rafe,/R/RWe have always admired your dedication to each other, family and friends. You are a beautiful example of, "TRUE LOVE LASTS".  Thank you for sharing your friendship with us.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love and admiration, Sandy & Harvey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As well as being "the best neighbors" ever they have become dear friends. Let's keep celebrating happy occasions together.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joan & Rick ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Words cannot express how lucky we feel to have had you in our life since our kids were babies.  Whether it was your boat, our house in Maryland, or the fun times we have had in the city, we cherish it all and look forward to many years of new memories together!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sending love,  Susie and Steve]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love sitting in their kitchen/den eating, drinking and shooting the breeze.  Laughs!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Art]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol is a Leo and Rafe is a Pisces, but just to let you know why they were made for each other - Carol acts like the Pisces and Rafe acts like a Leo...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Art]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol and Rafe, congradulations on these milestones...You both look good for AARP members.  I love you and treasure you as my Friends.  You have enriched my life for over 45 years. It's been great! I'm hoping this party was a complete surprise.  It was a good ploy.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Art]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[However, I always think it's better to know and look forward to the party rather than be surprised. But, in a way, you did look forward to our Eating Group, we haven't gotten together for a while.  You did look forward to it, right? It was a good ploy.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Art]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Carol and Rafe, I celebrate you, I'm sending love and kisses.  You will always have my Friendship...x x o o x x o o]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Art]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It is a joy knowing you and spending time with the both of you. Thank you for all the fun times we have had together and for being so supportive. /RYou are s wonderful couple and great roommates   With love. Enjoy and Celebrate!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elissa Sunshine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our Maid of Honor & Best Man,/RMay the road rise up to meet you./RMay the wind be always at your back./RMay the sun shine warm upon your face,/RThe rains fall soft upon your fields./RAnd until we meet again,/RMay God hold you in the palm of his hand./R             /R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lynn and Jerry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Let's put a return to Ireland on our Bucket List.../RHAPPY ANNIVERSARY! HAPPY BIRTHDAY!/RAnd many more HAPPY DAYS to follow./RYour friendship is our Irish Blessing....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lynn and Jerry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You can't pick your relatives, but with you, we hit the jackpot! You are the kindest and most generous people we know.  Happy special birthdays and Happy Anniversary.  We wish you good health and good times.  Hoping to be back here again to toast your 50th!!  Much love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gene and Lee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday & 40th anniversary!!!  We are so incredibly lucky to have you as our Mother /  Father / Mom Mom / Pop Pop. Our favorite thing is the love you show each and every one of us in everything you do. You are a shining example of the best way to live and love!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meredith, Matt, Liam, Gabriel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There is a camp in Zieglerville and Reeta is its name oh! We have celebrated many wonderful memories and one not so wonderful. Here's hoping that we can be together for more terrific numbers and events in the future. Much love to a great couple and terrific friends!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Betsy & Bob ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/RTogether in Paris, a day trip to Normandy, driven by a guide/friend, a stop for Gas on the way back, Diesel? Oh NO, regular…putt, putt, putt to a dead stop at the Arc de Triomphe !!! Congratulations. All our love, Cathy & Bob]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cathy & Bob Lipshutz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We've had so much fun together over the years. An evening with Carol and Rafe is always full of laughs. Our boat trips were memorable, to say the least.Thanks for all the good times. We love you and value your friendship./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Judy and Jerry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One last thought, Rafe give Carol the remote for 2 days a week!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Art, Remote Fairness Advocate]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Having known Carol since kindergarten and Rafe since he was smart enough to marry her, one thing has become evident:  really good friends remember your life stories and share chocolate chip cookies.  We look forward to sharing many more.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With love,  Lee and Frannie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[First,happy anniversary and happy birthday to two very special people. We consider ourselves very lucky to have you in our lives. Your selfless ways mean so much to our entire family. Love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Janet and Peter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amazing couple and so sweet no matter what hour or day it is they are always available to talk and help. God richly bless them for more healty life and more years to come. Love you much. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Britta Darkwa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing we like most about Carol and Rafe is their love for family and friends.  They give so much to help others and to bring family together.  And they have successfully passed along the same set of values to their children and grandchildren.  With lots of love...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barry, Diana and Hannah Glassman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So hard to pick just one great thing to say about Aunt Carol and Uncle Rafe.  We love so many things they do, but most of all we love that they’re always there when their loved-ones need them.  Wishing you a wonderful anniversary and many, many more.  With much love….]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marc, Kim, Sara & Matthew]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[How to find just one thing to write about two people that are so special to me...Aunt Carol and Uncle Rafe have been a part of my life since I was born. I love them as if they were my own parents. Hard to find the right words to sum up a lifetime of wonderful memories. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mindy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations!  There are so many memories that I do not think a single one stands out.  You are the heart of our family and we are lucky and blessed to have you in our lives.   We love you very much./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve, Beth, Ali, and Joel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary!  Thank you for always being there for us.  Thanks to you, every year on the first Saturday of Passover, my mom is smiling.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Larry, Vicki, Sam and Josh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love the relationship you have created with your grandchildren. It is a source of love and joy in all of our lives. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kyle (Lissack)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love the time we get to spend together as a family. Our times together are some of my fondest memories and they are for our kids as well. Thank you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kyle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have always been puzzled about why dad is the only one in our family who can actually get a tan. Is he really our father?  Just sayin...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anonymous ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite memories is when Dad told me meat doesn't have an expiration date.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anonymous]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that every time Marlies and I go away, our kids are super excited that they get to spend the week with the 2 of you instead of us!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kyle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I cherish the family time we spend together at random Sunday brunches and surprise weeknight dinners at our house. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kyle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I loved it that time dad asked me to reschedule my wedding because he had other plans that day. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Unknown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that whenever I am wrestling with a big or difficult problem, I can always turn to  Pop-Pop and he will know the answer,  whether or not he knows anything about the subject matter.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Impressed in Philadelphia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whenever anyone calls our home in Philadelphia and gets our voicemail, they have no idea about all of the fights that occurred while trying to record that outgoing message!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can thank my mom for my love of chocolate, and my dad for me feeling like i am always right... and faking it if I know I'm not! :-)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I loved our weekends on the boat, especially Dad's Miss Goody Two Shoes stories on the drive down to Great Oak Landing.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Meredith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love going to Mohonk with Mom Mom and Pop Pop...And I love their Passover seder because I get to stay up late, late, late!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Liam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love Mom Mom and Pop Pop and their snack cabinet full of gummies!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xxoo, Liam & Gabriel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love when Pop Pop watches television because it's loud enough that we can listen to our favorite shows (or MSNBC) from any room in the house.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Liam & Gabriel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Saaaandwiiich!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xxoo, Meredith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ah do...love Mom Mom Pop Pop!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xxoo, Gabriel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom, Remember when you were all dressed up, ready to go out, and covered with a splattering of whipped cream? Thank you for laughing and not getting mad at me.  I love you for that and so many other reasons.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, Meredith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Only the best dad in the world would wake me up every morning by rubbing my feet.  I love you for that and so many other reasons.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, Meredith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love going to Sixers games.  I love going to Mohonk.  And I love our trips to Miami.  Thank you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love it when you take us out to dinner and a play.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how you used to always have chocolate with you when you would come visit.  Where did all the chocolate go?!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dixie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To this day, Miss Goodie Two Shoes visits us in our dreams!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dixie and Julia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love always seeing your smiling faces at our plays and recitals.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dixie and Julia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for always taking care of us when our parents go away or go out (even though we are a hassle.)  We haven't even burned down the house yet!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ian, Dixie, Julia and Cormac]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>