<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2644-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/13/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Michael Hoddick]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[25131 Ebony ln ]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Lomita]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[CA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[90717]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[purple]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[To Be Continued...]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Mustafa and Amber Hakami]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[ From Your Family!]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love you Amber!! Ethan and I will miss you! You guys be safe, work hard, and have fun. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Autumn and Ethan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am so honored to have been welcomed into your lives like family. It's not often we are lucky enough to be able to surround ourselves with people we truly love. Thailand changed our friendship and my life in the most beautiful ways. I am forever grateful. See you soon!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember that one time in Thailand when Amber had me ROLLING TITS with just her finger rolls in the infinity pool?! /R/RIn a PHUKET state of TRANCE?/R/RYou will always be my ride or die]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[And to think all those pipe rips and EDM sets between classes brought you to MEDICAL SCHOOL. I am so proud and immensely impressed at your tenacity towards your future. Make Amber happy and you will be the happiest man alive! She is incredible, cherish her. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From my darkest nights to my brightest days you both stood by my side always having my well being in mind. I love you and wish only the best for both of you. They say that "Friends come and go but FAMILY is forever". I am truly blessed to be able to call you my FAMILY. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mikey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There comes a time in life when you must venture away from the security of home and travel into the vast unknown. With each other by your sides nothing in this world can not be conquered. Love one another with every breath in your body and enjoy this life together. <3]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mikey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Stafalaphagus, you dirty bastard. Better enjoy paradise while you can Dr. Hakami ;). You wont even forget me cuz I still owe you money :D BWAHAHAH. I'll be waiting to kick your ass at Naruto when you get back. See you when I see you on the other side mang, it's been fun]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dang, it's Tony Dang]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To all the amazing nights had amongst friends and all the crazy days in Vegas... May it always snow where ever you guys are. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jason Sorto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Guys, remember to have fun. Don't forget to enjoy where you are. Most people don't get the opportunity to see the world like you are doing. When you look back at the time spent away, you'll see the changes in your character and be thankful for all you've experience.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Travis and Sheena]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Don't do anything I wouldn't do.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Travis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["I'm so sad that my little sister and brother are leaving, but I'm so excited for what's to come! Mustafa, you make us all so proud!!! Hurry up and become a doctor so you can spoil your wife and her best friend (me!!) love you both to bits!! XOXOXO"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Saraz Jahernia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What can i say other than thank u. You guys have treated me like family and always welcomed me with open arms. I'll never forget the great moments we shared and all the laughs we've had. I'm truly blessed to have you guys in my life. Luv u guys best wishes on ur journey]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andy Kim & Dodger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Stafa and Amber, /RGood luck on your new journey over in the the Caribbean, I know you're going to do great things over there! We'll miss you back here in Cali. Can't wait til you guys come back!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randy and Emily Ferguson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm seriously gonna miss you guys and can't wait to visit you soon!  /R/RI wish you both all the health, happiness, luck and adventure on the journey that awaits you :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Zlatan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amber,/RI'm so happy to see you off on your new adventure. Always know that I will be there for you, no matter what ocean or land lies between us.  /RMustafa, /RI am proud of you for chasing your dream to be a surgeon. Can't wait to visit & explore the island with you two]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kaitlin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Mustafa and Amber,/R/RI hope the best for you two with your new endeavors! Mustafa, I hope you're happy with your new school and professors! Amber, I hope whatever you do makes you happy! I'll miss you guys! Have a great time! You are going to love it all!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Daniel Kato ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wish you guys all the luck on your new adventure /RHope all the best for both of you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ismael and rosa parra ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whats up! We can't believe that you two are on this crazy adventure. The greater the sacrifice, the greater the reward. Enjoy your time out there and have fun during your quest. We can't wait to hear your stories of experience!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Justin & Vanessa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So proud of you both on making this journey together. I can't wait to come visit and have some fun adventures. I love you both and cannot wait to see what the future holds for you...well other than Stafa working hard and Amber spending all that money. Bon Voyage! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christina Phillipis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To my amazing BFFs, Amber and Stafa. Words can't explain how much I love you two, admire the both of you, and am going to miss you. Stafa, since middle school you've always been there for me. I am so lucky to have someone like you, aka science but cool nerd, in my life!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[(Not done! Next card -Ann)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're going to do great in med school. No doubt about it. And Boo, I am so blessed to have you! I can't even begin to say how amazing you are!! Don't change a thing! I'll miss our walks and dinners! But before we know it, we'll be together again soon <3 (damn word limi]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[<3 Anna-banana Boo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I would like to wish you both the best of luck and happiness while you continue your epic journey together. You two are an inspiration to myself and others that true love exists and that we can all be happy. Keep ur eye open Stafa because I'm gonna get my chest punches!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bronson Greenwood]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have always told you Mustafa, that you are one LUCKY man! As it turns out Amber, you were lucky too. You were both blessed to have found each other. Enjoy life's journey and everything it has to offer. Have fun, but watch out for those Caribbean Rum Punch's!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lots of love, Cindy ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mustafa and Amber,/RI wish you both the best of luck on your new journey. Thank you for always being so welcoming to me. The group will not be the same without you two. I wish we had more time with you guys. Enjoy this new chapter & we will all be here when you get back!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Enrique Lopez]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amber and Mustafa,/R/RI am so proud and happy for you two.  This will be a new chapter in your life and it was well desrverved.  I already miss you guys!  We had a lot of fun times, and there will be more to come.  Good Luck out there and I'll see you in Dominica! <3]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Home is where the love of your life is."/RSo even though we'll all miss you guys, you'll be together, entering an exciting new phase of your lives. I'm so happy for both of you! /RAnd this isn't goodbye, its simply see you later...which always promises to be fun! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With love, J Hooks]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So sad to see you guys go after we just get back, but I'm excited for you at the same time.Make the most out of this and come back with tons of stories. HAVE A SAFE TRIP!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paul]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I don't have decades of memories with you two, like most of the people in this box do, but the memories I do have of you two will leave life-lasting impressions.  I will never forget how welcoming and warm you two have always been towards me. We will all miss you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Visit Soon! - Jessica Harris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I wish you both the best on your awesome new adventure. We'll miss you mofo's but change is always good. It's all about the journey!/R/R"May the wind always be at your back and the sun upon your face. And may the wings of destiny carry you aloft to dance with the stars."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alan Tran]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Amber and Mustafa,/RLove will conquer all. Be passionate and caring and everything will fall into place. I know both of you know this already but do not forget how you got here. I will miss you both so much and I hope to come visit you sooner than later! Love you!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jonathan Yi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We will truly miss you guys! I know we partied pretty hard together and we even had that "deep talk" about life and religion and to be honest, I really like that we shared that moment because it really hit home with me. Friends forever and ever! Love you guys!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aaron Son]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mustafa you're about to embark on an adventure of your lifetime. Whenever you start to doubt yourself remember all the people you left back home who all believe in you. I'll always be here for you to make sure you're not a bastard and don't get fat. lol]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shane Shahabi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amber these next couple years will be the foundation of what future you guys will have together. I want to thank you for everything you've done for my buddy. He truly does it all for you and will need you now more than ever. Please take care of him for me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shane Shahabi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Change is never easy for anyone. But when two people love each other, they can overcome any obstacles. I know there is nothing you guys can't figure out together. When you're feeling lonely, remember that you have each other and all of us back home love you guys so much]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shane Shahabi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The adventure has now begun, what exciting time! When you start to feel lonely or homesick, remember that at least your not stuck in Sri Lanka drinking white chai. We love you and wish you all the happiness in this new chapter. Home is where you both are. Xoxoxo ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Angela & Mohammad Haider]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ I am going to really miss the GoT nights and epic ragers; life will not be the same without you two. Finally I can catch up on sleep since Stafa can't call me at sunrise. I thank God everyday for bringing you two into my life and I wish you the best on this journey.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joshua Sacerio]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mustafa I remeber one of the first memories I have of you: We were getting ready for a rave at the Kato house & you were trying to dress as Cupid but resembled more of a fairy. It's been a blast working with you for so many years and you will definitely be missed dude!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin Curtis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Life is full of great adventures and both of you are about to embark on a brand new one. Good luck from all of us! Enjoy your new adventure and keep the mosquito net close.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amber it was great getting to know you over these last couple years. You have always been so nice & sincere to me. We have had many great memories at shows, Vegas trips & hanging out at your house. I hope you have an amazing adventure! You guys will not be forgotten :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin Curtis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["The world is not a pleasant place to be without someone to hold and be held by." -Nikki Giovanni-  Make sure to always say I love you after an argument, hold hands as often as you can. laugh and cry together. Life is an adventure enjoy it/R ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kenn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amber and Mustafa, /RI wish you both nothing but the best in your new life. Know that so many hearts will be broken when you two leave, especially mine :( I genuinely hope that you both find all the happiness you both deserve. Love you guys!/R/RXOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sara Kato]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mustafa, /RYour ambition and drive inspires all of us and I am so proud of you for working hard to make your dreams a reality. Enjoy this amazing experience and know that all of us here support you. You'll always be family to me. Love you Moo! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sara J. Kato]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Those times where Amber and I wanted to get to the next level and Stafa and Andy would give a look of "doom!" and even though they knew it was trouble we do it anyway! haha Some of the best times with you two. Lots of LOVE sent on your next chapter. Missing you both XoX]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chopsticks aka Wendy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The other time in Vegas when Stafa found out he was accepted and we were worried about how you were getting your couch out there! haha]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[W]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Stafa, thanks for always being inspiring and encouraging about school. You picked me up. Amber I wanna see abs and a killer tan. Love you both. Bye Felicia]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[W]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Amber & Mustafa,/R      I wish you both all the best with this next part of your lives and hope you come back with some kick ass stories and a great tan! I don't believe this is good bye so i will say until next time! /R/RBest Wishes!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jonathan Lim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mustafa & Amber/R/RBest of luck on your new adventure together. I wish you both love and happiness. Keep in touch and have a great summer!!!/R/RPS: Ménage à trois]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tony Farrokh-Siar]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Enjoy the world and take in what it has to offer. Never fear what lies ahead, rather have what lies ahead fear you for you cannot be stopped. On those days that you feel like you just don't want to do it anymore, look at each other and realize this is the reason why.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your most awesome Roommate. :)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[For now my heart is heavy, and my eyes filled with tears. For now is not forever and I look forward to seeing you two soon. I will forever hold your relationships in my heart and I will never forget the compassion you have shown me. I Love you both, Forever Family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Vermont Villa Care Taker :) MDH]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[purple]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>