<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2645-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/13/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Mollie Egginton]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[6236 Lake View Drive]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[PO Box 2155]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Pocono Pines]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[18350]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 60th Birthday!!!!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Colleen Durkin Lapowsky]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Messages from your family & friends]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Mom! You are the perfect example of how to be a mother, daughter, Grammy and friend. Thank you for being mine. We are so lucky to have you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love You, Mollie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday, Colleen! /RWe hope that you are having a beautiful 60th Birthday surrounded by family and friends! I remember you as a great MSJA " little sister" and Jerry remembers you as a fun prom date! Much happiness today and always! Love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate & Jerry Hathaway]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[60: it's about time, Colleen!/RThis is the decade when our little boys will become teenagers. Haha; won't it be fun to watch Mollie and Pete cope with those challenges? I so enjoy being a Co-Grandmother with you, the very effervescent,totally fabulous Colleen D./RLapowsky]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With Love and Admiration from Susan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[60 Years Old! A Milestone Birthday!/ROur friendship has seen countless milestones too/RMany marked with much laughter, a few tears, and always great love/RToday I celebrate the gift of our friendship and remember the incredible impact you've had in my life./RHappy Birthday]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Forever with love,  Lizzie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Col,/RYou've been so many things to me, my Leenie, my friend and mentor. We shared haircuts, vacations, hand-me down-clothes, my first joint, childhood memories, chicken pox, Grammy and Papa,  fireplace stage plays.. Mostly, we share love. /R Wishin you a beautiful day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy # 60 my Leenie!  Love, Erin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Phone rings, door chimes, in comes... another Birthday! Sending you love from Mykonos,wishing you a fabulous birthday, surrounded by the love of your friends & family. You're a special lady, sharing her time & talents, w/a little "good old broad" mixed in ;-) xoxo Babe"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy Babe Robinson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[" ...my mind is gushing with so many memories and moments spent together...my one wish for the future is that I'll always have the beautiful friendship we've shared."/RCol, you wrote this in my yearbook 42 years ago and you have  been a blessing in my life ever since!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I love you, Miss Twilly!  Carole]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Coll-Coll:/RHappy 60th!  You are truly an inspiration to me with the way in which you live your life.  You are one of the most uplifting, positive, and caring human beings I have ever known.  Happy Birthday to you and *MANY MOOOOOOORE!!!!*/RLove,/RPete]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pete]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[HAPPY 60th, COLLEEN!/RWhile it may be startling to comprehend that you now qualify for a Senior Discount at certain retail establishments, comfort yourself with the fact that you are still a gorgeous babe who radiates sizzle and flair. Love and admire you, girl!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Diane Bones]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[THE REASONS WHY I LOVE U SO MUCH ARE MANY: U ARE GENEROUS,  LOVING,  CARING, SMART,  FUNNY, INSIGHTFUL, TENDER YET STRONG &SUPPORTIVE.  I CAN ALWAYS COUNT ON U FOR ANYTHING.  I AM PROUD AND HONORED TO CALL U MY FRIEND, AND I BRAG ABOUT IT! THANK U FOR ENRICHING MY LIFE]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[CHIP BEHR]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Colleen I wish you the best day ever.Your friendship has meant so much to me in my life.Not many people get to say they have been friends for 46 years. It's a friendship of unconditional love. Thank you for being my friend and have a Happy Birthday. I LOVE YOU]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alison]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["As I was going up Pippen Hill,/RPippen Hill was dirty./RThere I met a pretty miss/RAnd she dropt me a curtsey./R/RLittle miss, pretty miss,/RBlessings light upon you!/RIf I had half a crown a day,/RI'd spend it gladly on you."/R/RI love you more!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sidney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You hold a very special place in my heart. Every time we speak I feel love and friendship. You are so funny and full of joy!!! Have a wonderful Birthday my dear friend.../RLove...XOXO/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary MacAvoy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My life is much fuller with you in it. I know we don't see each other as often as we'd like, but you are in my thoughts every day.  I wish you the happiest of birthdays and brightest tomorrow's my sister and best friend all these years. Love, love, and big smooches!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday to a truly amazing woman! You've done so much for others in your life, myself included, and deserve all of the love and attention you can handle on your special day! I miss you and can never thank you enough for all you've done./R/RAll my love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dan McGinly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[CD/RGreat memories of crazy circumstances is no illusion...crazy memories of great circumstances is not imaginary...faded memories of life's best is a joy always...Wishing you never let reality intrude upon a perfect revery...take it to the limit one more time...Bobby]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bobby B.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My dearest Colleen,/RHappiest of all to you and yours. Your a blessing to all of us./RLove you, /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David and Teresa Borisoff]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Colleen!!! We loved seeing you, thanks for coming to the party. Hope you have an awesome day! /RLove you!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Peter McDonald Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 60th Mom, /R/RThank you for everything that you do for me day in and day out. I am so grateful for the love and guidance that you constantly show me (also the occasional cash). Thank you for always being there and for molding me into the man I am today. I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tim]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can't think of anyone who loves more deeply, gives more thoroughly, and works more diligently to make other people feel special than you. I'm so lucky to see the example you've set and to have your comforting, compassionate presence in my life. I love you more! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Issie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[CollColl,  There are So many things about you that I love.. Your Face... Your Laugh... Your Boobs../Rto name a few... But it is your Heart I love the most. You have an endless capacity to love. And I find that so refreshing and comforting in this crazy world!/RLove you x]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday xox Chris McDonald ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the BEST godmother.  I love you./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[cece]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wishing you a very happy birthday.  Thank you for your energy, your enthusiasm, your kindness and your love.  We are all so lucky to have you in our lives. XOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meg (Chianese!) Durkin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Coll Coll!!  You are really nice and fun and I always have a really great time with you! I love you to the moon and back!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mollie the third ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[you're a great actress and singer!!! I love you!! HAPPY BIRTHDAY!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[claire durkin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You epitomize unconditional love.  How fortunate we all are to have you in our lives.  And... I smile because you are my sister and I laugh because there is nothing you can do about it!  Happy 60th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ted]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hey Pretty Lady! Have a wonderful birthday! Hope to see you soon.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Helene Susanin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Colleen!/R/RI won't be able to top last year's message so I won't even try. I just want to let you know that you're extremely loved by me and my family. We wish you many years of happiness./R/RI love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Colleen,/RHope you have a great celebration. We are thinking of you. Happy birthday!! /RLove,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellen, John and Sam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wow! It's hard to comprehend it. You're sixty years old. What a blessing for me to have witnessed fifty four of them. We've been though so, so much you and I.  You are an amazing person whom I'm proud to call my sister. /RI Love You!!!/RHappy Birthday Colleen!!!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'll always keep in mind laboring on draft after draft of La Salle's entrance essay under your attentive guidance, and obliging final judgement. Happy birthday, Aunt Colleen, and thank you for everything]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The summer of 1955 at 919 Electric Street was spent mostly in anticipation of Colleen's arrival.Lots of anxiety, because she was to be Frank and Marian's first grandchild, and Nana and Pop's first great grandchild.  Since the day she was born, she got lots of attention ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jane and Hank]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Colleen,/RHappy happy 60th birthday! You radiate such positivity and light, and I hope you feel all those things back on your special day. I feel so blessed to be part of such a special and loving family, made possible such an amazing woman! Enjoy your beautiful day]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rosie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When she was a youngster, we would drag her along on errands.  One day (in the days before seat belts) she was on the front seat between Hank and me.   At the corner of Wyoming and Greenridge Streets, Hank had to stop suddenly and baby C bounced off the windshield, and ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jane and Hank]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[within minutes had a gooseegg on her forehead.  After the primary grades, she and Michael would visit Arlington for a vacation.  It would take all of two days, and she would have the entire child population of 33rd Rd involved in her latest theatrical production. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jane and Hank]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Clothes lines, bed spreads, lawn furniture, all became props.  All great!  We have loved her always, and always will.  Jane and Hank]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jane and Hank]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sixty years is a long time. But, you have put it to great use. You give more love than anyone I know and are loved by everyone around you, including me. You are the best thing that has happened in my life. I love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday!! You have been such a rock for me throughout my entire life and an inspiration to better myself while helping those around me. We never fail to laugh when we're together, or cry at a Hallmark movie! I hope you have an amazing birthday. I love you Coll!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lucy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Grammy! I love you. You are great. I like having sleepovers with you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Pete ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Grammy, you're the best! I like having sleepovers and I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Charlie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your love, and color palette, fill up every room you're in and every heart you've touched. /RHappy Birthday!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Cheers to Sixty Colleen!/RFor all we have been through, I will always be thankful for how I learned the importance of being there for your family, no matter what, from all that you have done for yours... and yet I will still always love grey. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[maryelizabeth ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Because you are Exemplary,/Ryou showed me what it means to be a friend, to love selflessly & to keep ALL of my family close, you taught me to see through the lens of positivity,/Rbecause of the wonderful person you are, /RI will always look to up to you./RHappy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Caitlin and Izabelle xo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Coll, It's hard to put into a sentiment in a box what you mean to me. You are the hinge that holds our family together. You are the mother, the daughter the sister. The one who led us all by example. You're what means home for me.  Happy Birthday.  I love you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meggy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Coll! /RI will never be able to thank you enough for all that you've done for me. So this year is dedicated to you. A new regime, because you taught me that it's possible./R/Rthank you, I love you, and happy birthday.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Max]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[HB Coll.  I like my favorite things at Coll's. My basement and Pollyanna and train pictures.  Well thanks. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike (aka Mickey Higgins)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[hot-pink]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>