<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2653-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/14/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Bridget Thornton]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[35 Park Drive]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[Apartment 7]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Boston]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[MA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[02215]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 60th Birthday, Paul!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Paul Thornton]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love, your family and friends]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're the best dad a girl could ask for. You're my hero and my role model. I wouldn't be where I am today without you, so thank you for teaching me that it's the small things in life that mean the most and to live everyday to the fullest. "Let's go fishing!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love always, Bridget]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paulie, They threw away the mold after you were made. Glad Jake and Nona did not quit after Peter. You have added a unique layer to all of our lives for which we are richer in experiences with the law, medicine and  living life to the fullest. Love, Joe]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Thornton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing that I think of when PT's name is mentioned is his generosity. He's a 'big' man with an even bigger heart.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Roy St.Clair]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Who knew 45 years ago when I ripped your denim shirt at Cheverus and you wanted to punch me that it would be the beginning of a life long friendship?  College, careers,marriages,kids,illnesses the best of times the worst of times but the best part has been the laughter.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dennis Gears Honorary Brother]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The thing I like most about Paul is how uncompetitive he is about golf and how willing he is to concede strokes to his friends like Dennis and Mag. I also love how patient and thoughtful he is with others who have a different political, philosphical or religious view . ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[from his buddy Jed]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The thing we liked most about Paul was the gentleness and tenderness that he showed in accommodating all our many and different desires and needs. Thank you Paul!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Jusuits of Cheverus]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love the PASSION you have for your family and friends and life!!!!/RHappy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Gears]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always tell it like it is and never fail to  make me laugh!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mindy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love that he is such a great guy and honestly, one of the most generous people that we know. Paul's sense of humor and ready smile make you happy when you see him.  We are fortunate to count him as a friend and neighbor on Long Island.  xo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Zoeth and Karen Rich]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My little brother turning 60...who would have believed he survived....being lock in the shower room @ Commonwealth while his brothers entertained.....holding empty GIQ'S @ Evergreen while  a brother and Foley got ready for the ARMORY....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brother Mike]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[continue from PG1/Rthat early childhood development was the basis for the person he his today/Rlove ya brother]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brother Mike]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A Very Happy 60, Paul! Thanks for being such a role model for Dennis all of these years -  it has caused me many moments of questioning myself :-) May the road ahead be long and winding with good surprises at every bend. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda Trenholm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Paul!  We hope that you have an awesome day!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda and John]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[happy  birthday   paulie!!!  I hope  you and Roger have  a   good     day!!!   Ilove   you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Modakin (molly)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Uncle Paul-/R You are one of the most genuine people I know. Your smile and positivity are contagious! I am so lucky to have such an amazing uncle./RHope you have the happiest of birthdays!/RXoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul, Golly gee good buddy, what's not to like about you? So, as we all know well, when your friends stop giving you shit, you most likely don't have any friends left. Have you had any shit lately Paul? No? Good news! I'm here to be of service. Love u/RMichael McGonigle]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael McGonigle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Paul! It has been a long time and a lot of fun. You should be very proud of the way you have lived your life!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Barber]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul, you are a very giving person. I love that most about you.  That and your rapier wit.  Laughter and love are the best medicine for living and you bring that to us daily!  Happy 60th!  Ouch! Can you say Geritol?  Whatever happened to that anyway?  Love you!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lis, Phil and Jenna]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your genuine greeting. Every time I see you, you have a way of making me feel good about me. Thanks Paul]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paulie....happy b-day! You and I have been living the dream all these years, but no need to stop now! I'm thinking it's time to keep living, laughing and loving....?! Like me, you're not as good as you once were, but I'm guessing you're still good once a month or so!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Thornton Harris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Let us know when and where the Thornton party is.......I'm told you're buying for all the Thornton's except for brother Michael?! The big "60"....hard to believe that you haven't been shot by someone by now!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paulie has a great sense of humor.....never saw an adult beverage he didn't like and cheats at golf.... all the best Cous!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hoggie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One would think a girl would be exceedingly blessed to have 6 brothers...and I am...but as it turns out I actually have another...thanks for being the 7th! Happy 60th Paulie and many, many more. I love you! Long May You Run!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Annie D..]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My second dad./Rthank you for  everything you did 4 me, you teach me how to be a better person the love that you always give me, but thanks to you and your family make me feel like home,  Love u very much and i miss you alot wish very more bdays hope 2 see you soon]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your adopted son Gabriel Mateus ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have unconditional love for family and friends and you have such a big heart! You are a true beauty Paulie! We love you so much!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ashley & JpIV]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I also wanted 2 tell you thnx for openning the doors to your house to a person that you didnt know, i am very gratefull 4 that and the oportunity to learn from a another culture, i can thank you all mi life 4 that youre a great example of a great man and great person ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love u with all my heart Gabe Mateu]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am sure I am not alone in this sentiment. I love Paul's big and genuine smile! He has a way of making your day better with it!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rachael]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 60th Paul! Great Guy! Great Sense of Humor and one of the funniest people I have ever met. And by the way, did you ever pick your suit up at the cleaners? (UNH 1974)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Doaneza]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Let's see...one thing I like about you most Paul....hmmm lets see....well, hmmm still thinking, Jesus something should come to me, god I have been your friend for over 45 years, well you blamed me for breaking your dads car door when it was Raymond. Still love you Paul!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peter Martin...I am still thinking!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Blow Me]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Blow Me]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[where's the ramp]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[sookie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul is the most generous person I know, constantly giving to those who need; he's a good role model for us all]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[lortie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You and Bridget have the most beautiful father daughter relationship I have ever witnessed! Thanks for always sending a bit of that love my way too. It made my four years that much richer. Keep wearing that WWLAX jacket! Love you to pieces!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mads ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paulie,/RWho could have possibly guessed back in Richardson, Texas that our lives would have taken the turns they did. We've shared a lot, here's to sharing a lot more, but from now on just the good stuff. Love you and welcome to the club.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for being you! Don't ever stop! xxx]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mariah ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul Best Guy EVER ! Generous, kind and loyal. A true friend . Very Best wishes.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mick]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Podican! May your love for Mia Tia's grow stronger with each year, cheers!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike H.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul was" The Best Man" at my wedding 37 years ago. I know to this day he would still be there for me and my family for anything we ever needed,and for that we love him.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Kathy Sparta and Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your attitude and approach to life are qualities to be admired! Having you at our lacrosse games was more important to us than you'll ever know and it helped that your yelling always made us run faster! Never lose your positive outlook to life! Best wishes & Happy 60th!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chrissy Norberg #18]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul is one of the kindest and most thoughtful people I know. He is always there to support everyone else in their time of need. Since being diagnosed with cancer in May, I can count on Paul to give me a hug and words of encouragement every time I see him. Love you Paul]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shirley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you Paul for your generous support of my mission to support our troops and for matching funds when  goals  and postage was needed to complete a campaign. Count me among your biggest fans. I love you too!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brenda Reimels]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You give my whole family a kiss and a hug whenever you see us! We love you, Paulie!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lynn, Gabe, Jameson & Vivy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul, you've been my brother for 46 crazy good years. You're dependable, generous, and honest. The growing-up stories at Cheverus are legendary, a broken window or car door littering our wake. But, the bond is spiritual and it endures. Thank you. Love, Peace & Light...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Raymond!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Piggy, Happy birthday to a great friend and a great guy. BOOB!!, Hopefully we are in for several more years together]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom Holden and Mary]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The love of my life, my best friend, my true north..... TF143 /RHappy Birthday]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy Hardy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that Uncle Paul is "Uncle Paul" to all my friends and that he puts family first and lives everyday to the fullest.  Plus he is funny, not like a clown, just amusing.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt Thornton Sr.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your generosity knows no bounds and often times goes unaccredited but always greatly appreciated.  It is wonderful to see such a great trait passed down to Jake & Bridge.../R/RDuff also really likes the back scratches!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brett Beaurivage]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Paul!  Thank you for always putting a smile on my face!  Thanks for the great hugs and most of all, thank you for the unconditional friendship!  My world is a better place because we are friends!  All the best, God Bless.../RVin Ciampi]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vince Ciampi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul lights up any room with his smile and happy personality. He is such a charismatic, generous man and lots of fun to be around. Happiest of birthdays to you Paul!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lisa and mike yorke]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I like most is you're back!  You slipped away, as some of us did, but it's great to have you back in town. Your endless caring and generosity is a boon to the community. Thank you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Spinner & Sarah. ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Paul!/R/RWe hope that you have an amazing day.  Thank you for being the great person that you are :)  It would be great to see you sometime this summer so we will have to get that figured out with Jake./R/R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anna & Murphy (aka Duff)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY !!!!!!!!!!!/R/RYOU ARE THE BEST XO MOJO & FRED/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mojo & Fred]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite thing about Paul would be the way he makes me laugh. We can never have too much laughter.Thank you and a very Happy birthday! Love you, Da]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Martin family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you for your love of family, your smile and laughter, your sincerity and sensitivity and your great big hugs./R/RHappy Birthday, Winter Friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, Leah ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Peter, Peter, where is the beer Peter? One found memory with you and Peter Sparta heading to Augusta for a Cheverus BB playoff game. Thanks for always being there my good friend! Happy Birthday and may we share many more! Love ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[B]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Paul!!/RI'm thankful to have had the opportunity to work for you.  You were ALWAYS very generous and good for a few laughs.  I still don't believe no one has more fun than you. Your blessed, keep enjoying it. Love ya. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura Rendell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Favorite things about Paul in under 270 characters? Damn ok I guess that time he and dad taxied across Bermuda for swizzle, or all the Beyoncé, boat adventures, that there's never a dull moment! Love you Pauly!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[mae ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm happy for all your successes, but most of all I'm happy your my friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Howie Chadbourne ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He Is one great all around finest kinda guy positive attitude, caring , loving, a million dollar smile  a true friend . /RDon't go changing ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lovely Lorinda ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Paulie!/RI will never forget the first time we met at Sugarloaf when Peter Martin introduced us. We've had lots of fun and laughs. You have touched the hearts of so many with your smile and genuine kindness. I love you Paulie!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cal]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are so many things to love and admire about you, Paul! /RYou have an amazing connection with your children, grandchildren, and loving life partner, Nancy. You have a way of making your friends feel special just by your big smile and heartfelt hugs. Love you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cheers to your 60th! Melissa F.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul,/RFrom Commonwealth Drive to here! But how in the hell did we get this old?? Welcome to "The Club". Happy Birthday!!!           ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ron]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Paul! Thank you for all the fun, adventures and support over the years. I have a lot of uncles but I only have one Paul! (Don't tell them I said that) love you!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[LJ ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am so lucky to have you in my life Paulie.  You've always treated me like part of the family, glasses of wine and steak diners will only be best when you're grilling! Love you so much, thanks for being like another father, you truly are an amazing man! Lots of love, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Xoxo- Jenner ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are such a generous and kind person.   Thank you for your constant support on the lax field and for raising such a fantastic daughter! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Abbie Sherwin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like about Paul are his GREAT greeting hugs.  No matter where we run into each other, I can always expect a "Hey, Sweetie" to brighten the day. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allie Donovan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're a good man Paul and you've always been a great one to me, wishing you the happiest of birthdays!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Buoy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Truly a man for all seasons...equally at home at the Governors mansion as at Skee's Chevrolet! /R Paulie, you are a true friend, a/Rloving and caring father & spouse & super-proud grandparent!!  60 is the new 40 so  best is ahead of you! Keep on smilin'/R/R /R/R/R/R/R/R/R/R/R/R/R/R/R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[#steelerfan   #winterfriend]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're the man! Wheaton lacrosse just wouldn't have been the same without you.  Happy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[C. Grant (& the rest of the Grants)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Well, now is a better time than any to tell you....I'm pregnant. No, but seriously, you are an incredible role model and have raised a ridiculously amazing daughter. We are all very lucky to have you and I am very grateful to be even a small part of your family! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dave "The Wave" Wadsworth]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>