<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2661-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/16/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Lara Mathews]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[171 Pemaquid Trail]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[New Harbor]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[ME]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[04554-4610]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDEX_FEDEX2DAY]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[50 Years and Fabulous!!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Lois and Dave]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary!  Love, Lara]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember Lara's colic from the Malden apartment days when I would drop in and keep Lois company (Dave would be at a law school evening class) while she tried to get Lara calmed down and asleep. We (Lois and me) would dish for hours on end. Good times.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob Bernstein]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My first week in New York City I'll never forget Lois and Dave taking me to the Monkey Bar!  My first of many NYC dining experiences....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Parmentier]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have loved our annual "grandparents day" luncheon at Chadwicks - and hope to continue it in some form, even as the girls get older! Joel and I loved our dinner at your beautiful home in Maine. You have a special place in our hearts.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Papke Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always love seeing you both at all the ACDS events.  And don't forget the performances at Classika camp.  It's hard to believe we've been watching Alex, Bryan, Katie and Kirsten for all these years.  Congratulations on your 50th.  Someday we'll get together in Maine.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Diane Johnson and family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on 50 years and we are thrilled to have been part of your journey. Travels from Maui to Captiva to Vancouver. Dancing, tea, Loehmans, beach, bad golf, Fiesta Bowl, children and grandchildren, it has been great. We wish you many more years of happiness!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Treasured friendship Mark & Vanda ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We do share wonderful memories of 5th and 6th grade tween emotions and great fun at T Ball games many years ago. Congradulations, and now on to 75.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Helen and John Mertz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We became close friends in 1978 when Los and Dave moved to Fosbak Dr.  in Vienna. Our children brought us together. Lots of fun with t-ball and softball games and parties. We have  stayed close in spite of geography./RWish we could be there with you./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathi and Ed Walsh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It was February 22, 1969, and we were in your home in Malden, MA. watching the Johnny Carson show. We were laughing so hard, that your mother broke her water. It was a raging blizzard outside that night and my car was able to get your Mom to the hosp. and Lara was born.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[LARRY BADER]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lois and Dave,/RHappy 50th!  Our memory is of you moving on to the Oval.  You became a part of the family immediately and you always will be. Love laughing and talking politics with you!/RAll the best]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Denis and Sara Dwyer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[This couple is a rare find! I I never knew the day I laid eyes on them They would end up being 2 of the most amazing people I've come across on this planet ! The pleasure is all mine ! Cheers to there incredible years together and cheers to/RMany more unforgettable times]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda Johnson.  The Johnson Family ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[First in business then as neighbors you have shared the grace, humor and acceptance that support your own family.  We are so glad that you moved to the Oval, and now to have your lovely granddaughters here.  Love and best wishes from our family to yours.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom and Kathy Stenzel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Shot Blocked by Spud Webb/RDave and Lois are the best/RFifty years true love!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ilga & Kyle Parmentier]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary Lois and Dave! So many fond memories of you both during the UCLA years....fun times going home with Lara on the weekends and great Mom's and Dad's weekends together at school. The best to you from my parents as well - what a wonderful occasion!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Diane Kull]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lois & Dave - We adore your fabulous family, a creation from your 50 years of marriage. Lara is one of my dearest friends, and I know she is an absolute reflection of the two of you. Intelligence, glamour, wit and dedication to family & friends. Congratulations!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Danna and Brad Leahy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You were delightful neighbors the moment you moved next door. What makes you special is your enthusiasm for life and your sensitivity to the world around you. We remember our shared sadness over the loss of favorite dogs. Thankfully you are still part of our lives.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ann and Harry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary to you!  Cheers to many more years of happiness ahead. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Carrie and Mike Moore]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[November 2004, I had my first Thanksgiving dinner and it was at Lois and David's house. My parents were visiting, or checking us up since I just moved here. They were both very impressed by the warm and comfy house, and still talk about how yummy the turkey was. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tina Wang]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have a memory of sitting in the Bear's Den at U.M.O. trying to sell Lois on the glories of my friend,"Bernie." She worried about his wild side and I portraited him as a true gentleman. Both descriptions of him were true; the wildness in Lois said yes!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeano]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We've shared our wedding days and our children's weddings. MaZELL Tov.  We were meant to be together... Boston and now Florida and lots of fond memories from our youth in Orono, Bangor and Lewiston. Let's make more happy memories! May we celebrate our 75th together. LO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tanya and Greg ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Being your youngest cousin, I have known you as a couple since the age of 16. You still look marvelous and know how to live life to the fullest. It's truly special to be  able to share in this wonderful event with you in beautiful Maine (woods and water). /RCongrats, Luv]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Avi and Ellen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lara,/R/ROn behalf of my mother and I, thank you so much for bringing these two wonderful people into our lives! I waited two years for Lois and so happy I did! Couldn't imagine my life without them now! Linda and Paula]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Purple Goose]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Dave & Lois are the couple we aspire to be. Clearly in love after all these years, they make marriage look easy. Fun to be around, sage advise, fashionable... with more than enough love to go around. Happy 50th Anniversary! Way to go!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Santucci Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We met Lois and David through B.&D. Nason in Westlake Village CA. You were wonderful to us "newbies"! Aimee adored Lois. Then you moved to NJ. Who would have thought that today we would still be in contact! Congrats on 50 years of marriage to a fantastic couple! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim & Mary Anne Carlson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What an amazing couple you are!  You love each other, you like each other, and you always have such fun together!  It has been my honor to witness and enjoy your incredible relationship, as well as your laughter!  A most Happy 50th Anniversary to two very dear friends!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary Kay and Bill Friend]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lois and Dave, /R/RI want to start of by thanking both of you for welcoming me and my kids to your family. You have always made me feel like part of yours, and honestly that means the world to me. I wish you only the best for this anniversary and the many more to come.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Analy Solis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We love Dave and Lois! Not only are they smart, passionate and lovely, but great friends and parents/grandparents. They are our role models. Enjoy this special day for you are special.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Denise and Bill Loveless]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom and Dad, You have touched and inspired so many with the life you have built together-with love, generosity, humor, and strength-and the foundation you built for your kids and grandkids. The love of your family and friends is testament to this.  (continued)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Lara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mom and Dad (continued),/RYou truly are at your best as a team.  Thank you a million times over for everything you have given me as a daughter, Dan and I as a couple, and our girls most of all./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All my love, Lara]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Nanny and Papa D,/RHappy fiftieth anniversary to my #relationshipgoals! Love you both so much and look forward to many more years of marriage with singing and laughter!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Alex]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite people,/RWhere do I start, you two always make me happy even when I feel like the world is coming to an end. You always find a way  to make me laugh.  I am so happy I get to see you so much because I honestly don't know what my life would be like without you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Katie :) (continued)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[That is why I hope you both have the best anniversary and life together! You guys are my role models. I love you both so much!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I love you, Katie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember the first time I met Dave.  He had flown to Washington to pack up Lara and take her to law school in California.  I drove them to the airport where Dave offered his hand and said, "Thanks for the ride, it was nice to meet you."/R"No problem" I replied, "I can"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[(Continued)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[walk you in."  After pleasantly repeating his goodbyes at the security checkpoint, the shuttle bus, and finally the gate, I'm convinced Dave thought I was going to get on the plane too.  And thus began a 23 year friendship and so much more with Lois and Dave.  "]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[(Continued)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When people learn that my inlaws live a couple miles away and we see them all the time, you can hear the sympathy in their voices.  But I'm quick to correct their mistake and tell them, "Oh no, I won the inlaw lottery!"  You see, I really did board the Bernstein plane ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[(Continued)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[twenty three years ago; and what a wonderful ride it has been.  I am blessed to have you in my life, Lara's, and Alex and Katie's.  Thank you for bringing so much joy and happiness to us all.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Dan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Where have the 50 years gone. Once we were all young and beautiful and full of fun.   "Oh, those were the days, my friend, we thought they would never end." What great memories we have of these fabulous people who have been our closest friends for these years.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Joel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lois and Dave, I remember the 1st time D brought L home, late 50s, early 60s. My twin Bob & myself, early teens, we were shy. Aloft sitting near the top of the stairs we were out of sight of the rare creature just below us in the living room. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gerry (to be continued)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Yes, we could hear all the voices and draw conclusions from a safe distance. D had brought home a college girl. We did venture a peek now and then. Yikes. She was a pretty, vivacious college girl at that. Did I say we were shy...?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Gerry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Everyone knows that Lois and Gail really like to dance … a lot. You’ve heard the saying “shop ‘til you drop” (which by the way they also like to do). Well, this is a story of “dance ‘til you drop.” In Providence, Rhode Island for Chris and Kerri Nason’s wedding, ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Parmentiers (continued)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(continued) Lois and Gail decided to dance, dance, dance the night away, together (since Michael and David do not share their wives’ dancing genes). When the evening ended and we headed back to our rooms at the hotel, Lois was seen quite literally crawling up the stairs]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Parmentiers (continued)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(continued) I would remind you that Lois doesn’t drink, so it had to be the dancing.  David and Michael did not suffer from this dance-induced affliction.   /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, the Parmentiers]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Where can I Start? Baseball–College and Pro Basketball–Football–or Hockey. Let’s talk about attending the Fiesta Bowl; Rose Bowl; Liberty Bowl; and Super Bowl – ALL THE SAME YEAR. Chris and Richie experienced events within a short period most people hoped for a lifetime]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, the Nasons]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[After David had graduated from the University of Maine and Lois was still in school, David would drive up from Boston on weekends to make sure that Lois would not forget him. On one such weekend, David picked up a hitchhiker.  (continued)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, The Kelleters]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(continued) David, his mind strictly on the road ahead, pretty much ignored his rider, who tried to make small talk. Finally, the hitchhiker asked, “David, don’t you remember me?” “No,” said David. Clearly deflated, the hitchhiker said, “ But we were roommates.” ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, the Kelleters (continued)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[David never was able to place the face, but fortunately, he never forgot the route to Orono.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, the Kelleters]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sky-blue]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>