<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2678-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/19/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Cassie Rathbun]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[4543 W Greenway Rd.]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Glendale]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[AZ]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[85306]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Love! ]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Bryan Rathbun]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[xoxo Cass]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There is not just ONE thing I like most about you. I LOVE all of you and the way you make me feel safe, cherished and loved. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Wife]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love the way you always think of me and make each day special. xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cass]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like that Bryan makes KILLER beer.  Seriously good stuff.  Like, I would go into business with you good. Someday, my friend, someday ... until then, I hope you have the happiest of birthdays!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Morgan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[His obvious devotion to three of the most important things in life:/R1: A good woman/R2: A good dog/R3: Great Beer!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike Armstrong ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan!  We love how you always wear a great smile!  It reflects your welcoming attitude, genuine friendship, and positive character!  Plus...I'm sure that your dentist appreciates the advertising!  Happy Birthday and keep smiling!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Charlie & Nancy Brooks]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I miss hanging out with you guys bud! Looking forward to spending time together in Sept. Hope you have a great B'Day! Wish we were there to have a beer with you. Have an IPA for me!/R"Spicy story ese"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marc]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan,/RYou're an amazing husband to my best friend! I couldn't have asked for someone more loving and thoughtful to be her partner for life. I also love how you're a handyman and make some pretty amazing things in your garage :) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Deena Traina]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Bryan has everything you would want in a son....wit, strength, intelligence, handsome, loyal and honest....plus he married the right woman!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom and Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I like that Bryan is a crafter at heart. He also makes some dam good beer. Most important he is my friend my brother in law and proud we are family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The things that I love most about my brother...his heart and devotion to his family. He has been there for me when I needed him the most and for that I am forever grateful. His love is unconditional, and I am so proud to call him MY little brother. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Sister ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[His happy smile]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Forest Wallace]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I would have say my favorite thing I love about Bryan is the fact that he makes my Cassie so blissfully happy. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Calm, smooth and collected, you, Bryan always have it in control. Always seem to bring a sense of 'everything's going to be ok'  to the unexpected. Always thinking of everyone else. You bring safety with a scoop of love... and a dash of damn good homebrew!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you man, Ryan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There is a very fine line between 'hobby' and 'mental illness'. Stay slightly crazy and we'll all be drinking our new favorite beer.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ryan T]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that you're an amazing husband to my friend and that you're always willing to help others ? Have a truly wonderful birthday ???]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenn Prescott and Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Bryan is his kind smile and huge heart.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amanda H. K.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[How yoooouuu doooiiiinnn??? ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Bryan! It has been a blessing to have you in our family. You are hard working, devoted, loving and supportive to Cassie, and always fun to be around. Have a great one. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Martha K]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love your dedication to your craft! You are inspiring and wonderful at the same time! Thank you for being such a wonderful brother! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Trav]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bryan Rathbun, You are a gift to the beer world, have a hoppy birthday]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Hauser's]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have always been such a great friend and neighbor!  Thank you for your generosity and constant willingness to lend a helping hand! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shawn & Holli Klein]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[May every day be a good one. I love you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cass]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for all you do for us. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Rathbun menagerie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In case noone says it.. you are extremely special and I'm so lucky you picked me!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cass]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Today I have loved you for 4255 days.. approximately.. :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love me]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Love" doesn't seem like enough of a word to express all that I feel for you. You fill my heart. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My sweetheart, /RWhen you start your day or lay your head on your pillow, know how much I love you and think of you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your wife]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you more than a fat kid loves cake. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[cass]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I’ve never been so certain of anything in my life like I am of us]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[They say you fall in love only once. That is a lie. Every time I look at you, I fall in love all over again.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[cass]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Every single day, I am grateful for you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If you were a library book, I’d never give you back... then they'd send me to collections for stealing.. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Wife]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You look great today. How do I know? Because you look great every day. :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[cass]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Life is rushed and things get busy, but never forget that I love you and appreciate you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[cass]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for those days you let me sleep in.. the days you feed all the animals.. and for making me breakfast every day. I love you more.. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you. That is all. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[cass]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your thoughtfulness is unmatched. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[cass]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We've made it this far. Can't wait to see what the future holds in store. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If you wake up feeling blue. Just remember the kingdom of love you have have around you. We wouldn't trade you for anything. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[love me]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If you can stay in love for more than two years, you're on something. -Fran Lebowitz/RWE ARE ON TO SOMETHING! Woot!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love me]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kiss my neck. Bite me. Pull my hair. Trace my spine. Hold me down. Use your tongue. Don't stop till I'm shaking! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I just want you to be happy./R/RAnd naked. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love me]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[If you need a pick me up, I have two of them ready and waiting for you. On my chest. :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cass]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My six word love story: I can’t imagine life without you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[xoxo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because I love you, because it would be impossible not to love you. I love you without question, without calculation, without reason good or bad, faithfully, with all my heart and soul.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Me]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Let's be friends.. with benefits.. better yet.. lovers... with bonus benefits.. all the time.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[cass]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Life is a crazy ride. I'm sure glad I get to share it with you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Wife]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From tickly's at night.. to spontaneous presents. Know that you are always on my mind, and consuming my thoughts. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your wife]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my goals in this life, in this marriage, is to see you smile and make you laugh every day. I love you.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[cass]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are my favorite. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your wife]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>