<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2687-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/20/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Madeline Peek]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[503 LONDON WAY]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[BELTON]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[MO]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[64012-2863]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Ron Peek, Retiring]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Ron Peek]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Lorrie Peek]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron is someone i can truly depend on--a/Rman after my own heart]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andy Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember years ago when Ron and I were on the first phase of the NKCH hospital project. Ron took the time one afternoon to explain to me how chillers, cooling towers and chilled water systems worked. Knowledge I still carry to this day. Your friendship is cherished. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Cisper ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron is a genuine person whom I enjoyed working with over the years and has a dry sense of humor that you can't tell when he is joking or being serious. There was the one time in Warrensburg when he tried to bury me in a shallow grave under a golf cart./Renjoy retirement]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bryan & Darla Thrasher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank You Ron for all the knowledge you have passed on through the years]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marcus Conner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have worked really hard all these years for your family…Together at a slower pace, you and I start our new journey!/RI Love You, xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Lorrie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You shared a quote with me a number of years ago that has since been my favorite./R/RThere are no great men, only great challenges that ordinary men are forced by circumstance to meet./RI will always keep that quote and remember you when I read it.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Will Wall]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have had the pleasure to have worked with several different Pipefitter Locals throughout the Midwest, so I can say with personal authority that you rank among the highest in the nation in your craft.  It's been a true pleasure to have worked with you.  Stay in touch.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Fauser]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Ron,/RWhen I was managing work, it was always a pleasure for you to be my Pipefitter foreman. You seemed to always show great humble respect for me as the PM even though I was originally a plumber by trade. Thanks for being a gracious mentor./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Camren]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Ron,/RWhen I was managing work, it was always a pleasure for you to be my Pipefitter foreman. You seemed to always show great humble respect for me as the PM even though I was originally a plumber by trade. Thanks for being a gracious mentor./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Camren]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I think there have been many people who started out working with you and I'll bet everyone of them that was worth keeping around learned something from you.  /RI know that within our company we knew that if Ron was on the job it was going to work out fine.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grieg Engel - Johnson Controls]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[On the way fishing one early morning Ron was talking about an upcoming apprentice and he stated that he told him, "There's one thing that gets to the job before you do, and that's your reputation".  That's always stuck with me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Grieg Engel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We first met at WMMC and I could tell right away that I would learn a lot working with you and I did. You’d take the time to answer questions and explain systems I didn’t know much about. I’m lucky to have worked with you and to have learned from you. Thank you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bo Wempe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Wipe that smoke off kid, this is your legacy!" -Ron Peek  -This quote always makes me smile. Ron you are leaving one hell of a legacy for others to follow! From work you have done, to the jobs you have ran, to ALL the people you have taught! /RThank you, Ron!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leanna]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite personal memories, was tournament fishing with Ron at Lake of the Ozarks, when he caught his big bass, I will never forget the look on his face when we got it into the boat nearly 9lbs. The things he taught me about pipe fitting is too much to list. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Louie Collier]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron, working with you over the years has been a pleasure. From our first meeting I recognized that your ability to lead by example, rather than words alone would help you to succeed. May you retire knowing that you have made a remarkable contribution to the P1 family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Smitty G. Belcher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron, you were one of the first pipefitters I worked with. I enjoyed every job I worked with you. You quickly became a lifelong friend and I hope your retirement is fantastic!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Warren]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron Peek.......Fish TREMBLE at the mention of his name./RBest of luck to you Ron.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Fauser]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It was great working with the Legend of Ron Peek before you retired! Thanks for all the knowledge you shared with me while we were working together at Childrens Mercy!  Enjoy your retirement Ron, you deserve it!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Casey J. Drinkard]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Ron, this is Tina Grantham. First Congraultions on your Retirement. I remember when I worked for you at Centerpoint, you had to lay me off on Friday , I left on a Thrusday. I think you thought I was made because you laid me off.I wasn't , you paid me for that Friday.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tina Grantham]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A true sportsman and one hell of a avid bass angler! Ron, thanks for the memories at Old Hickory/Pickwick, Table Rock, Grand, Truman, Lake of the Ozarks...Enjoy your Retirement!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Louie Collier]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["And in the end it's not the years in your life that matters, but the life in your years." -Abraham Lincoln/R/REnjoy yourself Ron! You have earned it 10 times over!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[     ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ron's work ethic as a foreman is equal to the weight he pulls even when he works with tools.  I enjoyed many stories about him and Louis Collier fishing in bass tournaments rain or shine.  I can imagine both of them doing 60 mph up river wearing Frog Toggs.  Good times.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jordan King]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's impossible to say just one thing I enjoyed about working with Ron over the past few years.  No one worked as hard as Ron or knew a project as well as he did.  I always enjoyed his stories of places he had travelled to.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carey Minihan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[RON HAS ALWAYS BEEN ONE OF MY FAVORITE PEOPLE TO WORK WITH. HE ALWAYS KNOWS WHAT HE NEEDS OR WHAT WE CAN DO TO MAKE IT WORK. I ALWAYS ENJOY HIS PLEASANT PERSONALITY, WHICH MAKES MY JOB MUCH EASIER AND ENJOYABLE. WE WILL MISS HIM, BUT WISH HIM THE BEST. KEEP FISHING!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Milton Huckabey-MIDSTATES]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember lots from working for Ron, but what I remember most is I don't know anything Yet! He explained things very well and down to the 16th. He is very smart and extremely hard working!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shawn Boykin (Son in Law)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>