<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2712-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/26/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Chandra Baron]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[7647 South Wellington Street]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Centennial]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[CO]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[80122]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sand]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Mom!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Kaja Sceery-Burr]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[From Chandra & Many Loved Ones!!]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One special memory I have is you teaching me to drive a stick shift.  Like so many times in life you sacrificed (your car) while I grinded the gears, went too fast, and probably scared you a little.  Thanks for always hanging in there and teaching me the road of life!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chandra]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The night we went with Kit and Ron downtown to the bar and laughed so hard my ribs and face hurt the next day. We had those guys so fooled, good time]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mette]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Christmas morning 1970. All those clothes from the boutique. We were the envy of every  girl at school. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mette]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Listening to you sing all your songs, such talent. We could really harmonize back then. I thought we were pretty cool.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mette]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When you came to help me after Beau was born it was like an angel had come to be ease my load. I can never thank you enough for that.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mette]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I was pretty sick this past year, Kaja took the time to get me a really nice blender so I could make my own veggie/fruit shakes.    I LOVE that blender but most of all it was extremely thoughtful and generous of her. Happy Birthday sweet girl! Hope it is amazing!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Molly Londo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the best moments I have had with Kaja was attending the Kenny Loggins concert at Fiddlers Green in Denver and then the road trip to Glennwood And Steamboat Springs.  Good times.. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ciffored ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Swimming with you in Hawaii will always be a wonderful memory for me!  You showed me that being fearless can lead to beautiful things like making friends with a sea turtle in the wild and swimming with him for an hour!  That was truly magical!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chandra]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love grandma's pool and she lets me go there in the summer.  I remember when I squirted her with a water gun and thought it was so funny.  She laughed and squirted me back.  My mommy says grandma is sure a good sport.  I sure do love her!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jacob]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I fondly remember you telling me about the importance of my friends over a girlfriend that was unlikely to result in anything serious.  Now I lovingly call you Mom.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wayne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember when you and Gordon were getting married in Santa Fe. You had a  look on your face like, "what am I doing!"/RFortunately it was the right move,/RGlad you're in the family./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cindy and Rollie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So many derivatives of her name, but we knew it was to honor her Swedish great grandmother's name Kijsa.Cozette does have that same strong adventurous spirit that drove her great grandmother.We thankfully count her a 'priceless' gem in  our treasure chest. God Blessings]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Uncle Jerry and Aunt Valerie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are so many memories to choose from, but one that sticks out for me is when you took care of me when I was sick one time. My dad had to come get me from school early and you made me feel so much better and then the next morning I was fine! Happy birthday! Love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Cross]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our road trip to Canada was the most amazing trip we have ever had. I loved getting to spend so much time with you and experience new places together. Our road trips have always meant so much to me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aizlinne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As kids growing up together I was always in awe at how pretty you were and wished I had that same beauty. At 60, you're still the beautiful Kaja I knew growing up, both inside and out. Happy Birthday my friend, much love to you on this special day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paige Christensen ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Many great times with Kaja - crazy times in the office with rooms filled with balloons, limo rides, and pure laughter.  Or, how about the Christmas concerts, great way to start the holidays!  Drinks on your deck, watching Chandra grow up.  Love you girl, always will!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim Kroeger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kaja makes the most fabulous pies!  I have been blessed to have been on the receiving end of her baking on my Thanksgiving visits to Denver over the past 40+ years.  Thanks Kaja for sharing your many talents with your family!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dazhe Bitz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[On one of my visits to Denver, Kaja shared some folk style music that she composed and performed on her guitar for a citywide contest.  She is a very talented individual!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dazhe Bitz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Kaja!  /R/RMy special moments with you have been all the fun times we've shared observing, worshipping, cherishing, and protecting our beautiful natural world.  /RHave an amazing 40th!! /R(There is NO WAY you are 60!) /RWith Love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gina]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I chuckle to myself every time I think back to you dancing in the /Rkitchen and trying to get me to dance too!  Ummm... NO!!/R/RYour free spirit is what /RI admire the most!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenn Huber]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Yikes!/RFor every time you've walked around a corner and scared me!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenn Huber]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You were always very kind to everyone you knew & there is no doubt that you would be there for anyone that needed a shoulder.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pam Crane]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Loved hanging out with you at your house growing up in Billings. You were not only beautiful on the outside but also on the inside! You still are! So glad we were able to reconnect after all these years. Happy Birthday my friend!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brenda (Jalbert) Mora]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The most memorable moment with Kaja was when she told me that she had done some reflection on her life, and had returned to the faith of her childhood. It caused me to reflect on my own life, how God had guided it, resulting in my friendship with her, among others.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Schmidt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ /R   /RMy mother came across a large Whiskey Crock. Kaja thought it was cool so Mom /Rgave it to her . I remember she had to go outside and clean it all up . While she was /Rhosing out the inside dead mice popped out of the top scaring her and making her scream. Ha Ha Ha /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kit Sherman  Brother]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You were pregnant with Aizlinne when you, Michael Bryant and I were standing in the kitchen behind the front desk at ESI. Michael was giving you a shoulder message while I rubbed your belly. When we looked out into the waiting room a group clients watched open-mouthed.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You introduced me to wonderful new music!  My favorite to this day is Loreena MeKennitt.  Sometimes we would have tea, listen to 'New Age' tunes and talk about life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Lisa, Tammie and I loved piling into the cozy kitchen at the old house for family celebrations that usually included a fantastic dessert created especially for us by Chandra.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Some of the million reasons why I love you:/RYour wonderful heartfelt laugh and smile that light up your whole beautiful face./RYour genuineness and honesty./RYour love and acceptence of family and friends. /RYour sense of adventure, wit, and intelligence. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[For 5 minutes you and I considered moving into a home where the garage was converted into a bakery.  We were going to be a mother daughter operation who brought delicious homemade bread to the masses.  While it never happened, I love imagining that alternative reality!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chandra]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There was an Iguana named Iggy, a Science teacher named Mr Hainey and the prettiest girl in the whole school in my  Science class at Lewis & Clark Jr High. I can still see that girl with the great long brown hair, the greatest eyes on the planet and the BEST smile ever.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Toni Ready Milne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Many years ago your mother and I witnessed your eye contact with a dog being trained to retrieve duck decoys to a hunter's boat. Immediately, he spit out the decoy, swam from the middle of the lake to you and began licking your face. Divine Intervention?  /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My fondest memory during our Columbine days is aromatic!  If you wanted to find someone, you had to wander around the office.  Finding you was easy due to the wonderful perfume you wore.  I always knew when I was hot on your trail because that lovely scent lingered.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jackie Reynolds Parker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Running into you and Walter at Red Rocks after the birth of Aizlinne .  It was your first night out after the baby and you were so excited!  Imagine the disappointment when you learned your tickets were for the following night.  Maybe that's a memory better forgotten. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jackie Reynolds Parker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Grandma makes the BEST pancakes!  She makes them with syrup AND whipped cream.  I think she adds some love too and that's why they are the best!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jacob]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When Kaja was a hardworking single mama, I asked her how she could get up day after day, go to work, raise a little person, do all required and keep a smile.  She replied, "I like to eat!"  That is our Kaja, consider the need and get it done!  /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Val]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kaja, you used to be sort of like a daughter, but as the years go by, you are like a sister to me./RLove you so much, /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Val]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So many memories of the many get-togethers!  However, a favorite memory was seeing your face as you entered your office FULL of balloons.  Wishing you another very Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike and Debbie Roberts]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are an incredibly genuine, lovely soul.  You have guided me through countless frankly thoughtless acts with solid advice and a non-judgemental attitude.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Heidi Kennedy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It has been such a pleasure to know Kaja.  She has a kind heart, warm disposition and wicked sense of humor.  With a sarcastic remark and the roll of an eye, she will have you smiling! She is forever young at heart, /Rand with much love I wish her /Ranother 60 years!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Melanie Escobedo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kaja and I became friends years ago,when we help a new folk artist here in town. I knew at that time she was special! I realized later at the Peoples Fair, when we added our friend Dave to the group,we could of become a very good group with her as the singing,/Rlove KJ!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rodger Noll and David Weaver]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kaja told me she used to play the guitar, but it’d been a long time. She sat on a stool, adjusted the microphone, and she played the most wonderful version of “4+20”. Even twenty years later, whenever I play “4+20”, I think of Kaja and her beautiful voice.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Don, Susan, Evan, and Kyle Butman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will never forget the day that you and Chandra came fishing at St. Mary's Glacier, many years ago. Somehow, a lot of my neighbors showed up also "fishing".  After the two of you left: I was by myself again. I still can't think why. Perhaps or perhaps.......no.........]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gabe DB]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memory of Kaja was at Chandra's wedding.  It was beautiful as beautiful as the bride and her mother, but what struck me was how everyone in her family, extended, and "X" family /Rwere all present and had a great time.  I/Radmired how Kaja pulled that off.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bonnie Bogart]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kaja has been one of my closest friends for over 20 years, a true friend that has always been there if I needed something and I hope I have been the same to her.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you like a sister, Bonnie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[HappyBirthday Aunt Kaja! Both Cari and I enjoyed just this summer walking through the Botanical Gardens with you. It was so nice to just wander through it all after a great lunch. Be ready when we come see it during a different time of the year to join us again!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ahren & Cari]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In the summer of 85 auntie Kaja took us to the air conditioned theater, this was to be my first movie Ghostbusters! I grew into a science fiction geek. And developed an irrational fear of "scary" things. That fear lasted for the next 30 years. Thank you for that;-)/RLove]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Beau]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I met Kaja at Evolving Systems, she was always very kind and willing to help. My special moment has to be dinner at her home, with her family. She welcomed me and my son Max and my mom and made us feel like family. Have a fantastic Bday Kaja! Best Wishes.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Fuller]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Clueless at my first white-collar job.  Couldn't even tie a tie.  You took me in and protected me from Fran and Jackie.  I remember your warm smile, your beautiful piano playing, your happy little girl.  Happy birthday my friend!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Daniel Warren]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[20 years ago we met as two single moms with the most adorable little girls.  Wow where have the years gone.   Every time we reconnect, we pick up right where we left off and  I am always reminded of your gentle soul and nurturing heart for your family. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen Waldvogel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No one has a better smile than Kaja. Her eyes sparkle and her entire face lights up in delight. I see it most when she’s around her grandchildren. They love being with her and they bring out her best. (I’ve caught Scarlett practicing her phone calls to Grandma Kaja…)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Erin, Ilyana and Scarlett]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[No matter what the future brings, I want us to be as close as we can be, do everything together that we can do, and to live our lives to the fullest. I love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gordon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I wish she loved me as much as she loves birds and animals...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anonymous]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my favorite memories during high school was when I was invited to one of your family barbecues. I loved being able to help you get the food ready and I felt like part of the family. I hope you have a great birthday and hope to see you soon!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are one of the fiercest and most beautiful women I know. Only you could raise a family as classy, intelligent, and lovely as yours. Hope I can make it down there soon, happy birthday lady!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jasmine]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Oh my dear Kaja,/R  I want to share this with you on your birthday....the best memories I have of you Kaja...are at the grand piano singing so beautifully....with your smile to match!! I always thought you were the best I've ever heard!!/RHappy Birthday!! Love You Kaja!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelly Foos]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's hard to pick just one special memory we've shared...we've had so many! Weddings, holidays, vacations...we've spent them together as a family.  I hope you have a very special birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jodie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I must love you because I gave up my bed for you while you had severe lactose intolerance.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wayne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Kaja, You have always been an inspiration to me. You are a wonderful mother, a grandmother full of love and an amazing woman. You will always hold a special place in my heart. I hope you have a great birthday with lots of love and enjoy this gift from Chandra.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelly Byrd]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Purple turtle...andma."  Well he tried.  He's a little to young to share a memory but he sure does love love his grandma nonetheless.  Both my boys are so blessed to have you in their lives.  I love watching you with them and how their faces light up when they see you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tyler ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Brightest blessings on this special day ! My favorite memory with you is when Jasmine and I came to stay with you after the flood . You had a fun activity planned for each day , and you were very patient, nurturing , and loving during a difficult time in our childhood.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Sherman ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["There is a fountain of youth: it is your mind, your talents, the creativity you bring to your life and the lives of the people you love. When you learn to tap this source, you will have truly defeated age."/R-Sofia Loren]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Sherman ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["And in the end, it’s not the years in your life that count. It’s the life in your years."/R/R-Abraham Lincoln]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Sherman ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kaja, one of the greatest things you did, during the time we raised Chandra, was the 100% dedication you gave to your Daughters. I see this dedication now in Chandra with her two Boys she is raising. Now you get to Spoil this two Boys! "Have fun and Happy Birthday".]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dick Powell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will always share the memory of asking for your daughters hand in marriage. You make me feel like part of the family, something I always wanted in a mother in law. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christian ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a beautiful, classy and badass lady!!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Debi Conteras]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As your daughter's friend, you always treated me like your own. I never knew about organic foods or delicious herbs or special places like Glenwood Springs until you taught me about these things. Thank you so much for all you did for me when I was just a child!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Wendy Daniel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Kaja!!/ROne thing out of many comes to mind.  When we filled your entire office at Columbine Systems with balloons.  The look on your face was priceless.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Holly Fair]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the greatest mom in the world!  I wouldn't trade you for anyone else!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chandra]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>