<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2713-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/26/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Andrew Starr]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[3901 Martha Truman Road]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Kansas City]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[MO]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[64137]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDEX_FEDEX2DAY]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_60]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[scarlet]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Marilyn Creager]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Marilyn Creager]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[In Honor of your Retirement]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It is rare to have the opportunity to work with someone as committed as Marilyn.  Since I've joined the board, I've witnessed Marilyn give 110% everyday to our organization.  She is smart, dedicated, passionate and most of all caring.  I wish you the best my friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jodi Robinson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn I wish I had become involved with Wayside Waifs earlier so I would have had the opportunity to get to know you better.  However your commitment to Wayside's mission and the animals it serves is clear and you will be missed]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Morris & Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn../R/RIt has been an absolute pleasure to have know and worked with you over the last several years.   /R/RWishing you rest, peace, love, and happiness in your retirement. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike Tracy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I had the privilege of working with Marilyn during 2004 at MOCSA. I have been with the company for 14 years, but learned more from Marilyn than any other boss. She respected and believed in me, and made me feel good about myself. But above all, she was my friend!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sharon Booker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Oh, the changes you & I have seen.We have worked side by side for many years. We accountants are always behind the scenes & you were there providing steady guidance & strength as Wayside grew into the organization it currently is. Thank you. Enjoy retirement, my friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Melanie Hepperly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn, through my MANY years on the Wayside Board, you've been our "budget guru"...the person in whom we had complete confidence because of your attention to detail and your unwavering dedication to helping us be the best in the business!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan Wally]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you, Marilyn, for all your service and dedication to Wayside Waifs. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sherry Forsee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn is the world's greatest clogger./RWe all love her and are so glad that she started clogging. If not we probably would not have ever met her. She is a hugh asset to The Cowtown Cloggers. Love you Marilyn.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cowtown Cloggers]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn:  I will miss you so much. I always knew I could come to you with a question, problem or just for congenial conversation.  Your contributions to Wayside are too numerous to name.  I wish you all the best in retirement.  Please come see us often. God bless you!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pam Dooley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn,  I warmly recall working with you and your joie de vivre--especially the dancing!  I hope you have ample opportunity for that and other fun things in your retirement.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Palle Rilinger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Marilyn,/R/RI will miss you so much, it has been great to get to know you over the past 2 years.  I hope to see you around Wayside from time to time. Keep in touch!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amanda ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[	I'm so glad to have had the honor of working with you. Thank you for being a mentor and a constant inspiration to me. I hope to stay in contact, and will truly miss you. Good luck!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ashley McCoy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I owe my promotion less to my qualifications and more to the support of helpful colleagues like you.   Congratulations  to a wonderful, fabulous lady./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ronnie Laree Wise]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn, I have asked you thousands of questions and you have always been patient and provided guidance...even when the answer was no! Thank you for all you have done. We always laughed at sending each other pictures of food so don't forget to send me one now and then! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barry Baranowski]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn,/RIt was a pleasure to work with you. I love your spirit, your strength, and the way you care about Wayside. I will never forget your enthusiasm when you gave me my new board member tour, you show the same today! Looking forward to sharing some retirement fun!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All the best for you, Ellen Hanson ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn,/RI have admired and learned from your commitment to excellence at Wayside. You could always account for every single penny! You have been a joy to work with. I wish you the very best in retirement. I hope we still get to see you around!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shannon Barks]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whenever I think of you the first thing that comes to mind is your clogging.  I have not met anyone before who clogs so that makes you special!  How does one even get started or interested in clogging?!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Ritter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To a fellow GKCCF survivor, congratulations on your retirement.  Now you will have more time to alphabetize your canned goods.  :))]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carolyne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn,/RThank you for getting me off to good start at Wayside Waifs and all that you have done for Wayside and other organizations.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrew Starr]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn/R/RIt was a pleasure working with you at the Community Foundation.  I always enjoyed hearing your laugh!  Sorry I was unable to make it to your party but I do wish you the best in retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jodi Adams]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn, I admire /Ryour leadership and love for Wayside!  You have always run a highly successful tight ship.  We all love you and will miss you greatly my friend.  My Best to you - - - Chris Trainer]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Trainer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy retirement, dear Marilyn!  You were always so fun (and expert!) to work with.  I just never understood driving to Springfield to get your hair cut!?  Wishing you every blessing in this new part of your life & sending love]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Annie Heck]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm very happy for you Marilyn.  I'm sure you have wonderful plans beyond your retirement that will be as fulfilling as it has been with Wayside Waifs.  Thank you for your dedicated service for our community.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Walt Lane]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Many thanks for your dedication and service to the homeless pets at Wayside, Marilyn.  Wishing you a wonderful, fulfilling retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jan Kyle & Wayne Hunthausen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn, I have enjoyed working with you over the past several years. If there was ever a question I needed an answer to, you were always there with the answer. I'm going to miss you and your smile. My best to you in your new role as a retired Wayside Waifer.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Harold Melcher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Hi Marilyn,  we are looking forward to lunches and shopping, with no eye on the clock.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carolyn Osgood & Caroline Jeffries]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn--thanks for all of your help.   I always appreciated the fact the we had good financial information./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peter Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It’s been great working with you and getting to know you, Marilyn! I appreciate your constant willingness to cheerfully assist me. Your positive outlook and upbeat disposition made working with you a pleasure. Thanks for everything! I’ll miss you! Please keep in touch.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on your lengthy career and everything you have accomplished! You have achieved a lot. Enjoy your retirement.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Casey McDonald]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn has always been the person I turned to for figuring it out and getting it done.  We have had an amazing career working in different agencies and grappling with different issues.  I am, as always, so appreciative of Marilyn's dedication, commitment, and tenacity.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Patti Glass]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn,/R/RVery best of luck and thank you for all your service to Wayside. You are an inspiration!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gary Wolf]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I had the pleasure of working with you for many years at JF&CS. During those years, we shared many professional and personal accomplishments and challenges. Time can't take away my memories that are filled with smiles. I wish you a happy retirement filled with fun.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen Agron Flattery]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Multi-talented, Ambitious, Romantic, Incredible, Loving, Young-at-heart, Nuturing = MARILYN]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Kirt and Susan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn is a very caring person who I will miss greatly.  She has made me feel very welcome in the Finance Department and I am thankful I got to work closely with Marilyn in these past months.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sharon Kelly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn, you have always been so wonderful!  Anytime I had a question, you always had time to answer it or to provide an explanation.  You are always smiling, polite and kind.  I will miss seeing daily at Wayside, but I look forward to seeing you as a volunteer!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All the best to you! - Bonnie Still]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Marilyn,/RI will always fondly remember our work together on the audit of the Jewish Family Services so many years ago.  I still use the Mary Kay lotion that you introduced me to so my hands could be more smooth for my new baby.  Love every day of retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sharon Latimer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We wish you all the best in this new chapter of your life. Thank you for all the support, guidance and laughter over the years. Our family is always here for you! /RAbove all remember to always #enjoythemoment.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David, Trish, Fiona & Gavin Cross]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am so glad I had the chance to work with you these past years! Good luck in everything you do!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elise Mann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will miss my "bean counter"!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We can never thank you enough for your expertise, caring and enthusiasm for the animals and people at Wayside Waifs./RThank you, thank you, thank you./RMarilyn Creager]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom and Betty Scott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Marilyn,  How fortunate I have been to have crossed your path at WW.  Wayside has been blessed to have you in the many roles, not just being on top of all things financial....you are always there to lend a hand or ear for all...you are the calm in our hectic days.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Randy Clark]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for all you have done for Wayside.  Your smiling face and vast knowledge of our organization and history will be sorely missed.  Happy Retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandy Johnson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn, I am hoping you will enjoy your retirement as much as I enjoy mine.  It may take a few months but I predict you'll wake up one day & say, "I'm too busy -- I finally do have it all!"  Happy Trails To You.....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barbara Lawson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn - I hope you enjoy retirement ... you've certainly earned it!  Wayside has been lucky to have you all these years.  Best wishes.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vicky Whitney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have so enjoyed working with you!  I have always appreciated your friendliness and humor. You will be missed. Thank you for all you have given to Wayside and non-profits. I always think of you when I am reading a good mystery!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Taylor O'Connor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It has been a pleasure working with you.  I admire your work ethic, professionalism and dedication to WW and the huge responsibility you held.  You did what it took and truly made a difference.  And you did it with a smile.  Dance on into the next stage of your life!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Connie Bonovich]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on your retirement and your wonderful career of transforming the lives of both people and animals. We are all so fortunate to have known your class, kindness and humor and you have left an indelible mark on our hearts. Best wishes in all your endeavors!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Geoff Hall]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your caring heart and strong spirit have contributed to your successful career in creating a better community!  Others with your talents are drawn to vocations that bring in the "big bucks."  Instead, what you have given this world is priceless!  Enjoy your retirement!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allison Basinger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn, we are all so thankful to you for the tireless and diligent work you've put into Wayside Waifs over the years.  It has  had a direct impact on making it possible for thousands of pets to find new, loving homes.  All the very best to you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[John Goodman]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on your retirement, dear friend! I am so envious you beat me to it! You have been a wonderful friend for 15+ years. Your caring & unrivalled common sense helped me thru some tough times. Also, thank you for Jack & Stephanie Plum! Hugs to you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Virginia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are irreplaceable and will be missed by humans and the waifs alike!! You always made me feel like I mattered something special when I began as a volunteer and I continue to think of you when snuggling the doggies. You will be a hard act to follow!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Donna Williams]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Marilyn - your commitment, leadership, and belief has saved the lives of thousands of shelter pets. Thank you for everything and don't be a stranger!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Robin & Alfie Rowland]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It always hurts to lose that one best person, who leads the pack at work and gets everything done. The person who moves ahead and takes everyone else along, who builds a winning team by making everyone strong. Congratulations on you retirement. You will be missed!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Debbie Brown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I've enjoyed knowing you all these years clogging.  And I'm happy that you will still be clogging with us in the future./R/RYour dancing friend,   /REllie Behrmann]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ellie Behrmann]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[scarlet]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>