<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2733-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/27/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Leslie Gudel]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[531 Winston Way]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Berwyn]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19312]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_200]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Jeanette]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Jeanette]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[We Love You]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You did not know me well but went out of your way to help me aquire a shirt. It made a huge impact,your generosity and overwhelming kindness makes me want to be better. . You exemplify womanhood and strength, an awesome roLE model for all. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joyce (PSP family)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love you because you were always there for us. The misfits. Because no matter what you had our backs. Because we could talk about anything. We will always be more than even a family. We love you beyond words, and we carry you in our hearts. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The misfits. Eric, Laurene and Ron.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[oh let me count the ways, you are my Photographer providing such great shots of our kids. You are my Secretary, keeping me updated re: when or what I need to order, return or pay for. You drove this Ms. Daisy everywhere. But most of all I love you because you are YOU!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bernadette Klohoker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I've had the pleasure of knowing you most of my life with fantastic memories of sharing a drink (several) in the driveway in the summertime.  What I love most is watching your kids grow into fine young adults which is a true testament to what makes you so special!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian Holst]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I ran out of characters, 270 characters just isn't anywhere near enough!/R/RLove and miss all of you guys!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian Holst]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you have given our community a HERO. You've given my Grace a woman to look up to, a mom who smiles while fighting, a wife who has never given up. You our the one we all call "our Wonder Woman." & like a superhero your story will forever be told. X.O]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vicki, Dave,David & Grace Burns]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wow - too many to fit in just 270 letters. One of the fearsome 4 of that I first met in the very early days of middle school. We twirled our batons together and then both joined the rifle squad. From band camps to practices to hunting vampires to sewing comp uniforms.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pam Litwin Theisen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Still more - dissecting crayfish in bio, taking a frog from the bio closet and wrapping it to give to the principal (for all you do this frogs for you) to the bubba mobile and the car fire on Halloween. To cape may trips and senior week. One of my best childhood friends]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pam Litwin Theisen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I met you through our love of scrapbooking and then we bonded over cancer. You are such a fighter that you keep encouraging me even if you don't know it. You never give up and you are such a positive role model for everyone!! Love you, girl! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tricia Kleber ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeanette was my alarm clock. She would beep her horn on her bus every morning to say hello.  It made me smile each morning. She is a truly amazing woman!/RMiss those days!/RML & R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nicole and the Brown family ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Was it about a year or so ago?. You had a bus trip out our way and we got together at the Robinsons.. We had a great day of catching up.. Talking about our kids of course the guys and "the job" Laughing over old times! We all knew how to have a good time;) Great day!!-X]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelly Neely ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remember 1st meetin u at Kat's in Slatington. Wasn't sure what I thought of u.  Yrs later started goin to cabin 4 family get togethers & u started to grow on me. Now think of u as part of my family. Ur strength amazed me then & continues to amaze me now! Love ya!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Deb Smith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have touched so many lives both adults and children! You are a hero- so many look up to you! You are "Wonder Woman" for sure! Always enjoyed seeing where the Big Yellow Bus was taking the kids for a trip! God Bless YOU and your family! Love YOU!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mrs. Kensey:)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ok so best memory ever... My birthday at retreat 2 or 3 yrs back at Texas Roadhouse. Lemon Drop shots and Judge Love.... bwah haha!!! Thanks for being my scrapping bud! <3]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Donna Davila AKA S.A.M]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Love Jeanette because she always has a friendly smile for you even when she is not feeling like smiling . She has a great heart and a  beautiful soul . Love you girl.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stacy Poppert ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Oh What can I say I love just sitting next to her or even across from her at our retreats and all we have to do s look at each other and we would know what each other would be thinking. Also love all the paper that she would bring so I could use . Love you always ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pam West ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The kindness and patience you showed Brian when you drove him. Your big cheerful smile and wave whenever you saw us on our walk..xo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dee Barnes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because of your infectious smile and laugh also Your courage to face everyday with all that you have no matter the obstacles! Lets see the memory oh yes glitter/ depends/Scrap retreat .. Yah you know what i am talking about!! Glitter on girlfriend glitter on]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Christina Lefferts]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We had a fun time at the Pampered Chef convention in Chicago! The plane ride playing Scrabble and Jenny Mars and I cheating with the tiles to see how long it took them to notice our fancy cooking words. Jeanette soon caught on and it was a riot! Lots of laughs that trip]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura D'Uva]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeanette, you are a very strong women. Your courage is amazing. Your family love and dedication is like no other. Having you & your family added to ours has and will always bring so much more happiness. You are in my thoughts everyday, many prayers for you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[You are loved your stepsister Terri]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You will always be 'Jenny' to me. :) But so many great times growing up together. All the sleepovers and roller skating parties and exploring in the creek... great memories. Now I admire your strength and grace as a woman and a mother. You are an inspiration to so many.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michelle (Shelly) Wheatley Galloway]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeanette, you were always there for me when i had a question about treaments. You always were encouraging. Thank you for that!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy Nakonieczny]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[your my best friend and I will always cherish every single solitary second I have spent with you:) thank you for being my mom and for always being there. I love you and always will]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[E]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are so strong and with only knowing your kids, I can tell what an amazing mother you are. Never forget how strong and amazing you are. Also I love your tattoos, they're awesome. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amanda Nowell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember when Jeanette and Bobby graciously allowed me to stay overnight, when I attended a weekend course at Willow Grove Naval Air Station. Took me in, and made me comfortable, so I didn't have to drive back and forth from Allentown. Thanks again! God Bless!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dale Yoder, Lebanon, PA]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Jeanette,/RYou have been there for me when no one else was. You have been my rock at a time when I felt like my whole world was ending. You supported me, no matter what I decided. I can't even imagine where my life would be now had I not met you. I love you so much.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laurene]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Even though we've never met in real life I'm proud to call you one of my "axe-murdering" friends!! You are an inspiration to me!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ann Stumpe- Walk A Different Street]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I LOVE my daughter Jeanette because she is my first born adorable DOLL..& she will always be. She is great to have sitting on your lap, getting GREAT hugs & kisses. Taking me to her church&,trips of many kinds. Fond memories of trips to Florida, camping at Ocean View ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[with her sister-Dawn. LOVE MOM-MOM]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are friend that has completed me. The 3 of us are one of a kind. You've taught me to be strong, proud, and to love unconditionally. To be a better mom,  that NO is a complete sentence and it's ok to be me. Your my inspiration. Love you lots beautiful! Xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dana]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are always quick with a smile and have a contagious laugh.  You are an amazing person and I thank you from the bottom of my heart for letting me share precious moments with your family!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jamie Kemm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thankful for the many DC retreats and your smile and contagious laughter that made each scrapbooking session 100% better!  Thanks for being a part of such sweet memories with a great bunch of women that I call "My Friends"!  Love ya!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kimberly Przybyl (Kim in NC)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I first came on the job you and Bobby took me in like family and always made me feel welcome in your home. I never knew if I wanted to have kids until I saw the love that could be given to such little souls by the two of you thank you for that gift and so many more]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jamie Kemm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I had a ton of fun at your house and the parties and get togethers you had.  None more than the time we were playing drinking games in your living room and I happen to spill a couple drinks and then realized it was leaking down into the basement - ton of laughs!!! Sorry]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jamie Kemm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Jeanette,/R         I could say more than one thing but I will single out how your Christmas parties made my Christmas better every year. Every corner of the house is full of Christmas. You and Bobby are the best hosts. I love being your fb friend. J and I love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aileen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Having followed your journey through Facebook, a few things are evident; you are undeniably strong, admirably courageous and have a great sense of humor, even in the face of adversity. Your love of family shines through in everything you do. You are in our prayers. xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leslie Kemm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being such a great aunt. I love when we hang at camp, play games, and go to Penn State games. You are so fun and have a great sense of humor. I always look forward to when the family gets together -you are such a key, cornerstone part of it!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your niece, Katie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From the first time Pam and I sat across from you and Dawn at a scrap retreat, I have been in love with you both. Your sense of humor is legendary. You've shared paper, beer, Nutter *@!^ers, stories, and vodka gummy blobs with us.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I <3 you! Diana Banzhoff]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Though I know you from afar you have been an incredible inspiration to me. A woman of strength, hope, and Faith. Seeing you up front at the 5:00 Mass even though I knew you were not feeling well was an inspiration. My love and prayers and a wish for a peaceful heart. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sister Maryanne]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeanette thank you for being there for me when I was learning to become a single mom. Thank you for giving me strength and becoming part of your family.  I love you and your family and will never forget you or your family for what you've done.  Love you ??]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Regina and Kaia Ganges ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Mrs. King,/RYou are so strong and such an amazing mother. My family and I think about you daily and keep you in our prayers.You are not alone in this, we are all here for you!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Troy Family (Allison)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love that you are an inspiration to so many people. I enjoy reading your posts, and am truly inspired by your courage and strength and the amazing bond you share with your family and community! -A true HERO. XOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Adrienne (Jones)Rouse]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I love most about Jeanette is her ability to fight as hard as she can!   She is a true SuperWoman!!  Thanks too Jeanette and Bobby for sharing Bobby and Elizabeth with us during their Preschool years,,,,,always will remember those days with all of you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Patti Petrunis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I REMEMBER ALL THE FUN TIMES AT RUSCH'S PARTIES. THEY WERE ALWAYS A LOT OF FUN. WE HAD SOME GOOD LAUGHS.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marynne Bauder alias Mrs B]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Jeanette because she has always kept it 100 percent with me. She has a magnetic personality and a smile that just makes me melt. She let's me be me and accepts my flaws. I love me some Jeanette!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Anthony Johnson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeanette, I love that you are a scrapbook paper hoarder like me!  I will never forget the fun we all had at the DC scrapbook retreats.  The "Batue of Liberty" lives on forever!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lori Dearing (aka loridear)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always know where Jeanette's seat is at a scrapbook retreat - and it's not because her gigantic paper tower gives her away. It's because it's where you want to be sitting so you can share in the constant laughter that emanates from her corner of the room.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shelly Conkey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[How open and honest you are in observations of things going on. When I called you about an issue you never hesitated to answer any question with total honesty.  And I so appreciated it! (And you play a mean Words with Friends)!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Roseann Casey]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A kind and loving fellow PSP wife!! My thoughts and many prayers for you. God Bless. ??]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bianca Fagan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have never met; however you are my sister. ? I will always be thankful for fb as it has brought such an amazing person into my life.  Thank you for your countless hours of keeping me sane monitoring the psp boards!!! Forever in my heart & prayers.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cindy Franklin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Oh that devilish smile and energy during the teen years when just being together meant laughter and shenanigans.  I love your gutsy honesty! Especially when you stood up for me during those hellish times when everyone else had turned their backs. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leah and Steinar Garhovd ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have never met, but I feel like I know you just from our psp wife bond. I have only known you from facebook, but I think of you and pray for you. The love your family has for eachother is evident from smiles on everyone's faces and light in their eyes in pictures.?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Melissa Levinsky (Lissa levi) ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have only met in person once at DC scrap retreat but I so enjoyed getting to know you and the laughter we shared!  Your chicken stories always make me smile.  Your strong spirit and caring heart shows thru all you do especially with your family.  Always in my prayers]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen Akens (k in va)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Did a ride along with Jeanette in Abington 18 years ago. I was fresh out of the police academy and she was a force to be reckoned with. Still is. She was an inspiration to me then as she is every single day now. Through our husbands,we became friends again, so grateful.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nadine Johns]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[On a funny note, Rich comes home with tomatoes from your garden and tells me about the time Bobby, in an "off" state, "watered" all of the tomato plants. Which were ripped out at your demand the next day. We laughed, until we had 2nd thoughts about the one we ate! :) ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nadine Johns]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have never laughed so hard as the night a certain mutual friend hit me right between the eyes with a peanut flung from across the room.  The look on your face made me laugh harder.  That is the first image I see when I think of you.  And I do, quite often.  Much love!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Murphy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We only met once at an EP reunion. You and Bobby, the best dressed couple in the room and your love for each other, very apparent. We share membership in a club no one wants to join, but your Grace, your Grace,  is an example for all. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marcy Miller ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeanette,  Although only thru our kids  were we acquaintances, I do have to tell you that I have admired you and your strength thru your battle.  Peace to you and your family as you continue to inspire everyone who has ever come in contact with you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lorraine Howald]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ From the first time Pam and I sat across from you and Dawn at a scrap retreat, I was hooked. Your sense of humor is legendary. You've shared paper, beer, stories, and vodka gummy blobs with us. I want more! You've been so supportive about my issues.. I can't ask more.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[<3 you, Diana Banzhoff]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A few things I love most about you, is your sarcastic, no holds barred take on people and the situations they find themselves in.  Your selfless volunteering and the love she has and shows for her family. Take care till we meet again!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lori Kramer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I admire how strong and positive you are throughout everything.  I have always loved your kick $#@ attitude.  You are a true inspiration to everyone around you.  You are a fabulous person both inside and out no matter what is happening in life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gayle Allain]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Late night chat sessions, mutual compassion and understanding, laughter in the face of tears, a listening ear...All these things you shared with me, my friend.  Words cannot express the positive energy you have gifted me with and the world is better for your being here.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Because you are my friend, my "partner in crime." For your unselfish way of always being there.  For being YOU and making me a better ME. For listening,talking,crying together. This is not goodbye, just till I see you again! Keep a watch over us... we'll need it]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lisa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love all the times our families shared over the years. The memories will last forever.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Katie Focht]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you because you understood and accepted me for me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Danny Focht]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[...because you took such good care of me when my humans were away!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lady]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I pray because thats all I can do. Because you are way too young. You are a truly beautiful person and stronger than Wonder Woman!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jen Trzaska]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have the most beautiful and contagious smile, it's addictive. Miss you alot!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob Parisi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I loved suffering through the police academy with you. You were the perfect example of being calm and kickass at the same time!  It was great to reconnect through FB and see what an amazing mom, wife, and person you are. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim (Russell) Morales]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I think back on the years we have known each other I am reminded of sitting in the bleachers for hours watching our children playing on the same teams. Great fun! Pedicures and lunch were always a fun time too! You are an amazingly strong woman! I miss you! Praying]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[michelle Orr ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memory. ..our trip to Chicago with pampered chef...playing scrabble on the plane,  torturing you because you were scared stiff the whole flight, shenanigans in the hotel with Jenny and everything else I may have forgotten. Love you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Danielle Lips]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being the "love" of my brother's life, raising such great kids, and allowing me to have the honor of being their "aunt weeza."  Your strength, resilience, candor and sense of humor make you an irreplaceable part of our crazy family. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you lots & lots, Louisa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wow Jeanette, looking back through the years lots of fun times, from school and church events, family party's,one time that stands out was our Pocono snow tubing trip...and weekend game night, but most of all you would always be there to help someone...God bless ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Greg Lips]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Where do even start?  Our friendship blossomed over lunch in the radio which turned into a daily tradition. I was very sad to see you leave.  Too many good times there.  Then there was the party at your house where I got laid, by your beloved dog, Rocky (RIP). Love ya]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matt White]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how passionate you are for family, friends, & all things furry.  You are an inspiration not for just being a fighter but for your dedication to your family & community.  I was always amazed at the energy you brought to both swim teams Gators & Tritons. God Bless!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stephanie Hopf]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Oh Dear God  = Jägermeister ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[That Guy ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To look back over the years from your first days at APD to So full of energy and a smile that made you wonder what she was up to. I have come to know her and her family and know  her to be  a wife, daughter, mother and friend to so many.  I love your conviction and care]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brian Focht ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I love most?? Strength. As a mother, police officer and cancer fighter you have always exhibited strength. Wild and crazy but also strong and dedicated!/R/RI love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Monica Costello]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeanette - I wish I could post all about our fun times together, but life did not grant them for us to share.  What we do share is connection due to the daily battles that we face.  I admire and respect you &your fight, positive outlook, &being the wonderful mother/wife]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carolyn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Even though many of us are not current Pampered Chef gals, we will always be ONE.  I remember the Chicago trip and the laughs we had with your many stories.  I  remember one about a trip to/from Germany maybe and a rattling suitcase-wink wink. You made that trip so fun!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Deb Stofka]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have only known Jeanette for a short time but in that time I have come to admire her strength and courage.  You are an amazing person and definitely fit the description of Hero & Wonder Woman. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelli Moran]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are so loved. I could not believe how many people came to your bell ringing celebration, it was packed. Every time I would see you it would be with a group... Moths to a flame. You are strong, fun and true.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michele Cohen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeanette/RI have always enjoyed your great sense of humor and candor in conversations. You have given us a great niece and nephew that you have raised each to be a good person. I will always remember the fun our families had Rivendell and the crazy family reunion stories]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Glenn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I love about you most is you always have a smile on and can put a smile on anyone's face with a great story. Having known you most of my life, I could not envision a better next door neighbor than you and your family! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin Holst]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm one of those internet ax murderer friends who has only met you a few times at scrapbooking retreats.  You and Dawn were always the life of the party!  You have a gorgeous smile and a fantastic attitude.  Keep on fighting.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jill Cleaves a/k/a Jill in FL]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will always love our scrabble games at the swim club and knowing that you  would yell kids if they did something wrong at  swim club when I had to work. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Searles Family ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[All the rides you gave me and the kids when I couldn't drive. Scrabble at the pool, Pocono trip with  the games and we all pointed to you but no one  guessed "police officer".   Tonelli's delivery at your Chistmas shin dig. "rockstar".  Many others.  Know you are loved.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate McGoldrick ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have always loved all of the good times we have had.  All of the family get-togethers and your wonderful sense of humor.  You have also given me wonderful cousins and raised them to be impeccable human beings.  You have been a blessing in mine and our family's life./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Glenny Clark]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Jeanette,/RIn the church we are told our lives must be in service to God. You chose to have a family, and  beautiful you did. Both offspring I see you in them and they are strong because of your strength. Whenever I think of God's will, I know that you made the most]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elliott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love the fact she gave us 2 beautiful grandchildren. She has made our son very happy.  She has been a wonderful Mother to Josh Gable. She is a good person.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bob and Kathy King]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how honest you are, your sense of humor and your witty sarcasm.  You made the swim team committee so much more fun than it ever should have been. I love that your beautiful smile lights up any room. The world needs more people JUST LIKE YOU! You're the best!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maria Stoltz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love being with Jeanette, at work she would tell us about the chickens and the eggs there laying.  We would bring egg boxes in, she would fill them up, such fun.  Great Stories you told./RThe Christmas parties, You are such a Wonderful Woman. Love your Smile./RMiss you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carol Brandt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeanette,I remember and loved the way you took such good care of Kattie when she had that seizure.You were so caring, protective and helpful.Thanks for being there for Kattie and me at that time and other times.I am with you and your beautiful family in prayer.God Bless]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Diane Betz ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[you are the strongest woman I know, mrs. king! no one is as strong as you are and no one is as brave as you are??]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gabrielle DeLucca ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are such an inspiration to everyone, and we admire your strength and courage! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kayla Perre and Shea Tomlinson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being such an amazing inspiration Mrs. King! It's women like you who show me what it really means to be strong! /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Gab Greene]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeanette, I have always admired your passion & dedication to your husband and children. It has been an honor to be your friend. My most cherished memory of us was developing the St. David Triton Swim Team. You were and always will be the back bone of this team! Love u!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Claire Toner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My husband John knew Jeannette since she was a cop (he is a paramedic). I met her when our daughters were in the same little league team in Upper Moreland, several years ago. I noticed how cheerful and upbeat she is. Love that smile! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lori & John Hill ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your strength and courage are second to none. You have raised beautiful, intelligent children who will achieve great things. I will always hold the memories close to my heart; Penn State games, family reunions and Coronas at King's Propane Paradise. /REphesians 3:16]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Joseph C.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our thoughts and prayers are with you and your family]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Conroy Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeanette,/RI love cropping with you at the DC crop. You and Dawn liven up the group./RLaura]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Laura]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jen You have always made me proud even after you told me you wanted to  be a police officer.  Even after I told you about my many years on the job.  But you still did it and made me even more prouder. You did a great job and kept your head about you with all the problem]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your strength and courage is a true inspriration to others.  You are Wonder Woman and Super Hero all in one.  I love you for the person you are and how you accepted me without question.  I admire you for the wife and mother you are.  I am proud to be part of your family]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your step-mom, Nancy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Mrs. King,/RMy family and I are praying for peace and strength for you during this difficult time. We wish you and your family the best. Please do not hesitate to let us know if there is anything we can do for you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ryan Young]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Even though I don't know you super well, I can say you are one of the strongest people I've ever met. Your so positive and funny even when life gets rough. I hope to be like you someday. I hope I can someday see the world as positively and beautifully as you have.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julia Capreri]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're an inspiration. Stay strong. Keep fighting. And never stop smiling./RLots of love forever and ever.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julia Capreri]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember meeting you when Nats and Elizabeth started cheer for UM in 1st grade. I saw you in your police uniform and thought "wow" look at her! I admired you then and even more now as years have passed! You truly are an amazing inspiration to us all! You're beautiful!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love the Cornelys]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I met Jeanette through my husband Sean. They worked together and I instantly liked her. She reminds me a lot of him. She is fun, kind, tough, great smile and you always knew where you stood! We shared some pretty fun times together, ones I will never forget!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Melissa Gargan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You stayed when so many left. You didn't give up on me. You gave me hope when I couldn't see it, you showed me strength at my weakest. You have shown me how to live, to fight and never give up. /RYou are my inspiration, my hero. Much Love XOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim Simms]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Of New Year's Eve 2010 ;-) /RBecause you didn't kill me when I swung at you during my panic ridden drunken breakdown. /RYou always invited me to gatherings when I was hiding from the world. /RBecause I couldn't be more honored to have you and Bobby as Abbeys godparents. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim Simms]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jeanette - I hope you feel all the love in this box.  You have so many very special people in your life.  You've clearly had a tremendous impact on all of them.  Much love to you from the Kemm Family.  Thanks for allowing me to put this together for you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leslie Kemm]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>