<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2751-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/28/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Pooneh Aminian]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[8490 Fountain Avenue]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[#304]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[West Hollywood]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[CA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[90069]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_60]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sand]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[What Everyone Loves About You]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Hossein Aminian]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love Pooneh, Taraneh and Afsaneh]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You gave me the greatest gift anyone could give another person: you believed in me. I always felt that I can accomplish anything and that led me to become the confident woman that I am today. No matter how challenging the path was, I never gave up because of you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pooneh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I admire Hossein's love for his family and friends. I always appreciate how much he has welcomed us into his home. My favorite memory is seeing the pure joy on his face while dancing with Pooneh during the father-daughter dance at the wedding. Best wishes!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nina Castillo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What I like about Hossein is his positive personality and his high energy level. At his current age, he still drinks tequila and have fun like a teenager. I desire in life is to become like him when I get to his age. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bijan Almassian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Someone who truly knows the meaning of friendship.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peyman yekta]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Icing: When it comes to kobideh at 75 F (good old time!), slicing lime, and getting people drunk with tequila shots (miscounting his!) nobody does it better than Hossien. /RCake: His willingness to help his friends, below or above 75 F, with a huge smile on his face. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Majid A]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When it comes to sustainability Hosseini Agha is the man. He knows how to sustain everything from a good job to a bad weather meaning below 75 degrees so he doesn't have to make kabobs.On a more serious note, I think Hossein is a wonderful father, husband &great friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Homa khamsi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A true friend, as we call sustainable friend. I always wish for 70 degree weather in Danville for Kabob, but lately Danville hasn't seen 72 - lol Happy birthday my friend]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mehran Yekta]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Not only Hossein is a great friend, wonderful husband and father to his family, he is also the best host. He makes a great martini and for some reason always insists to make it stronger for me.  Lets drink to your birthday Hossein jan.  Have a happy one. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Neda Yekta]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I most appreciate Hossein for his willingness to help and how much he really enjoys spending time with his friends./RBest wishes,/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nader]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When it comes to three mandatory and three optional tequila shots nobody does it better than Hossein Agha! Especially when Khajeh Khamiri is singing./RHappy Birthday,/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mitra]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We only met 4 times. I can feel your sincerity for every words I heard from you.  Now I know very well what/R Paul shared w/ us about you- you're truly a caring, fun, loving,kind,supportive father.    Have a blessed b'day through the whole year!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Violets Dimalanta]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our friendship have begun when both of us were hired on 1/6/1985 at Intergraph Corp in Huntsville, Alabama.  We have shared many memories from our kids’ birthdays, graduations, and weddings as well as many vacations and parties./R/RWishing you a birthday full of joy!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mostafa Madani & Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Best drinking body, a man with a great taste in music, a happy man and a great host. We like his 3 mandatory and unlimited volentary drinks rule!/RFunny-Great host,offers to make kabab for friends while not eating himself-using enema to prep for colonoscopy the next day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cyrus and Manijeh Danaye-elmi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Good friends are hard to find and don’t just get old. They only get better as they age, like a fine wine. Wishing Hossein a birthday full of joy.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mostafa Madani]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I met Hossien, when I was engaged with my wife here in Huntsville Alabama 1985.  We get together with few other friends and having Guys party. Started with Vodka Oranjuce and ended up with TQUILA. Dear Hossien Happy birthday.   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ahmad Khoshgavar]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm so proud to call you Dad.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paul Dimalanta]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Generous, caring, and always will to negotiate./R/R/R(I'm a better man having been able to watch you in action.)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paul Dimalanta]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hossein's love of Iran and its culture and people and traditions is admirable. I love receiving his emails w amazing photography of beautiful scenery from Iran. I also know he adores his family and I respect that tremendously. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Floria Hakimi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hossein makes keeping in touch with family a priority, both here and in Iran. He helps us all stay connected with each other. ( and makes one mean appletini too! ) Happy belated birthday!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Saeid, Stacy, Cameron & Alex]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have too many memories with Hossein to list here. Lunches at Intergraph, our poker nights, vacation trips, watching rainbow parade in NYC, our kids growing inseparably, and many more. Happy birthday, old man./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ahmad Alavi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sense of humor! Thanks for always making everyone around you laugh. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bobak Emamian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/RI always had fun with Daash Hossein and I enjoyed his jokes.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frydon Torabi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sadly, I haven't had the opportunity to get to know Hossein's most inner qualities yet. However, from limited period of time I have spent with him, his best qualities are being jolly, easy going with ever available helping attitude. Wishing him many happy returns.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mahmoud Amirfathi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hossein agha is very funny, his jokes crack me & Soussan up....He is a great friend, reliable & trustworthy, and on top of all he makes awsome kabob koobideh....Happy Belated Birthday Hossein Jaan/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Vahid & Soussan Haghiri]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have always loved that Hossein get to our gathering and the dynamic change immediately. my personal favorite of him is our family trip together, is so much fun!   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mahnaz Emamian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He is funny and very able to put you at ease. I enjoy his presence and always looking forward to seeing him./RWish him a very late happy Bday./RThank you Pooneh jon./RHabib]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[HABIB ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My friend is fun and full of life. /RHe creats a positive fun atmosphere around his friends. /RHe is easy to talk to and a loyal friend./RHappy birthday Hossein ?/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mojgan Ahmadi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Amoo Hossein, I love your sense of humour and laughing with you. Your laughs are contagious and you have such a positive presence, it is so great to be around you. /R/RHere is to many more birthdays and hopefully a big reunion very soon with everyone! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Neshat ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hossein is kind, sincere and a friend with principles that I have come to admire, share and value. I actually look forward to receiving Hossien’s e-mails; the range of material that he selects to forward is impeccable and speaks to his principles and love. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ali Torabi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear uncle /RYou cant imagine how l love you/R i always think about abeautiful days which we have in tehran...../RPlease dont forget .../R"Distance means so little when someone means so much..../RI love you with all of my heart and wish you the best /RKiss you /RHappy birthday"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Parisa aminian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hossein is my beloved brother. He is so kind, supportive and generous. Every time I think about him, I am grateful to God for giving him to me and my family. I can't imagine one minute of my life without him. He is my hero. He is everything to me. I love you Dadashi.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leila]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hossein has one of the best sense of humors and that goes very well with his warm personality./R/RHappy belated birthday Hossein jan ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[saied behzad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He loves the three ladies I love very much and makes them happy. He looks so rugged and stubborn but when it comes to his kids, he is very accommodating and loving. He is so ugly that next to him I feel very handsome and attractive.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Masood & Sophia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hosseinam, parandeye mohaajeram ke kheili zood az man joda shodi, agar budi az to dars haaye mohabat va fadaakari va khanevadeh doosti ra bishtar mi aamokhtam. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Madarat]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aknoon ham be hame migoyam agarche Hossein az man door ast vali gooya ba man zendegi mikonad va be man kheili nazdik ast. Khatere haaye khobi az to daram ke hich gaah faraamoosh nemikonam. Doostat daram.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Madarat]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Hossein. I am so happy and proud to have you as a brother-in-law. I have always admired your enthusiasm toward life.  I will always remember your happy and emotional face at Pooneh’s wedding, especially your first dance.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, Parvaneh & Fariborz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I remember your wedding with Afsaneh in Utah with everything that we all did together. The cooking, salad preparation and decoration. Fariborz and I still talk about those memories.  Looks like the activities were repeated, but this time it was for your oldest daughter.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, Parvaneh & Fariborz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The second day after Pooneh and Paul's wedding, at breakfast prepared by Amou Hossein, my dad and Amou Hossein are making jokes at each other's expense. A family friend assures me, “Don’t worry, in Persian culture, this is how we say I love you.” ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarvnaz Torabi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hossein jon:/RFirst of all Happy Birthday, hope you stay happy and healthy for years to come./RWe always have fun when we get together, lots of joking, drinking and Persian music./RI admire your caring for friends and relatives and staying in touch with everyone./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Hassan Emamian ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hossein is a lovely and friendly man and is great company!/R/RI wish him Happy Belated Birthday and may he be blessed with a wonderful year!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Minoo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday my friend, you are that one treasure I found in Huntsville and hope I never lose. I miss old days that I would gang up with Afsaneh and would give you hard time to help up in the kitchen ...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sousan Karimi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Man 25 sal ast ke ba Hossein doost hastam. Ba eenkeh dar 20 sale gozashteh az ham door boodim, vali hamisheh ghalbe pak va bi alayesh uo ra kenar khodam mesle baradar dashteh am.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Saeed Karimi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday! What we love most about you is how u always bring laughter into the room & it always makes everyone feel comfortable. It's a gift that not many can claim to have bc it has to be natural and truthful & u have that touch! We love ur warmth & genuineness!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tima & Poorang Aurasteh ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Awesome Cousin that I grew up with,/RHappy belated birthday and wish you the  best on your birthday Hossein jon!/RLove ,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Farid Ashoor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love Hossein's passion for good persian music! I always think of Hoessein having the best selection of good music and his love for the Iranian culture! And I absolutely love the energy and attention he gives my baby girls!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Parnaz Aurasteh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love to play with "Hossie"!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lilly Foruzesh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I truly appreciate how warm hearted you are. We clicked from the get go and I always have a smile on my face when I see you. Thanks for being on my team.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Danny Foruzesh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your pep talks! As soon as something "bad" happens I call you and you put me at ease. You erase my anxiety and give me strength. Your words are always so comforting. I don't know what I would do without your support & perspective. I only hope I can do the same for you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Taraneh ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Salam Dadash, /R/RYadete ghadima too khuneh tanhaa ke mishodim mishesti roo sinam, dastamo migerefti va mizadi too suratam va migofti hala mikhay chikar koni?! :) Hamishe ba in khaterat be yadet hastam va hamishe dustet daram.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ali]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We've always had fun,/RWe always shared great time. I'm So very glad that u are a /Rcousin of Mine ... /RHappy birthday to u !!!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Haleh ashour]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to you! I hope you live happily with your lovely family. /R/RWish you the best :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maryam Aminian]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Uncle,/R/RI hope that for every candle on your cake you get a wonderful surprise. /R/RHave a fabulous year, love you forever.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Parsa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Pesaram,/R/RHamishe baase eftekhar va sarbolandiye man hasti, Tavalodet Mobarak.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Baba]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We always enjoyed your delicious and best kabob Koobideh in town. Felix is looking forward to have temperatures over 85 when he is in Danville. Anne and I are hoping to try your vegetarian Koobideh. Happy birthday Hossein,/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anne, Felix and Mansour]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are such an amazing father and an incredible role model. I am so very lucky to have been raised by you and to know that I can always count on your support whenever I need it, even if I don't ask for it. All of my happiness in life is because of your many sacrifices.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pooneh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hossein jan/R/REy famil aziz/R(hamsare Afsaneh-jan)/R&/REy doost aziztar/R(behtarin doost hamsaram Alijan)/R/Rtavalodet mobarak.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sharareh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hossein,/RYou've enriched my life with wonderful memories that makes me smile. And many embarrassing moments makes me laugh./R/RYou are a true friend. You are a brother to me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Maziar]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Words to describe my man would be: /RVery very../Rsmart, handsome, funny, loving, protective, stubborn, trustworthy,so manly, goofy, loyal, amazing husband,wonderful father, great friend, beautiful soul.. the absolute best. He is one of a kind and he is mine forever.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, your beautiful wife]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love how easy you make it look to put your family before yourself and to always take care of us. There has never been a moment in my life where I didn't feel supported & safe-- I am truly blessed to have you in my life. Because of you I know how to love selflessly!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Taraneh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>