<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2758-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/30/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Susan Peters]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[836 Commercial Street]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Weymouth]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[MA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[02189]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_60]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sand]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[To Anne & Paul 9-12-2015]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Anne and Paul Noble]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[With love and best wishes!]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul and Anne,/RThanks so much for the memories you have created: Holidays,Birthdays, Weddings, Many wonderful times, THANKS/RTHE BEST SHRIMP!/RLove]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Marie and Uncle Frank]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are so many things I like most about the two of you, but your love of family is by far my favorite. You are the most gracious hosts of every family celebration. Happy Birthday to you both! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, Lois]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My cousin Paul basically pulled the trigger for me and got me into EMC for 8 unforgettable years. One of the many things I will never forget. Paul and Anne always go out of there way to ask my wife Judy and I how we are doing? How are our 3 kids? They care about Family!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Greg & Judy Stapleton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My wife Judy always says to Mom , Marie Stapleton of course at the bar when we arrive." Marie I will send Greg over for more of that Shrimp and Wine I can't stop eating and drinking at Paul's Parties" His parties are so special!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Greg & Judy Stapleton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aunt Anne and Uncle Paul you have always inspired me with your kindness and generosity. But it is your devotion to your family and to your values that warm my heart. Wishing you the best in this milestone year and beyond.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kenneth and Jodi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Anne and Paul Happy Birthday to you both!  Thank you for your kindness throughout the years!/RCheers!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary & Joe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/RTo our good friends and neighbors who make Black Rock a special place to live. We thank you for the wonderful times we spend together.  We wish you a very happy birthday celebration.  Cheers to a great couple!  Sheila and Dennis ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dennis and Sheila Haley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Anne's crockpot beef stew/RExtra Oreo's and milk after dinner in Westfield/RFor this and much more.../RTHANK YOU!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The best bed and breakfast in Massachusetts]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David and Melanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Anne and Paul! We will be sending our love and big "cheers" from Chicago! Here's to making 60 the best year yet! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love,  Brian and Heather ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Golfing with Paul has been a lot of fun, he is a very gracious guy....both on and off the course.  Best wishes to Paul and Ann for many more happy and healthy years together!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rick and Jill Blake]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 60th to Anne and Paul...always among the first to lend a  helping hand or a word of encouragement, but most noteworthy is their generosity and commitment to family....oh, and Paul's rendition of Madeline Kahn's "I'm So Tired."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pat & Steve]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's hard to choose just one thing but if I have to choose one it would be the profound love you have for each other. That love has inspired not only your children but all of your nieces and nephews. I'm one lucky girl to witness such great love! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[~Megan ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wow! Our idea, and we are hard pressed to find just one thing.  It would have to be the extraordinary love you have for all - each other, your family, your friends. Your devotion is an inspiration to us all. Best wishes for the happiest birthdays ever!  We love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tim and Susan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing we like most about Anne and Paul is their dedication to each other.  It's almost like one word - "Anne and Paul".  Their love and respect for each other is so prominent that it refreshing to see a couple so in love.  Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary and George McG]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From holidays and weddings, to neighborhood parties and BBQ's, when we were growing up our house was always where good times happened! /R/RThank you both for being the world's best host and hostess, the ones who always bring our large, crazy, and fun family together!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joanne, Ted, Jack and Sam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There is not enough space here to tell you how important you are to our family! We are so very lucky to have such kind, loving, and generous people in our lives! Your commitment to each other and family is inspirational. You also laugh at our jokes, which is awesome! :)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The LaFleurs]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Generous in spirit, opening your doors for celebrations, togetherness, respite. Generous with your time and energy, always thinking of how to make life beautiful for the others. Generous in love and joy, your marriage inspires and blesses us. Happy Birthday. Loveyou.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lauren & Matt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Anne & Paul, I will always be grateful to Montrose for introducing me to your wonderful family.  Your passion for leading and helping others inspires me to follow in your footsteps. Lauren is a cherished friend and colleague and I love her girls. We are blessed!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, the Schiller Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for creating such beautiful memories, laughs and good times for our family.  Faith, Family, Friends.  Happy Birthday wishes to you both./R/RLove Jane]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jane Stapleton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Anne,/ROne of the best things in Montrose history is my chance to work with you on the DeTore Dinner.  I learned so much from your generous knowledge and skill.  Thank you for giving selflessly to the school we all love.  I hope to continue your legacy of greatness.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Jen Schiller]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can't say enough about all that you've done for me. Everything from co-signing the contract for my first cellphone, to helping to set me straight when I had dropped out of college, I wouldn't be where I am if it weren't for you. Thank you, and happy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Liam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for the wonderful parties you have had over the years. It is always a highlight to enjoy such good times with you & our whole family together. Thank you for celebrating your “special” birthday with us all this year! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frank & Kristin Stapleton ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will always appreciate and cherish your open hearts and open doors...whether we are crawling through caves in NH, or you are giving me huge life advice in ACK, it's always a positive and happy experience. I love you both! Happy Birthday(s)!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jane (and Mat & Patrick)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ One thing I like most about Anne & Paul is the kindnesses they have extended to so many.  What 60...when did that happen! Enjoy, nothin' to it!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Much Love To You Both, Alicia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aunt Anne and Uncle Paul, /RI admire both of you. I admire your dedication to your family, your faith, and to one another. I admire your willingness to put others first and feel fortunate to count myself among those others! Happy birthday to you both. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Emily]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A very happy birthday to you both!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barbara and Jack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[They're my parents.  They're the most kind, charitable, and loving people I've ever known.  They're the example upon which I model my life and they represent the goal I can only hope to someday achieve in my life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gregory ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday !! Wishing you a wonderful celebration. You both have contributed so much to Black Rock and the community./RThank you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gail and Larry O'Toole]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I love most about Aunt Anne and Uncle Paul is their kindness. They have always been so warm and welcoming and loving. We are honored to be a part of this celebration.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer and Matthew Batson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday!! Wishing you a wonderful celebration. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Don and Dorothy ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Paul and Anne,/R/ROver the years we have had many opportunities to observe your generosity of spirit and strong sense of family.  We have enjoyed being there for many special family events along the way.   Wishing you joy and happiness for many years to come.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Liz and Dave McHugh]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to a very/RNoble Couple!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy & Charlie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["What lies behind you and what lies in front of you, pales in comparison to what lies inside of you."/R/R- Ralph Waldo Emerson/R/RThe happiest of birthdays to both of you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tom Fiske]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Anne and Paul, /RI want to wish you the happiest of birthdays on this day. I can't thank you enough for everything you have done for not only myself but the entire Peters family. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kevin ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 60th Birthday to two of our best & kindness friends!!! We've had great times from Anne's first fishing derby to the Stroll with Smelly/RSanta at the White Elephant & so many more especially those great dinner parties!  Thanks for so many good times over the years!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Karen & Bob ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I often feel myself lucky to have such an incredible family.  Aunt Anne and Uncle Paul, you truly embody this idea of family with your love, generosity, and inspiration to live life fully.  To you on the great occasion... Slainte!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brendan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul and Anne, your friendship means a lot to us. Happy 60th and many, many more?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Judy and Barry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 60th Birthdays Aunt Anne and Uncle Paul!  As you reflect on this milestone, I want thank you both for the support and kindness you have always shown me.  Keep living life to the fullest, notice the good, laugh, savor memories. Each day we have is a privilege!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Meighan, Tim and the girls]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Anne and Paul, I would like to thank you for including Paula and I in your 60th birthday celebration.  To get to this place and age with the person you love is truly a Blessing from God.  Happy birthday! and God bless!  love, Paula and Paul McCarthy ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Paula & Paul McCarthy ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[They are a constant source of advice, fun, and support.  We can always count on them to share their beautiful home(s), delicious meals, and many many stories with us.  We owe so much of who we are as a family to them and their example.  All our love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Greg, Irina & Izabela ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bacon.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Benji]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 60th Birthday! Come on in, join the party. Bring your own joints. Not the ones from the 70's. The new titanium ones. Seriously, you guys are great and we're so happy for you. You both have done so much to bring the families together for such wonderful memories.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Thank you.  With Love, Ray & Chris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Paul and Anne,/RWishing you both the happiest of Birthdays!/REnjoy your Celebration!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Bob and Donna]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[That best portion of a good man's life, /RHis little, nameless, unremembered acts of kindness and of love./R~William Wordsworth/R/RIf Wordsworth knew you both, he'd have included "woman's" & "her" in this phrase. He didn't, but I do. Consider it edited, with love & thanks.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bethie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to two very special people that ooze a ridiculous amount of generosity, support and love into our family & pretty much the whole earth in general! Here's to 60 more yrs enjoying knitting, loud reggae music & pasta necklaces with kisses from the grandkids!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nicole, Nathan & the boys]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your Aunt Gloria and I Have fond memories of Welland Rd. Christmases at Myopia Rd. and your hospitality in Norfolk and Hingham when our families could all be together]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lots of Love, Uncle Bob]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 60th Birthday to two great friends.....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Terry and Pam McDermott]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love going to the beach with Grammy and having s'mores./R/RGrampy always gives us chocolate milk!/R/RI love snuggling with Grammy, and Grampy gave me a piggyback to the deep end of the pool.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Josephine, Anna Rose, & Mary]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whether it's snacks, wine, Toots and the Maytals, or your home, you're always willing to share fun, wonderful things! Thanks for buying extra milk and keeping Yorks in the freezer. Living with you was one of my most favorite summers ever. Happy birthday! Love you both.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Katherine ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aunt Anne & Uncle Paul, where do I even begin. Thank you both for your support, your hospitality, and your love (and also those Lola dinners and porch snacks.) Happy 60th to both of you, love you guys so much! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Erin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our hearts hold more than the brain can ever express./RHow do we say who we are to each other? We're laughter & tears, strong support, comfort, wholeness & acceptance. We're so much love & gratitude. We're family./RWords are dumb & can't quite do it -- but our hearts know]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Loveyou, Karen, Larry & the crew]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy, happy birthdays!/RWith much love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Noble - Hepinstall Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[These three remain - Faith, Hope, and Love.   And the greatest is love.  Amazing how your love for each other, for family and for your friends was such a common theme. Not surprising, just amazing!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>