<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2760-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[8/31/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Jennifer Stein]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[1220 E. Osborn Rd]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[Ste. 102]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Phoenix]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[AZ]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[85014]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Tony: 40 Years of Awesome]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Tony Stein]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[From all the people who adore you]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're damn good looking.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your damn good looking wife]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're a good papa because you've never dropped me on my head.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Noah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are always there for the people you love. No matter what. Your loyalty and devotion to your friends and especially your family, shows the amazing kind of man you are.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, your wife]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are such an amazing dad. Not a day goes by that I don't hear you tell Noah that you're proud of him, you love him or something that will boost his confidence. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, your wife]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tony is a great dad, husband and friend.  It is always nice to talk with him about sports, religion or just to catch up about life.  Tony is one the best people I know and I'm grateful to have him as a friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jon Larsen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Loyal, Caring, Respectful, Honest, Dependable with such attributes as this I truly have been blessed to have friend like you. We met when we were 13 that was 27 years ago. I look forward to another 27+ years of friendship. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alex Cota (AKA Scooter!)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tony has to be one of the nicest, layed back guys I have ever encountered.  Great family man,  great friend and I consider myself very lucky to have him in my life.   Happy bday bud!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Glynner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tony's the definition of a guy's guy.  I can go years without seeing him and the moment we see one another, it's like no time has passed.  I had some of the best times of my life side by side with Tony and look forward to more  of those as we grow older!  Love you man.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Preston]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Tony! Happy Birthday you old man?! I can only say that for one more year and then I'll join you. I can't believe we're reaching the 40 yr milestone. You are a great family man(expanding I hear-Congrats!)and a sincere,kind and genuine friend. Never change. Cheers!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stephanie Ray]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Aside from being an all-around stand up guy, Stein has kept my hiney warm on MANY a night (camping, folks!).  Our own personal Paul Bunyan and Fire Stoker, we owe countless warm nights, and bronze marshmallows, to Tony's master fire building/poking/logging skills!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shana and the Kinnerpup's]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Man, mushy is tough but in my nearly 20 years of first working with Tony (sweet pony tail brotha man), then becoming great friends, it's been a pleasure to see this guy evolve into such a great family man. Blessed to have great friends like you Big Stein.  Happy 40th!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dan Carter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Because there are so many things to say about Tony; it is difficult to focus on only one thing.../RBut here goes./RTony  is one of the most kind and thoughtful man I have ever had the priviledge to know. God has blessed my life by allowing me to be his Mother.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Best son-in-law anyone could ask for. Best dad to Noah and husband to Jen. We are blessed to have you as part of the family. Love you lots!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carolyn Steere]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tony, you help me be a man around the house! Not only do I not know how to use a power tool; I might actually be afraid of them. I appreciate your willingness, and time, to help me anytime I need something done. You are very giving which makes you a real man! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike Saxby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We were so honored to have you be the person to marry us.  You embody peace, love and faith and there was no one else we wanted to join us together in holy matrimony!  In that way, and many others, you will always hold a special place in our hearts.  Love you, Tony!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Saxby Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bachelor party! From hour one it was shenanigans & indulgence with a solid gang celebrating your next chapter. If I had to pick one moment, or maybe compilation of moments, I would reference it as “Dave.” Crazy we were all single with no kids then…]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Saxby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Every time I'm kicking Mama and she says, "quick, Stein, feel, she's kicking!" I rarely cooperate and continue to kick. Not because I don't want you to feel me, but because I want to stop and feel YOU. I love you already Papa.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your baby girl]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're my real life "Super Man." Sure, you can't fly and your eyebrows don't hold a candle to Clark Kent's, but you are the best Papa in the world. You make me feel like I can fly just by being around me. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Noah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are too many amazing memories with you to count. One of my favorites was on our trip to Sweden. When you so sweetly made me that Nespresso and didn't mix it all the way and I almost yacked on myself. You laughed so hard you almost puked too. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You will always have a special place in our hearts, your kindness, charisma and sense of humor light up any room you are in. Wishing you health and happiness and very Happy Birthday! /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brett, Connie and Blake]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tony, you've always displayed such class and care for those you love and I admire your dedication to your wife, boy, and soon to arrive daughter. I'm glad to call you my family! Happy Birthday bud! Have a great day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your cousin, Drew]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tony, you truly are an awesome human being. From taking care of my rad cousin Jen, all the way to that first time we openly discussed bowel movements- I can honestly say that you are truly a part of and loved by our family. Happy Birthday dude!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Smelly (AKA Kelly)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tone - wow 40 years or 480 months...time passes fast. I wish you a great birthday. You are in my thoughts always. Remember to brush your teeth, look both ways when crossing the street and don't forget to CHANGE your underwear (not add another pair HA HA!) Love you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tony, not sure you will remember, but you allowed me to console you one time when you were having girl trouble. I listened and said everything would be fine. Boy aren't you glad you moved on, what a great wife you found! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Pam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can't begin to tell you how much I appreciate the man you have become and the spiritual leader you are for your family. Thank you for being a part of my life and a great son to the love of my life, your father.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, Pam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I feel blessed to have a son-in-law like Tony!  I have watched him grow as a wonderful husband and father with a strong faith as the center of his life. I am in awe of Tony's steady and focused demeanor. He manages all the bumps in the road with grace. Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gordon Steere]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you like a brother Tony.  Always there, always solid! Remember?...Big Red, Cletus, TJ's Basement, Taco Night, "Jerr's" Cabin, New River, Tractor Party, Mountain Biking Summer, Hungover Soccer, Page & Plant, SB XXX, Montana, Rocky Point, Guys Trips. New Families!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy 40th, Stein! ~ Eric Vicars]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tony,/RHappy 40th! You only get better with time!  You have grown and evolved so much over the years, you are an inspiration. You are a true testament of the power of faith and love. I am honored to be your sister. /R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Molly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tony,/R/RAs we compose your "40th" Birthday card, we can think of so many wonderful memories from the day you were born and thru the years until today as you turn "40". The most important thing is that you lead a good life and live your dreams for many more years to come!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Peach & T-Bird]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tony, ,/RCan't believe it's your 40th Birthday already! ! Seems like yesterday we were hanging up Jordan posters and filing up your water bed and searching for leaks. :) Hope the next 40 treat you as good as the first. . Wishing you a great 40TH BIRTHDAY! !!!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lamberts ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Tony, what a wild ride we've had since I've known you back in 2000! From the times of going to San Diego with a bottle of Jack Daniels or going to Hollywood we used to have a lot of great times together At Balboa.  Happy 40th brother, and here's to 2nd part & many more]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dave & Mary Jo Gollobit ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When driving across country in the middle of the night, even when you want to get back to Indiana quickly, always remember to take out the gas nozzle before leaving the station!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love ya, Miranda]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I know I made your life miserable for a while (chewing up the contents of your wallet - twice, jumping the fence hundreds of times so you or Mom had to come get me, bringing you a decaying carcass as a gift), but you loved me anyway. Thanks for that. You're my master.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I love you, Snoop Dogg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I know I'm your favorite. Snoop Dogg doesn't hold a candle to my good behavior or rotten breath. I love you so much, you make my life so much better. You always take such good care of me and our family. I'll continue to be the best dog and prettiest pet, just for you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Kylie ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What an amazing life you have built. From our beautiful, growing family to the safe and joyful home we keep. You are the center of it all - grounding us, loving us, making everything better. God smiles on you for the man you are -faithful, loving, loyal, sweet & strong.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you, your adoring wife]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am proud of you and how awesome you are, how successful you are and charming, blah, blah, blah :) I love you a lot.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sister Jen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[For the past 10 years, I've brought you shelter, pain, a place to lay your head, frustration, mice, great memories, gray hair, falling tree limbs, sweat, tears and many other things you'd probably shake your fist and conversely, smile at. You're welcome and I'm sorry.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[2241 East Whitton Avenue]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bro, happy birthday!!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So glad you found so much happiness in Jennifer, thanks for giving me a sis from another mother!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm so blessed to have such a wonderful brother!You're amazing! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for being such an inspiration, I'm so proud of you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Of all these years we've shared, it's hard to believe you're 40, May we continue to walk through these years together and create even more memories.... Happy 40th Bro...<3]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 40th to you, my 40's were spectacular, hope yours are too. May your day be filled/RWith joy. Can't wait to get back out to Phoenix, MamaKat Bday weekend was't long enough.... Boy did we have fun though. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mike ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will never forget the 1st day I met you at the bus stop in August 1987. Both new to Tukee, new school and you were new to shorts apparently...sporting those pimp short shorts with the mullet. Classic!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kinnerup]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[How could I forget the many stories that came out of "Tonto Street" and "Grove Parkway?" All that needs to be said!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kinnerup]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will never forget and owe you forever for marrying Shana and I, means the world to me bro. Ken Dog always thought extremely highly of you and the boy he knew you as and the man you were becoming. If it wasn't him, you were the closest thing I had to a brother. Thanks.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kinnerup]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Stein, what a ride it's been. Want you to know that I consider you a brother and have learned countless, fantastic traits from you over the almost 30 years. Growing with you has helped me strive to be a better man. Love you for this brother!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kinnerup]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Jennifer, Noah and the little prize on the way are extremely blessed to have you./R/RHappy 40th birthday you old effer!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your bro, Kinnerup]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[This year brings many milestones: Your 1st Super Bowl, our son turning 4 years old, our marriage celebrating 10 years, your 1st round of golf on Pebble Beach, your 40th year of life and bringing in a new family member. What a ride! I hope the next 40 are just as great!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love you so much, Jennifer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>