<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2768-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[9/2/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Constance Sizemore]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[1038 John Hill Road]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Walnut Cove]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[NC]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[27052]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[What do they have me doing...?]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[F. Alan Koontz, M. D.]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Friends, Colleagues & Co-workers]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm so sad you're retiring! You have been so good to us over the years, especially helping with wonderful EPIC issues!!  Thank you for always being so down to earth and making us feel special! Hope you have many happy hunting trips now! Many best wishes to you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tammy Johnson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Over the years and through our many name changes, you have been a pillar of this corporation.  Providing valuable insight and support. /R/RAnd so it is with a heavy heart and many fond memories that we wish you all the best in your new adventure ~ retirement./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Piedmont Triad Anesthesia, P.A.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hearing all the entertaining stories from his childhood. My favorite was the one about little Alan and his friends accidentally starting a fire. /R/RHappy retirement! You will be missed! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rachel Smith]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The visits with Max, Jack and Teddy.  Their visits always give me hope that one day, my Blue Heelers will be as well behaved.  Your wisdom and humor will be missed among the PTA family. Thanks for making PTA such a great place to work. Go make this world a better place]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Crystal Bryant, Business Office]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dr.  Koontz is always so kind and willing to lend a helping hand!  He will truly be missed!/R  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Radar Scabilloni ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am so going to miss my Stokes County Buddy! It has been a wonderful experience getting to know the kind and compassionate person you are; a light for those around you. I hope your next adventures are full of love and lots of laughter! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Emma Joyce]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There have been many changes over the years that I have been with PTA and you have always been there with your smile and good humor. Thank you for just coming around to say Hi when you came by the office and sharing your dogs with us. Enjoy Retirement, you deserve it!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy Moser]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a great teacher!  Always patient and kind!   Truly a joy to work with and will be missed!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathleen Boyd, CRNA]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Best of luck with your new adventures, Alan!  You will be missed around the halls of Forsyth.  You were always a pillar of knowledge and experience, and we thank you for all of your years of dedication to our group, helping build the wonderful practice we have today.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Simon Chao]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alan, my favorite memory of you is the time you let my friend Xu and I crash your home.  You helped me evaluate a shotgun, then showed us all of your hunting trophies and shared funny stories about hunts you had been on.  Thanks for being a great colleague and friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Simon]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always enjoyed his "animal" pictures and stories!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrea Robinson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[For 13 years I've been privileged to work with you- a very kind man and fabulous story teller. I've always enjoyed discussing history, comparing "baby" stories, and your smiling face each morning. Wishing you many years of relaxation & puppy kisses- you WILL be missed!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amy Oghalai]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Alan,/RIt was a pleasure and honor to work with you all these years. I am sorry you are retiring due to health reasons. I am sure you will find time to rest and get well and do things which makes you happy.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kumar]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for always being a great physician, boss, and friend.  You are a true "southern gentleman". I have enjoyed working with you over the years. Now it is time to kick back and relax and enjoy retirement. (You may even learn to love summertime).   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marlene Fulp]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for referring all those special friends of yours to me for anesthesia care during the last few decades, I really appreciated your confidence in me. Live life fully, enjoy the moments. Has it only been forty years?!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Peggy Jones]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alan taught a new graduate CRNA to use a miller 3 blade in 1997 . His quote "Learn to use this blade when you don't need it! Then when you do you can " I still intubated with the "shovel" many a times I have needed it. Thank you for teaching! Have a great retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Donna Clark-Riddle CRNA]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alan,/R/RThanks for the memories. . . /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Judy Ray]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It has been my pleasure to know and work with you and for you during my ten year tenure at PTA! I can't even imagine 39 years! I certainly appreciate ALL you did for us in the billing office! /R Take care - God's blessings /R HAPPY RETIREMENT!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Patricia Brannock]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have really enjoyed getting to know Dr. Koontz in the last year. We have had the most interesting non-anesthesia related conversations about foreign policy, world travels, and, of course, his dogs! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kellar lambert]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for all you've done to help make PTA such a wonderful company to work for! You will surely be missed. Enjoy this new chapter of life!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Taylor Bennett, Billing]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[He was such a delightful person every time he came in the office and called. Always made us here in the billing office feel so special! Gonna miss his jokes over the phone!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Courtney Miller]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I enjoyed most about working with Dr. Koontz was getting my daily dose of sweet puppy photos:).  I especially loved listening to his stories from "back in the day"!  /R/RThanks for being so kind and always sharing a smile! /RHappy RETIREMENT!  Enjoy!!!/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica Rose, CRNA ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We will miss your stories Alan, they really lit up the room! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Curt Johnsrude]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We will miss you so much. I will especially miss hearing you talk about the boys!! I hope you will send us photos and updates of you & your puppies!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for everything that you taught me over these past 10 years!  I've really appreciated working with you!  Happy retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Fabrizio]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have really enjoyed being able to work with you. Thanks for all the teaching in the CVOR! Enjoy your retirement! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jessica May]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It has truly been a pleasure to work for you for the past 30 years!  You are a great person and I wish you and Carrie the best in your retirement.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Darlene Shanahan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dr. Koontz,/R  It has been a pleasure to work along side of you. I have enjoyed your stories and jokes. You will be missed. Enjoy your retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Roshen Edathil ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Since I am a part time CRNA, I have only worked with Dr Koontz  a few times. His expertise in anesthesia was obvious but his love of the profession was even more impressive. Just wish I could have worked with him more. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Terri Walker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You brought a friendly hello to us. You shared your knowledge and experience with us. I admire that you and your wife use your dogs to help so many people. It's a very special gift that you give to others, especially the children. Enjoy your retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer Warren]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have had the pleasure of knowing and working with Alan for many years.  He and his wife Carrie are truly a blessing in my life.  I am so excited for his retirement and plan to continue to be a part of their lives.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan McGee]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It has been a wonderful working with you all the years. You and I have grown up in anesthesia together from the time I  first met in anesthesia school. I wish you, Carrie and the boys the very best as you continue to serve people but in a different way. Keep in touch. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sue Rikard]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite story is the time your Mom took  to get  shot of PCN. You told  how you run out and got under the car  and would not come out. I thank you for all the wonderful stories and advise over the years. Best of luck to a wonderful person.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sue Rikard]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's always nice to see you in the billing office with a smile as you make your way down the hall speaking to everyone. Don't be a stranger and make sure you bring Max and Jack back to say hello sometime.  Best wishes  Dr. Koontz!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Whitney Culbreth]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[  Dr. Koontz is a wonderful person to work with . I learned so much from him until this day I am very thankful God bless and keep thank you .]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[  Patricia Tucker  ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on your retirement, Dr. Koontz!  It was so great working with you - thank you for being such a wonderful mentor.  Wishing you much happiness, fun, and relaxation during your retirement.  You will certainly be missed!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Holly Pegram]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's been a pleasure to work beside someone with your knowledge and experience. I always knew that I could count on you in the difficult cases, it was the simple ones you were too busy for :). I pray that you, Carrie, and the boys enjoy this next adventure in your life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Danny Menser]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will miss how he comes around the billing office to talk to everyone and makes them feel special. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Megan Grohs]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Remembering your smiles, stories, and boys in the office, your frequent compliments on the staff, and the way you lobbied the legislators and advocated for the medical community.  You have been inspiring and will be greatly missed!  Best wishes for a happy retirement.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sherry Williams]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alan, I have valued our friendship over the years and have enjoyed working with you on the "never-ending" health care challenges.  We have won many battles, reached a stalemate on some, yet lost very few.  Your leadership and dedication has been a key to our success.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ted Fyock]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Best wishes Dr. Koontz in the next chapter of your life! I am going to miss that "positivity" in your voice regarding the "schedule"....you always say, "that's no schedule, that's a list!" And you were POSITIVE about that! I will miss that mischievous grin of yours! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Amanda Barnes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hearing all the wonderful stories about "The Boys" and logging in to watch them on camera at doggie daycare. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alison Lane]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will miss all your stories about your dogs. I loved the one about the skunk.  Carrie was on her own, you took care of the dog. I  remember the time you made it rain in OR 14, even the W-S fire department showed up for that.  Enjoy this new adventure. We will miss you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Celeste Conner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a true gentleman and I enjoyed working with you at PTA and getting to know you (and your dogs) better each year. Thank you for all your kindness and generosity.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelly Shircliffe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Dr. Koontz was a wonderful person to work for I learned a lot of good things from him he showed me how to do my job and for that I'm truly grateful may God bless and keep them always thank you ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Patricia Tucker ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I think the thing I will remember most is how he could always find humor in about any situation. He always had a smile and very polite.  His love for his dogs (which speaks volumes about character) and Angie's wish to be reincarnated as one of his dogs. We will miss you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Diana Jones ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I first came to work with PTA after anesthesia school, Dr. Koontz taught me so much. He was patient and kind, and had a calm demeanor which was  comforting to me as a new CRNA.  Thank you for helping me to adjust to my new role. God bless you in your retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer Grachen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We have enjoyed working with you over the years since your residency - from both sides of the ether screen! We wish you all the best as you begin this exciting chapter of your life. Let the hunting and fishing begin!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joel and Linda Morgan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It was great to work with you, I hope you have a long, happy, and healthy retirement. Enjoy!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shawn Brooks]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dr. Koontz,/R/RCongratulations and best wishes to you and Carrie.  You have always been a true gentleman. I will miss the stories about your childhood, your dogs, and your travels. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Melanie Good]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alan,/RI really appreciated the time you gave me your locker at FMC. I feel very fortunate and humbled to be taking over a legends "spot." Thanks for everything.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Will Andersen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alan/RIt's been such a pleasure getting to know you this past year! Not only did you help me with my anesthesia questions, but also with my puppy questions!? Thank you for always being so friendly and helpful - no matter what the subject was. I wish you all the best!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aliana Sindram]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Work doesn't end here.  Your new job is to ensure that you enjoy being retired, with flexible hours and relaxation!/R/RThank you for all your stories, your compassion and for bringing me muffins & calling me sunshine for so many years!/R/RI will miss you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Connie (CJ) Sizemore]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Well, it's been 31 years and I'm still waiting for the sky to fall as you have so consistently predicted. Scholar, Gentleman, Friend, yarn spinner and dog lover (though not so to all the mammals). Do not go gentle into that good night.../RMissing you already old friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dr. Dan and Kathy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm going to miss your stories about "the boys" and traveling advice for Yellowstone. (I have saved all your emails about the park.)  Hopefully, we will get out there someday!  Best of luck in your retirement! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jackie Gibbons]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alan/RIt surely was a pleasure working with you over the past few years. Thank you for your guidance and inspiration. You will be missed. Enjoy your well earned retirement]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ben]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It has been such a pleasure working with you these past few years, Alan!  I am very grateful to be able to call you my friend and colleague. You have had a wonderful career, but I truly believe that your best days are still to come!!  Happy hunting!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[McNeil Cronin ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for always championing what Piedmont Triad Anesthesia stands for:  THE PATIENT'S INTERESTS AND WELFARE MUST ALWAYS BE PARAMOUNT!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe and Chris McConville]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am glad my sons got to meet Dr. Koontz, to see what a true gentleman looks and acts like. If they grow up to be half as considerate and generous as Alan, they will be miles ahead of the rest of society.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dan Kennedy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alan you'll never know how much I've enjoyed our conversations over the years (a decades worth!).  Whether it was discussing anesthesia, the political horizon, or ballistic coefficients, I always came away enlightened.   Let's not stop now - I'll see you on the range.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Derek Reid]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alan you'll be deeply missed, but Carrie and the boys will still visit us, right?!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Derek Reid]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Alan. Always a gentleman. I respect the political efforts that you put in. Something I never had interest in. The practice and the management of it has certainly changed in our careers. It'll certainly change as much or more for the young Docs. /RIt's been a pleasure./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Middleton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Had a patient for Portacath insertion under MAC in OR 3 when we were called stat for acute EMD. Team was scrambling, started CPR, Dr Koontz performs emergent TEE, finds cardiac tamponade, his diagnosis saves patient's life, one of your finest hours we'll never forget!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Curt Johnsrude]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Alan,/R/RIt has truly been an honor, a pleasure, and a privilege to work along side you for the last three years. Your legacy in our organization and in our community is something for which you should be very proud. Congratulations on  a job well done!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Saliba and Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What a run we had. A roller coaster ride with merger, Med Net, Dixon, Pain Clinic, CRNA uprising, and that was just local. The state and national front was where you alone took us places we had never been. Thanks for that. We'll miss your statesmanship and steady hand.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Greg Hardie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It was a pleasure working with Alan over the years. He has represented our group and our profession very well at the state and national level. He is probably the best known entity of PTA throughout the state, and his footsteps will be hard to fill. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Terry Almengual, MD]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can always count on Alan to inject good humor and a generous dose of common sense into any conversation or thorny negotiation. His friendship, generosity and concern for others are some of the main reasons I have enjoyed my years with PTA. Thank you so very much.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[David Colonna]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dr. Koontz,/RThank you for always being so kind every time you came to the billing office, and for the many things you did for us to let us know how much we are appreciated. We will miss you. I sure hope you enjoy retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kipperly Miller]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>