<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2776-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[9/4/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Kristy Kluczwski]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[110 Hillwood Ave]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Stoughton]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[MA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[02072]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sand]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy 40th Birthday Kelly!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Kelly Spencer]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Love, Kristy, Mark, Caden & Shane]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Kelly! /R/R/RWe love you dearly xo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Caden and Shane Bubba]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You're such a beautiful person and awesome part is you are my cousin! I have so many memories of my visits with you and the family when I was younger and now! And you've grown into such an awesome person and an even greater mom to your littles. Enjoy your special day! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michelle Defaria]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[you are a hott badass mom! Never forget that ?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your cuz Jennifa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[For Kelly, /RYou are the "sassiest" girl I know. The one I can always laugh and gossip with. Hope you have a fabulous birthday like only you can!  To many more years of friendship.... Love you!  Enjoy your 40th birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lauren Sweeney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[40yrs ago a star was born & the world has been your stage ever since. Your life has been one the greatest performances for me to follow. With grace & dignity you have guided me, listened to me, fought with me & for me. You are one of my greatest gifts. /RHappy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love always, Kristy ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 40th to one of the most important people to me. I can always count on you to be thinking the same exact thing I'm thinking at any given time. You've seen me at my best, at my worst, and everything in between. I love you. Razzy and Dazzy forever!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jodi Petrillo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From 7th grade to college, the MeatLoaf fiasco, 5 Sullivan Ave  & “no regrets,” to torturous LMIC, to now family life, our friendship has never wavered. Countless chats & we can still have more to share. A friendship so unique, we can say it all with just one look.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy 40th dear friend! Love Ginger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kelly has been someone that I have admired since 7 years old.  She is the most caring individual with an awesome fashion sense that I always tried to emulate.  Now as an adult our friendship has grown into one that I will cherish forever.  /RHappy 40th!  Love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim Kelliher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am thankful for so many things in my life.  But more than anything I am blessed to have such an amazing person by my side to share them with.  Thank you for always being there.   I love you.  Happy Birthday.  /R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim  ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kelly  ~  Here is to wishing you the happiest birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kim Spencer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 40th birthday!  You look fabulous-as always!!!  So happy we became friends-your smile can brighten anyone's day! Looking forward to more years of laughs with you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stacey & Doug ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am one of the lucky ones to have had you a part of my life for...ever! I always admired you growing up. Your hair, your friends, your dancing! And I still admire who you are as a friend, mother and teacher! Thank you always for your kindness! Cheers to 40! Love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeannie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Mom/RI wish you a very happy great birthday. I am so proud of you!  I can't believe you're 40. I'm so glad you're my mom!  You're the best mom I've ever known. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sydney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Mommy.  I love you so much and you are the best mom in the entire universe.  I am so greatful that you are my mom and I am so excited that you are turning 40.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jake]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Beautiful Kelly I can NOT believe your turning 40...... I've watched you grow up, graduate, get married and have children! ?? /RHappy Birthday!!! ?? love Aunty Debbie Dunlop]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Deborah Dunlop]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I often think:/R"If I were Kelly, I would know how to do this!". She would say I'm crazy, but I know that it's true. /RLifelong bonds are rare and difficult things these days. I feel so lucky to have forged one with such a talented, funny, and beautiful friend.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tricia Barrueta-Stilley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My strongest memories with you are of the laughter we shared. The millions of giggles and belly laughs.  You were always the one who really "got me".  We Both had a crazy sense of humor and looking back on it we were pure comedy.   The countless late night conversations]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shoshanah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kelly, I am so thankful to be in your tribe. You are a true & loyal friend, & always have been. You speak your mind, I love that. Thank you for always listening with compassion&perspective. I ? your wit, style,&honesty. You know friends are with us for life&embrace it!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love forever girlfriend! Sarah DC]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's hard to believe it's been 36 years since I first met you.   Although there are many wonderful memories and stories.  I'll always remember my beautiful little flower girl who stole the show!!   That beautiful little girl has grown into an amazing woman.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Ya, Michelle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My partner in crime-literally. From B&E to stalking-we should be in the big house sporting orange jumpsuits. Maybe we should have formed a girl group singing Diana?. Let's not forget our stellar party throwing capabilities. I had some of the best times with you-HBD!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Alison McCormack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have too many fabulous memories to pick just one. You are special in so many ways and I have loved you to the moon and back since the day you were born!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kelly, you mean the world to my wife and to my family. Thank you for always being there for us, we greatly appreciate your acts of kindness and generosity. HAPPY 40TH BIRTHDAY!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Kluczwski]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Kelly/RWe wanted to wish you the happiest of birthdays this year.  You look too fabulous to be 40!!!  Can't wait to celebrate with you!!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Mike and Rachel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have been my friend for as long as I can remember. You have supported, journeyed, laughed, cried, listened and advised me... I could not have asked for a better a friend.  Thank you for our friendship./RHappy Birthday to my dear friend! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[love, tara and Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I can"t believe your 40!!!! You we're an awesome daughter,  You've meant the world to me!!!!/Rone of the memories I have of us is at the cottage in N.H.  When I went into the bedroom 1st and went into the closet--It was dark. You walked in I shined the light U sank floor"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[love Dad  I still laugh!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kelly,/RWe have been through every stage of our lives together....Greenwood Ave. days, dancing, working together, driving to high school together, and now raising our kids in Mansfield and trips to the beach. I am so lucky to have had you as a friend for all these years!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[I love you!  Love Kerry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the person who never wore the same outfit twice.  You truly are one of a kind!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Danny C]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am proud to know Kelly and call her my cousin. She is amazing in many ways. She is a wonderful and caring mom. My memories are always of her with a big smile frequently laughing. At forty she is as beautiful as ever and can rock that red lipstick ;) Happy 40th cuz xox]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cuz'n Kristen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[HAPPY HAPPY BIRTHDAY KELLY.     HOPE YOU HAVE A WONDERFUL BIRTHDAY.   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[DAVE & FRANKIE ANN]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sometimes we are just so lucky to have a wonderful friend walk into our lives...happened when I met you!!/RHappiest birthday ever, Kelly.....love you to the moon and back?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy  (aka Mrs. Sliney)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sand]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>