<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2788-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[9/9/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[David Plastino]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[1614 Sorrell Rd]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Malvern]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[PA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[19355]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Great Chief Riener]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Chief Riener]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Texas Nation]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[With your retirement as chief, I am one step from getting you out of here.  Then I will have a real chance to win the corn hole tournament!  Thank you for recruiting me and and my three daughters to join Texas and for the lifetime memories we have from the trips.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe V. ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Certified bad a$$!/RHonored to know you/RIdiot (the best kind)/REnvied by other tribes/RF. YOU!/R/RThanks for the good times bro. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tate]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[To the man that teachs the power of doing less to achieve more. That the air space under the radar is less crowed and less choppy./RAnd no one receives  a head shot when they keep their head down]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rich Lucia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mighty Chief Riener now fly into Great Sky with Brother Eagle.../R/RRest well Oh Mighty One. May the Great Spirit shower you in many beaver pelts and wampum.../R/RYour Warrior Brother,/R/RChief Two Dogs F$$$$$$]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Taki]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Texas Tribe Cornhole Tournament Champions/R/RSpring 2015]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Fran Sudall & Michael Riener]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Texas Tribe Cornhole Tournament Champions/R/RFall 2013/RDepends who you ask ...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Unknown]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Texas Tribe Cornhole Tournament Champions/R/RSpring 2014]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael Riener & Willie Jacovini]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[All the things I need to know I learned from Chief Riener./R- How to do as little as possible and embrace it./R- How to relax to songs without words./R-That the true honor is NOT being honor tribe./R-How to not worry if I haven't seen my daughters for two days./RThanks Chief]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dave Plastino]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[All I need to say is thanks for inviting me and girls to Indian Princess! Good time throwing bags and hanging out! More important the girls really enjoyed the trips!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barajas Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Best Skit by the Texas Girls under Chief Riener's leadership was Spring 2011 -  Seal Team Six: The Raid on Osama Bin Laden!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Proud Texas Fathers]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[How How Chief,/R/RThank you for inviting me and my girls to join your tribe.  You helped make us feel right at home from the beginning and look forward to future trips.  Now if you can only get Valencia to curb his drinking, we'll be in good shape!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Saydam Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Michael,/RThank you for making me and my daughter Isa, feel welcomed during our first Indian Princess trip. We look forward to many more!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Bartolini Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your welcome to my Greek Pistachio's anytime]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Taki]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We need another log on the fire]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Willie "Pigpen" Jacovini]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's not fair daddy.  Why do they (Texas Tribe) get to eat crabs and we don't?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Another Jealous Tribe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Girls, GIRLS... what the hell happened in here? God, that smells awful. Did Mr. Plastino bring candy, whoopie pies and doughnuts again?/R/R-Chief Riener overheard in the girl's bunkhouse/RFall 2013]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anonymous]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Do we have any songs with words in them?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[?]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm not walking all the way up there to greet them (Honor Tribe).  They can come down here.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chief Riener @ Camp Saginaw]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Good News Fellows.....2nd Place is Wide Open]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chief Riener starting cornhole]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Camp Administrator(CA),"Who parked on the septic tank?"/RChief Riener(CR),"Not us"/RCA,"Who left a present in the bathroom?"/RCR,"Not us"/RCA,"Who stole a bed?"/RCR,"Not us"/RCA,"So, you're saying you didn't do anything?"/RCR,"We're Texas, we never do anything."/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[-]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["No Honey, Greg, Dickey and Duane are not back up singers for Justin Bieber. Please go play Sweetie, Chief Riener just got a bad headache."/R/RChief overheard talking to one of the Marengo girls./R/R ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Warren and Derek]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chief Riener made every Indian Princess weekend one to remember. I can honestley say that those weekends were a highlight of my middle school years. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julia Brewington]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mr Riener was the best chief anyone could ask for!! He kept us out of trouble which was a near impossible task! Adventure guides was one of my favorite things I have ever done! Our Texas tribe family has an unbreakable bond thanks to Cheif Riener! Thank you so much!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Katie Economou]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chief Reiner,  with your unique leadership style, you have helped create memories that will last a lifetime for my daughters and me. It's been nice to develop some friendships along the way as well. Hail to the Chief and long live the pursuit of "Fire on the Mountain".]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Willie Jack ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As the late great Jim Valvano said "If you laugh, you think, and you cry, that's a full day.  Each trip I have laughed at Cheif proudly wearing his barbecue sauce or meatball gravy on his face, I have thought about the most favorable cornhole tiebreaker rules, and now--"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Willie Jack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[--and now I'm crying thinking of you retiring.  Also Jimmy V. forgot if you poop and you vomit--now that's a full day!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Willie Jack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the biggest laughs I have had over the last few trips was when Tom Faith fell over and landed in a zero gravity recliner trying to get to the Haagen-Dazs bribery ice cream at Canadensis. The look on his face was priceless!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Willie Jack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being my chief. You've made it one of the best experiences that I've had./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Willow]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you so much for everything you have done from setting up the whole thing, to calming all the kids down when there is a bear 200 feet away. Every memory in the Texas tribe has been a good one thanks to you. We will all miss you Chief Riener!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Savanna Jacovini]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Through the years I've been at Indian princesses I've seen almost all the sides of Chief Riener, the good side, the weird side, the embarrassing side, the serious side but my favorite side to see is his happy side!!! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sammy Plastino ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being a great chief and for picking all the fun activities like archery and pellet guns.  I always enjoyed the Saturday night steak dinners we had. They were the best!  You rock!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Isabella Valencia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being a wonderful chief. I am sad you have to stop.  We have had so many fun times with you as our chief like the fun activities we did -  archery and pellet guns.  One of my favorite memories is almost every time we ate crabs.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Katrina Valencia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I just found out you were the chief.  All these years I thought you were just communications lead for Texas since all I ever noticed from you was the emails about the trips:-)]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Just kidding!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[a simple thank you would not be enough to express how thankful i am that you were the chief. if it weren't for you, i wouldn't be part of texas in the first place! thanks for being an amazing chief!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[gabi valencia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Honor Tribe - Fall 2014]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Texas Tribe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Daddy  We have gone on so many fun adventures.  I love the banana boat rides, seeing a big bear and especially when we were honor tribe  All because of you.  It was a lot of work and I am going to miss you being chief!  I love listening to fire on the mountain/R love you]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Allie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Our first Indian Princess trip was at Conrad Weiser. On our way there & I started crying because I wanted to go home. In that moment, we were unsure about the trip & neither of us knew what to expect. Now I know they were the best weekends. Thank you for these memories.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sophie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/R/RChief Riener,/RWith Valencia becoming the new chief of the Texas tribe, does that mean we are going to have a hot bologna and PBR  get together every trip?  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dakota Tribe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The Grand Chief was trying to convince  Chief Riener to have Texas volunteer and be more involved. Chief listened . Finally, Chief said," You just don't get it. Our goal is to do as little as possible, fly under the radar and have fun." That is leadership at it's best.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[In Awe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["I think we should supervise the skit next year"  Chief Riener 2011, 2012, 2013, 2014, 2015.............]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sam Totoro ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When the skit called for a curtain,  the Dad's formed a human curtain that could open and close when cued. Dads will do anything for their daughters!   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[WPJ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I see no need for the professions of Attorney, Marketing or Sales executives - in a barter system, these men are for all intents and purposes useless. So these brave souls will be on the front lines. Some of you may die.  But this is a chance I am willing to take.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chief Riener - Canadensis 2012]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Texas is unlike any other tribe in the nation - Picture non conformity and/Rcomprehensive indulgence.  I promise, you and your daughter will leave as happy campers!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chief Riener - Letts 2014]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Tribal Council: "Sorry.  All the good activities are taken." /R/RChief Riener: " what are you taking about?   The pellet gun range is wide open.  Texas will take it"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Great memory]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[As usual, they put us at the far end of the camp...... which is perfect!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ - Canadensis 2012]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chief, you put us all in a place to succeed – a place where we could be hero’s to our daughters while feeling like we’d never left a Barcalounger.  Thank you   ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bear ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Not surprisingly, the girls all get along very well.  Something to do with Mom not being present.  The Dads are pre-screened by a very rigorous process to ensure you will be a proper fit to the band.  So, consider yourself honored to be invited to join Texas]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Texas Recruitment Letter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You asked for songs with words, I give you Ozzy Osborne……. All aboard! Hahaha]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Owsley “Bear” Stanley ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I believe we have set a precedence of late night activities and feel fairly certain we will be properly ostracized and isolated. However, let's coordinate early arrivals to secure the most righteous spot regardless of cabin assignments.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Saginaw 2013]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I was forced into a YMCA camp by older, smelly men.  I got them beer, food, & retrieved Corn Hole bags. Wordless songs filled the air and, worst of all, I watched some dirty spoiled little girls.  Then, they made me humiliate myself in some Quentin Tarantino type skit]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Au-pair's diary - unsigned]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["I think it would be cool to have all the Chiefs don a headdress and be part of Council Fire" - Chief of Chiefs Wolfington email to all Chiefs/R/RHmmm, I think it would be cool to have you be part of the Council Fire - Valencia add more accelerant.... ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Tockwah Fire]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mr. Riener/RDid we bring any other music aside from the Grateful Dead ?/RI'm only 10 and know every song in the Europe 72 album by heart./RMy Mom tells me that I ought to be in college to experience this life altering event. I guess you have given me head start in life. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brew]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chief/RIt has been 10 years since we were introduced. I immediately new at that time that I was meeting someone that will be a best friend of mine for the rest of my life. My family and I cherish the wonderful memories that we have shared and look forward to those ahead ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[God Bless Brew]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[his own music) and to Mr. Valencia, he delegated  . . . well, everything else.  The point is, Chief subordinated his own ego and the need to be in the spotlight to others.  One such opportunity arose when Texas was responsible to be the Master of Ceremonies at skit time]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Disciple Rossi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I was so thrilled when he provided me (a shy person who doesn't care much for public speaking) the opportunity to shine before the Nation.  While his motivations for subordinating his own ego are known only to him, I became a better person because of it.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Disciple Rossi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Chief, you have done a great community service in connecting such a wonderful group of girls and their fathers together.  The Texas Tribe is strong and you have left it in very capable hands (although Joe should  remember - the inmates will always rule the asylum). ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Disciple Rossi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thanks for inviting Julia and me./R/RIt was a stone groove, my man! You are, the most, righteous... .]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Disciple Rossi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Leadership exemplifies itself in many ways. Chief Riener's leadership style is subtle and nuanced. He consistently and graciously enabled and empowered others - like Mr. Marengo to whom he delegated culinary and entertainment duty (at least until Chief wanted to hear ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Disciple Rossi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being our Chief.  You were always there for us, whether it was reassuring us when we saw the bear or just helping us with our skit.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Megan Marengo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for many good years !  They were great and you were the best you could be !  We will miss you being Chief.  Thank you so much !]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Katherine Marengo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mr. Reiner - You were the best chief ever.  You made the best and safest rules and my 4 years so far the best years ever.  You couldn't be a better Chief because you already were the best Chief ever.  You always had everyone's back. Thank you so much.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Caroline Marengo]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>