<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2805-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[9/12/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Kira Sorensen]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[811 34th Ave E]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Seattle]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[WA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[98112]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[navy]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Don]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Don Sorensen]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[love, your friends and family]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It was "Some Enchanted Evening..." when you saw me across "the crowded" room and decided I was the one you would marry.  Thank you for the past 54 years.  You are a wonderful husband, father, friend and great horse helper.  I love, love, love, you.     ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Irene]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Don,/R/RI always think of you wearing an apron and making biscuits, or whipping up an angelfood cake, or checking out a simmering pot of jam, with Kate or Elle or Cal.  /RHappy Birthday!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Will, Nick and I have always valued your friendship, if not your politics.  I really love my role as your "little sister".  Happy number 80.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jonelle]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Life-10% is what happens to you - 90% is what you do with the experience. You have done much and we look forward to seeing you do even more! Happy Bday! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy and Craig Cupp]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have so many fond memories--I remember singing around the campfire on our many camping trips. Also the many wonderful delicacies Don created in the kitchen and on the campfire. My favorite memories were from just sitting and talking--I love to hear him tell stories.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandy Cornell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Don has a great sense of humor, and could always keep us laughing. When I think of Don, I see that knowing grin on his face when he has just given one of his jokes and he's waiting for the punch line to hit you. Have a wonderful birthday, Don, you deserve it!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandy Cornell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have fond memories of visiting in Bishop, cooking meals and making angel food cakes.  I firmly believe these moments started my love of cooking.  I started canning because of your raspberry jam! I love you tons Uncle Don and wish you a most adventurous 80th Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Jennifer ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Dad! Thank you for always being the most present, engaged, interested dad (and grandfather!).  Thank you for showing me how to be a great parent. You are the best and I'm the luckiest!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[love, Kira]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Gosh, we went all through Harvard School from the 9th grade; Stanford University in the same freshman dorm and later the same fraternity; and active duty at the same duty stations in the Army. Lucky for you Irene we didn't have the same wives,/RHappy 80th Don, many more!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Byron M. Tarnutzer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite memories with Don are our occasional lunch outings.  I always enjoy our conversations over good food and a glass of wine.  Colton is also very good buddies with Don, racing out of the house to say hello and wave anytime Don is outside.  Happy 80th birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Shane, Rebecca, Colton, Mason]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[1957 Stanford, CA: We heard Don had gotten bad news went to The Lanai, SanMateo to drown in MaiTais. We raced there and found Don snockered at the bar. We got him outside where he acted totally out of his perfect character--he relieved himself on the restaurant grounds.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dave Pastorius    ....   muta]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Kind, discerning,perceptive, thoughtful, witty, patient, helpful, intelligent, generous...just a sample of the very positive thoughts I have of you!  /RMany memories, but popcorn in the sun room when yours were young and mine not even imagined.../RMiss seeing you both!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barbara Kelley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your warm and wonderful smile upon arriving at Rotary, your invitation to get to know Chuck and me better, and especially your words of support when I was grappling with my 2nd breast cancer: "No problem, you already have the sweat shirt from that race."/RHappy Birthday]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chuck and Babara Atcheson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU! /RI always think of you and appreciate you to share time with me in Bishop. I learned a lot from your family.Thank you very much again and again.  With Love.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Keiko Yoshida , from Japan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From my 6th grade media project to Stanford to serving as my kids' "Papa" and everything in between, you are my steady example of how to live a life of hospitality, love, and good humor.  So grateful to have you as part of my family.  All our love and happy birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Leanna Beaber]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Don!  Wishing you many, many more.  Don't forget to Celebrate with some wonderful Cabernet like the Wente you and Irene introduced me to when you last visited Coalinga!  Have a Great One!  Denise LaMalfa]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Denise LaMalfa]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In the summer of 2014 I visited Don in Seattle.  It was a wonderful trip.  Not only did I acquire the camper, but Don taught me how to make jam. I'll never forget the stories of his family and history.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[XOX Gala]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Bday to my "little brother! We are the only ones to share a multitude of memories..that is very special.  Have a grand celebration, welcome to the 80's and next year we will celebrate together!  I love you, Josie..happy BD from my kids, dogs, grandkids and all!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Josie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Don:  Here's wishing you the Best Happy Birthday ever.  A memory I have of you is that you were the "greatest husband" that Irene could have.  You 100 %  supported her in devotion that she had for her horse and achieving the very most possible.   Your friend,  Bill]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Biggs]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Think of me and have a glass of wine for the two of us:   MY 80th BIRTHDAY also]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Biggs]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My favorite of memory of Uncle Don is from Christmas 1989. I had a brand new truck & Mom bought me a set of seat covers. Later in the day Uncle Don helped me put them on. Having grown up without a Father, that time spent with him was very special to me. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dorothy]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's been my honor and pleasure to know you over the years. You impress me every day with your work ethic and inspire me to do more and be more.  I hope to be able to be as active as you at your age. Youre a great man with a huge heart, and a good friend. Happy b day]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff , Kara, and sidney]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[All I want is to even the score.. lets see...I've sent one brisket and at least 2-Chicago Style pizzas. you-2 shipments of smoked salmon. I'm behind. That's what I love about brother Don; we don't know the score but we love the wagers..the bets on for 20 more..promise !]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brother John]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[...and one more thing..thanks for being there for our family..and for partnering in a marriage we all learn from..you and Irene are special ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[jsb again]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's amazing to realize that we met in the late 60's, Don, when Irene and I enjoyed making art at your lovely home in Palos Verdes!/R/RThen, what a treat to keep in touch occasionally, with our respective moves to different places!/R/RThank you for your good friendship.../R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Judy Schuster]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Don, Happy Birthday to a gentle-man in the grandest sense of the word; a loving and caring husband; a father who is an inspiration and mentor to his children; a beacon of light and a pillar of strength to all his family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary and Victor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Having you as a friend these past years has given us insight into the meaning of thoughtfulness, kindness and generosity. /ROur warmest regards,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mary and Victor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We are so happy to have reconnected with you after all these years!/ROur visits have been filled with great conversation, many laughs, much Wine, not enough Champagne(ha), reliving old family memories and just getting to know each other again./RDon, you are a great guy!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sandra and John Dye]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Don! I hope your day is filled with joy. Can't wait to see you in the gym soon! Keep being awesome ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Willie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Don, /RTwo exhausted schoolteachers, Bobean & V, will never forget your exquisitely prepared soups with lovingly-made breads which alleviated our daily sufferings. Then you'd crack a few droll jokes and ceremoniously bring out the surprise dessert!  We soldiered on...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Victoria Hamilton & Bobean Sorensen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday! I can imagine you celebrating in your cardinal red Stanford sweatshirt and college beanie with a cookbook in one arm and a dog on a leash on the other. In all the world, such a loyal, thoughtful, and attentive husband can only be found with Dragon Lady!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Victoria Hamilton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Don, We want to wish you the best on your big 80!! We've enjoyed our times with you through the years - hiking and fishing in the Sierras; touring Costa Rica & Italy together. Hope we can do another trip with you soon!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill and Carolyn Davis]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[/RThere is no friend like an old friend who has shared our morning days, no greeting like his welcome, no homage like his praise.              ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Oliver Wendell Holmes, Sr. (SMR&G)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Many men can make a fortune but very few can build a family" said J. S Bryan.  Well done!  You are one of a special few.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stan, Mary, Robbie & Grant]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When my father didn't have my hand, he had my back./R                  -Linda Poindexter]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Stan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You don't stop laughing when you grow old.  You grow old when you stop laughing!/R           -George Bernard Shaw]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Papa! (SMR&G)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Men are like wine.  Some turn to vinegar, but the best improve with age!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Pope John XXIII (SMR&G)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Wisdom is knowing I am nothing/RLove is knowing I am everything/RAnd between the two my life moves./R             -Nisargadatta Maharaj]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[We love you Papa! (SMR&G)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The most indispensable ingredient of all good home cooking:  Love for those you are cooking for./R                        -Sophia Loren]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[To the chef! Love, SMR&G]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[May you have all the joy your heart can hold, all the smiles a day can bring, all the blessings life can unfold.  May you get the word's best of everything!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Happy Birthday and everyday! (SMRG)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY DON!/R/RYou have lived a life worth celebrating - these 80 years!  Professional and educational accomplishments, Family, Civic contributions, and a wide circle of friends - we are so lucky to have met up with you (& Irene).  Besides being charming and fun! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan Teel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ENJOY Every Minute]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Susan T]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Uncle Don! I'll never forget the wonderful time we had when you came to Colorado for our wedding! You are such a fun, genuine person. I am lucky to have you as part of my family!! xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda Anderson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A memory I cherish is of a lunch we shared in Seattle after you picked me up from the airport. We talked about life and love over french onion soup and red wine. I remember thinking, "I am so lucky to here making this memory." All my love and happy birthday!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenny Pachucki]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ I hope you have the happiest Bd yet!  I love growing up across the street in Bishop & having you as a friend and 4-H Leader.  So enjoy having you share recipes with me.  Favorite?  Pasta Primavera, always brings back great memories including the fun in 4H Cooking class]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kristi Litman-Silene]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your friendship throughout the years has meant so much to me.  Even though we live many miles apart, I think of you & Irene often.  Please keep in touch./R/RMuch Love]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Krissti Litman-Silene]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Don:/R/RHappy#80!!  We have many happy memories of times spent with you and Irene.  Will always remember your beautiful Bishop house.  We pray there will be lots more shared occasions down the line.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Barb & Rick Wilson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy birthday Papa! You are the best baking, jam-making, giant hug-giving grandpa ever! /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kate]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy 80th Birthday!  I like making jam with you and having chicken dinners at your house.  You are the best grandpa ever!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cal]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[“It`s not how old you are, it`s how you are old.” - Jules Renard/R/RWords that you live by - baking, cooking, camping, canning, and all the things you bring to our family.  Happy 80th Birthday, and looking ahead already to 90!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of my many favorite memories with you is making jam. You were patient, helpful, and overall a great cooking partner. The jam ended up being great, and the experience was equally amazing./RI love you so much, and hope to continue making memories beside you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Elle Jones]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[My dearest Don:  From the day you delivered a guitar to me at the parking lot of Inyo Mono Bank you have made my day brighter and funnier. Your stories of growing up in Bel-Air and entertaining yourself baking carried into our lives with the delicious cakes!  /R/R/R/R/R/R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy Garner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ To continue: Sharing so much of our lives was a gift I will always treasure  You have a place in my heart right next to Irene's spot. You shall live there forever.  Sad I won't be there to see your smiling face You are a blessed man./RHappy Birthday and Hugs!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy Garner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for always lighting up my day with your quick wit and dashing smile!  You are truly a special person that I feel super lucky to know.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Katrina Rising]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Who could forget the great times we had as "Cal Sierra Appaloosa" members, when you handed off the gavel to Sue as President and the first thing she asked if anyone had anything to throw up on the floor for discussion?  I thought you were going to fall off your chair. /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Win and Sue Green]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ (continued)...script on Frances Perkins for Natl. HD.  I just thought that was so nice and generous of you.  That is who you are./RMay you have a wonderful day, and just remember, you've done a lot of good for a lot of people in this world!/RWith much affection.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy Zack,    Bishop]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Don:  Best wishes on your wonderful 80th birthday!/ROne of my favorite recollections Is when Anne was in 8th grade (8-9 yrs ago).  You and Irene were vacationing. Instead of relaxing over dinner, you discussed how Anne could improve her HD performance script]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kathy Zack]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Happy Birthday:  To me, I remember you as a spry, young lad bringing in delicious treats to HD meetings; leading us around the state cap filling our minds with interesting facts.  You were so kind to open your arms to me as family.  You welcomed my sarcasm & talked....]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shannon Winzenread]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Don Sorensen: We adore and admire your intellect, humor & great heart. You are our cherished friend, fellow wine taster & travel companion. From Bishop to Apple Hill, Stanford, Berkeley, Claremont, NY City, Plymouth, France, Iceland and Virginia, you are Mr. Saga Class!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tons of love from Carol & Charly]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[.  (continued)...to me as if I were an adult. You treated me with respect as you listened to my ideas,  Our friendship grew while I was a teenager.  You were someone I could be silly with, discuss food, or squeeze for a big tight hug.  /R   Though far away, our ........]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shannon Winzenread]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[  (continue)....our relationship will always be close.  I am blessed to have you enrich my life & to share my children when you visit Bishop.  Us folks in Bishop /RLOVE and MISS/Ryou!!/RXOXO]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Shannon Winzenread]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[   I have so many memories of hanging out with you & Irene. The best things in life are the people you meet & the impact they make.....consider your impact made!  Whether it be silly jokes, serious conversation, a life-lesson, I've been impacted by you.  Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lots of Love,  Sandi Linden]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Hi Don:  An absolute truth! You are the only good friend I would ever consider crawling beneath a raised foundation to help with electrical wiring, etc, that memorable day In Bishop.  Never told you I have a weeee bit of claustrophobia in those situations.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Terry Russi]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[(continued)   To keep me on task, I just kept looking at your rear!!  A most joyful 80th Birthday Wish from me to you, my friend.  Your Pal,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Terry]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the things I admire most about Don is his passionate patriotism.  At the UW Veterans Day parade, Don snapped to attention, saluting as each flag passed.  Recently, he gave me a bound edition of the U.S. Constitution and Declaration of Independence.  What a guy!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joan Wilson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[navy]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>