<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2807-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[9/14/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Matt Sebastionelli]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[2510 N. Shelley St]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Alexandria]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[VA]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[22311]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDEX_PRIORITYOVERNIGHT]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_50]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[For the Birthday Girl]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Ashley Sebastionelli]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Matty]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From the moment we first met, I knew what a special person you are! Your kind heart, dynamic personality, witty sense of humor, thoughtfulness and warm spirit are just a few of the wonderful things about you. I admire your strength and tenacity! Love you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bricklin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love having you as a sweet, caring, kind and fashion-forward friend and Theta sister in DC! Happy birthday! xoxo]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Taryn]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love when you speak with a Jewish grandmother accent....you are a great gal and friend. I am so blessed to have you in my life!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer Graebe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ashley's best quality is being an amazing person. She is such a great mother also an awesome friend to have, and I am proud to call her my cousin. Happy Birthday Ashley!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Olivia]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your welcoming smile, heart of gold, and sparkling personality make you a very special person to all who know you. /RHappy birthday. We all love you!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Rockwell and family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[one thing I like most about Ashley is her outlook on life in general.  She sets a goal and keeps on until she obtains.  She is a really classy lady and I admire that about her.  She is truly a special person and I am proud to have her as my great niece.  Love]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Aunt Bert]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love when you quote Mrs. Doubtfire: "Aaaaaargh! Laila, get back into your cell! Don't make me get the hose!" /RMakes me laugh every time.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Liz Weiss]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are such a loving friend, sister, wife and mother. We feel lucky to know you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Liz & Scott Weiss]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are sassy and stylish, even in pink sparkly shrugs or heart-shaped mom jeans.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Liz Weiss]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a true southern belle and serious businesswoman. /RI love that you are as likely to be reading Fast Company as Garden & Gun magazine. And could easily be featured in either.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Liz Weiss]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ashley, you are such a positive light in the world and we are so happy to have you as a friend!  /RThe grace and poise with which you balance being a business maven and an amazing mother is truly inspirational.  /RWe "Theta Love" you! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Abbey & Paul Ruby]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ashley, you are always so poised and professional.  Even on your busiest days, you flawlessly balance work and life; Matt and Kennedy are lucky to have you!  You are so sweet and we admire and appreciate how you always make others feel welcome.  Cheers to you, friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mallory & Chris Gurley]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Life's about opportunities. Thanks for giving me the opportunity to prove to myself, family, friends, and the idustry that I can make a difference on something I hold at such a high regard.  I hope I've allowed opportunities to spend time with Matt, K-Ro, and Nova.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bobby Twing]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your drive, strength, and energy is AMAZING!  You manage to make being a new mom, small business owner, and wife look easy.  We know how hard it is to balance all those and yet you still make your faith and church community a priority.  In short - YOU'RE AWESOME!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Stephanie and Jeff Day]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ashley is inspiring. She inspires everyone around her in different ways, whether it's to follow their dreams, to work harder, or to have more fun. Her passion for life is definitely contagious, and her birthday is the perfect reminder of that. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carol Burger]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing we like about Ashley is how warm and welcoming she is! Besides outer beauty, she really has a true inner beauty that shines. We are so lucky to be in the same family and wish you a very Happy Birthday! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Luis, Kat, Soph, Liam & BabyM]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The one thing we like about it is how creative and thoughtful you are. Happy Birthday]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Stolle's]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ashley makes any situation fun. She has an amazing ability to read any given situation and to determine what it needs to make everyone happy and comfortable.  Ash- I love you, thank you for being so good to everyone, always. Happy Birthday!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[ET]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to one of the most amazing daughters a man could be blessed with. I Love you unconditionally.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What an amazing mother, daughter, business woman and individual you are. I could not be more proud of you. Love ya.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dad ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Ashley is her refusal to fail. She is simply unwilling to miss her objective, doing what ever is required to achieve success. I am excited to see her teach our children the same life skills and watch them flourish in their life journeys.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matty]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are a great mom, a successful business woman and a good wife. I am blessed to have such a wonderful young woman in my life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Teri]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, I hope you have a wonderful day, wish we could be there with you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Teri]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[In conversation with any friends or family I call you my daughter-not stepdaughter. You have given me many years of joy and a lot of fun and couldn't have asked for a more caring, level headed and hard working young lady. Thank you for letting me be a part of your life.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Daryl]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Ashley's fierce loyalty to her friends and family is one of the things I love the most about her. She inspires me to be a better son, brother, friend and father. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matty]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the true definition of love at first sight. You have accomplished every goal you set so far. I could not be more proud of the beautiful, successful and wonderful person you have become. I look at you and say WOW that's my girl! I Love you more than words can say]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Ashley is her profound dedication to being a mother. She frequently leaves me in awe of her devotion to our new family.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Matty]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Not all sisters are born to us. Life saves some for along the way." Ashley is my soul sister; we think alike, act alike, and even look alike. I've had the time of my life with her by my side in so many ways. There is no one I'd rather be confused for in this world.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[MelRoc]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for being one of my first close girlfriends in DC- from epic book club meetings to camping trips and BBQs, it has been so much fun to be your friend. I am so happy for all of the love and success in your life :) Cheers to another wonderful year!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Siobhan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have a great sense of humor & can make people laugh and cheer them up! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You always take time for, not just me, but others in general. Thanks for all the great advice over the years! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have a 9 month old baby and somehow still have abs! Seriously, you look hot! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Even though we're all grown up now, I still want to be like my big sis in a lot of ways! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I am in awe of the many special qualities you possess that has captured my heart; your grace, charm, intelligence, energy, and love. And that you love my son with the intensity and wisdom of a wife and the gentleness of an angel./RI love you dearest daughter-in-law]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Judi Sebastionelli]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[sea-foam]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>