<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2809-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[9/14/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Susan Scott]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[3603 Kimberly Lane]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Ft. Worth]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[TX]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[76133]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[We love Noonie because...]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Susan Scott]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[Your Northeast Friends & Family]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You've made my life more beautiful and more joyful just by your presence. Thank you./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[joanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You've been such an integral part of my mothering experience, and I've learned so much from you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Seeds? No seeds?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joanie and Hannah]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[So many memories, not enough words adequate enough to express what you've meant to me.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Your charity, enthusiasm for babies & long career as a nanny have always inspired me!  I pray your nan-sons grow up quickly, marry & have many nan-children to delight you.  May God bless & keep you & Texas appreciate the darling they are inheriting!  Love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tora]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You have a God given peace about you.  You are always caring and loving in your words and actions.  I feel honored and blessed to have been in group with you a few times over the years.  I pray that God blesses you with all that you desire in TEXAS.  I will miss you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Libba Griffin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You may have moved West, but you will always have a permanent place in my heart and the hearts of all who have been lucky enough to know you. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Noonie, We can't help but be joyful when we are with you! Thank you for loving us and making us feel so very special. Our days at the pool will forever be our favorite Connecticut summer memories! We're thankful that we will get to see you in Fort Worth and Austin! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Nancy, Justin, Annie, Elliott & Sam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whether it was playdates in the park, Jodie's gym, seeing a Broadway show, studying the Bible, sharing a meal or simply taking a walk - everthying was always more fun when we did it together. Thank you. Looking forward to many more outings and adventures with you./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[“Many people will walk in and out of your life, but only true friends will leave footprints in your heart.” /R/RThank you for leaving yours on mine./R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[jb]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["The greatest gift of life is friendship, and I have received it." Can't claim this as an original thought. Hubert Humphrey said it first, but I couldn't agree more./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[joanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["A friend is one who knows you and loves you just the same." Thank you my friend./R/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joanie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Fair, Kind & Strong/R    Funny & Bright/RYour foundation in God's Word informs the essence of you ~/RI'll miss being in your orbit]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jenny Z]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[She has been determinedly steadfast to the best interest of our boys.  Even in challenging times (as there were bound to be over more than twenty-one years), she thought of them first, last and always.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff Williams]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I appreciate Noonie's steadfast friendship and kindness. I hope we will have the opportunity to enjoy a silly TV show or some Amarula in the future. All the best in Texas! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rebecca ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Sisterhood!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[XOXO, Mayree]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Susan is one of the most genuine and kind ladies I've ever met.  Her love for others is so noticeable and special... I will never forget the many kindnesses she bestowed upon our family and baby Seth this past year.  Everyone should have a "Noonie."  We'll miss you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jennifer (and Seth)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There isn't just ONE thing! But since I need to pick, Her special ability to be my safe friend who I can talk to about anything without judgement, and who has taught me about and helped me accept a whole new world for which I will be forever grateful.  With much love,]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Toni]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The way the light of Christ shines through your smiling eyes. It has been a gift& blessing to know you. Even though we didn't have the opportunity to connect much this past year you are in my heart,my thoughts & prayers. Jesus will walk with you in this new chapter!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelly Orban]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The Lord makes firm the steps /Rof the one who delights in him; though he may stumble, /Rhe will not fall, for the Lord upholds him with his hand. /R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Psalm 37:23-24]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You bring joy wherever you go! May God's joy and peace be with you and go with you always.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meg Newton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for loving on all our children, Noonie! They love you back, and we treasure remembering you snuggle and hold and smile at and delight in our little ones.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[CBS Mamas]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for sharing your love of Jesus and your love of his Word - may it be a lamp to your feet and light to your Texas path!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Meg]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[For I, the Lord your God, hold your right hand; it is I who say to you, "Fear not, I am the one who helps you."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Your Heavenly Father]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Susan, you delight in the Lord and trust in him, and your faith and faithfulness are such an encouragement to all your spiritual sisters. Thank you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All your CBS Core Groups!]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Noonie,/RWhat a joy to be greeted by your warm and loving smile every Thursday morning. Your gracious manner and kind words put all who meet you at ease and want to spend more time with you. Your compassion beautifully reflects the Christ-like love in your heart.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[With love and blessings, Kate Odre]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Noonie means caring and a loving attitude]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The love you have shown your boys has encouraged me to show more love at home.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will never forget the arm that crosses in front of me when I start to cross the street to soon or the hand that grabs mine if I fall behind.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The organizing and motivation to make the time for plays has given me memories I will never forget.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I laugh every time I think about the comments our kids have said to try to put us down- thanks for helping turn these in to humorous statements.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The whole relationship with the Williams has opened my eyes to a true selfless relationship, filled with love and putting others before yourself- it is a blessing to have you as a mother.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Friendships and family are important to you and I am grateful to feel important because of our friendship!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I loved it when we would get delirious and could not quit laughing.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One of the few in this part of the country that understands the finer cuisine: grits, biscuits and gravy, sweet tea, brisket, fried chicken and apple crisp, queso and other Texas jewels.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I love you and you are very special to me- thank you for your Texas support!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The wonderettes are wonderful women and you made a great president!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Barami and the 3 for 1 turtleneck deals.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The fact that I am coming to Ft. Worth makes saying good-bye mean see you later!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tiffany]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Take some Scottish Country Dancing back to Texas.  We are happy you were able to be a part of our wedding.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Michael and Tipton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Roses are Red,/RViolets are Blue,/RYou are going back to Texas,/REveryone will miss you./R/RBest wishes, excellent adventures, and  /Rdon't forget to build a tornado shelter into your new house.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love Sam, Karen, Michael, Tipton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Mud, messiness, swearing, buzz cuts and dangling your charges upside down over the pool...you are a good sport!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tipton]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We think they wouldn't have survived so well without you...thank you for all the pictures, the scheduling, the thoughtfulness and the love.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tipton, Michael, Karen, Sam]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Give my regards to Broadway, remember me to Herald Square,/RTell all the gang at Forty-Second Street, that I will soon be there;/RWhisper of how I'm yearning to mingle with the old time throng;/RGive my regards to old Broadway and say that I'll be there ere long. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[written by George M. Cohan 1904]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Susan,/RI love what a tender heart you have for children of all ages, and the nurturing way you show them the love of God!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Debbie Travers]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are not only my friend but a member of our family.  Over these many years we have prayed, laughed, cried and rejoiced in our blessings!  I look forward to this next phase in our lives and our friendship forever!  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Colleen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I have learned so much from your strength and faith ~ thank you for walking with me!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Love, Colleen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always thank God for you because of his grace given you in Christ Jesus./R/R1 Corinthians 1:4]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Colleen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[What's not to love about Noonie!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Harkey Family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Noonie  [noo-nee]/Rnoun, Texas Slang./R1. a term of address for a woman having  the status, function, authority of a parent/grandparent./R2.	a wise and trusted counselor or teacher./R3. a female friend or protector regarded as a sister./R4. someone who inspires/encourages]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Everyone needs a Noonie. How blessed am I to be gifted such a treasure.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Dear Susan, I absolutely love your cheerfulness, optimism and sense of adventure.  Your unwavering love and support for the boys, and the whole family, has not gone unnoticed. You have enriched all of us with your strength of character and good humor. I'll miss you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Natasha Kimmins]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Some people, like flowers,/Rgive pleasure just by being./RYou are one of them.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your selflessness, loyalty and dedication to your family and friends inspire me to be a better person.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I will always remember you with a smile on your face, serving with love and gratitude!/R/RMy verse for you: "... It is God who works in you to will and to act in order to fulfill his good purpose." - Phil 2:13/R/RPraying all his blessings in this next chapter of your life!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Crista Mathew ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I like most about Susan is that there isn't just one thing to love about her! Susan is the friend we all crave. She is the sister we all wish we had and the aunt all our children need. Beautiful Susan makes others feel hopeful and loved. Who doesn't like that?]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sarah King]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["You'll be with me. Like a handprint on my heart."/R/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cale]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[It's only been a day and I already miss you more than I ever could have imagined. Thank you for everything you've done for me over the years. I can't wait to visit you in Texas, even though we both know brownies are a big part of that.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cale]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Because we knew you/Rwe've ALL have been changed.../RFor good.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[When I first meet Susan I knew immediately that she's the kind of person I would want to have as a good friend!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Anita Budd]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[pumpkin]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>