<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<order xmlns="http://fbns/">
<subOrder>
    <orderId>2826-001</orderId>
    <orderDate><![CDATA[9/19/15]]></orderDate>
    <shipTo><![CDATA[Tommy Bruno]]></shipTo>
    <shipAdd1><![CDATA[65 Steiner Ave]]></shipAdd1>
    <shipAdd2><![CDATA[]]></shipAdd2>
    <shipCity><![CDATA[Akron]]></shipCity>
    <shipState><![CDATA[OH]]></shipState>
    <shipZip><![CDATA[44301]]></shipZip>
    <giftWrapped><![CDATA[No]]></giftWrapped>
    <shipVia><![CDATA[FDXG_FEDEXGROUND]]></shipVia>
    <box>
        <shipQty>1</shipQty>
        <sku><![CDATA[FB_100]]></sku>
        <font><![CDATA[Unknown]]></font>
        <substrate><![CDATA[Unknown]]></substrate>
        <boxType><![CDATA[acrylic-clear]]></boxType>
		<cardcolor><![CDATA[charcoal]]></cardcolor>
        <titlecard>
            <heading><![CDATA[This is your life Bill Gruber!]]></heading>
            <to><![CDATA[Bill Gruber]]></to>
            <from><![CDATA[High Atop The Summit]]></from>
        </titlecard>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[One thing I enjoyed most about working with Bill is that I got to do it from four miles away! Actually, it would have been dangerous had we worked in the same office, building or even zip code.  Too much concentrated sarcasm.  Love ya', BG.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Williamson]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your incredible attention to detail, unmatched work ethic, and ability to make the complex - simple. /R/RI am forever grateful for you picking up my phone call back in 1988, and then recruiting me in 2000. /R/RI will miss you dearly.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tommy Bruno]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A thoughtful, introspective mover/groover who forged a sound (and vision) for The Summit that will serve it well into the future! Relax and have fun!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Rick Krochka & Steve Schmidt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[After moving from Akron to Lexington KY, the one thing I could count on to bring me a little of Akron was listening to Bill Gruber on the 91.3 The Summit app.  Plus you always reported what the weather was like back home.  Thanks Bill, you will be missed.  Congrats Bill]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carl Haines]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill, you always make Carol and me feel our music choices are important. Because you know so many facts about musical artists and bands you are able to talk about everyone's favorite artist.  Thank you for everything. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Carol and George Bruner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Bill, as a board member I was amazed and humbled by the impact you made in our community.  From board and staff, to the musicians whose first record you played "on air", you left a lasting impression. I will miss your voice at The Summit.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brenda Cummins]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill/R/RIt was a real privilege and pleasure to get to know you. I really admired your dedication and passion for The Summit. You made it a better station and you'll really be missed. Good luck and happy retirement. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Gary Benz]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The happiness in your voice, a pleasure. Your appreciation of music style and variety, remarkable. Your love of wine, history and new artists , encompasing. I joined because you helped me rediscover the joy of music I almost forgot long ago./RYou're a good music mentor.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frank Gorsuch]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for always making me feel welcome as a 91.3 The Summit volunteer.  Over the years I have enjoyed the Studio C interviews, members-only events and listening to you over the air.  Congratulations and good luck!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Mitchell]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Congratulations on a lifetime of building positive relationships that have made an impact within the community that surrounds you!/RTime to pursue your hobbies.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dante M. D'Avello and the TC family]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[IMO, Bill made a lasting impact in the lives of many in the listening area.  Always making time to promote community services, songs that seemed to speak to you when you needed it most, and a voice that always feels like a trusted friend.  Thanks and congratulations!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Crouse & all of us at PPBH]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From the moment I met Bill, I was struck by his passion for his work. He has always shown me genuine kindness and support, and I  am grateful to know him. /R/RCongrats, Bill!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[JD Eicher]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Where do you begin with an icon who has been a mainstay of the station?  The Summit would not be the Summit without Bill's nurturing its growth.  You have, my friend, left an indelible mark (or was that a rash?). With fondness we say: "Gruber has left the building."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Feltes]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill,/RIt's been a pleasure working with you and learning the nuances of copywriting for public radio. You are the best (comparative)! Come by anytime for your free Black Magic Cake (inducement) or I can deliver to you in my "Sky Scooter".  Enjoy your work free life!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joey Harper]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ I've loved your amazing outlook on life, getting dining tips, and wondering what you ate to have THOSE DREAMS! How can I  pick one thing from such a unique and special guy! You made me welcome from my 1st day at the station & your ode to me on Studio B "iced the cake"!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marilyn Stroud]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I'm adding my unique Life & Lyrics, since I'm the only person to have you as the interviewer! Bill Hall couldn't do evenings & I was teaching; you filled in very nicely, making m feel very comfortable in a very alien setting as it was so early in my "Summit Life". Hugs!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marilyn Stroud]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always enjoyed and valued Bill's breadth of knowledge of the industry.  From artists and songs to discussing the technical details of programming and running a station, I always learned something when Bill was in the room.  We will greatly miss you!!  Best wishes.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Mark Belgya]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I always enjoyed just talking radio with Bill./RFrom radio formats, Disc Jockeys, and station signals. He always was kind enough to lend an ear when I needed to vent my frustrations regarding our air sound on Saturdays on WKTL... I'm going to miss you Bill! Congrats!!!!!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dennis Spisak]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill, while working with you I've most enjoyed learning editing in studio D. You've always been patient and generous with your time when I had questions. The recounts of your dreams have definitely been entertaining. You are THE reason I'm here and love WAPS. HD2 rules!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie (Twin Peaks Lucy) DiVitto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill, I will never forget riding in a different car from your stunning fleet, many summer Tuesdays to and from Canal Park.      /R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julie (Twin Peaks Lucy) DiVitto]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill,/R/RYour intense knowledge, humor and wit will be missed! A true expert and professional, The Summit and the region is losing a gem./R/RAll the best to you!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Kelly Eppink ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you for making us feel so welcome.  From the first day, your smile and warmth truly made our team feel like part of your team! /R/REnjoy your new found freedom, just know you will be missed!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[All our best, Erin & Todd]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill,/RI most appreciated your wit, detail, and professionalism. It has been a pleasure working with you.  Thank you for giving me an opportunity at the Summit.  /R"No Fear" in your retirement years, relax and enjoy-you deserve it./RCongratulations and best wishes!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim and Patty Dyer]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[I was in my car listening to Gruber.  It was August 1st, Herman Melville's birthday.  Gruber gave Herman all the normal accolade about his book Moby Dick but the most fascinating thing was he injected "Sperm Whale" into the dialogue not just once but twice./RBrilliant!/R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Annette Yoho Feltes and her cats]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[ Who can forget that special moment over the Easter holiday weekend when Bill Gruber used his leaf blower to 'dust off the shelves' in the library and school house building. I have fond memories of good work, good philanthropy and good tunes coming from the Summit. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Thank You Bill. Skip Summerville]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You’ve become an icon within the station icon, Bill.  Thanks for your unwavering commitment. Every time I see the words ‘Death Cab for Cutie’,  I hear your voice.  Long may you rock!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Helen Fire]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill, yours was the first voice I heard one day while surfing the airwaves many years ago. I remember thinking "I could listen to this guy all day". Then I got hooked on the great music and service announcements too.  Thanks/ Best Wishes on a well deserved retirement!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andy & Linda Platt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill has been so welcoming to me as both a member of the Summit and a member of the Board. His kindness, rich wisdom, and love of music and the region come through in every word and action. His warm, familiar voice will be missed! ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Erin Driscoll]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill /RCongratulations on your retirement from 913 The Summit. My fondest memories of you are the many historical tidbits you would provide about the performers, venues and what was going on at the time the song was produced. You will be missed but your legacy endures.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Cliff Deveny]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill, Wishing you the best in your years of retirement . It's been a pleasure being part of "The Summit" experience with you. I appreciate your giving me that opportunity as much so you will enjoy spending your free time however you choose in the coming years.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Janice Dillen]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill accomplished things that most Program Directors could only dream of. He built The Summit into a nationally-recognized station. I am very proud to have been recruited by him. I will certainly miss our discussions and my daily, “Bill Hall, good morning.”]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Bill Hall]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Going to miss your dry, subtle on-air humor (re: Chaz Bono). Enjoy your next life adventure!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joe Breindel]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill has been an integral part of the Summit listening experience.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Betsy Kling, WKYC ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Linda and I will definitely miss you, as you have been a musical part of our lives. Good luck in the next phase of your life. We wish you the best!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda and Gary Sirak ]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill Gruber- I love this guy! His impact on 91.3 has been huge- what knowledge of AAA radio- I love hearing him on air & he saved the day many times when the station would suddenly go off air.  A longtime treasured friend of my husband who has become a friend of mine.  ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Megan Bruno]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill, working for you at The Summit (WAPS) was one of the coolest jobs I've ever had. Also, thanks for introducing me to Kids in the Hall, which I still watch to this day. I hope you have a fulfilling retirement, though you're too young to really retire. ]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Chris Miller]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[You are the rarest of birds.  You brought a unique, once in a generation vision to build and grow The Summit while personally being one of the most rounded and interesting individuals I have ever met. You will go down in Akron history]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Steve Poholski]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[From the days when the radio station shutdown at sunset, WAPS has come a long way under your direction and influence.  Glad to be part of your success through the years and best wishes on the next phase of your journey./R]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jay Minkin]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[There are only two words that /Rcan accurately and affectionately describe my time working /Rwith Bill Gruber:/R"Gentleman Rancher"/R/RCongrats on a great run, Bill! /R91.3 The Summit won't be the same without you.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Ryan Humbert]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill, it's been great to get to know you through the several paths we've met on over the years. I still have the email chain from our dialogue on the station's music selection --from 1996!! Enjoy all your newly free time and next adventures - cheers!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Katie]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The one thing that immediately comes to mind when coming up with an appropriate accolade for the Great Bill Gruber, is the meticulous manner, in which he would construct, our now famous "Frozen Ghost Weekends."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Chenot]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill, what can I say. You introduced me to Ministry, Jesus and Mary Chain, and Nine Inch Nails. My life is better for having WAPS in it. All the best to you in your next adventure.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Tina Boyes, Akron Community Fdn.]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[  It's been a long and winding road, spanning over 30 years. Your love of music and radio shaped the world of WAPS. I'm glad I took this journey with you./RTake care and enjoy your retirement.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Morgan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill, working with you has been quite a ride. You have created a radio station that is a destination for people who love music and you helped me to the most rewarding work of my career. Rock and Recovery & KIDJAM would not have happened without your support. Thank You!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Garrett Hart]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Thank you so much for taking a chance on me being on the air fresh out of college. I've learned so much from you in just a short period of time, and any success that I have in this business will be a direct result of your guidance and mentoring. Best of luck!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jeff Looker]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill was very helpful when we first went on the air - his character was evident in his manner - his vocal inflection was pitch perfect...............]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Larry Crabbe]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[A fabulous ear for music, a great eye for the visual, and a terrible diet. "You work & work for many years always on the go. You never take the minute off too busy making dough. Someday you'll say You'd had your fun" and step away from the mic. Well..Enjoy yourself...]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Brad Knapp]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Bill,/R/RThanks for taking a chance on a mid-twenties long hair with no radio experience.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Andrew James]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Maybe I'll see you on the street some day]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Desiree Hicks]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[We LOVE Modest Mouse/R/RSuch good timing]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Frankie & Betty Spetich]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Gibbon Gibbon Gibbon!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Mind of Gruber]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["...and ignorant people sleep in their beds like the doped white mice in the college lab"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Del Amitri]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["baby needs a brand new pair of eyes, 'cause the ones you've got now see only goodbyes"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Replacements]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["baby you're too well-read, too outspoken, too pristine, when I cry do you feel anything?"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lloyd Cole]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["we're no more than friends and that's where it ends, but funny enough we're both wearing grins"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jason Falkner]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["I'm tired"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Lindsay White]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Whee!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Joey Harper on a Sky Scooter]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["What kind of f*cked up Grape Ape is this?"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Mind of Gruber]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Andrew's alcohol stash in the bottom drawer of the filing cabinet...complete with plastic cups]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Mind of Gruber]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["tonight I should have stayed home playing with my pleasure zone"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[New Order]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["I have no hatred, though I have no love, I feel deserted by your touch"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Adam Schmitt]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["I believe right now if I could, I would swallow you whole"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Suzanne Vega]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Molly! Molly! Molly!/R/RBastard! Bastard! Bastard!]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[backyard neighbor]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["you're half-naked ambition and half out of your wits"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA['til Tuesday]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["I am very, very much in like with you, I know that it's not much, but it's the best that I can do"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Julia Fordham]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["if I could walk away from him, I would run away with you, and every night in my dreams I do"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Marti Jones]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Karen Ingraham as a fairy...with pixie dust]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Mind of Gruber]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Leah Mercer, as news anchor, reading the news, brought to life by real-life actors]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The Mind of Gruber]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["Not goin' out TODAY!"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[The APS Mailroom]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[The el Camino and Ranchero...preferred by gentlemen ranchers everywhere]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Car and Driver]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["The trouble is..."]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Jim Morgan (stroking stache)]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA["This is RFC1B telemetry control, status OFF"]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Sine System]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Your brilliance as both program and music director is instinctual and self-taught.  The Summit is a shining testament to your unwavering devotion. You inspire us all. Enjoy your break.  Reflect on you accomplishments.  Plot your return to keep radio a vibrant force.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Linda Jackson Stepan]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[Knowing Bill's passion for the station and mission.]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[Dave & Cindy Glass]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
        <card>
            <note><![CDATA[]]></note>
            <author><![CDATA[]]></author>
            <image><![CDATA[charcoal]]></image>
        </card>
    </box>
</subOrder>
</order>